<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 06:18:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-0565 | ZZCMS index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0565</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZZCMS 2023. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 06:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8722 | WP All Import Pro &amp;lt;= 4.9.7 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8722</link><description>The Import any XML or CSV File to WordPress PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 04:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0564 | code-projects Fantasy-Cricket authenticate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0564</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Fantasy-Cricket 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /authenticate.php. The manipulation of the argument uname leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 03:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45652 | IBM Maximo Asset Management directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45652</link><description>IBM Maximo MXAPIASSET API 7.6.1.3 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 03:03:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45653 | IBM Sterling Connect:Direct Web Services information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45653</link><description>IBM Sterling Connect:Direct Web Services 6.0, 6.1, 6.2, and 6.3 could disclose sensitive IP address information to authenticated users in responses that could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 03:03:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45654 | IBM Security ReaQta improper input validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45654</link><description>IBM Security ReaQta 3.12 could allow an authenticated user to perform unauthorized actions due to reliance on untrusted inputs.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 02:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0562 | Codezips Gym Management System health_status_entry.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0562</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Gym Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /dashboard/admin/health_status_entry.php. The manipulation of the argument usrid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 01:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0563 | code-projects Fantasy-Cricket update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0563</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Fantasy-Cricket 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /dash/update.php. The manipulation of the argument uname leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 01:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0561 | itsourcecode Farm Management System add-pig.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0561</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Farm Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /add-pig.php. The manipulation of the argument pigno leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 23:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45662 | IBM Safer Payments denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45662</link><description>IBM Safer Payments 6.4.0.00 through 6.4.2.07, 6.5.0.00 through 6.5.0.05, and 6.6.0.00 through 6.6.0.03 could allow a remote attacker to cause a denial of service due to improper allocation of resources.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 16:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47106 | IBM Jazz for Service Management information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47106</link><description>IBM Jazz for Service Management 1.1.3 through 1.1.3.22 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information from improper access restrictions that could aid in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 16:21:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47113 | IBM ICP - Voice Gateway XML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47113</link><description>IBM ICP - Voice Gateway 1.0.2, 1.0.2.4, 1.0.3, 1.0.4, 1.0.5, 1.0.6. 1.0.7, 1.0.7.1, and 1.0.8 could allow remote attacker to send specially crafted XML statements, which would allow them to attacker to view or modify information in the XML document.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 15:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49354 | IBM Concert information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49354</link><description>IBM Concert 1.0.0, 1.0.1, and 1.0.2 is vulnerable to sensitive information disclosure through specially crafted API Calls.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 15:25:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49824 | IBM Robotic Process Automation security bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49824</link><description>IBM Robotic Process Automation 21.0.0 through 21.0.7.18 and 23.0.0 through 23.0.18 and 

IBM Robotic Process Automation for Cloud Pak 21.0.0 through 21.0.7.18 and 23.0.0 through 23.0.18

could allow an authenticated user to perform unauthorized actions as a privileged user due to improper validation of client-side security enforcement.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 15:25:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51448 | IBM Robotic Process Automation privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51448</link><description>IBM Robotic Process Automation 21.0.0 through 21.0.7.17 and 23.0.0 through 23.0.18 could allow a local user to escalate their privileges. All files in the install inherit the file permissions of the parent directory and therefore a non-privileged user can substitute any executable for the nssm.exe service. A subsequent service or server restart will then run that binary with administrator privilege.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 15:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49338 | IBM App Connect Enterprise information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49338</link><description>IBM App Connect Enterprise 12.0.1.0 through 12.0.7.0and 13.0.1.0 under certain configurations could allow a privileged user to obtain JMS credentials.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 15:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0560 | CampCodes School Management Software Photo Gallery Page photo-gallery cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0560</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in CampCodes School Management Software 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /photo-gallery of the component Photo Gallery Page. The manipulation of the argument Description leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 15:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0559 | Campcodes School Management Software Create Id Card Page create-id-card cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0559</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Campcodes School Management Software 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /create-id-card of the component Create Id Card Page. The manipulation of the argument ID Card Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 14:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0558 | TDuckCloud tduck-platform QueryProThemeRequest.java QueryProThemeRequest sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0558</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TDuckCloud tduck-platform up to 4.0. This vulnerability affects the function QueryProThemeRequest of the file src/main/java/com/tduck/cloud/form/request/QueryProThemeRequest.java. The manipulation of the argument color leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 13:03:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0557 | Hyland Alfresco Community Edition URL s cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0557</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Hyland Alfresco Community Edition and Alfresco Enterprise Edition up to 6.2.2. This affects an unknown part of the file /share/s/ of the component URL Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 7.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 09:08:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13184 | The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended &amp;lt;= 3.0.12 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via Login Attempts Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13184</link><description>The The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the Login Attempts module in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.12 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 08:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13375 | Adifier System &amp;lt;= 3.1.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Password Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13375</link><description>The Adifier System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.7. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their details like password through the adifier_recover() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 08:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13392 | Rate Star Review Vote – AJAX Reviews, Votes, Star Ratings &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13392</link><description>The Rate Star Review Vote – AJAX Reviews, Votes, Star Ratings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'videowhisper_reviews' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 07:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12385 | WP Abstracts &amp;lt;= 2.7.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12385</link><description>The WP Abstracts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.2. This is due to missing nonce validation on the wpabstracts_load_status() and wpabstracts_delete_abstracts() functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 07:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12696 | Picture Gallery – Frontend Image Uploads, AJAX Photo List &amp;lt;= 1.5.22 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via videowhisper_picture_upload_guest Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12696</link><description>The Picture Gallery – Frontend Image Uploads, AJAX Photo List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's videowhisper_picture_upload_guest shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.22 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 07:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13317 | ShipWorks Connector for Woocommerce &amp;lt;= 5.2.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Service Password/Username Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13317</link><description>The ShipWorks Connector for Woocommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.5. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'shipworks-wordpress' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the services username and password via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 07:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13385 | JSM Screenshot Machine Shortcode &amp;lt;= 2.3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13385</link><description>The JSM Screenshot Machine Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ssm' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 07:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13391 | MicroPayments – Fans Paysite: Paid Creator Subscriptions, Digital Assets, Tokens Wallet &amp;lt;= 2.9.29 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13391</link><description>The MicroPayments – Fans Paysite: Paid Creator Subscriptions, Digital Assets, Tokens Wallet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'videowhisper_content_upload_guest' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.29 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 07:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13393 | Video Share VOD – Turnkey Video Site Builder Script &amp;lt;= 2.6.31 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13393</link><description>The Video Share VOD – Turnkey Video Site Builder Script plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'videowhisper_videos' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.31 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 07:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13432 | Webcamconsult &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13432</link><description>The Webcamconsult plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 07:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13433 | Utilities for MTG &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13433</link><description>The Utilities for MTG plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'mtglink' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 07:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13517 | Easy Digital Downloads – Sell Digital Files &amp;amp; Subscriptions (eCommerce Store + Payments Made Easy) &amp;lt;= 3.3.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Title</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13517</link><description>The Easy Digital Downloads – eCommerce Payments and Subscriptions made easy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Title value in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 07:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13519 | MarketKing — Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution &amp;lt;= 1.9.80 - Authenticated (Shop Manager+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13519</link><description>The MarketKing — Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via plugin's settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.80 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 07:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0369 | Jet Engine &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via list_tag Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0369</link><description>The JetEngine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘list_tag’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 07:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0515 | Buzz Club – Night Club, DJ and Music Festival Event WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Arbitrary Option Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0515</link><description>The Buzz Club – Night Club, DJ and Music Festival Event WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to a denial of service due to a missing capability check on the 'cmsmasters_hide_admin_notice' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update option values to 'hide' on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update an option that would create an error on the site and deny service to legitimate users or be used to set some values to true such as registration.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 07:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9020 | List category posts &amp;lt; 0.90.3 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9020</link><description>The List category posts WordPress plugin before 0.90.3 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 06:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13515 | Image Source Control Lite – Show Image Credits and Captions &amp;lt;= 2.28.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13515</link><description>The Image Source Control Lite – Show Image Credits and Captions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'path' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.28.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 05:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13516 | Kubio AI Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.3.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13516</link><description>The Kubio AI Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'message' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 05:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0308 | Ultimate Member &amp;lt;= 2.9.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0308</link><description>The Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the search parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 05:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0318 | Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp;amp; Membership Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.1 - Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0318</link><description>The Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.1 through different error messages in the responses. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to exfiltrate data from wp_usermeta table.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 05:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0554 | Podlove Podcast Publisher &amp;lt;= 4.1.25 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Feed Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0554</link><description>The Podlove Podcast Publisher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Feed Name value in version &lt;= 4.1.25 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 05:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12071 | Evergreen Content Poster – Auto Post and Schedule Your Best Content to Social Media &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12071</link><description>The Evergreen Content Poster – Auto Post and Schedule Your Best Content to Social Media plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the delete_network_post() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary posts and pages.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 03:29:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23209 | Potential RCE with a compromised security key in craft/cms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23209</link><description>Craft is a flexible, user-friendly CMS for creating custom digital experiences on the web and beyond. This is an remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability that affects Craft 4 and 5 installs where your security key has already been compromised. Anyone running an unpatched version of Craft with a compromised security key is affected. This vulnerability has been patched in Craft 5.5.8 and 4.13.8. Users who cannot update to a patched version, should rotate their security keys and ensure their privacy to help migitgate the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 02:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50739 | A buffer overflow vulnerability has been identified in the Internet Printing Protocol (IPP) in various Lexmark devices.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50739</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability has been identified in the Internet Printing Protocol (IPP) in various Lexmark devices. The vulnerability can be leveraged by an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11923 | Sensitive Information Disclosure in Fortra Application Hub Prior to version 1.3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11923</link><description>Under certain log settings the IAM or CORE service will log credentials in the iam logfile in Fortra Application Hub (Formerly named Helpsystems One) prior to version 1.3</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9387 | In multiple functions of mnh-sm.c, there is a possible way to trigger a heap overflow due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9387</link><description>In multiple functions of mnh-sm.c, there is a possible way to trigger a heap overflow due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9389 | In ip6_append_data of ip6_output.c, there is a possible way to achieve code execution due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9389</link><description>In ip6_append_data of ip6_output.c, there is a possible way to achieve code execution due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9401 | In many locations, there is a possible way to access kernel memory in user space due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9401</link><description>In many locations, there is a possible way to access kernel memory in user space due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9405 | In BnDmAgent::onTransact of dm_agent.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9405</link><description>In BnDmAgent::onTransact of dm_agent.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9406 | In NlpService, there is a possible way to obtain location information due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9406</link><description>In NlpService, there is a possible way to obtain location information due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9461 | In onAttachFragment of ShareIntentActivity.java, there is a possible way for an app to read files in the messages app due to a race conditio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9461</link><description>In onAttachFragment of ShareIntentActivity.java, there is a possible way for an app to read files in the messages app due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9464 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to read protected files due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9464</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to read protected files due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-13322 | In endCallForSubscriber of PhoneInterfaceManager.java, there is a possible way to prevent access to emergency services due to a logic error ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13322</link><description>In endCallForSubscriber of PhoneInterfaceManager.java, there is a possible way to prevent access to emergency services due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to a local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed.  User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9375 | In multiple functions of UserDictionaryProvider.java, there is a possible way to add and delete words in the user dictionary due to a confus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9375</link><description>In multiple functions of UserDictionaryProvider.java, there is a possible way to add and delete words in the user dictionary due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9379 | In multiple functions of MiniThumbFile.java, there is a possible way to view the thumbnails of deleted photos due to a confused deputy. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9379</link><description>In multiple functions of MiniThumbFile.java, there is a possible way to view the thumbnails of deleted photos due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9382 | In multiple functions of WifiServiceImpl.java, there is a possible way to activate Wi-Fi hotspot from a non-owner profile due to a missing p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9382</link><description>In multiple functions of WifiServiceImpl.java, there is a possible way to activate Wi-Fi hotspot from a non-owner profile due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9384 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to bypass KASLR due to an unusual root cause. This could lead to local information disclosure...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9384</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to bypass KASLR due to an unusual root cause. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9434 | In multiple functions of Parcel.cpp, there is a possible way to bypass address space layout randomization. This could lead to local escalati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9434</link><description>In multiple functions of Parcel.cpp, there is a possible way to bypass address space layout randomization. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:26:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9447 | In onCreate of EmergencyCallbackModeExitDialog.java, there is a possible way to crash the emergency callback mode due to a missing null chec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9447</link><description>In onCreate of EmergencyCallbackModeExitDialog.java, there is a possible way to crash the emergency callback mode due to a missing null check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:26:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9383 | In asn1_ber_decoder of asn1_decoder.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local inform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9383</link><description>In asn1_ber_decoder of asn1_decoder.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23208 | IdP group membership revocation ignored in zot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23208</link><description>zot is a production-ready vendor-neutral OCI image registry. The group data stored for users in the boltdb database (meta.db) is an append-list so group revocations/removals are ignored in the API. SetUserGroups is alled on login, but instead of replacing the group memberships, they are appended. This may be due to some conflict with the group definitions in the config file, but that wasn't obvious to me if it were the case. Any Zot configuration that relies on group-based authorization will not respect group remove/revocation by an IdP. This issue has been addressed in version 2.1.2. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 22:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0541 | Codezips Gym Management System edit_member.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0541</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Gym Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /dashboard/admin/edit_member.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 21:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23207 | \htmlData does not validate attribute names in KaTeX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23207</link><description>KaTeX is a fast, easy-to-use JavaScript library for TeX math rendering on the web. KaTeX users who render untrusted mathematical expressions with `renderToString` could encounter malicious input using `\htmlData` that runs arbitrary JavaScript, or generate invalid HTML. Users are advised to upgrade to KaTeX v0.16.21 to remove this vulnerability. Users unable to upgrade should avoid use of or turn off the `trust` option, or set it to forbid `\htmlData` commands, forbid inputs containing the substring `"\\htmlData"` and sanitize HTML output from KaTeX.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 21:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50738 | A firmware downgrade prevention vulnerability has been identified in newer Lexmark devices.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50738</link><description>A new feature to prevent Firmware downgrades was recently added to some Lexmark products. A method to 
override this downgrade protection has been identified.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 21:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0540 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System expadd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0540</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /expadd.php. The manipulation of the argument expcat leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 21:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23206 | IAM OIDC custom resource allows connection to unauthorized OIDC provider in aws-cdk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23206</link><description>The AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK) is an open-source software development framework to define cloud infrastructure in code and provision it through AWS CloudFormation. Users who use IAM OIDC custom resource provider package will download CA Thumbprints as part of the custom resource workflow. However, the current `tls.connect` method will always set `rejectUnauthorized: false` which is a potential security concern. CDK should follow the best practice and set `rejectUnauthorized: true`. However, this could be a breaking change for existing CDK applications and we should fix this with a feature flag. Note that this is marked as low severity Security advisory because the issuer url is provided by CDK users who define the CDK application. If they insist on connecting to a unauthorized OIDC provider, CDK should not disallow this. Additionally, the code block is run in a Lambda environment which mitigate the MITM attack. The patch is in progress. To mitigate, upgrade to CDK v2.177.0 (Expected release date 2025-02-22). Once upgraded, users should make sure the feature flag '@aws-cdk/aws-iam:oidcRejectUnauthorizedConnections' is set to true in `cdk.context.json` or `cdk.json`. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:38:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0538 | code-projects Tourism Management System manage-pages.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0538</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in code-projects Tourism Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/manage-pages.php. The manipulation of the argument pgedetails leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:38:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57252 | OtCMS &lt;=V7.46 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in /admin/read.php, which can Read system files arbitrarily.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57252</link><description>OtCMS &lt;=V7.46 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in /admin/read.php, which can Read system files arbitrarily.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23202 | Improper Input Validation in Bible Module for ROBLOX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23202</link><description>Bible Module is a tool designed for ROBLOX developers to integrate Bible functionality into their games. The `FetchVerse` and `FetchPassage` functions in the Bible Module are susceptible to injection attacks due to the absence of input validation. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to manipulate the API request URLs, potentially leading to unauthorized access or data tampering. This issue has been addressed in version 0.0.3. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23205 | `frame-ancestors: self` grants all users access to formgrader in nbgrader</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23205</link><description>nbgrader is a system for assigning and grading notebooks. Enabling frame-ancestors: 'self' grants any JupyterHub user the ability to extract formgrader content by sending malicious links to users with access to formgrader, at least when using the default JupyterHub configuration of `enable_subdomains = False`. #1915 disables a protection which would allow user Alice to craft a page embedding formgrader in an IFrame. If Bob visits that page, his credentials will be sent and the formgrader page loaded. Because Alice's page is on the same Origin as the formgrader iframe, Javasript on Alice's page has _full access_ to the contents of the page served by formgrader using Bob's credentials. This issue has been addressed in release 0.9.5 and all users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may disable `frame-ancestors: self`, or enable per-user and per-service subdomains with `JupyterHub.enable_subdomains = True` (then even if embedding in an IFrame is allowed, the host page does not have access to the contents of the frame).</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57033 | WeGIA &lt; 3.2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the dados_addInfo parameter of documentos_funcionario.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57033</link><description>WeGIA &lt; 3.2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the dados_addInfo parameter of documentos_funcionario.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57035 | WeGIA v3.2.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection viathe nextPage parameter in /controle/control.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57035</link><description>WeGIA v3.2.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection viathe nextPage parameter in /controle/control.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21606 | Local Privilege Escalation via Exposed XPC Method Due to Client Verification Failure in stats</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21606</link><description>stats is a macOS system monitor in for the menu bar. The Stats application is vulnerable to a local privilege escalation due to the insecure implementation of its XPC service. The application registers a Mach service under the name `eu.exelban.Stats.SMC.Helper`. The associated binary, eu.exelban.Stats.SMC.Helper, is a privileged helper tool designed to execute actions requiring elevated privileges on behalf of the client, such as setting fan modes, adjusting fan speeds, and executing the `powermetrics` command. The root cause of this vulnerability lies in the `shouldAcceptNewConnection` method, which unconditionally returns YES (or true), allowing any XPC client to connect to the service without any form of verification. As a result, unauthorized clients can establish a connection to the Mach service and invoke methods exposed by the HelperTool interface. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability to modify the hardware settings of the user’s device and execute arbitrary code with root privileges. This issue has been addressed in version 2.11.21 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23039 | Cross Site Scripting on URL decode Tooltip in Caido</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23039</link><description>Caido is a web security auditing toolkit. A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in Caido v0.45.0 due to improper sanitization in the URL decoding tooltip of HTTP request and response editors. This issue could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary scripts, potentially leading to the theft of sensitive information. This issue has been addressed in version 0.45.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13026 | Inadequate Encryption Strength Vulnerability in Roche Algo Edge</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13026</link><description>A vulnerability exists in Algo Edge up to 2.1.1 - a previously used (legacy) component of navify® Algorithm Suite.  The vulnerability impacts the authentication mechanism of this component and could allow an attacker with adjacent access to the laboratory network and the Algo Edge system to craft valid authentication tokens and access the component. Other components of navify® Algorithm Suite are not affected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57031 | WeGIA &lt; 3.2.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /funcionario/remuneracao.php via the id_funcionario parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57031</link><description>WeGIA &lt; 3.2.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /funcionario/remuneracao.php via the id_funcionario parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57032 | WeGIA &lt; 3.2.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control in controle/control.php. The application does not validate the value of the old pass...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57032</link><description>WeGIA &lt; 3.2.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control in controle/control.php. The application does not validate the value of the old password, so it is possible to change the password by placing any value in the senha_antiga field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57034 | WeGIA &lt; 3.2.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in query_geracao_auto.php via the query parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57034</link><description>WeGIA &lt; 3.2.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in query_geracao_auto.php via the query parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0537 | code-projects Car Rental Management System manage-pages.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0537</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Car Rental Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/manage-pages.php. The manipulation of the argument pgdetails leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57030 | Wegia &lt; 3.2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /geral/documentos_funcionario.php via the id parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57030</link><description>Wegia &lt; 3.2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /geral/documentos_funcionario.php via the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52870 | Teradata Vantage Editor 1.0.1 is mostly intended for SQL database access and docs.teradata.com access, but provides unintended functionality...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52870</link><description>Teradata Vantage Editor 1.0.1 is mostly intended for SQL database access and docs.teradata.com access, but provides unintended functionality (including Chromium Developer Tools) that can result in a client user accessing arbitrary remote websites.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 19:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57370 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in sunnygkp10 Online Exam System master version allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57370</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in sunnygkp10 Online Exam System master version allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the w parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 19:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57372 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in InformationPush master version allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the title,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57372</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in InformationPush master version allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the title, time and msg parameters</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 19:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0536 | 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System edit_action.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0536</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit_action.php. The manipulation of the argument attendance_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 19:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57369 | Clickjacking vulnerability in typecho v1.2.1.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57369</link><description>Clickjacking vulnerability in typecho v1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 19:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21185 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21185</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 19:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21399 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Update Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21399</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 19:25:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0535 | Codezips Gym Management System edit_mem_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0535</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Codezips Gym Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /dashboard/admin/edit_mem_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument uid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 19:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0534 | 1000 Projects Campaign Management System Platform for Women loginnew.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0534</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Campaign Management System Platform for Women 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Code/loginnew.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 18:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0533 | 1000 Projects Campaign Management System Platform for Women sc_login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0533</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Campaign Management System Platform for Women 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Code/sc_login.php. The manipulation of the argument uname leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 18:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12757 | Nedap Librix Ecoreader Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12757</link><description>Nedap Librix Ecoreader 
 is missing authentication for critical functions that could allow an 
unauthenticated attacker to potentially execute malicious code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 17:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0430 | Belledonne Communications Linphone-Desktop NULL Pointer Dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0430</link><description>Belledonne Communications Linphone-Desktop 
 is vulnerable to a NULL Dereference vulnerability, which could allow a remote attacker to create a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 17:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0532 | Codezips Gym Management System new_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0532</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Gym Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /dashboard/admin/new_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument m_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 17:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45832 | Ossur Mobile Logic Application Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45832</link><description>Hard-coded credentials were included as part of the application binary. 
These credentials served as part of the application authentication flow 
and communication with the mobile application. An attacker could access 
unauthorized information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53683 | Ossur Mobile Logic Application Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53683</link><description>A valid set of credentials in a .js file and a static token for 
communication were obtained from the decompiled IPA. An attacker could 
use the information to disrupt normal use of the application by changing
 the translation files and thus weaken the integrity of normal use.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54681 | Ossur Mobile Logic Application Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54681</link><description>Multiple bash files were present in the application's private directory.
 Bash files can be used on their own, by an attacker that has already 
full access to the mobile platform to compromise the translations for 
the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26153 | ETIC Telecom Remote Access Server (RAS)  Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26153</link><description>All versions of ETIC Telecom Remote Access Server (RAS) prior to 4.9.19 
are vulnerable to cross-site request forgery (CSRF). An external 
attacker with no access to the device can force the end user into 
submitting a "setconf" method request, not requiring any CSRF token, 
which can lead into denial of service on the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26154 | ETIC Telecom Remote Access Server (RAS) Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26154</link><description>All versions of ETIC Telecom Remote Access Server (RAS) prior to 4.5.0 
are vulnerable to reflected cross site scripting in the appliance site 
name. The ETIC RAS web server saves the site name and then presents it 
to the administrators in a few different pages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26155 | ETIC Telecom Remote Access Server (RAS) Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26155</link><description>All versions of ETIC Telecom Remote Access Server (RAS) prior to 4.5.0 
expose clear text credentials in the web portal. An attacker can access 
the ETIC RAS web portal and view the HTML code, which is configured to 
be hidden, thus allowing a connection to the ETIC RAS ssh server, which 
could enable an attacker to perform actions on the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26156 | ETIC Telecom Remote Access Server (RAS) Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26156</link><description>All versions of ETIC Telecom Remote Access Server (RAS) prior to 4.5.0 
are vulnerable to reflected cross site scripting (XSS) attacks in the 
method parameter. The ETIC RAS web server uses dynamic pages that gets 
their input from the client side and reflects the input in its response 
to the client.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26157 | ETIC Telecom Remote Access Server (RAS) Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26157</link><description>All versions of ETIC Telecom Remote Access Server (RAS) prior to 4.5.0 
are vulnerable to reflected cross site scripting (XSS) attacks in get 
view method under view parameter. The ETIC RAS web server uses dynamic 
pages that get their input from the client side and reflect the input in
 their response to the client.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0531 | code-projects Chat System leaveroom.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0531</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Chat System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /user/leaveroom.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0530 | code-projects Job Recruitment _feedback_system.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0530</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /_parse/_feedback_system.php. The manipulation of the argument type leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0529 | code-projects Train Ticket Reservation System Login Form stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0529</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Train Ticket Reservation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Login Form. The manipulation of the argument username leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:07:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50967 | The /rest/rights/ REST API endpoint in Becon DATAGerry through 2.2.0 contains an Incorrect Access Control vulnerability. An attacker can rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50967</link><description>The /rest/rights/ REST API endpoint in Becon DATAGerry through 2.2.0 contains an Incorrect Access Control vulnerability. An attacker can remotely access this endpoint without authentication, leading to unauthorized disclosure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0528 | Tenda AC8/AC10/AC18 HTTP Request telnet command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0528</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda AC8, AC10 and AC18 16.03.10.20. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /goform/telnet of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13502 | A command injection in the NTC2218, NTC2250, NTC2299 modems&amp;#x27; web interfaces allows to exeucte arbitrary shell commands.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13502</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Newtec/iDirect NTC2218, NTC2250, NTC2299 on Linux, PowerPC, ARM allows Local Code Inclusion.This issue affects NTC2218, NTC2250, NTC2299: from 1.0.1.1 through 2.2.6.19.


The `commit_multicast` page used to configure multicasts in the modem's web administration interface uses improperly parses incoming data from the request before passing it to an `eval` statement in a bash script. This allows attackers to inject arbitrary shell commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13503 | Stack-Based Buffer Overflow in Newtec&amp;#x27;s update signaling causes RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13503</link><description>Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in Newtec NTC2218, NTC2250, NTC2299 on Linux, PowerPC, ARM (Updating signaling process in the swdownload binary modules) allows Local Execution of Code, Remote Code Inclusion.
This issue affects NTC2218, NTC2250, NTC2299: from 1.0.1.1 through 2.2.6.19. The issue is both present on the PowerPC versions of the modem and the ARM versions.

A stack buffer buffer overflow in the swdownload binary allows attackers to execute arbitrary code. The parse_INFO function uses an unrestricted `sscanf` to read a string of an incoming network packet into a statically sized buffer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:00:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0527 | code-projects Admission Management System signupconfirm.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0527</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Admission Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /signupconfirm.php. The manipulation of the argument in_eml leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10497 | CWE-639: Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability exists that could allow an
authorized attacker to modify values outs...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10497</link><description>CWE-639: Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability exists that could allow an
authorized attacker to modify values outside those defined by their privileges (Elevation of Privileges) when the
attacker sends modified HTTPS requests to the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 10:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10498 | CWE-119: Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer vulnerability exists that
could allow an unauthorized attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10498</link><description>CWE-119: Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer vulnerability exists that
could allow an unauthorized attacker to modify configuration values outside of the normal range when the
attacker sends specific Modbus write packets to the device which could result in invalid data or loss of web
interface functionality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 10:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12703 | CWE-502: Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability exists that could lead to loss of confidentiality, integrity
and potential remote c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12703</link><description>CWE-502: Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability exists that could lead to loss of confidentiality, integrity
and potential remote code execution on workstation when a non-admin authenticated user opens a malicious
project file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 10:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12142 | CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability exists that could
cause information disclosure of restrict...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12142</link><description>CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability exists that could
cause information disclosure of restricted web page, modification of web page and denial of
service when specific web pages are modified and restricted functions are invoked.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 10:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12476 | CWE-611: Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability exists that could
cause information disclosure, impacts worksta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12476</link><description>CWE-611: Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability exists that could
cause information disclosure, impacts workstation integrity and potential remote code execution on the
compromised computer, when specific crafted XML file is imported in the Web Designer configuration tool.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 09:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12399 | CWE-924: Improper Enforcement of Message Integrity During Transmission in a Communication Channel vulnerability
exists that could cause part...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12399</link><description>CWE-924: Improper Enforcement of Message Integrity During Transmission in a Communication Channel vulnerability
exists that could cause partial loss of confidentiality, loss of integrity and availability of the HMI when attacker performs
man in the middle attack by intercepting the communication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 09:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13377 | GravityForms &amp;lt;= 2.9.1.3 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;alt&amp;#x27; parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13377</link><description>The Gravity Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘alt’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 09:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13378 | GravityForms 2.9.0.1 - 2.9.1.3 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;style_settings&amp;#x27; parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13378</link><description>The Gravity Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘style_settings’ parameter in versions 2.9.0.1 up to, and including, 2.9.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The attack is only successful in the Chrome web browser, and requires directly browsing the media file via the attachment post.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 09:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11425 | CWE-131: Incorrect Calculation of Buffer Size vulnerability exists that could cause Denial-of-Service of the
product when an unauthenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11425</link><description>CWE-131: Incorrect Calculation of Buffer Size vulnerability exists that could cause Denial-of-Service of the
product when an unauthenticated user is sending a crafted HTTPS packet to the webserver.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 09:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11139 | CWE-119: Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer vulnerability exists that
could allow local attackers to ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11139</link><description>CWE-119: Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer vulnerability exists that
could allow local attackers to exploit these issues to potentially execute arbitrary code when opening a
malicious project file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 08:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12370 | WP Hotel Booking &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12370</link><description>The WP Hotel Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check when adding rooms in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add rooms with custom prices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 08:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12203 | RSS Icon Widget &amp;lt;= 5.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12203</link><description>The RSS Icon Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘link_color’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 07:12:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12466 | Proofreading &amp;lt;= 1.2.1.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12466</link><description>The Proofreading plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'nonce' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 07:12:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12508 | Glofox Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 2.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12508</link><description>The Glofox Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'glofox' and 'glofox_lead_capture ' shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 2.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 07:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12598 | MyBookProgress by Stormhill Media &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via book Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12598</link><description>The MyBookProgress by Stormhill Media plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘book’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 07:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12637 | Moving Users &amp;lt;= 1.05 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12637</link><description>The Moving Users plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.05 via the export functionality. The JSON files are stored in predictable locations with guessable file names when exporting user data. This could allow unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive user data, for instance, email addresses, hashed passwords, and IP addresses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 07:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13366 | Sandbox &amp;lt;= 0.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13366</link><description>The Sandbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'debug' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 07:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13367 | Sandbox &amp;lt;= 0.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sandbox Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13367</link><description>The Sandbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the export_download action in all versions up to, and including, 0.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to download an entire copy of a sandbox environment which can contain sensitive information like the wp-config.php file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 07:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13386 | quote-posttype-plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13386</link><description>The quote-posttype-plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Author field in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 07:12:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10799 | Eventer &amp;lt;= 3.9.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10799</link><description>The Eventer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.7 via the eventer_woo_download_tickets() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 05:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13333 | Advanced File Manager 5.2.12 - 5.2.13 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13333</link><description>The Advanced File Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'fma_local_file_system' function in versions 5.2.12 to 5.2.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above and upload permissions granted by an administrator, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. The function can be exploited only if the "Display .htaccess?" setting is enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 05:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11146 | TrueFiling authorization bypass via user-controlled keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11146</link><description>TrueFiling is a collaborative, web-based electronic filing system where attorneys, paralegals, court reporters and self-represented filers collect public legal documentation into cases. TrueFiling is an entirely cloud-hosted application. Prior to version 3.1.112.19, TrueFiling trusted some client-controlled identifiers passed in URL requests to retrieve information. Platform users must self-register for an account, and once authenticated, could manipulate those identifiers to gain partial access to case information and the ability to partially change user access to case information. This vulnerability was addressed in version 3.1.112.19 and all instances were updated by 2024-11-08.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 05:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13398 | Checkout for PayPal &amp;lt;= 1.0.32 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13398</link><description>The Checkout for PayPal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'checkout_for_paypal' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.32 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 04:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13401 | Payment Button for PayPal &amp;lt;= 1.2.3.35 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13401</link><description>The Payment Button for PayPal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wp_paypal_checkout' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3.35 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 04:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13434 | WP Inventory Manager &amp;lt;= 2.3.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13434</link><description>The WP Inventory Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'message' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 04:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51462 | IBM QRadar WinCollect Agent data manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51462</link><description>IBM QRadar WinCollect Agent 10.0.0 through 10.1.12 could allow a remote attacker to inject XML data into parameter values due to improper input validation of assumed immutable data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 02:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52363 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52363</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 02:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34579 | Fuji Electric Alpha5 SMART Stack-Based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34579</link><description>Fuji Electric Alpha5 SMART 

is vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow, which may allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 01:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21325 | Windows Secure Kernel Mode Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21325</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 01:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>