<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:43:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-54417 | Craft contains a theoretical bypass for CVE-2025-23209</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54417</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences. Versions 4.13.8 through 4.16.2 and 5.5.8 through 5.8.3 contain a vulnerability that can bypass CVE-2025-23209: "Craft CMS has a potential RCE with a compromised security key". To exploit this vulnerability, the project must meet these requirements: have a compromised security key and create an arbitrary file in Craft's /storage/backups folder. With those criteria in place, attackers could create a specific, malicious request to the /updater/restore-db endpoint and execute CLI commands remotely. This issue is fixed in versions 4.16.3 and 5.8.4.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54888 | @fedify/fedify: Improper Authentication and Incorrect Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54888</link><description>Fedify is a TypeScript library for building federated server apps powered by ActivityPub. In versions below 1.3.20, 1.4.0-dev.585 through 1.4.12, 1.5.0-dev.636 through 1.5.4, 1.6.0-dev.754 through 1.6.7, 1.7.0-pr.251.885 through 1.7.8 and 1.8.0-dev.909 through 1.8.4, an authentication bypass vulnerability allows any unauthenticated attacker to impersonate any ActivityPub actor by sending forged activities signed with their own keys. Activities are processed before verifying the signing key belongs to the claimed actor, enabling complete actor impersonation across all Fedify instances. This is fixed in versions 1.3.20, 1.4.13, 1.5.5, 1.6.8, 1.7.9 and 1.8.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54996 | OpenBao Root Namespace Operator May Elevate Token Privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54996</link><description>OpenBao exists to provide a software solution to manage, store, and distribute sensitive data including secrets, certificates, and keys. In versions 2.3.1 and below, accounts with access to highly-privileged identity entity systems in root namespaces were able to increase their scope directly to the root policy. While the identity system allowed adding arbitrary policies, which in turn could contain capability grants on arbitrary paths, the root policy was restricted to manual generation using unseal or recovery key shares. The global root policy was not accessible from child namespaces. This issue is fixed in version 2.3.2. To workaround this vulnerability, use of denied_parameters in any policy which has access to the affected identity endpoints (on identity entities) may be sufficient to prohibit this type of attack.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55152 | oak: ReDoS in x-forwarded-proto and x-forwarded-for headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55152</link><description>oak is a middleware framework for Deno's native HTTP server, Deno Deploy, Node.js 16.5 and later, Cloudflare Workers and Bun. In versions 17.1.5 and below, it's possible to significantly slow down an oak server with specially crafted values of the x-forwarded-proto or x-forwarded-for headers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46709 | GPU DDK - Security fix for PP-171570 can lead to an uninitialised pointer dereference and memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46709</link><description>Possible memory leak or kernel exceptions caused by reading kernel heap data after free or NULL pointer dereference kernel exception.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 23:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8744 | CesiumLab Web lodmodels sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8744</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in CesiumLab Web up to 4.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /lodmodels/. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 23:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6573 | GPU DDK - RGXFW_CTL.pui8FWScratchBuf Leak/Overwrite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6573</link><description>Kernel software installed and running inside an untrusted/rich execution environment (REE) could leak information from the trusted execution environment (TEE).</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 23:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8743 | Scada-LTS Virtual Data Source Property data_source_edit.shtm cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8743</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Scada-LTS up to 2.7.8.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /data_source_edit.shtm of the component Virtual Data Source Property Handler. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 23:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8742 | macrozheng mall Admin Login excessive authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8742</link><description>A vulnerability was found in macrozheng mall 1.0.3. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Admin Login. The manipulation leads to improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 22:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8741 | macrozheng mall login cleartext transmission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8741</link><description>A vulnerability was found in macrozheng mall up to 1.0.3. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/login. The manipulation leads to cleartext transmission of sensitive information. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 21:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8740 | zhenfeng13 My-Blog Category save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8740</link><description>A vulnerability was found in zhenfeng13 My-Blog up to 1.0.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/categories/save of the component Category Handler. The manipulation of the argument categoryName leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 21:10:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55188 | 7-Zip before 25.01 does not always properly handle symbolic links during extraction.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55188</link><description>7-Zip before 25.01 does not always properly handle symbolic links during extraction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 20:53:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8739 | zhenfeng13 My-Blog save cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8739</link><description>A vulnerability was found in zhenfeng13 My-Blog up to 1.0.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/tags/save. The manipulation of the argument tagName leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 20:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8738 | zlt2000 microservices-platform Spring Actuator Interface actuator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8738</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in zlt2000 microservices-platform up to 6.0.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /actuator of the component Spring Actuator Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 20:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8737 | zlt2000 microservices-platform OauthLogoutSuccessHandler.java onLogoutSuccess redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8737</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in zlt2000 microservices-platform up to 6.0.0. This affects the function onLogoutSuccess of the file src/main/java/com/central/oauth/handler/OauthLogoutSuccessHandler.java. The manipulation of the argument redirect_url leads to open redirect. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8736 | GNU cflow Lexer c.c yylex buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8736</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in GNU cflow up to 1.8. Affected by this issue is the function yylex of the file c.c of the component Lexer. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4796 | Eventin &amp;lt;= 4.0.34 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Privilege Escalation via User Email Change/Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4796</link><description>The Eventin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.34. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity or capability prior to updating their details like email in the 'Eventin\Speaker\Api\SpeakerController::update_item' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to change arbitrary user's email addresses, including administrators, and leverage that to reset the user's password and gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8735 | GNU cflow Lexer c.c yylex null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8735</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in GNU cflow up to 1.8. Affected by this vulnerability is the function yylex of the file c.c of the component Lexer. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2010-10013 | AjaXplorer &amp;lt; 2.6 checkInstall.php Unauthenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2010-10013</link><description>An unauthenticated remote command execution vulnerability exists in AjaXplorer (now known as Pydio Cells) versions prior to 2.6. The flaw resides in the checkInstall.php script within the access.ssh plugin, which fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input to the destServer GET parameter. By injecting shell metacharacters, remote attackers can execute arbitrary system commands on the server with the privileges of the web server process.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10036 | Project Pier &amp;lt;= 0.8.8 Arbitrary File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10036</link><description>Project Pier 0.8.8 and earlier contains an unauthenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability in tools/upload_file.php. The upload handler fails to validate the file type or enforce authentication, allowing remote attackers to upload malicious PHP files directly into a web-accessible directory. The uploaded file is stored with a predictable suffix and can be executed by requesting its URL, resulting in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10041 | WAN Emulator v2.3 Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10041</link><description>WAN Emulator v2.3 contains two unauthenticated command execution vulnerabilities. The result.php script calls shell_exec() with unsanitized input from the pc POST parameter, allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands as the www-data user. The system also includes a SUID-root binary named dosu, which is vulnerable to command injection via its first argument. An attacker can exploit both flaws in sequence to achieve full remote code execution and escalate privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10042 | Sflog! CMS 1.0 Arbitrary File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10042</link><description>Sflog! CMS 1.0 contains an authenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the blog management interface. The application ships with default credentials (admin:secret) and allows authenticated users to upload files via manage.php. The upload mechanism fails to validate file types, enabling attackers to upload a PHP backdoor into a web-accessible directory (blogs/download/uploads/). Once uploaded, the file can be executed remotely, resulting in full remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10043 | ActFax 4.32 Client Importer Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10043</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in ActFax Server version 4.32, specifically in the "Import Users from File" functionality of the client interface. The application fails to properly validate the length of tab-delimited fields in .exp files, leading to unsafe usage of strcpy() during CSV parsing. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious .exp file and importing it using the default character set "ECMA-94 / Latin 1 (ISO 8859)". Successful exploitation may result in arbitrary code execution, leading to full system compromise. User interaction is required to trigger the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10044 | MobileCartly 1.0 savepage.php Arbitrary File Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10044</link><description>MobileCartly version 1.0 contains an arbitrary file creation vulnerability in the savepage.php script. The application fails to perform authentication or authorization checks before invoking file_put_contents() on attacker-controlled input. An unauthenticated attacker can exploit this flaw by sending crafted HTTP GET requests to savepage.php, specifying both the filename and content. This allows arbitrary file creation within the pages/ directory or any writable path on the server, allowing remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10045 | XODA 0.4.5 Arbitrary PHP File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10045</link><description>XODA version 0.4.5 contains an unauthenticated file upload vulnerability that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary PHP code on the server. The flaw resides in the upload functionality, which fails to properly validate or restrict uploaded file types. By crafting a multipart/form-data POST request, an attacker can upload a .php file directly into the web-accessible files/ directory and trigger its execution via a subsequent GET request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10046 | E-Mail Security Virtual Appliance learn-msg.cgi Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10046</link><description>The E-Mail Security Virtual Appliance (ESVA) (tested on version ESVA_2057) contains an unauthenticated command injection vulnerability in the learn-msg.cgi script. The CGI handler fails to sanitize user-supplied input passed via the id parameter, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary shell commands. Exploitation requires no authentication and results in full command execution on the underlying system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10047 | Cyclope Employee Surveillance Solution v6.x SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10047</link><description>Cyclope Employee Surveillance Solution versions 6.x is vulnerable to a SQL injection flaw in its login mechanism. The username parameter in the auth-login POST request is not properly sanitized, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary SQL statements. This can be leveraged to write and execute a malicious PHP file on disk, resulting in remote code execution under the SYSTEM user context.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10048 | Zenoss 3.x showDaemonXMLConfig Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10048</link><description>Zenoss Core 3.x contains a command injection vulnerability in the showDaemonXMLConfig endpoint. The daemon parameter is passed directly to a Popen() call in ZenossInfo.py without proper sanitation, allowing authenticated users to execute arbitrary commands on the server as the zenoss user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10049 | WebPageTest Arbitrary PHP File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10049</link><description>WebPageTest version 2.6 and earlier contains an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the resultimage.php script. The application fails to validate or sanitize user-supplied input before saving uploaded files to a publicly accessible directory. This flaw allows remote attackers to upload and execute arbitrary PHP code, resulting in full remote code execution under the web server context.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10050 | CuteFlow &amp;lt;= 2.11.2 Arbitrary File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10050</link><description>CuteFlow version 2.11.2 and earlier contains an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the restart_circulation_values_write.php script. The application fails to validate or restrict uploaded file types, allowing unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary PHP files to the upload/___1/ directory. These files are then accessible via the web server, enabling remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10051 | Photodex ProShow Producer 5.0.3256 load File Handling Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10051</link><description>Photodex ProShow Producer version 5.0.3256 contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the handling of plugin load list files. When a specially crafted load file is placed in the installation directory, the application fails to properly validate its contents, leading to a buffer overflow when the file is parsed during startup. Exploitation requires local access to place the file and user interaction to launch the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10052 | EGallery 1.2 Arbitrary PHP File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10052</link><description>EGallery version 1.2 contains an unauthenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the uploadify.php script. The application fails to validate file types or enforce authentication, allowing remote attackers to upload malicious PHP files directly into the web-accessible egallery/ directory. This results in full remote code execution under the web server context.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10053 | Simple Web Server Connection Header Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10053</link><description>Simple Web Server 2.2 rc2 contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in its handling of the Connection HTTP header. When a remote attacker sends an overly long string in this header, the server uses vsprintf() without proper bounds checking, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. This flaw allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with the privileges of the web server process. The vulnerability is triggered before authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8734 | GNU Bison scan-code.c code_free double free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8734</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in GNU Bison up to 3.8.2. Affected is the function code_free of the file src/scan-code.c. The manipulation leads to double free. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52913 | A vulnerability in the NuPoint Unified Messaging (NPM) component of Mitel MiCollab through 9.8 SP2 (9.8.2.12) could allow an unauthenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52913</link><description>A vulnerability in the NuPoint Unified Messaging (NPM) component of Mitel MiCollab through 9.8 SP2 (9.8.2.12) could allow an unauthenticated attacker to conduct a path traversal attack due to insufficient input validation. A successful exploit could allow unauthorized access, enabling the attacker to view, corrupt, or delete users' data and system configurations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:50:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52914 | A vulnerability in the Suite Applications Services component of Mitel MiCollab 10.0 through SP1 FP1 (10.0.1.101) could allow an authenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52914</link><description>A vulnerability in the Suite Applications Services component of Mitel MiCollab 10.0 through SP1 FP1 (10.0.1.101) could allow an authenticated attacker to conduct a SQL Injection attack due to insufficient validation of user input. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL database commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8733 | GNU Bison obprintf.c __obstack_vprintf_internal assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8733</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GNU Bison up to 3.8.2. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function __obstack_vprintf_internal of the file obprintf.c. The manipulation leads to reachable assertion. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50927 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the List All FTP User Function in EHCP v20.04.1.b allows authenticated attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50927</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the List All FTP User Function in EHCP v20.04.1.b allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript via injecting a crafted payload into the ftpusername parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5095 | Burk Technology ARC Solo Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5095</link><description>Burk Technology ARC Solo's password change mechanism can be utilized without proper 
authentication procedures, allowing an attacker to take over the device.
 A password change request can be sent directly to the device's HTTP 
endpoint without providing valid credentials. The system does not 
enforce proper authentication or session validation, allowing the 
password change to proceed without verifying the request's legitimacy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50928 | Easy Hosting Control Panel EHCP v20.04.1.b was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter in the Change Settin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50928</link><description>Easy Hosting Control Panel EHCP v20.04.1.b was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter in the Change Settings function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:24:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50465 | OpenMetadata &lt;=1.4.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. An attacker can extract information from the database in function listCount in the Test...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50465</link><description>OpenMetadata &lt;=1.4.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. An attacker can extract information from the database in function listCount in the TestDefinitionDAO interface. The testPlatform parameter can be used to build a SQL query.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50466 | OpenMetadata &lt;=1.4.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. An attacker can extract information from the database in function listCount in the Test...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50466</link><description>OpenMetadata &lt;=1.4.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. An attacker can extract information from the database in function listCount in the TestDefinitionDAO interface. The entityType parameter can be used to build a SQL query.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50467 | OpenMetadata &lt;=1.4.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. An attacker can extract information from the database in function listCount in the Test...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50467</link><description>OpenMetadata &lt;=1.4.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. An attacker can extract information from the database in function listCount in the TestDefinitionDAO interface. The supportedDataTypeParam parameter can be used to build a SQL query.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50468 | OpenMetadata &lt;=1.4.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. An attacker can extract information from the database in function listCount in the DocS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50468</link><description>OpenMetadata &lt;=1.4.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. An attacker can extract information from the database in function listCount in the DocStoreDAO interface. The entityType parameters can be used to build a SQL query.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8732 | libxml2 xmlcatalog xmlParseSGMLCatalog recursion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8732</link><description>A vulnerability was found in libxml2 up to 2.14.5. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function xmlParseSGMLCatalog of the component xmlcatalog. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled recursion. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The code maintainer explains, that "[t]he issue can only be triggered with untrusted SGML catalogs and it makes absolutely no sense to use untrusted catalogs. I also doubt that anyone is still using SGML catalogs at all."</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46414 | EG4 Electronics EG4 Inverters Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46414</link><description>The affected product does not limit the number of attempts for inputting
 the correct PIN for a registered product, which may allow an attacker 
to gain unauthorized access using brute-force methods if they possess a 
valid device serial number. The API provides clear feedback when the 
correct PIN is entered. This vulnerability was patched in a server-side 
update on April 6, 2025.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8284 | Packet Power EMX and EG Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8284</link><description>By default, the Packet Power Monitoring and Control Web Interface do not
 enforce authentication mechanisms. This vulnerability could allow 
unauthorized users to access and manipulate monitoring and control 
functions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8393 | Dreame Technology iOS and Android Mobile Applications Improper Certificate Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8393</link><description>A TLS vulnerability exists in the phone application used to manage a 
connected device. The phone application accepts self-signed certificates
 when establishing TLS communication which may result in 
man-in-the-middle attacks on untrusted networks. Captured communications
 may include user credentials and sensitive session tokens.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47872 | EG4 Electronics EG4 Inverters Observable Discrepancy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47872</link><description>The public-facing product registration endpoint server responds 
differently depending on whether the S/N is valid and unregistered, 
valid but already registered, or does not exist in the database. 
Combined with the fact that serial numbers are sequentially assigned, 
this allows an attacker to gain information on the product registration 
status of different S/Ns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53520 | EG4 Electronics EG4 Inverters Download of Code Without Integrity Check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53520</link><description>The affected product allows firmware updates to be downloaded from EG4's
 website, transferred via USB dongles, or installed through EG4's 
Monitoring Center (remote, cloud-connected interface) or via a serial 
connection, and can install these files without integrity checks. The 
TTComp archive format used for the firmware is unencrypted and can be 
unpacked and altered without detection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52586 | EG4 Electronics EG4 Inverters Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52586</link><description>The MOD3 command traffic between the monitoring application and the 
inverter is transmitted in plaintext without encryption or obfuscation. 
This vulnerability may allow an attacker with access to a local network 
to intercept, manipulate, replay, or forge critical data, including 
read/write operations for voltage, current, and power configuration, 
operational status, alarms, telemetry, system reset, or inverter control
 commands, potentially disrupting power generation or reconfiguring 
inverter settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4576 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.133, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4576</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.133, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.4 ,2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.7, 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.15, 7.4 GA through update 92 allows an remote non-authenticated attacker to inject JavaScript into the modules/apps/blogs/blogs-web/src/main/resources/META-INF/resources/blogs/entry_cover_image_caption.jsp</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 15:59:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8355 | XXE leading to SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8355</link><description>In Xerox FreeFlow Core version 8.0.4, improper handling of XML input allows injection of external entities. An attacker can craft malicious XML containing references to internal URLs, this results in a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF).</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 15:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8356 | Path Traversal leading to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8356</link><description>In Xerox FreeFlow Core version 8.0.4, an attacker can exploit a Path Traversal vulnerability to access unauthorized files on the server. This can lead to Remote Code Execution (RCE), allowing the attacker to run arbitrary commands on the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 15:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8731 | TRENDnet TI-G160i/TI-PG102i/TPL-430AP SSH Service default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8731</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TRENDnet TI-G160i, TI-PG102i and TPL-430AP up to 20250724. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the component SSH Service. The manipulation leads to use of default credentials. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 15:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36023 | IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation security bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36023</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation 24.0.0 through 24.0.0 IF005 and 24.0.1 through 24.0.1 IF002 could allow an authenticated user to view sensitive user and system information due to an indirect object reference through a user-controlled key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 15:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8730 | Belkin F9K1009/F9K1010 Web Interface hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8730</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Belkin F9K1009 and F9K1010 2.00.04/2.00.09 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Web Interface. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 14:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36119 | IBM i authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36119</link><description>IBM i 7.3, 7.4, 7.5, and 7.6 is affected by an authenticated user obtaining elevated privileges with IBM Digital Certificate Manager for i (DCM) due to a web session hijacking vulnerability. An authenticated user without administrator privileges could exploit this vulnerability to perform actions in DCM as an administrator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 14:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-9322 | The /users endpoint in Statamic Core before 2.11.8 allows XSS to add an administrator user. This can be exploited via CSRF. Stored XSS can o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9322</link><description>The /users endpoint in Statamic Core before 2.11.8 allows XSS to add an administrator user. This can be exploited via CSRF. Stored XSS can occur via a JavaScript payload in a username during account registration. Reflected XSS can occur via the /users PATH_INFO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 14:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8729 | MigoXLab LMeterX upload_service.py process_cert_files path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8729</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in MigoXLab LMeterX 1.2.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function process_cert_files of the file backend/service/upload_service.py. The manipulation of the argument task_id leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is f1b00597e293d09452aabd4fa57f3185207350e8. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 14:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8749 | Path traversal vulnerability in MiR robot software via API requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8749</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in API Endpoint in Mobile Industrial Robots (MiR) Software Versions prior to 3.0.0 on MiR Robots allows authenticated users to extract files from the robot file system via a crafted API request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8088 | Path traversal vulnerability in WinRAR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8088</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability affecting the Windows version of WinRAR allows the attackers to execute arbitrary code by crafting malicious archive files. This vulnerability was exploited in the wild and was discovered by Anton Cherepanov, Peter Košinár, and Peter Strýček
     from ESET.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8748 | OS command injection in MiR robots and MiR fleet via crafted HTTP requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8748</link><description>MiR software versions prior to version 3.0.0 are affected by a command injection vulnerability. A malicious 
HTTP request crafted by an authenticated user could allow the execution of arbitrary commands on the 
underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48913 | Apache CXF: Untrusted JMS configuration can lead to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48913</link><description>If untrusted users are allowed to configure JMS for Apache CXF, previously they could use RMI or LDAP URLs, potentially leading to code execution capabilities.  This interface is now restricted to reject those protocols, removing this possibility.

Users are recommended to upgrade to versions 3.6.8, 4.0.9 or 4.1.3, which fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53606 | Apache Seata (incubating): Deserialization of untrusted Data in Apache Seata Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53606</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache Seata (incubating).

This issue affects Apache Seata (incubating): 2.4.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.5.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6572 | OpenStreetMap for Gutenberg and WPBakery Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6572</link><description>The OpenStreetMap for Gutenberg and WPBakery Page Builder (formerly Visual Composer) WordPress plugin through 1.2.0 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 06:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54958 | Powered BLUE 870 versions 0.20130927 and prior contain an OS command injection vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54958</link><description>Powered BLUE 870 versions 0.20130927 and prior contain an OS command injection vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary OS commands may be executed on the affected product.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:06:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54959 | Powered BLUE Server versions 0.20130927 and prior contain a path traversal vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54959</link><description>Powered BLUE Server versions 0.20130927 and prior contain a path traversal vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary file in the affected product may be disclosed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:06:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54940 | An HTML injection vulnerability exists in WordPress plugin "Advanced Custom Fields" prior to 6.4.3. If this vulnerability is exploited, craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54940</link><description>An HTML injection vulnerability exists in WordPress plugin "Advanced Custom Fields" prior to 6.4.3. If this vulnerability is exploited, crafted HTML code may be rendered and page display may be tampered.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 04:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58255 | EnzoH has an OS command injection vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary command execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58255</link><description>EnzoH has an OS command injection vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 03:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58256 | EnzoH has an OS command injection vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary command execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58256</link><description>EnzoH has an OS command injection vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 03:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58257 | EnzoH has an OS command injection vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary command execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58257</link><description>EnzoH has an OS command injection vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 03:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8707 | Huuge Box App com.huuge.game.zjbox AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8707</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Huuge Box App 1.0.3 on Android. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.huuge.game.zjbox. The manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 03:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8708 | Antabot White-Jotter com.gm.wj.config.ShiroConfiguration ShiroConfiguration.java CookieRememberMeManager deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8708</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Antabot White-Jotter 0.22. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function CookieRememberMeManager of the file ShiroConfiguration.java of the component com.gm.wj.config.ShiroConfiguration. The manipulation with the input EVANNIGHTLY_WAOU leads to deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 03:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8706 | Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System Energy Overview Module CreateFunctionLog sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8706</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /CommonSolution/CreateFunctionLog of the component Energy Overview Module. The manipulation of the argument MM_MenID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8705 | Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System Energy Overview Module GetTargetConfig sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8705</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /WEAS_HomePage/GetTargetConfig of the component Energy Overview Module. The manipulation of the argument BP_ProID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54793 | Astro: Duplicate trailing slash feature can lead to Open Redirects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54793</link><description>Astro is a web framework for content-driven websites. In versions 5.2.0 through 5.12.7, there is an Open Redirect vulnerability in the trailing slash redirection logic when handling paths with double slashes. This allows an attacker to redirect users to arbitrary external domains by crafting URLs such as https://mydomain.com//malicious-site.com/. This increases the risk of phishing and other social engineering attacks. This affects sites that use on-demand rendering (SSR) with the Node or Cloudflare adapters. It does not affect static sites, or sites deployed to Netlify or Vercel. This issue is fixed in version 5.12.8. To work around this issue at the network level, block outgoing redirect responses with a Location header value that starts with `//`.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54886 | skops: Card.get_model does not block arbitrary code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54886</link><description>skops is a Python library which helps users share and ship their scikit-learn based models. In versions 0.12.0 and below, the Card.get_model does not contain any logic to prevent arbitrary code execution. The Card.get_model function supports both joblib and skops for model loading. When loading .skops models, it uses skops' secure loading with trusted type validation, raising errors for untrusted types unless explicitly allowed. However, when non-.zip file formats are provided, the function silently falls back to joblib without warning. Unlike skops, joblib allows arbitrary code execution during loading, bypassing security measures and potentially enabling malicious code execution. This issue is fixed in version 0.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54887 | jwe: Missing AES-GCM authentication tag validation in encrypted JWEs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54887</link><description>jwe is a Ruby implementation of the RFC 7516 JSON Web Encryption (JWE) standard. In versions 1.1.0 and below, authentication tags of encrypted JWEs can be brute forced, which may result in loss of confidentiality for those JWEs and provide ways to craft arbitrary JWEs. This puts users at risk because JWEs can be modified to decrypt to an arbitrary value, decrypted by observing parsing differences and the GCM internal GHASH key can be recovered. Users are affected by this vulnerability even if they do not use an AES-GCM encryption algorithm for their JWEs. As the GHASH key may have been leaked, users must rotate the encryption keys after upgrading. This issue is fixed in version 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8703 | Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System Environmental Real-Time Data Module GetAreaTrendChartData sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8703</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /WEAS_HomePage/GetAreaTrendChartData of the component Environmental Real-Time Data Module. The manipulation of the argument energyId leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8704 | Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System Analysis Conclusion Query Module GetAlarmResultProcessList sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8704</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /WEAS_AlarmResult/GetAlarmResultProcessList of the component Analysis Conclusion Query Module. The manipulation of the argument resultId leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54368 | uv is vulnerable to ZIP payload obfuscation through parsing differentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54368</link><description>uv is a Python package and project manager written in Rust. In versions 0.8.5 and earlier, remote ZIP archives were handled in a streamwise fashion, and file entries were not reconciled against the archive's central directory. An attacker could contrive a ZIP archive that would extract with legitimate contents on some package installers, and malicious contents on others due to multiple local file entries. An attacker could  also contrive a "stacked" ZIP input with multiple internal ZIPs, which would be handled differently by different package installers. The attacker could choose which installer to target in both scenarios. This issue is fixed in version 0.8.6. To work around this issue, users may choose to set UV_INSECURE_NO_ZIP_VALIDATION=1 to revert to the previous behavior.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8702 | Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System Historical Data Query Module GetVariableByOneIDNew sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8702</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /CommonSolution/GetVariableByOneIDNew of the component Historical Data Query Module. The manipulation of the argument ObjectID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 23:51:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54952 | An integer overflow vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause smaller-than-expected memory regions to be allocated, potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54952</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause smaller-than-expected memory regions to be allocated, potentially resulting in code execution or other undesirable effects. This issue affects ExecuTorch prior to commit 8f062d3f661e20bb19b24b767b9a9a46e8359f2b.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 23:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54950 | An out-of-bounds access vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause the runtime to crash and potentially result in code exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54950</link><description>An out-of-bounds access vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause the runtime to crash and potentially result in code execution or other undesirable effects. This issue affects ExecuTorch prior to commit fb03b6f85596a8f954d97929075335255b6a58d4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 23:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54951 | A group of related buffer overflow vulnerabilities in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause the runtime to crash and potentially result...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54951</link><description>A group of related buffer overflow vulnerabilities in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause the runtime to crash and potentially result in code execution or other undesirable effects. This issue affects ExecuTorch prior to commit cea9b23aa8ff78aff92829a466da97461cc7930c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 23:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30405 | An integer overflow vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause objects to be placed outside their allocated memory area, po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30405</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause objects to be placed outside their allocated memory area, potentially resulting in code execution or other undesirable effects. This issue affects ExecuTorch prior to commit 0830af8207240df8d7f35b984cdf8bc35d74fa73.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 23:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54949 | A heap buffer overflow vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can potentially result in code execution or other undesirable effec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54949</link><description>A heap buffer overflow vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can potentially result in code execution or other undesirable effects. This issue affects ExecuTorch prior to commit ede82493dae6d2d43f8c424e7be4721abe5242be</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 23:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30404 | An integer overflow vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause overlapping allocations, potentially resulting in code execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30404</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability in the loading of ExecuTorch models can cause overlapping allocations, potentially resulting in code execution or other undesirable effects. This issue affects ExecuTorch prior to commit d158236b1dc84539c1b16843bc74054c9dcba006.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54787 | SuiteCRM: Improper Authorization for attachment downloads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54787</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. There is a vulnerability in SuiteCRM version 7.14.6 which allows unauthenticated downloads of any file from the upload-directory, as long as it is named by an ID (e.g. attachments). An unauthenticated attacker could download internal files when he discovers a valid file-ID.
Valid IDs could be brute-forced, but this is quite time-consuming as the file-IDs are usually UUIDs. This issue is fixed in version 7.14.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45765 | ruby-jwt v3.0.0.beta1 was discovered to contain weak encryption. NOTE: the Supplier's perspective is "keysize is not something that is enfor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45765</link><description>ruby-jwt v3.0.0.beta1 was discovered to contain weak encryption. NOTE: the Supplier's perspective is "keysize is not something that is enforced by this library. Currently more recent versions of OpenSSL are enforcing some key sizes and those restrictions apply to the users of this gem also."</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53767 | Azure OpenAI Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53767</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53774 | Microsoft 365 Copilot BizChat Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53774</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53787 | Microsoft 365 Copilot BizChat Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53787</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53792 | Azure Portal Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53792</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8701 | Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System GetPageList sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8701</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Wanzhou WOES Intelligent Optimization Energy Saving System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /OL_OprationLog/GetPageList. The manipulation of the argument optUser leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 21:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26513 | The installer for SAN Host Utilities for Windows versions prior to 8.0 is susceptible to a vulnerability which when successfully exploited c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26513</link><description>The installer for SAN Host Utilities for Windows versions prior to 8.0 is susceptible to a vulnerability which when successfully exploited could allow a local user to escalate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8698 | Open5GS AMF Service nsmf-handler.c amf_nsmf_pdusession_handle_release_sm_context assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8698</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function amf_nsmf_pdusession_handle_release_sm_context of the file src/amf/nsmf-handler.c of the component AMF Service. The manipulation leads to reachable assertion. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is 66bc558e417e70ae216ec155e4e81c14ae0ecf30. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48709 | An issue was discovered in BMC Control-M 9.0.21.300. When Control-M Server has a database connection, it runs DBUStatus.exe frequently, whic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48709</link><description>An issue was discovered in BMC Control-M 9.0.21.300. When Control-M Server has a database connection, it runs DBUStatus.exe frequently, which then calls dbu_connection_details.vbs with the username, password, database hostname, and port written in cleartext, which can be seen in event and process logs in two separate locations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47183 | In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the isomp4 plugin's qtdemux_parse_tree function may read past the end of a heap buffer while parsing an MP4 fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47183</link><description>In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the isomp4 plugin's qtdemux_parse_tree function may read past the end of a heap buffer while parsing an MP4 file, leading to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47219 | In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the isomp4 plugin's qtdemux_parse_trak function may read past the end of a heap buffer while parsing an MP4 fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47219</link><description>In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the isomp4 plugin's qtdemux_parse_trak function may read past the end of a heap buffer while parsing an MP4 file, possibly leading to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47806 | In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the subparse plugin's parse_subrip_time function may write data past the bounds of a stack buffer, leading to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47806</link><description>In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the subparse plugin's parse_subrip_time function may write data past the bounds of a stack buffer, leading to a crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47807 | In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the subparse plugin's subrip_unescape_formatting function may dereference a NULL pointer while parsing a subtit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47807</link><description>In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the subparse plugin's subrip_unescape_formatting function may dereference a NULL pointer while parsing a subtitle file, leading to a crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47808 | In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the subparse plugin's tmplayer_parse_line function may dereference a NULL pointer while parsing a subtitle file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47808</link><description>In GStreamer through 1.26.1, the subparse plugin's tmplayer_parse_line function may dereference a NULL pointer while parsing a subtitle file, leading to a crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7195 | Operator-sdk: privilege escalation due to incorrect permissions of /etc/passwd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7195</link><description>Early versions of Operator-SDK provided an insecure method to allow operator containers to run in environments that used a random UID. Operator-SDK before 0.15.2 provided a script, user_setup, which modifies the permissions of the /etc/passwd file to 664 during build time. Developers who used Operator-SDK before 0.15.2 to scaffold their operator may still be impacted by this if the insecure user_setup script is still being used to build new container images. In affected images, the /etc/passwd file was created during build time with group-writable permissions and a group ownership of root (gid=0). An attacker who can execute commands within an affected container, even as a non-root user, may be able to leverage their membership in the root group to modify the /etc/passwd file. This could allow the attacker to add a new user with any arbitrary UID, including UID 0, leading to full root privileges within the container.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8697 | agentUniverse MCPSessionManager/MCPTool/MCPToolkit StdioServerParameters os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8697</link><description>A vulnerability was found in agentUniverse up to 0.0.18 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function StdioServerParameters of the component MCPSessionManager/MCPTool/MCPToolkit. The manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50675 | GPMAW 14, a bioinformatics software, has a critical vulnerability related to insecure file permissions in its installation directory. The di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50675</link><description>GPMAW 14, a bioinformatics software, has a critical vulnerability related to insecure file permissions in its installation directory. The directory is accessible with full read, write, and execute permissions for all users, allowing unprivileged users to manipulate files within the directory, including executable files like GPMAW3.exe, Fragment.exe, and the uninstaller GPsetup64_17028.exe. An attacker with user-level access can exploit this misconfiguration by replacing or modifying the uninstaller (GPsetup64_17028.exe) with a malicious version. While the application itself runs in the user's context, the uninstaller is typically executed with administrative privileges when an administrator attempts to uninstall the software. By exploiting this flaw, an attacker could gain administrative privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the admin, resulting in privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50692 | FoxCMS &lt;=v1.2.5 is vulnerable to Code Execution in admin/template_file/editFile.html.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50692</link><description>FoxCMS &lt;=v1.2.5 is vulnerable to Code Execution in admin/template_file/editFile.html.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55077 | Tyler Technologies ERP Pro 9 SaaS application escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55077</link><description>Tyler Technologies ERP Pro 9 SaaS allows an authenticated user to escape the application and execute limited operating system commands within the remote Microsoft Windows environment with the privileges of the authenticated user. Tyler Technologies deployed hardened remote Windows environment settings to all ERP Pro 9 SaaS customer environments as of 2025-08-01.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51533 | An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in Sage DPW v2024.12.003 allows unauthorized attackers to access internal forms via sending a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51533</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in Sage DPW v2024.12.003 allows unauthorized attackers to access internal forms via sending a crafted GET request. This is fixed in Halbjahresversion 2024_12_004.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41530 | Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the app_contact parameter in appsearch.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41530</link><description>Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the app_contact parameter in appsearch.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41531 | Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in func3.php via the username1 and password2 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41531</link><description>Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in func3.php via the username1 and password2 parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41532 | Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the doctor_contact parameter in doctorsearch.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41532</link><description>Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the doctor_contact parameter in doctorsearch.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41525 | Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the patient_contact parameter in patientsearch.php...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41525</link><description>Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the patient_contact parameter in patientsearch.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41526 | Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in func1.php via the username3 and password3 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41526</link><description>Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in func1.php via the username3 and password3 parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41527 | Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the password2 parameter in func.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41527</link><description>Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the password2 parameter in func.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41528 | Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in contact.php via the txtname, txtphone, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41528</link><description>Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in contact.php via the txtname, txtphone, and txtmail parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41529 | Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in func2.php via the fname and l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41529</link><description>Hospital Management System v4 was discovered to contain multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in func2.php via the fname and lname parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41520 | Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in createClassArms.php via the clas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41520</link><description>Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in createClassArms.php via the classId and classArmName parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41521 | Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in createSessionTerm.php via the id...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41521</link><description>Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in createSessionTerm.php via the id, termId, and sessionName parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41522 | Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in createStudents.php via the Id, f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41522</link><description>Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in createStudents.php via the Id, firstname, and admissionNumber parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41523 | Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the emailAddress parameter at createClas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41523</link><description>Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the emailAddress parameter at createClassTeacher.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41524 | Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the username parameter at index.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41524</link><description>Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the username parameter at index.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51629 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the PdfViewer component of Agenzia Impresa Eccobook 2.81.1 allows attackers to execute arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51629</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the PdfViewer component of Agenzia Impresa Eccobook 2.81.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the Temp parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40992 | Hospital Management System 4 is vulnerable to a SQL injection in /Hospital-Management-System-master/func.php via the password2 parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40992</link><description>Hospital Management System 4 is vulnerable to a SQL injection in /Hospital-Management-System-master/func.php via the password2 parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41519 | Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the sessionName parameter a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41519</link><description>Student Attendance Management System v1 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the sessionName parameter at createSessionTerm.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:43:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24000 | WordPress Post SMTP plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Account Takeover Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24000</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in WPExperts Post SMTP allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Post SMTP: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42048 | OpenOrange Business Framework 1.15.5 provides unprivileged users with write access to the installation directory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42048</link><description>OpenOrange Business Framework 1.15.5 provides unprivileged users with write access to the installation directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34148 | Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater OS Command Injection via WISP SSID</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34148</link><description>An unauthenticated OS command injection vulnerability exists in the Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater (hardware model MT02). When configuring the device in WISP mode, the 'ssid' parameter is passed unsanitized to system-level scripts. This allows remote attackers within Wi-Fi range to inject arbitrary shell commands that execute as root, resulting in full device compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34149 | Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater OS Command Injection via WPA2 Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34149</link><description>A command injection vulnerability affects the Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater (hardware model MT02) during WPA2 configuration. The 'key' parameter is interpreted directly by the system shell, enabling attackers to execute arbitrary commands as root. Exploitation requires no authentication and can be triggered during wireless setup.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34150 | Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater PPPoE Username Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34150</link><description>The PPPoE configuration interface of the Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater (hardware model MT02) is vulnerable to command injection via the 'user' parameter. Input is processed unsafely during network setup, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary system commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34151 | Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater PPPoE Password Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34151</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in the 'passwd' parameter of the PPPoE setup process on the Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater (hardware model MT02). The input is passed directly to system-level commands without sanitation, enabling unauthenticated attackers to achieve root-level code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34152 | Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater OS Command Injection via Time Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34152</link><description>An unauthenticated OS command injection vulnerability exists in the Shenzhen Aitemi M300 Wi-Fi Repeater (hardware model MT02) via the 'time' parameter of the '/protocol.csp?' endpoint. The input is processed by the internal date '-s' command without rebooting or disrupting HTTP service. Unlike other injection points, this vector allows remote compromise without triggering visible configuration changes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54392 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 allows XSS for authentication error data, a different vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54392</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 allows XSS for authentication error data, a different vulnerability than CVE-2025-47189.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54393 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 allows Static Code Injection. Authenticated users can obt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54393</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 allows Static Code Injection. Authenticated users can obtain administrative access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54394 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 has Insufficiently Protected Credentials for requests to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54394</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 has Insufficiently Protected Credentials for requests to remote Excel resources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54395 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 allows XSS for authentication configuration data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54395</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 allows XSS for authentication configuration data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54396 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 allows SQL Injection. Authenticated users can exploit thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54396</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 allows SQL Injection. Authenticated users can exploit this.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54397 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 inserts Sensitive Information Into Sent Data to authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54397</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) 11.0.0.0 before 11.1.25162.02 inserts Sensitive Information Into Sent Data to authenticated users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55137 | LinkJoin through 882f196 mishandles lacks type checking in password reset.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55137</link><description>LinkJoin through 882f196 mishandles lacks type checking in password reset.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55138 | LinkJoin through 882f196 mishandles token ownership in password reset.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55138</link><description>LinkJoin through 882f196 mishandles token ownership in password reset.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56339 | IBM WebSphere Application Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56339</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 9.0 and WebSphere Application Server Liberty 17.0.0.3 through 25.0.0.7 could allow a remote attacker to bypass security restrictions caused by a failure to honor security configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55133 | In Agora Foundation Agora fall23-Alpha1 before b087490, there is XSS via topicName in client/agora/public/js/editorManager.js.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55133</link><description>In Agora Foundation Agora fall23-Alpha1 before b087490, there is XSS via topicName in client/agora/public/js/editorManager.js.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55134 | In Agora Foundation Agora fall23-Alpha1 before b087490, there is XSS via tag in client/agora/public/js/editorManager.js.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55134</link><description>In Agora Foundation Agora fall23-Alpha1 before b087490, there is XSS via tag in client/agora/public/js/editorManager.js.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55135 | In Agora Foundation Agora fall23-Alpha1 before 690ce56, there is XSS via a profile picture to server/controller/userController.js. Formats o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55135</link><description>In Agora Foundation Agora fall23-Alpha1 before 690ce56, there is XSS via a profile picture to server/controller/userController.js. Formats other than PNG, JPEG, and WEBP are permitted by server/routes/userRoutes.js; this includes SVG.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55136 | ERC (aka Emotion Recognition in Conversation) through 0.3 has insecure deserialization via a serialized object because jsonpickle is used.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55136</link><description>ERC (aka Emotion Recognition in Conversation) through 0.3 has insecure deserialization via a serialized object because jsonpickle is used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47907 | Incorrect results returned from Rows.Scan in database/sql</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47907</link><description>Cancelling a query (e.g. by cancelling the context passed to one of the query methods) during a call to the Scan method of the returned Rows can result in unexpected results if other queries are being made in parallel. This can result in a race condition that may overwrite the expected results with those of another query, causing the call to Scan to return either unexpected results from the other query or an error.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7054 | Infinite loop triggered by connection ID retirement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7054</link><description>Cloudflare quiche was discovered to be vulnerable to an infinite loop when sending packets containing RETIRE_CONNECTION_ID frames.

QUIC connections possess a set of connection identifiers (IDs); see  Section 5.1 of RFC 9000 https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc9000#section-5.1 . Once the QUIC handshake completes, a local endpoint is responsible for issuing and retiring Connection IDs that are used by the remote peer to populate the Destination Connection ID field in packets sent from remote to local. Each Connection ID has a sequence number to ensure synchronization between peers.

An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability by first completing a handshake and then sending a specially-crafted set of frames that trigger a connection ID retirement in the victim. When the victim attempts to send a packet containing RETIRE_CONNECTION_ID frames,  Section 19.16 of RFC 9000 https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc9000#section-19.6  requires that the sequence number of the retired connection ID must not be the same as the sequence number of the connection ID used by the packet. In other words, a packet cannot contain a frame that retires itself. In scenarios such as path migration, it is possible for there to be multiple active paths with different active connection IDs that could be used to retire each other. The exploit triggered an unintentional behaviour of a quiche design feature that supports retirement across paths while maintaining full connection ID synchronization, leading to an infinite loop.This issue affects quiche: from 0.15.0 before 0.24.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44779 | An issue in Ollama v0.1.33 allows attackers to delete arbitrary files via sending a crafted packet to the endpoint /api/pull.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44779</link><description>An issue in Ollama v0.1.33 allows attackers to delete arbitrary files via sending a crafted packet to the endpoint /api/pull.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50952 | openjpeg v 2.5.0 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the component /openjp2/dwt.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50952</link><description>openjpeg v 2.5.0 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the component /openjp2/dwt.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47188 | A vulnerability in the Mitel 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones, including the 6970 Conference Unit through 6.4 SP4, coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47188</link><description>A vulnerability in the Mitel 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones, including the 6970 Conference Unit through 6.4 SP4, could allow an unauthenticated attacker to conduct a command injection attack due to insufficient parameter sanitization. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands within the context of the phone, leading to disclosure or modification of sensitive configuration data or affecting device availability and operation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52680 | EyouCMS 1.6.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /login.php?m=admin&amp;c=System&amp;a=web&amp;lang=cn.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52680</link><description>EyouCMS 1.6.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /login.php?m=admin&amp;amp;c=System&amp;amp;a=web&amp;lang;=cn.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 14:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55401 | An issue in 4C Strategies Exonaut before v22.4 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55401</link><description>An issue in 4C Strategies Exonaut before v22.4 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 13:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8533 | Incorrect Authorization of XPC Service in Fantastical.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8533</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in the XPC services of Fantastical. The services failed to implement proper client authorization checks in its listener:shouldAcceptNewConnection method, unconditionally accepting requests from any local process. As a result, any local, unprivileged process could connect to the XPC service and access its methods.




This issue has been resolved in version 4.0.16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35970 | On multiple products of SEIKO EPSON and FUJIFILM Corporation, the initial administrator password is easy to guess from the information avail...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35970</link><description>On multiple products of SEIKO EPSON and FUJIFILM Corporation, the initial administrator password is easy to guess from the information available via SNMP. If the administrator password is not changed from the initial one, a remote attacker with SNMP access can log in to the product with the administrator privilege.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29866 | : External Control of File Name or Path vulnerability in TAGFREE X-Free Uploader XFU allows : Parameter Injection.This issue affects X-Free ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29866</link><description>: External Control of File Name or Path vulnerability in TAGFREE X-Free Uploader XFU allows : Parameter Injection.This issue affects X-Free Uploader: from 1.0.1.0084 before 1.0.1.0085, from 2.0.1.0034 before 2.0.1.0035.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32094 | An issue was discovered in Akamai Ghost, as used for the Akamai CDN platform before 2025-03-26. Under certain circumstances, a client making...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32094</link><description>An issue was discovered in Akamai Ghost, as used for the Akamai CDN platform before 2025-03-26. Under certain circumstances, a client making an HTTP/1.x OPTIONS request with an "Expect: 100-continue" header, and using obsolete line folding, can lead to a discrepancy in how two in-path Akamai servers interpret the request, allowing an attacker to smuggle a second request in the original request body.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:35:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29865 | : Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in TAGFREE X-Free Uploader XFU allows Path Tr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29865</link><description>: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in TAGFREE X-Free Uploader XFU allows Path Traversal.This issue affects X-Free Uploader: from 1.0.1.0084 before 1.0.1.0085, from 2.0.1.0034 before 2.0.1.0035.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8576 | Use after free in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8576</link><description>Use after free in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted Chrome Extension. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8577 | Inappropriate implementation in Picture In Picture in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8577</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Picture In Picture in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8578 | Use after free in Cast in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8578</link><description>Use after free in Cast in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8579 | Inappropriate implementation in Picture In Picture in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8579</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Picture In Picture in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8580 | Inappropriate implementation in Filesystems in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8580</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Filesystems in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8581 | Inappropriate implementation in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8581</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to leak cross-origin data via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8582 | Insufficient validation of untrusted input in Core in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to spoof the contents o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8582</link><description>Insufficient validation of untrusted input in Core in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to spoof the contents of the Omnibox (URL bar) via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8583 | Inappropriate implementation in Permissions in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8583</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Permissions in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.66 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3770 | SMM IDT Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3770</link><description>EDK2 contains a vulnerability in BIOS where an attacker may cause “Protection Mechanism Failure” by local access. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will lead to arbitrary code execution and impact Confidentiality, Integrity, and Availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54783 | SuiteCRM: Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) through HTTP Referrer header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54783</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Versions 7.14.6 and below have a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code by modifying the HTTP Referer header to include some arbitrary domain with malicious JavaScript code at the end. The server will attempt to block the arbitrary domain but allow the JavaScript code to execute. This is fixed in version 7.14.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54784 | SuiteCRM is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) through its email viewer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54784</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. There is a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the email viewer in versions 7.14.0 through 7.14.6. An external attacker could send a prepared message to the inbox of the SuiteCRM-instance. By simply viewing emails as the logged-in user, the payload can be triggered. With that, an attacker is able to run arbitrary actions as the logged-in user - like extracting data, or if it is an admin executing the payload, takeover the instance. This is fixed in versions 7.14.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54798 | tmp does not restrict arbitrary temporary file / directory write via symbolic link `dir` parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54798</link><description>tmp is a temporary file and directory creator for node.js. In versions 0.2.3 and below, tmp is vulnerable to an arbitrary temporary file / directory write via symbolic link dir parameter. This is fixed in version 0.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54799 | Lego does not enforce HTTPS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54799</link><description>Let's Encrypt client and ACME library written in Go (Lego). In versions 4.25.1 and below, the github.com/go-acme/lego/v4/acme/api package (thus the lego library and the lego cli as well) don't enforce HTTPS when talking to CAs as an ACME client. Unlike the http-01 challenge which solves an ACME challenge over unencrypted HTTP, the ACME protocol requires HTTPS when a client communicates with the CA to performs ACME functions. However, the library fails to enforce HTTPS both in the original discover URL (configured by the library user) and in the subsequent addresses returned by the CAs in the directory and order objects. If users input HTTP URLs or CAs misconfigure endpoints, protocol operations occur over HTTP instead of HTTPS. This compromises privacy by exposing request/response details like account and request identifiers to network attackers. This was fixed in version 4.25.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54882 | Himmelblau&amp;#x27;s Kerberos credential cache collection is world readable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54882</link><description>Himmelblau is an interoperability suite for Microsoft Azure Entra ID and Intune. In versions 0.8.0 through 0.9.21 and 1.0.0-beta through 1.1.0, Himmelblau stores the cloud TGT received during logon in the Kerberos credential cache. The created credential cache collection and received credentials are stored as world readable. This is fixed in versions 0.9.22 and 1.2.0. To work around this issue, remove all read access to Himmelblau caches for all users except for owners.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54885 | Thinbus generates insufficient entropy: 252 bits vs minimum 256 bits</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54885</link><description>Thinbus Javascript Secure Remote Password is a browser SRP6a implementation for zero-knowledge password authentication. In versions 2.0.0 and below, a protocol compliance bug causes the client to generate a fixed 252 bits of entropy instead of the intended bit length of the safe prime (defaulted to 2048 bits). The client public value is being generated from a private value that is 4 bits below the specification. This reduces the protocol's designed security margin it is now practically exploitable. The servers full sized 2048 bit random number is used to create the shared session key and password proof. This is fixed in version 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>