<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 19:11:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-2259 | Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo component HTTP server single PUT request integer underflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2259</link><description>In NetX HTTP server functionality of Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo before 
version 6.4.3, an attacker can cause an integer underflow and a 
subsequent denial of service by writing a very large file, by specially 
crafted packets with Content-Length in one packet smaller than the data 
request size of the other packet. A possible workaround is to disable 
HTTP PUT support.




This issue follows an incomplete fix of CVE-2025-0727</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 19:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2260 | Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo HTTP component server denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2260</link><description>In NetX HTTP server functionality of Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo before 
version 6.4.3, an attacker can cause a denial of service by specially 
crafted packets. The core issue is missing closing of a file in case of 
an error condition, resulting in the 404 error for each further file 
request. Users can work-around the issue by disabling the PUT request 
support.




This issue follows an incomplete fix of CVE-2025-0726.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 19:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2258 | Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo HTTP server single PUT request integer underflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2258</link><description>In NetX Duo component HTTP server functionality of Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo before 
version 6.4.3, an attacker can cause an integer underflow and a 
subsequent denial of service by writing a very large file, by specially 
crafted packets with Content-Length smaller than the data request size. A
 possible workaround is to disable HTTP PUT support.




This issue follows an uncomplete fix in CVE-2025-0728.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 18:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3318 | Kenj_Frog 肯尼基蛙 company-financial-management 公司财务管理系统 ShangpinleixingController.java page sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3318</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Kenj_Frog 肯尼基蛙 company-financial-management 公司财务管理系统 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function page of the file src/main/java/com/controller/ShangpinleixingController.java. The manipulation of the argument sort leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 14:17:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3317 | fumiao opencms dataPage.jsp path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3317</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in fumiao opencms up to a0fafa5cff58719e9b27c2a2eec204cc165ce14f. Affected is an unknown function of the file opencms-dev/src/main/webapp/view/admin/document/dataPage.jsp. The manipulation of the argument path leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 11:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3316 | PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System search-invoices.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3316</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/search-invoices.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 11:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3315 | SourceCodester Apartment Visitor Management System view-report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3315</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Apartment Visitor Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /view-report.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 10:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3314 | SourceCodester Apartment Visitor Management System forgotpw.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3314</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Apartment Visitor Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /forgotpw.php. The manipulation of the argument secode leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 08:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3313 | PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System add-customer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3313</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/add-customer.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 08:10:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3312 | PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System add-customer-services.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3312</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/add-customer-services.php. The manipulation of the argument sids[] leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 07:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32370 | Kentico Xperience before 13.0.178 has a specific set of allowed ContentUploader file extensions for unauthenticated uploads; however, becaus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32370</link><description>Kentico Xperience before 13.0.178 has a specific set of allowed ContentUploader file extensions for unauthenticated uploads; however, because .zip is processed through TryZipProviderSafe, there is additional functionality to create files with other extensions. NOTE: this is a separate issue not necessarily related to SVG or XSS.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 06:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3311 | PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System about-us.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3311</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/about-us.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 06:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32369 | Kentico Xperience before 13.0.181 allows authenticated users to distribute malicious content (for stored XSS) via certain interactions with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32369</link><description>Kentico Xperience before 13.0.181 allows authenticated users to distribute malicious content (for stored XSS) via certain interactions with the media library file upload feature.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 06:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3310 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3310</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument Search leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 06:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3309 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System campsdetails.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3309</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/campsdetails.php. The manipulation of the argument hospital leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 05:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1264 | Broken Link Checker by AIOSEO &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1264</link><description>The Broken Link Checker by AIOSEO – Easily Fix/Monitor Internal and External links plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'orderBy' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 04:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3308 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System viewrequest.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3308</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /viewrequest.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 04:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58131 | FISCO BCOS 3.11.0 has an issue with synchronization of the transaction pool that can, for example, be observed when a malicious node (that h...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58131</link><description>FISCO BCOS 3.11.0 has an issue with synchronization of the transaction pool that can, for example, be observed when a malicious node (that has modified the codebase to allow a large min_seal_time value) joins a blockchain network.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 03:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58132 | In chainmaker-go (aka ChainMaker) before 2.3.6, multiple updates to a single node's configuration can cause other normal nodes to perform co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58132</link><description>In chainmaker-go (aka ChainMaker) before 2.3.6, multiple updates to a single node's configuration can cause other normal nodes to perform concurrent read and write operations on a map, leading to a panic.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 03:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3307 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System reset.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3307</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /reset.php. The manipulation of the argument useremail leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 03:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58133 | In chainmaker-go (aka ChainMaker) before 2.4.0, when making frequent updates to a node's configuration file and restarting this node, concur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58133</link><description>In chainmaker-go (aka ChainMaker) before 2.4.0, when making frequent updates to a node's configuration file and restarting this node, concurrent writes by logger.go to a map are mishandled. Creating other logs simultaneously can lead to a read-write conflict and panic.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 03:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3306 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System don.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3306</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /don.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 01:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32366 | In ConnMan through 1.44, parse_rr in dnsproxy.c has a memcpy length that depends on an RR RDLENGTH value, i.e., *rdlen=ntohs(rr-&gt;rdlen) and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32366</link><description>In ConnMan through 1.44, parse_rr in dnsproxy.c has a memcpy length that depends on an RR RDLENGTH value, i.e., *rdlen=ntohs(rr-&gt;rdlen) and memcpy(response+offset,*end,*rdlen).</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 23:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3305 | 1902756969/code-projects IKUN_Library Borrow MvcConfig.java addInterceptors access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3305</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 1902756969/code-projects IKUN_Library 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function addInterceptors of the file MvcConfig.java of the component Borrow Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 22:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32364 | A floating-point exception in the PSStack::roll function of Poppler before 25.04.0 can cause an application to crash when handling malformed...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32364</link><description>A floating-point exception in the PSStack::roll function of Poppler before 25.04.0 can cause an application to crash when handling malformed inputs associated with INT_MIN.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 22:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32365 | Poppler before 25.04.0 allows crafted input files to trigger out-of-bounds reads in the JBIG2Bitmap::combine function in JBIG2Stream.cc beca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32365</link><description>Poppler before 25.04.0 allows crafted input files to trigger out-of-bounds reads in the JBIG2Bitmap::combine function in JBIG2Stream.cc because of a misplaced isOk check.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 22:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3304 | code-projects Patient Record Management System dental_not.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3304</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /dental_not.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 22:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3303 | code-projects Patient Record Management System birthing_record.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3303</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /birthing_record.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 21:25:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32357 | In Zammad 6.4.x before 6.4.2, an authenticated agent with knowledge base permissions was able to use the Zammad API to fetch knowledge base ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32357</link><description>In Zammad 6.4.x before 6.4.2, an authenticated agent with knowledge base permissions was able to use the Zammad API to fetch knowledge base content that they have no permission for.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 20:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32358 | In Zammad 6.4.x before 6.4.2, SSRF can occur. Authenticated admin users can enable webhooks in Zammad, which are triggered as POST requests ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32358</link><description>In Zammad 6.4.x before 6.4.2, SSRF can occur. Authenticated admin users can enable webhooks in Zammad, which are triggered as POST requests when certain conditions are met. If a webhook endpoint returned a redirect response, Zammad would follow it automatically with another GET request. This could be abused by an attacker to cause GET requests for example in the local network.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 20:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32359 | In Zammad 6.4.x before 6.4.2, there is client-side enforcement of server-side security. When changing their two factor authentication config...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32359</link><description>In Zammad 6.4.x before 6.4.2, there is client-side enforcement of server-side security. When changing their two factor authentication configuration, users need to re-authenticate with their current password first. However, this change was enforced in Zammad only on the front end level, and not when using the API directly.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 20:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32360 | In Zammad 6.4.x before 6.4.2, there is information exposure. Only agents should be able to see and work on shared article drafts. However, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32360</link><description>In Zammad 6.4.x before 6.4.2, there is information exposure. Only agents should be able to see and work on shared article drafts. However, a logged in customer was able to see details about shared drafts for their customer tickets in the browser console, which may contain confidential information, and also to manipulate them via API.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 20:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56370 | Net::Xero 0.044 and earlier for Perl uses insecure rand() function for cryptographic functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56370</link><description>Net::Xero 0.044 and earlier for Perl uses the rand() function as the default source of entropy, which is not cryptographically secure, for cryptographic functions.

Specifically Net::Xero uses the Data::Random library which specifically states that it is "Useful mostly for test programs". Data::Random uses the rand() function.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 18:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52322 | WebService::Xero 0.11 for Perl uses insecure rand() function for cryptographic functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52322</link><description>WebService::Xero 0.11 and earlier for Perl uses the rand() function as the default source of entropy, which is not cryptographically secure, for cryptographic functions.

Specifically WebService::Xero uses the Data::Random library which specifically states that it is "Useful mostly for test programs". Data::Random uses the rand() function.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 16:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57835 | Amon2::Auth::Site::LINE versions through 0.04 for Perl uses insecure rand() function for cryptographic functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57835</link><description>Amon2::Auth::Site::LINE uses the String::Random module to generate nonce values. 

String::Random defaults to Perl's built-in predictable random number generator, the rand() function, which is not cryptographically secure</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 16:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58036 | Net::Dropbox::API 1.9 and earlier for Perl uses insecure rand() function for cryptographic functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58036</link><description>Net::Dropbox::API 1.9 and earlier for Perl uses the rand() function as the default source of entropy, which is not cryptographically secure, for cryptographic functions.

Specifically Net::Dropbox::API uses the Data::Random library which specifically states that it is "Useful mostly for test programs". Data::Random uses the rand() function.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 16:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57868 | Web::API 2.8 and earlier for Perl uses insecure rand() function for cryptographic functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57868</link><description>Web::API 2.8 and earlier for Perl uses the rand() function as the default source of entropy, which is not cryptographically secure, for cryptographic functions.

Specifically Web::API uses the Data::Random library which specifically states that it is "Useful mostly for test programs". Data::Random uses the rand() function.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 15:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30401 | A spoofing issue in WhatsApp for Windows prior to version 2.2450.6 displayed attachments according to their MIME type but selected the file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30401</link><description>A spoofing issue in WhatsApp for Windows prior to version 2.2450.6 displayed attachments according to their MIME type but selected the file opening handler based on the attachment’s filename extension. A maliciously crafted mismatch could have caused the recipient to inadvertently execute arbitrary code rather than view the attachment when manually opening the attachment inside WhatsApp.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 11:51:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3299 | PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3299</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /appointment.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 11:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3298 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop Registration Master.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3298</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /oews/classes/Master.php?f=save_product of the component Registration Handler. The manipulation of the argument email leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 10:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3297 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop Master.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3297</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /classes/Master.php?f=save_product. The manipulation of the argument brand leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 08:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3296 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop Users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3296</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /classes/Users.php?f=delete_customer. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 08:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2941 | Drag and Drop Multiple File Upload for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Move</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2941</link><description>The Drag and Drop Multiple File Upload for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file moving due to insufficient file path validation via the wc-upload-file[] parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to move arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is moved (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 07:09:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13776 | ZoomSounds - WordPress Wave Audio Player with Playlist &amp;lt;= 6.91 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Options Update and Settings Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13776</link><description>The ZoomSounds - WordPress Wave Audio Player with Playlist plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to a denial of service due to a missing capability check on the 'dzsap_delete_notice' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 6.91. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update option values to 'seen' on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update an option that would create an error on the site and deny service to legitimate users or be used to set some values to true such as registration. There are several other functions also vulnerable to missing authorization.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 05:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0839 | ZoomSounds &amp;lt;= 6.91 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0839</link><description>The ZoomSounds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 6.91 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 05:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1233 | Lafka Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Theme Option Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1233</link><description>The Lafka Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the 'lafka_options_upload' AJAX function in all versions up to, and including, 7.1.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update the theme option that overrides the site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 05:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2789 | MultiVendorX – The Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution &amp;lt;= 4.2.19 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Table Rates Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2789</link><description>The MultiVendorX – Empower Your WooCommerce Store with a Dynamic Multivendor Marketplace – Build the Next Amazon, eBay, Etsy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the delete_table_rate_shipping_row function in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.19. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete Table Rates that can impact the shipping cost calculations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 05:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47667 | An OS command injection vulnerability in lib/NSSDropoff.php in ZendTo 5.24-3 through 6.x before 6.10-7 allows unauthenticated remote attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47667</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability in lib/NSSDropoff.php in ZendTo 5.24-3 through 6.x before 6.10-7 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands via shell metacharacters in the tmp_name parameter when dropping off a file via a POST /dropoff request.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 05:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32352 | A type confusion vulnerability in lib/NSSAuthenticator.php in ZendTo before v5.04-7 allows remote attackers to bypass authentication for use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32352</link><description>A type confusion vulnerability in lib/NSSAuthenticator.php in ZendTo before v5.04-7 allows remote attackers to bypass authentication for users with passwords stored as MD5 hashes that can be interpreted as numbers. A solution requires moving from MD5 to bcrypt.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 05:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13604 | KB Support – Customer Support Ticket &amp;amp; Helpdesk Plugin, Knowledge Base Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13604</link><description>The KB Support – Customer Support Ticket &amp; Helpdesk Plugin, Knowledge Base Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.4 via the 'kbs' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/uploads/kbs directory which can contain file attachments included in support tickets. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 1.7.3.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 02:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0810 | Read More &amp;amp; Accordion &amp;lt;= 3.4.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0810</link><description>The Read More &amp; Accordion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.5. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the addNewButtons() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary PHP files via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2544 | AI Content Pipelines &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2544</link><description>The AI Content Pipelines plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2933 | Email Notifications for Updates &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2933</link><description>The Email Notifications for Updates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the awun_import_settings() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1500 | IBM Maximo Application Suite file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1500</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite 9.0 could allow an authenticated user to upload a file with dangerous types that could be executed by another user if opened.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 01:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2889 | Link Library &amp;lt;= 7.7.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Link Additional Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2889</link><description>The Link Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Link Additional Parameters in all versions up to, and including, 7.7.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 23:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3268 | qinguoyi TinyWebServer http_conn.cpp improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3268</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in qinguoyi TinyWebServer up to 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file http/http_conn.cpp. The manipulation of the argument m_url_real leads to improper authentication. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 21:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3267 | qinguoyi TinyWebServer http_conn.cpp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3267</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in qinguoyi TinyWebServer up to 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /http/http_conn.cpp. The manipulation of the argument name/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 20:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3265 | PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System add-category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3265</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /add-category.php. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 19:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3266 | qinguoyi TinyWebServer http_conn.cpp stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3266</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in qinguoyi TinyWebServer up to 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /http/http_conn.cpp. The manipulation of the argument name/password leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 19:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29476 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in compress_chunk_fuzzer with oss-fuzz on commit 16450518afddcb3139de627157208e49bfef6987 in c-blosc2 v.2.17.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29476</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in compress_chunk_fuzzer with oss-fuzz on commit 16450518afddcb3139de627157208e49bfef6987 in c-blosc2 v.2.17.0 and before.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 18:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29477 | An issue in fluent-bit v.3.7.2 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the function consume_event.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29477</link><description>An issue in fluent-bit v.3.7.2 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the function consume_event.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 18:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11235 | Reference counting in php_request_shutdown causes Use-After-Free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11235</link><description>In PHP versions 8.3.* before 8.3.19 and 8.4.* before 8.4.5, a code sequence involving __set handler and exceptions can lead to a use-after-free vulnerability. If the third party can control the memory layout leading to this, it could lead to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 17:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3259 | Tenda RX3 SetOnlineDevName formSetDeviceName stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3259</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11. This issue affects the function formSetDeviceName of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName. The manipulation of the argument devName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 17:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3258 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3258</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 17:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3256 | xujiangfei admintwo updateSet access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3256</link><description>A vulnerability was found in xujiangfei admintwo 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/updateSet. The manipulation of the argument email leads to improper access controls. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3257 | xujiangfei admintwo updateSet cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3257</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in xujiangfei admintwo 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /user/updateSet. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32112 | WordPress  Sidebar Manager Light plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32112</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in OTWthemes Sidebar Manager Light allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Sidebar Manager Light: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32113 | WordPress Libro de Reclamaciones y Quejas plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32113</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Renzo Tejada Libro de Reclamaciones y Quejas allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Libro de Reclamaciones y Quejas: from n/a through 0.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32118 | WordPress CMP – Coming Soon &amp;amp; Maintenance plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.13 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32118</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in NiteoThemes CMP – Coming Soon &amp; Maintenance allows Using Malicious Files. This issue affects CMP – Coming Soon &amp; Maintenance: from n/a through 4.1.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32120 | WordPress Easy Query – WP Query Builder &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32120</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Erick Danzer Easy Query – WP Query Builder allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Easy Query – WP Query Builder: from n/a through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32121 | WordPress Video &amp;amp; Photo Gallery for Ultimate Member plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32121</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in SuitePlugins Video &amp; Photo Gallery for Ultimate Member allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Video &amp; Photo Gallery for Ultimate Member: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32122 | WordPress uListing plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32122</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Stylemix uListing allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects uListing: from n/a through 2.1.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32124 | WordPress Behance Portfolio Manager plugin &amp;lt;=1.7.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32124</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in eleopard Behance Portfolio Manager allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Behance Portfolio Manager: from n/a through 1.7.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32125 | WordPress Silvasoft boekhouden Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32125</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in silvasoft Silvasoft boekhouden allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Silvasoft boekhouden: from n/a through 3.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32126 | WordPress Pay with Contact Form 7 Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32126</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in cmsMinds Pay with Contact Form 7 allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Pay with Contact Form 7: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32127 | WordPress onOffice for WP-Websites plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32127</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in onOffice GmbH onOffice for WP-Websites allows SQL Injection. This issue affects onOffice for WP-Websites: from n/a through 5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32129 | WordPress Welcome Bar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32129</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Data443 Risk Migitation, Inc. Welcome Bar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Welcome Bar: from n/a through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32130 | WordPress Posts Footer Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32130</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Data443 Risk Migitation, Inc. Posts Footer Manager allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Posts Footer Manager: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32131 | WordPress Social Intents plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32131</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in socialintents Social Intents allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Social Intents: from n/a through 1.6.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32132 | WordPress FunnelCockpit Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32132</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FunnelCockpit FunnelCockpit allows Stored XSS. This issue affects FunnelCockpit: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32133 | WordPress Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32133</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ays Pro Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking: from n/a through 4.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32134 | WordPress URL Shortify Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32134</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in KaizenCoders URL Shortify allows Stored XSS. This issue affects URL Shortify: from n/a through 1.10.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32135 | WordPress Split Test For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32135</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in rocketelements Split Test For Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Split Test For Elementor: from n/a through 1.8.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32136 | WordPress ActiveCampaign Plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.16 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32136</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in activecampaign ActiveCampaign allows Stored XSS. This issue affects ActiveCampaign: from n/a through 8.1.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32137 | WordPress s2Member plugin &amp;lt;= 250214 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32137</link><description>Relative Path Traversal vulnerability in Cristián Lávaque s2Member allows Path Traversal. This issue affects s2Member: from n/a through 250214.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32138 | WordPress Easy Google Maps plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11.17 - XML External Entity vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32138</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in supsystic Easy Google Maps allows XML Injection. This issue affects Easy Google Maps: from n/a through 1.11.17.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32141 | WordPress MasterStudy LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.23 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32141</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Stylemix MasterStudy LMS allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects MasterStudy LMS: from n/a through 3.5.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32142 | WordPress Motors plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.65 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32142</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Stylemix Motors allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Motors: from n/a through 1.4.65.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32146 | WordPress JS Job Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32146</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in JoomSky JS Job Manager allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects JS Job Manager: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32147 | WordPress Easy WP Optimizer Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32147</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in coothemes Easy WP Optimizer allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Easy WP Optimizer: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32148 | WordPress Daisycon prijsvergelijkers plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32148</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Daisycon Daisycon prijsvergelijkers allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Daisycon prijsvergelijkers: from n/a through 4.8.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32149 | WordPress teachPress plugin &amp;lt;= 9.0.11 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32149</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in winkm89 teachPress allows SQL Injection. This issue affects teachPress: from n/a through 9.0.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32150 | WordPress Real Estate Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 7.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32150</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Rameez Iqbal Real Estate Manager allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Real Estate Manager: from n/a through 7.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32151 | WordPress BuddyForms Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.15 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32151</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Sven Lehnert BuddyForms allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects BuddyForms: from n/a through 2.8.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32152 | WordPress Slider a SlidersPack Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32152</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Essential Plugins by WP OnlineSupport Slider a SlidersPack allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Slider a SlidersPack: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32153 | WordPress VG WooCarousel plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32153</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in vinagecko VG WooCarousel allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects VG WooCarousel: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32154 | WordPress Catch Dark Mode plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32154</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Catch Themes Catch Dark Mode allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Catch Dark Mode: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32155 | WordPress Beds24 Online Booking plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.26 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32155</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in markkinchin Beds24 Online Booking allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Beds24 Online Booking: from n/a through 2.0.26.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32156 | WordPress Just Post Preview Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32156</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Alex Prokopenko / JustCoded Just Post Preview Widget allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Just Post Preview Widget: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32157 | WordPress Sparkle Elementor Kit plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32157</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Jakub Glos Sparkle Elementor Kit allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Sparkle Elementor Kit: from n/a through 2.0.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32159 | WordPress Radius Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32159</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in RadiusTheme Radius Blocks allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Radius Blocks: from n/a through 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32161 | WordPress Arkhe Blocks &amp;lt;= 2.27.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32161</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ryo Arkhe Blocks allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Arkhe Blocks: from n/a through 2.27.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32162 | WordPress Chamber Dashboard Business Directory plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32162</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Morgan Kay Chamber Dashboard Business Directory allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Chamber Dashboard Business Directory: from n/a through 3.3.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32163 | WordPress Xpro Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32163</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Xpro Xpro Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Xpro Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.4.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32165 | WordPress Doppler Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32165</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in fromdoppler Doppler Forms allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Doppler Forms: from n/a through 2.4.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32166 | WordPress Emma for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32166</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in John Housholder Emma for WordPress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Emma for WordPress: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32167 | WordPress SurveyJS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.12.20 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32167</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in devsoftbaltic SurveyJS allows Stored XSS. This issue affects SurveyJS: from n/a through 1.12.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32168 | WordPress Gutenify plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32168</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodeYatri Gutenify allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Gutenify: from n/a through 1.4.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32169 | WordPress Showeblogin Social plugin &amp;lt;= 7.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32169</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Suresh Prasad Showeblogin Social allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Showeblogin Social: from n/a through 7.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32170 | WordPress Motors plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.65 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32170</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Stylemix Motors allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Motors: from n/a through 1.4.65.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32171 | WordPress Table Block by Tableberg – Best WordPress Table Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32171</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Imtiaz Rayhan Table Block by Tableberg allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Table Block by Tableberg: from n/a through 0.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32172 | WordPress YaMaps for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.31 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32172</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Yuri Baranov YaMaps for WordPress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects YaMaps for WordPress: from n/a through 0.6.31.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32173 | WordPress B Blocks - The ultimate block collection plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32173</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bPlugins B Blocks - The ultimate block collection allows Stored XSS. This issue affects B Blocks - The ultimate block collection: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32174 | WordPress Tockify Events Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.13 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32174</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tockify Tockify Events Calendar allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Tockify Events Calendar: from n/a through 2.2.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32175 | WordPress VK Filter Search plugin &amp;lt;= 2.14.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32175</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Vektor,Inc. VK Filter Search allows Stored XSS. This issue affects VK Filter Search: from n/a through 2.14.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32176 | WordPress Gallery Blocks with Lightbox plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.5 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32176</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GalleryCreator Gallery Blocks with Lightbox allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Gallery Blocks with Lightbox: from n/a through 3.2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32177 | WordPress Embed Chessboard plugin &amp;lt;= 3.07.00 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32177</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in pgn4web Embed Chessboard allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Embed Chessboard: from n/a through 3.07.00.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32178 | WordPress 6Storage Rentals Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.18.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32178</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in 6Storage 6Storage Rentals allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects 6Storage Rentals: from n/a through 2.18.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32179 | WordPress Maps for WP Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32179</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in icopydoc Maps for WP allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Maps for WP: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32181 | WordPress Search, Filters &amp;amp; Merchandising for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.57 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32181</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Fast Simon Search, Filters &amp; Merchandising for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Search, Filters &amp; Merchandising for WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.0.57.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32182 | WordPress Spider Elements – Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32182</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Spider Themes Spider Elements – Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Spider Elements – Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32183 | WordPress Video Playlist For YouTube plugin &amp;lt;= 6.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32183</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Galaxy Weblinks Video Playlist For YouTube allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Video Playlist For YouTube: from n/a through 6.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32184 | WordPress Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32184</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bdthemes Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons: from n/a through 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32185 | WordPress Colibri Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.319 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32185</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Extend Themes Colibri Page Builder allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Colibri Page Builder: from n/a through 1.0.319.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32186 | WordPress Turbo Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32186</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Turbo Addons Turbo Addons for Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Turbo Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32187 | WordPress Administrator Z plugin &amp;lt;= 2025.03.04 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32187</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Quý Lê 91 Administrator Z allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Administrator Z: from n/a through 2025.03.04.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32188 | WordPress Advanced Woo Labels plugin &amp;lt;= 2.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32188</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ILLID Advanced Woo Labels allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Advanced Woo Labels: from n/a through 2.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32189 | WordPress BWD Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.20 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32189</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Best WP Developer BWD Elementor Addons allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects BWD Elementor Addons: from n/a through 4.3.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32190 | WordPress Musician&amp;#x27;s Pack for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32190</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in smartwpress Musician's Pack for Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Musician's Pack for Elementor: from n/a through 1.8.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32191 | WordPress News Element Elementor Blog Magazine plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32191</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in webangon News Element Elementor Blog Magazine allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects News Element Elementor Blog Magazine: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32192 | WordPress Ultra Addons Lite for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32192</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in UltraPress Ultra Addons Lite for Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ultra Addons Lite for Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32193 | WordPress Simple WP Events plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.17 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32193</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPMinds Simple WP Events allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Simple WP Events: from n/a through 1.8.17.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32194 | WordPress LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32194</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LA-Studio LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor: from n/a through 1.4.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32195 | WordPress Ecwid Shopping Cart plugin &amp;lt;= 7.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32195</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ecwid by Lightspeed Ecommerce Shopping Cart Ecwid Shopping Cart allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ecwid Shopping Cart: from n/a through 7.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32196 | WordPress News Kit Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32196</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in blazethemes News Kit Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS. This issue affects News Kit Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32197 | WordPress Piotnet Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.34 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32197</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in piotnetdotcom Piotnet Addons For Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Piotnet Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 2.4.34.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32200 | WordPress Advanced WordPress Backgrounds Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.12.4 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32200</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in Nikita Advanced WordPress Backgrounds allows Code Injection. This issue affects Advanced WordPress Backgrounds: from n/a through 1.12.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32201 | WordPress Xpro Theme Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.8.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32201</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Xpro Xpro Theme Builder allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Xpro Theme Builder: from n/a through 1.2.8.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32203 | WordPress Falling things Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.08 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32203</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in manu225 Falling things allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Falling things: from n/a through 1.08.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32204 | WordPress Split Test For Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32204</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in rocketelements Split Test For Elementor allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Split Test For Elementor: from n/a through 1.8.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32207 | WordPress Ni WooCommerce Cost Of Goods plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32207</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Anzar Ahmed Ni WooCommerce Cost Of Goods allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ni WooCommerce Cost Of Goods: from n/a through 3.2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32217 | WordPress Ai Image Alt Text Generator for WP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32217</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Messiah Ai Image Alt Text Generator for WP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Ai Image Alt Text Generator for WP: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32218 | WordPress TableOn – WordPress Posts Table Filterable  Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32218</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in RealMag777 TableOn – WordPress Posts Table Filterable allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects TableOn – WordPress Posts Table Filterable: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32219 | WordPress eaSYNC plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.19 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32219</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Syntactics, Inc. eaSYNC allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects eaSYNC: from n/a through 1.3.19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32220 | WordPress Salon Booking System plugin &amp;lt;= 10.10.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32220</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Dimitri Grassi Salon booking system allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Salon booking system: from n/a through 10.10.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32224 | WordPress Privyr CRM plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32224</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in shivammani Privyr CRM allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Privyr CRM: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32225 | WordPress WP Event Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.47 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32225</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Event Manager WP Event Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP Event Manager: from n/a through 3.1.47.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32226 | WordPress Display product variations dropdown on shop page plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32226</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Anzar Ahmed Display product variations dropdown on shop page allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Display product variations dropdown on shop page: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32229 | WordPress Variable Inspector plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32229</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Bowo Variable Inspector allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Variable Inspector: from n/a through 2.6.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32231 | WordPress Bookingor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32231</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Bookingor Bookingor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Bookingor: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32232 | WordPress StaffList plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32232</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ERA404 StaffList allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects StaffList: from n/a through 3.2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32233 | WordPress Revive.so &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32233</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Chill Revive.so – Bulk Rewrite and Republish Blog Posts allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Revive.so – Bulk Rewrite and Republish Blog Posts: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32234 | WordPress AdMail plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32234</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in aleswebs AdMail – Multilingual Back in-Stock Notifier for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects AdMail – Multilingual Back in-Stock Notifier for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32235 | WordPress MP3 Audio Player – Music Player, Podcast Player &amp;amp; Radio by Sonaar plugin &amp;lt;= 5.9.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32235</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in sonaar MP3 Audio Player for Music, Radio &amp; Podcast by Sonaar allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects MP3 Audio Player for Music, Radio &amp; Podcast by Sonaar: from n/a through 5.9.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32237 | WordPress MasterStudy LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.23 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32237</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Stylemix MasterStudy LMS allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects MasterStudy LMS: from n/a through 3.5.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32238 | WordPress Online Booking &amp;amp; Scheduling Calendar for WordPress by vcita plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32238</link><description>Generation of Error Message Containing Sensitive Information vulnerability in vcita Online Booking &amp; Scheduling Calendar for WordPress by vcita allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Online Booking &amp; Scheduling Calendar for WordPress by vcita: from n/a through 4.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32239 | WordPress Social Share Buttons &amp;amp; Analytics Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32239</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Joao Romao Social Share Buttons &amp; Analytics Plugin – GetSocial.io allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Social Share Buttons &amp; Analytics Plugin – GetSocial.io: from n/a through 4.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32241 | WordPress Official CleverReach WooCommerce Integration Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.3 - CSRF to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32241</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CleverReach® Official CleverReach Plugin for WooCommerce allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Official CleverReach Plugin for WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32246 | WordPress 1-Click Backup &amp;amp; Restore Database &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32246</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tim Nguyen 1-Click Backup &amp;amp; Restore Database allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects 1-Click Backup &amp;amp; Restore Database: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32247 | WordPress AI Content Creator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32247</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ABCdatos AI Content Creator allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects AI Content Creator: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32248 | WordPress SwiftXR (3D/AR/VR) Viewer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32248</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SwiftXR SwiftXR (3D/AR/VR) Viewer allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects SwiftXR (3D/AR/VR) Viewer: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32249 | WordPress DirectoryPress – Business Directory And Classified Ad Listing Plugin &amp;lt;=3.6.19 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32249</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in designinvento DirectoryPress allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects DirectoryPress: from n/a through 3.6.19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32250 | WordPress Rollbar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32250</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in rollbar Rollbar allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Rollbar: from n/a through 2.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32251 | WordPress Jetpack Feedback Exporter &amp;lt;= 1.23 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32251</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in J. Tyler Wiest Jetpack Feedback Exporter allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Jetpack Feedback Exporter: from n/a through 1.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32252 | WordPress WP Genealogy plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32252</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in blackandwhitedigital WP Genealogy – Your Family History Website allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP Genealogy – Your Family History Website: from n/a through 0.1.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32253 | WordPress Course Booking System Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.0.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32253</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ComMotion Course Booking System allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Course Booking System: from n/a through 6.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32254 | WordPress WPBookit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32254</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Iqonic Design WPBookit allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects WPBookit: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32255 | WordPress StaffList plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.6 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32255</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in ERA404 StaffList allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects StaffList: from n/a through 3.2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32256 | WordPress SurveyJS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.12.20 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32256</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in devsoftbaltic SurveyJS allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects SurveyJS: from n/a through 1.12.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32257 | WordPress 1 Click WordPress Migration Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32257</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information Due to Uncleared Debug Information vulnerability in 1clickmigration 1 Click WordPress Migration allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects 1 Click WordPress Migration: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32258 | WordPress Simple Website Logo plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32258</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in InfoGiants Simple Website Logo allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Simple Website Logo: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32261 | WordPress Advanced All in One Admin Search by WP Spotlight &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32261</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Kuppuraj Advanced All in One Admin Search by WP Spotlight allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Advanced All in One Admin Search by WP Spotlight: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32262 | WordPress RDP Wiki Embed plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.20 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32262</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Robert D Payne RDP Wiki Embed allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects RDP Wiki Embed: from n/a through 1.2.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32263 | WordPress Sequential Order Numbers for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32263</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in BeRocket Sequential Order Numbers for WooCommerce allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Sequential Order Numbers for WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32264 | WordPress UltraAddons – Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32264</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Saiful Islam UltraAddons Elementor Lite allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects UltraAddons Elementor Lite: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32265 | WordPress JobWP plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32265</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Hossni Mubarak JobWP allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects JobWP: from n/a through 2.3.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32266 | WordPress 404 Image Redirection (Replace Broken Images) plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32266</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wp-buy 404 Image Redirection (Replace Broken Images) allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects 404 Image Redirection (Replace Broken Images): from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32267 | WordPress WP to Hootsuite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.8 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32267</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wpzinc Post to Social Media – WordPress to Hootsuite allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Post to Social Media – WordPress to Hootsuite: from n/a through 1.5.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32268 | WordPress QR Code Tag for WC plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.36 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32268</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in www.15.to QR Code Tag for WC allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects QR Code Tag for WC: from n/a through 1.9.36.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32269 | WordPress  WP Zendesk for Contact Form 7, WPForms, Elementor, Formidable and Ninja Forms Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32269</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CRM Perks WP Zendesk for Contact Form 7, WPForms, Elementor, Formidable and Ninja Forms allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Zendesk for Contact Form 7, WPForms, Elementor, Formidable and Ninja Forms: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32270 | WordPress Broadstreet Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.51.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32270</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Broadstreet Broadstreet allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Broadstreet: from n/a through 1.51.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32271 | WordPress Woocommerce Role Pricing Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32271</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ablancodev Woocommerce Role Pricing allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Woocommerce Role Pricing: from n/a through 3.5.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32272 | WordPress Wishlist Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.44 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32272</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PickPlugins Wishlist allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Wishlist: from n/a through 1.0.44.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32273 | WordPress Freetobook Responsive Widget Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32273</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in freetobook Freetobook Responsive Widget allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Freetobook Responsive Widget: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32274 | WordPress w3all phpBB integration Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32274</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in axew3 WP w3all phpBB allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP w3all phpBB: from n/a through 2.9.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32276 | WordPress Administrator Z plugin &amp;lt;= 2025.03.04 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32276</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Quý Lê 91 Administrator Z allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Administrator Z: from n/a through 2025.03.04.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32277 | WordPress RepairBuddy plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8211 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32277</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ateeq Rafeeq RepairBuddy allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects RepairBuddy: from n/a through 3.8211.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32278 | WordPress Table Block by RioVizual plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32278</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wprio Table Block by RioVizual allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Table Block by RioVizual: from n/a through 2.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32280 | WordPress WP Project Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.22 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32280</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in weDevs WP Project Manager allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Project Manager: from n/a through 2.6.22.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3254 | xujiangfei admintwo add server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3254</link><description>A vulnerability was found in xujiangfei admintwo 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /resource/add. The manipulation of the argument description leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3255 | xujiangfei admintwo home access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3255</link><description>A vulnerability was found in xujiangfei admintwo 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /user/home. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25178 | GPU DDK - PhysmemWrapExtMem uiSize=0 corrupts kernel memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25178</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to cause kernel system memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0468 | GPU DDK - ui64RobustnessAddress can overwrite Freelist / HWRT (and bypass PMMETA)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0468</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to subvert GPU HW to write to arbitrary physical memory pages.

Under certain circumstances this exploit could be used to corrupt data pages not allocated by the GPU driver but memory pages in use by the kernel and drivers running on the platform altering their behaviour.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3252 | xujiangfei admintwo add cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3252</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in xujiangfei admintwo 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /resource/add. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3253 | xujiangfei admintwo insertTree cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3253</link><description>A vulnerability was found in xujiangfei admintwo 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ztree/insertTree. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3250 | elunez eladmin Maintenance Management Module testConnect deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3250</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in elunez eladmin 2.7. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/database/testConnect of the component Maintenance Management Module. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:21:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3251 | xujiangfei admintwo updateSet cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3251</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in xujiangfei admintwo 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /user/updateSet. The manipulation of the argument motto leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31480 | aiven-extras allows PostgreSQL Privilege Escalation through format function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31480</link><description>aiven-extras is a PostgreSQL extension. This is a privilege escalation vulnerability, allowing elevation to superuser inside PostgreSQL databases that use the aiven-extras package. The vulnerability leverages the format function not being schema-prefixed. Affected users should install 1.1.16 and ensure they run the latest version issuing ALTER EXTENSION aiven_extras UPDATE TO '1.1.16' after installing it. This needs to happen in each database aiven_extras has been installed in.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31130 | gitoxide does not detect SHA-1 collision attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31130</link><description>gitoxide is an implementation of git written in Rust. Before 0.42.0, gitoxide uses SHA-1 hash implementations without any collision detection, leaving it vulnerable to hash collision attacks. gitoxide uses the sha1_smol or sha1 crate, both of which implement standard SHA-1 without any mitigations for collision attacks. This means that two distinct Git objects with colliding SHA-1 hashes would break the Git object model and integrity checks when used with gitoxide. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.42.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27520 | BentoML Allows Remote Code Execution (RCE) via Insecure Deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27520</link><description>BentoML is a Python library for building online serving systems optimized for AI apps and model inference. A Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability caused by insecure deserialization has been identified in the latest version (v1.4.2) of BentoML. It allows any unauthenticated user to execute arbitrary code on the server. It exists an unsafe code segment in serde.py. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3249 | TOTOLINK A6000R mtkwifi.lua apcli_cancel_wps command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3249</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A6000R 1.0.1-B20201211.2000. Affected by this vulnerability is the function apcli_cancel_wps of the file /usr/lib/lua/luci/controller/mtkwifi.lua. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22285 | WordPress Pallet Packaging for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.15 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22285</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Eniture Technology Pallet Packaging for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Pallet Packaging for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.1.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51800 | WordPress Homey theme &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51800</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Favethemes Homey allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Homey: from n/a through 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22281 | WordPress Simplish theme &amp;lt;= 2.6.4 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22281</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in joshix Simplish allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Simplish: from n/a through 2.6.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2798 | Woffice &amp;lt;= 5.4.21 - Authentication Bypass via Registration Role</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2798</link><description>The Woffice CRM theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.21. This is due to a misconfiguration of excluded roles during registration. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register with an Administrator role if a custom login form is being used. This can be combined with CVE-2025-2797 to bypass the user approval process if an Administrator can be tricked into taking an action such as clicking a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:52:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31381 | WordPress Booking Calendar and Notification plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31381</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in shiptrack Booking Calendar and Notification allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Booking Calendar and Notification: from n/a through 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:52:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31384 | WordPress Videos plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31384</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in Aviplugins Videos allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Videos: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:52:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31389 | WordPress Sequel plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31389</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sequel.Io Sequel allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Sequel: from n/a through 1.0.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31403 | WordPress Booking Calendar and Notification plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31403</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in shiptrack Booking Calendar and Notification allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Booking Calendar and Notification: from n/a through 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28146 | Edimax AC1200 Wave 2 Dual-Band Gigabit Router BR-6478AC V3 1.0.15 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via fota_url i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28146</link><description>Edimax AC1200 Wave 2 Dual-Band Gigabit Router BR-6478AC V3 1.0.15 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via fota_url in /boafrm/formLtefotaUpgradeQuectel</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31405 | WordPress Fami WooCommerce Compare plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31405</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in zankover Fami WooCommerce Compare allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Fami WooCommerce Compare: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31407 | WordPress Tiger theme &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31407</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in hutsixdigital Tiger allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Tiger: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31416 | WordPress Awesome Event Booking plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31416</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AwesomeTOGI Awesome Event Booking allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Awesome Event Booking: from n/a through 2.8.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31418 | WordPress Gravel theme &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31418</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in noonnoo Gravel allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Gravel: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31420 | WordPress wpForo Forum plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31420</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Tomdever wpForo Forum allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects wpForo Forum: from n/a through 2.4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:07:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31421 | WordPress Srbtranslatin plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31421</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Externally-Accessible File or Directory vulnerability in Oblak Studio Srbtranslatin allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Srbtranslatin: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3189 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in DoWISP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3189</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in DoWISP in versions prior to 1.16.2.50, which consists of an stored XSS through the upload of a profile picture in SVG format with malicious Javascript code in it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3245 | itsourcecode Library Management System Forgot.java search sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3245</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Library Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function Search of the file library_management/src/Library_Management/Forgot.java. The manipulation of the argument txtuname leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3243 | code-projects Patient Record Management System dental_form.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3243</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /dental_form.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3244 | SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System Create User Page add-admin.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3244</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /add-admin.php of the component Create User Page. The manipulation of the argument Avatar leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3241 | zhangyanbo2007 youkefu XML Document CallCenterRouterController.java xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3241</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in zhangyanbo2007 youkefu up to 4.2.0. This affects an unknown part of the file src/main/java/com/ukefu/webim/web/handler/admin/callcenter/CallCenterRouterController.java of the component XML Document Handler. The manipulation of the argument routercontent leads to xml external entity reference. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3242 | PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System search-result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3242</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /search-result.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22282 | WordPress ez Form Calculator - WordPress plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 2.14.1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22282</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in EPC ez Form Calculator - WordPress plugin allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ez Form Calculator - WordPress plugin: from n/a through 2.14.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3239 | PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System edit-guard-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3239</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System 1.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-guard-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3240 | PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3240</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System 1.2. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3237 | Tenda FH1202 wrlwpsset access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3237</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1202 1.2.0.14(408). It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/wrlwpsset. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3238 | PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System search-request.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3238</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System 1.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file /search-request.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1865 | Local Privilege Escalation in Virtual CloneDrive Kernel Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1865</link><description>The kernel driver, accessible to low-privileged users, exposes a function that fails to properly validate the privileges of the calling process. This allows creating files at arbitrary locations with full user control, ultimately allowing for privilege escalation to SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2243 | SSRF in GravityZone Console via DNS Truncation (VA-12634)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2243</link><description>A server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Bitdefender GravityZone Console allows an attacker to bypass input validation logic using leading characters in DNS requests. Paired with other potential vulnerabilities, this bypass could be used for execution of third party code. This issue affects GravityZone Console: before 6.41.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2244 | Insecure PHP deserialization issue in GravityZone Console (VA-12634)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2244</link><description>A vulnerability in the sendMailFromRemoteSource method in Emails.php  as used in Bitdefender GravityZone Console unsafely uses php unserialize() on user-supplied input without validation. By crafting a malicious serialized payload, an attacker can trigger PHP object injection, perform a file write, and gain arbitrary command execution on the host system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2245 | Server Side Request Forgery in GravityZone Update Server Using Null Bytes (VA-12646)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2245</link><description>A server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in the Bitdefender GravityZone Update Server when operating in Relay Mode. The HTTP proxy component on port 7074 uses a domain allowlist to restrict outbound requests, but fails to properly sanitize hostnames containing null-byte (%00) sequences. By crafting a request to a domain such as evil.com%00.bitdefender.com, an attacker can bypass the allowlist check, causing the proxy to forward requests to arbitrary external or internal systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3235 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3235</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/profile.php. The manipulation of the argument adminname leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 09:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3236 | Tenda FH1202 Web Management Interface VirSerDMZ access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3236</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1202 1.2.0.14(408). It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/VirSerDMZ of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 09:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3231 | PHPGurukul Zoo Management System aboutus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3231</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /aboutus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 09:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3229 | PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System edit-subadmin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3229</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /edit-subadmin.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 08:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3220 | PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System dashboard.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3220</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /dashboard.php. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 08:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3105 | Vehica Core &amp;lt;= 1.0.97 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3105</link><description>The Vehica Core plugin for WordPress, used by the Vehica - Car Dealer &amp; Listing WordPress Theme, is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.97. This is due to the plugin not properly validating user meta fields prior to updating them in the database. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change escalate their privileges to Administrator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3219 | CodeCanyon Perfex CRM Project Discussions Module 2 cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3219</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeCanyon Perfex CRM 3.2.1. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /perfex/clients/project/2 of the component Project Discussions Module. The manipulation of the argument description leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2780 | Woffice Core &amp;lt;= 5.4.21 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2780</link><description>The Woffice Core plugin for WordPress, used by the Woffice Theme, is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'saveFeaturedImage' function in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.21. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2797 | Woffice Core &amp;lt;= 5.4.21 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to User Registration Approval</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2797</link><description>The Woffice Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.21. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'woffice_handle_user_approval_actions' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to approve registration for any user via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3217 | PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System registration.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3217</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /registration.php. The manipulation of the argument emailid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32111 | The Docker image from acme.sh before 40b6db6 is based on a .github/workflows/dockerhub.yml file that lacks "persist-credentials: false" for ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32111</link><description>The Docker image from acme.sh before 40b6db6 is based on a .github/workflows/dockerhub.yml file that lacks "persist-credentials: false" for actions/checkout.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:53:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3086 | User in anonymous role could create and delete views</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3086</link><description>Improper isolation of users in M-Files Server version before 25.3.14549 allows anonymous user to affect other anonymous users views and possibly cause a denial of service</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:53:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3087 | Stored XSS Vulnerability in M-Files Web</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3087</link><description>Stored XSS in M-Files Web versions from 25.1.14445.5 to 25.2.14524.4 allows an authenticated user to run scripts</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3215 | PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System add-subadmin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3215</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/add-subadmin.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3216 | PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System password-recovery.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3216</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /password-recovery.php. The manipulation of the argument username/contactno leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2159 | Stored XSS in M-Files Admin user interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2159</link><description>Stored XSS in Desktop UI in M-Files Server Admin tool before version 25.3.14681.7 on Windows allows authenticated local user to run scripts via UI</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2279 | Maps - Google Maps &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2279</link><description>The Maps  WordPress plugin through 1.0.6 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3214 | JFinal CMS readTemplate engine.getTemplate path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3214</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in JFinal CMS up to 5.2.4 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function engine.getTemplate of the file /readTemplate. The manipulation of the argument template leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The vendor explains that this is not a bug but a feature.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13645 | TagDiv Composer &amp;lt;= 5.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary PHP Object Instantiation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13645</link><description>The tagDiv Composer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Instantiation in all versions up to, and including, 5.3 via module parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to Instantiate a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13708 | Booster for WooCommerce 4.0.1 - 7.2.4 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13708</link><description>The Booster for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in versions 4.0.1 to 7.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13898 | Simple Banner &amp;lt;= 3.0.4 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13898</link><description>The Simple Banner – Easily add multiple Banners/Bars/Notifications/Announcements to the top or bottom of your website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42208 | HCL Connections is vulnerable to an information disclosure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42208</link><description>HCL Connections is vulnerable to an information disclosure vulnerability which could allow a user to obtain sensitive information they are not entitled to, caused by improper handling of request data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2270 | Countdown, Coming Soon, Maintenance – Countdown &amp;amp; Clock &amp;lt;= 2.8.9.1 - Unauthenticated Limited Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2270</link><description>The Countdown, Coming Soon, Maintenance – Countdown &amp; Clock plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.9.1 via the createCdObj function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute files with the specific filenames on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in some cases.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2317 | Product Filter by WBW &amp;lt;= 2.7.9 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via filtersDataBackend Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2317</link><description>The Product Filter by WBW plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the filtersDataBackend parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2836 | RegistrationMagic – Custom Registration Forms, User Registration, Payment, and User Login &amp;lt;= 6.0.4.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2836</link><description>The RegistrationMagic – Custom Registration Forms, User Registration, Payment, and User Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘payment_method’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3211 | code-projects Patient Record Management System birthing_print.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3211</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /birthing_print.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3213 | PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System view-note.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3213</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /view-note.php?noteid=11. The manipulation of the argument remark leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3191 | All versions of the package react-draft-wysiwyg are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the Embedded button which will then result ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3191</link><description>All versions of the package react-draft-wysiwyg are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the Embedded button which will then result in saving the payload in the  tag.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3192 | Versions of the package spatie/browsershot from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Server-side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the setUrl() function due to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3192</link><description>Versions of the package spatie/browsershot from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Server-side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the setUrl() function due to a missing restriction on user input, enabling attackers to access localhost and list all of its directories.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3194 | Versions of the package bigint-buffer from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the toBigIntLE() function. Attackers can exploit this ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3194</link><description>Versions of the package bigint-buffer from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the toBigIntLE() function. Attackers can exploit this to crash the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3197 | Versions of the package expand-object from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution in the expand() function in index.js. This function e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3197</link><description>Versions of the package expand-object from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution in the expand() function in index.js. This function expands the given string into an object and allows a nested property to be set without checking the provided keys for sensitive properties like __proto__.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3209 | code-projects Patient Record Management System add_patient.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3209</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /add_patient.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3210 | code-projects Patient Record Management System birthing_pending.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3210</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /birthing_pending.php. The manipulation of the argument birth_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3208 | code-projects Patient Record Management System xray_print.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3208</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /xray_print.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 04:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13744 | Booster for WooCommerce 4.0.1 - 7.2.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13744</link><description>The Booster for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the validate_product_input_fields_on_add_to_cart function in versions 4.0.1 to 7.2.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 04:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2075 | Uncanny Automator &amp;lt;= 6.3.0.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2075</link><description>The Uncanny Automator – Easy Automation, Integration, Webhooks &amp; Workflow Builder Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 6.3.0.2. This is due to add_role() and user_role() functions missing proper capability checks performed through the validate_rest_call() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to set the role of arbitrary users to administrator granting full access to the site, though privilege escalation requires an active account on the site so this is considered an authenticated privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 04:22:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3207 | code-projects Patient Record Management System birthing_form.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3207</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /birthing_form.php. The manipulation of the argument birth_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 04:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3206 | code-projects Hospital Management System doctor-specilization.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3206</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Hospital Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/doctor-specilization.php. The manipulation of the argument doctorspecilization leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 03:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3204 | CodeAstro Car Rental System returncar.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3204</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in CodeAstro Car Rental System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /returncar.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 03:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3205 | CodeAstro Student Grading System studentsubject.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3205</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in CodeAstro Student Grading System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file studentsubject.php. The manipulation of the argument studentId leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 03:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3202 | ageerle ruoyi-ai SysNoticeController.java improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3202</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in ageerle ruoyi-ai up to 2.0.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file ruoyi-modules/ruoyi-system/src/main/java/org/ruoyi/system/controller/system/SysNoticeController.java. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.0.1 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 6382e177bf90cc56ff70521842409e35c50df32d. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 03:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3203 | Tenda W18E setModules formSetAccountList stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3203</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Tenda W18E 16.01.0.11. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetAccountList of the file /goform/setModules. The manipulation of the argument Password leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 03:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24310 | Improper restriction of rendered UI layers or frames issue exists in HMI ViewJet C-more series, which may allow a remote unauthenticated att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24310</link><description>Improper restriction of rendered UI layers or frames issue exists in HMI ViewJet C-more series, which may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to trick the product user to perform operations on the product's web pages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24317 | Allocation of resources without limits or throttling issue exists in HMI ViewJet C-more series and HMI GC-A2 series, which may allow a remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24317</link><description>Allocation of resources without limits or throttling issue exists in HMI ViewJet C-more series and HMI GC-A2 series, which may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25061 | Unintended proxy or intermediary ('Confused Deputy') issue exists in HMI ViewJet C-more series and HMI GC-A2 series, which may allow a remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25061</link><description>Unintended proxy or intermediary ('Confused Deputy') issue exists in HMI ViewJet C-more series and HMI GC-A2 series, which may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to use the product as an intermediary for FTP bounce attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26401 | Weak encoding for password vulnerability exists in HMI ViewJet C-more series. If this vulnerability is exploited, authentication information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26401</link><description>Weak encoding for password vulnerability exists in HMI ViewJet C-more series. If this vulnerability is exploited, authentication information may be obtained by a local authenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3199 | ageerle ruoyi-ai API Interface SysModelController.java improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3199</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ageerle ruoyi-ai up to 2.0.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file ruoyi-modules/ruoyi-system/src/main/java/org/ruoyi/system/controller/system/SysModelController.java of the component API Interface. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.0.2 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is c0daf641fb25b244591b7a6c3affa35c69d321fe. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3195 | itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System bbms.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3195</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /bbms.php. The manipulation of the argument Search leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3196 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp Malformed File MD2Loader.cpp InternReadFile stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3196</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. Affected is the function Assimp::MD2Importer::InternReadFile in the library code/AssetLib/MD2/MD2Loader.cpp of the component Malformed File Handler. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3198 | GNU Binutils objdump bucomm.c display_info memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3198</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in GNU Binutils 2.43/2.44 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function display_info of the file binutils/bucomm.c of the component objdump. The manipulation leads to memory leak. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is named ba6ad3a18cb26b79e0e3b84c39f707535bbc344d. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25000 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25000</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25001 | Microsoft Edge for iOS Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25001</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29796 | Microsoft Edge for iOS Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29796</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29815 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29815</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3187 | PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3187</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument logindetail leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3188 | PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System add-notes.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3188</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /add-notes.php. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>