<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 02:37:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-1845 | ESAFENET DSM examExportPDF command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1845</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in ESAFENET DSM 3.1.2 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function examExportPDF of the file /admin/plan/examExportPDF. The manipulation of the argument s leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 02:37:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1844 | ESAFENET CDG backupLogDetail.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1844</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in ESAFENET CDG 5.6.3.154.205_20250114. Affected is an unknown function of the file /CDGServer3/logManagement/backupLogDetail.jsp. The manipulation of the argument logTaskId leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 02:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1843 | Mini-Tmall ProductMapper.java select sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1843</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Mini-Tmall up to 20250211. This issue affects the function select of the file com/xq/tmall/dao/ProductMapper.java. The manipulation of the argument orderBy leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:21:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25948 | Incorrect access control in the component /rest/staffResource/create of Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia Student Information System (SIS)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25948</link><description>Incorrect access control in the component /rest/staffResource/create of Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia Student Information System (SIS) EagleR v1.0.118 allows create and modify user accounts, including an Administrator account.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25949 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia Student Information System (SIS) EagleR v1.0.118 al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25949</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia Student Information System (SIS) EagleR v1.0.118 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the User ID parameter at /rest/staffResource/update.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25950 | Incorrect access control in the component /rest/staffResource/update of Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia Student Information System (SIS)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25950</link><description>Incorrect access control in the component /rest/staffResource/update of Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia Student Information System (SIS) EagleR v1.0.118 allows create and modify user accounts, including an Administrator account.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25951 | An information disclosure vulnerability in the component /rest/cb/executeBasicSearch of Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia Student Informat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25951</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability in the component /rest/cb/executeBasicSearch of Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia Student Information System (SIS) EagleR v1.0.118 allows attackers to access sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25952 | An Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) in the component /getStudemtAllDetailsById?studentId=XX of Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25952</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) in the component /getStudemtAllDetailsById?studentId=XX of Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia Student Information System (SIS) EagleR v1.0.118 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via a crafted API request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25953 | Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia Student Information System (SIS) EagleR v1.0.118 was discovered to contain an Azure JWT access token exp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25953</link><description>Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia Student Information System (SIS) EagleR v1.0.118 was discovered to contain an Azure JWT access token exposure. This vulnerability allows authenticated attackers to escalate privileges and access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27583 | Incorrect access control in the component /rest/staffResource/findAllUsersAcrossOrg of Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia Student Informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27583</link><description>Incorrect access control in the component /rest/staffResource/findAllUsersAcrossOrg of Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia Student Information System (SIS) EagleR v1.0.118 allows create and modify user accounts, including an Administrator account.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27584 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia Student Information System (SIS) EagleR v1.0.118 al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27584</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia Student Information System (SIS) EagleR v1.0.118 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the First Name parameter at /rest/staffResource/update.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27585 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia Student Information System (SIS) EagleR v1.0.118 al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27585</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Serosoft Solutions Pvt Ltd Academia Student Information System (SIS) EagleR v1.0.118 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the Print Name parameter at /rest/staffResource/update.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1842 | FITSTATS Technologies AthleteMonitoring login.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1842</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in FITSTATS Technologies AthleteMonitoring up to 20250302. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:21:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1841 | ESAFENET CDG ClientSortLog.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1841</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in ESAFENET CDG 5.6.3.154.205. This affects an unknown part of the file /CDGServer3/logManagement/ClientSortLog.jsp. The manipulation of the argument startDate/endDate leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 01:21:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1840 | ESAFENET CDG updateorg.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1840</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5.6.3.154.205. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /CDGServer3/workflowE/useractivate/updateorg.jsp. The manipulation of the argument flowId leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27579 | In Bitaxe ESP-Miner before 2.5.0 with AxeOS, one can use an /api/system CSRF attack to update the payout address (aka stratumUser) for a Bit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27579</link><description>In Bitaxe ESP-Miner before 2.5.0 with AxeOS, one can use an /api/system CSRF attack to update the payout address (aka stratumUser) for a Bitaxe Bitcoin miner.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1836 | Incorta Edit Insight csv injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1836</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Incorta 2023.4.3. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the component Edit Insight Handler. The manipulation of the argument Service Name leads to csv injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1835 | osuuu LightPicture Api.php upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1835</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in osuuu LightPicture 1.2.2 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function upload of the file /app/controller/Api.php. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 22:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1834 | zj1983 zz resolve unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1834</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in zj1983 zz up to 2024-8. This affects an unknown part of the file /resolve. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1833 | zj1983 zz HTTP Request Customer_noticeAction.java sendNotice server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1833</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in zj1983 zz up to 2024-8. Affected by this issue is the function sendNotice of the file src/main/java/com/futvan/z/erp/customer_notice/Customer_noticeAction.java of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 21:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1832 | zj1983 zz ZroleAction.java getUserList sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1832</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in zj1983 zz up to 2024-8. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getUserList of the file src/main/java/com/futvan/z/system/zrole/ZroleAction.java. The manipulation of the argument roleid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 21:10:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1831 | zj1983 zz ZorgAction.java GetDBUser sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1831</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in zj1983 zz up to 2024-8. Affected is the function GetDBUser of the file src/main/java/com/futvan/z/system/zorg/ZorgAction.java. The manipulation of the argument user_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 20:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1830 | zj1983 zz Customer Information cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1830</link><description>A vulnerability was found in zj1983 zz up to 2024-8. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Customer Information Handler. The manipulation of the argument Customer Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 19:34:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1829 | TOTOLINK X18 cstecgi.cgi setMtknatCfg os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1829</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X18 9.1.0cu.2024_B20220329. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setMtknatCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument mtkhnatEnable leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 19:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1821 | zj1983 zz ZorgAction.java getUserOrgForUserId sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1821</link><description>A vulnerability was found in zj1983 zz up to 2024-8 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function getUserOrgForUserId of the file src/main/java/com/futvan/z/system/zorg/ZorgAction.java. The manipulation of the argument userID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 18:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36353 | Insufficient clearing of GPU global memory could allow a malicious process running on the same GPU to read left over memory values, potentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36353</link><description>Insufficient clearing of GPU global memory could allow a malicious process running on the same GPU to read left over memory values, potentially leading to loss of confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 17:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1820 | zj1983 zz ZworkflowAction.java getOaWid sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1820</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in zj1983 zz up to 2024-8 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getOaWid of the file src/main/java/com/futvan/z/system/zworkflow/ZworkflowAction.java. The manipulation of the argument tableId leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 17:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1819 | Tenda AC7 1200M telnet TendaTelnet os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1819</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda AC7 1200M 15.03.06.44. Affected is the function TendaTelnet of the file /goform/telnet. The manipulation of the argument lan_ip leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 16:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1818 | zj1983 zz ZfileAction.upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1818</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in zj1983 zz up to 2024-8. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file src/main/java/com/futvan/z/system/zfile/ZfileAction.upload. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 16:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55907 | IBM Cognos Mobile information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55907</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics Mobile 1.1 for iOS application could allow an attacker to reverse engineer the codebase to gain knowledge about the programming technique, interface, class definitions, algorithms and functions used due to weak obfuscation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 15:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0895 | IBM Cognos Mobile information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0895</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics Mobile 1.1 for Android could allow a user with physical access to the device, to obtain sensitive information from debugging code log messages.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 15:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1817 | Mini-Tmall Admin Name admin cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1817</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Mini-Tmall up to 20250211. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin of the component Admin Name Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 14:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-49733 | ALSA: pcm: oss: Fix race at SNDCTL_DSP_SYNC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-49733</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ALSA: pcm: oss: Fix race at SNDCTL_DSP_SYNC

There is a small race window at snd_pcm_oss_sync() that is called from
OSS PCM SNDCTL_DSP_SYNC ioctl; namely the function calls
snd_pcm_oss_make_ready() at first, then takes the params_lock mutex
for the rest.  When the stream is set up again by another thread
between them, it leads to inconsistency, and may result in unexpected
results such as NULL dereference of OSS buffer as a fuzzer spotted
recently.

The fix is simply to cover snd_pcm_oss_make_ready() call into the same
params_lock mutex with snd_pcm_oss_make_ready_locked() variant.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 14:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1816 | FFmpeg IAMF File iamf_parse.c audio_element_obu memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1816</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in FFmpeg up to 6e26f57f672b05e7b8b052007a83aef99dc81ccb. This affects the function audio_element_obu of the file libavformat/iamf_parse.c of the component IAMF File Handler. The manipulation of the argument num_parameters leads to memory leak. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is 0526535cd58444dd264e810b2f3348b4d96cff3b. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 14:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1815 | pbrong hrms resource.go HrmsDB improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1815</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in pbrong hrms up to 1.0.1. This affects the function HrmsDB of the file \resource\resource.go. The manipulation of the argument user_cookie leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 12:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1814 | Tenda AC6 WifiExtraSet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1814</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda AC6 15.03.05.16. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /goform/WifiExtraSet. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 11:09:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1813 | zj1983 zz cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1813</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in zj1983 zz up to 2024-08. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 10:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1812 | zj1983 zz SuperZ.java GetUserOrg sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1812</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in zj1983 zz up to 2024-08. Affected is the function GetUserOrg of the file com/futvan/z/framework/core/SuperZ.java. The manipulation of the argument userId leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 09:15:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1811 | AT Software Solutions ATSVD Login Endpoint login.aspx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1811</link><description>A vulnerability was found in AT Software Solutions ATSVD up to 3.4.1. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /login.aspx of the component Login Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument txtUsuario leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.4.2 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 08:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1810 | Pixsoft Vivaz Login Endpoint servlet cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1810</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Pixsoft Vivaz 6.0.11. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /servlet?act=login&amp;amp;submit=1&amp;amp;evento=0&amp;amp;pixrnd=0125021817031859360231 of the component Login Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument sistema leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 07:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1809 | Pixsoft Sol Login Endpoint servlet sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1809</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Pixsoft Sol up to 7.6.6c and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /pix_projetos/servlet?act=login&amp;amp;submit=1&amp;amp;evento=0&amp;amp;pixrnd=0125021816444195731041 of the component Login Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument txtUsuario leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 06:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25724 | list_item_verbose in tar/util.c in libarchive through 3.7.7 does not check an strftime return value, which can lead to a denial of service o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25724</link><description>list_item_verbose in tar/util.c in libarchive through 3.7.7 does not check an strftime return value, which can lead to a denial of service or unspecified other impact via a crafted TAR archive that is read with a verbose value of 2. For example, the 100-byte buffer may not be sufficient for a custom locale.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 02:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1808 | Pixsoft E-Saphira Login Endpoint servlet sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1808</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Pixsoft E-Saphira 1.7.24 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /servlet?act=login&amp;amp;tipo=1 of the component Login Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument txtUsuario leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 01:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1807 | Eastnets PaymentSafe Edit Manual Reply directRouter.rfc cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1807</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Eastnets PaymentSafe 2.5.26.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /directRouter.rfc of the component Edit Manual Reply Handler. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to basic cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 01:09:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1806 | Eastnets PaymentSafe URL Default.aspx improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1806</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Eastnets PaymentSafe 2.5.26.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Default.aspx of the component URL Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 23:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1804 | Blizzard Battle.Net profapi.dll uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1804</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Blizzard Battle.Net up to 2.39.0.15212 on Windows and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality in the library profapi.dll. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. The attack needs to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 18:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1800 | D-Link DAR-7000 HTTP POST Request sxh_vpnlic.php get_ip_addr_details command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1800</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DAR-7000 3.2 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function get_ip_addr_details of the file /view/vpn/sxh_vpn/sxh_vpnlic.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument ethname leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 18:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1799 | Zorlan SkyCaiji Tool.php previewAction server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1799</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Zorlan SkyCaiji 2.9. This affects the function previewAction of the file vendor/skycaiji/app/admin/controller/Tool.php. The manipulation of the argument data leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 17:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1797 | Hunan Zhonghe Baiyi Information Technology Baiyiyun Asset Management and Operations System anyUserBoundHouse.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1797</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Hunan Zhonghe Baiyi Information Technology Baiyiyun Asset Management and Operations System up to 20250217. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /wuser/anyUserBoundHouse.php. The manipulation of the argument huid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 14:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41778 | IBM Controller information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41778</link><description>IBM Controller 11.0.0 through 11.0.1 and 11.1.0 does not require that users should have strong passwords by default, which makes it easier for attackers to compromise user accounts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 14:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1791 | Zorlan SkyCaiji Tool.php fileAction unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1791</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Zorlan SkyCaiji 2.9 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function fileAction of the file vendor/skycaiji/app/admin/controller/Tool.php. The manipulation of the argument save_data leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 13:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1788 | rizinorg rizin utf8.c rz_utf8_encode heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1788</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in rizinorg rizin up to 0.8.0. This affects the function rz_utf8_encode in the library /librz/util/utf8.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 12:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1491 | WP Posts Carousel &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via auto_play_timeout Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1491</link><description>The WP Posts Carousel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘auto_play_timeout’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 12:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13833 | Album Gallery – WordPress Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Authenticated (Editor+) PHP Object Injection via Gallery Meta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13833</link><description>The Album Gallery – WordPress Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.3 via deserialization of untrusted input from gallery meta. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 11:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1404 | Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking &amp;lt;= 4.4.7 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated User Email Retrieval via ays_sccp_reports_user_search Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1404</link><description>The Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the ays_sccp_reports_user_search() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve a list of registered user emails.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 11:30:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1786 | rizinorg rizin pdb.c msf_stream_directory_free buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1786</link><description>A vulnerability was found in rizinorg rizin up to 0.7.4. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function msf_stream_directory_free in the library /librz/bin/pdb/pdb.c. The manipulation of the argument -P leads to buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 0.8.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 10:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13546 | GenerateBlocks &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via &amp;#x27;get_image_description&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13546</link><description>The GenerateBlocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.1 via the 'get_image_description' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including the content of private, draft, and scheduled posts and pages.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 09:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13611 | Better Messages – Live Chat for WordPress, BuddyPress, PeepSo, Ultimate Member, BuddyBoss &amp;lt;= 2.6.9 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13611</link><description>The Better Messages – Live Chat for WordPress, BuddyPress, PeepSo, Ultimate Member, BuddyBoss plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 via the 'bp-better-messages' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/uploads/bp-better-messages directory which can contain file attachments included in chat messages.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 08:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13697 | Better Messages – Live Chat for WordPress, BuddyPress, PeepSo, Ultimate Member, BuddyBoss &amp;lt;= 2.7.4 - Unauthenticated Limited Server-Side Request Forgery in nice_links</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13697</link><description>The Better Messages – Live Chat for WordPress, BuddyPress, PeepSo, Ultimate Member, BuddyBoss plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.4 via the 'nice_links'. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services. Successful exploitation requires the "Enable link previews" to be enabled (default).</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 08:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13910 | Database Backup and check Tables Automated With Scheduler 2024 &amp;lt;= 2.36 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13910</link><description>The Database Backup and check Tables Automated With Scheduler 2024 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the 'database_backup_ajax_delete' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.35. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php). The vulnerability was partially patched in version 2.36.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 08:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1291 | Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks &amp;lt;= 3.4.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;icon&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1291</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘icon’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 08:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12544 | SurveyJS: Drag &amp;amp; Drop WordPress Form Builder to create, style and embed multiple forms of any complexity &amp;lt;= 1.12.17 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion via SurveyJS_DeleteFile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12544</link><description>The SurveyJS: Drag &amp; Drop WordPress Form Builder to create, style and embed multiple forms of any complexity plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to a missing capability check on the callback function of the SurveyJS_DeleteFile class in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.17. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php). This function is still vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery as of 1.12.20.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 07:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13806 | Authors List &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13806</link><description>The The Authors List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 07:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13911 | Database Backup and check Tables Automated With Scheduler 2024 &amp;lt;= 2.35 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13911</link><description>The Database Backup and check Tables Automated With Scheduler 2024 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.35 via the /dashboard/backup.php file. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including full database credentials.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 07:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1564 | SetSail Membership &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Authentication Bypass via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1564</link><description>The SetSail Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to  in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a users identity through the social login. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any user, including administrators and take over access to their account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 07:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1638 | Alloggio Membership &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authentication Bypass via Social Login Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1638</link><description>The Alloggio Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity through the alloggio_membership_init_rest_api_facebook_login and alloggio_membership_init_rest_api_google_login functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any user, including administrators, without knowing a password.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 07:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1671 | Academist Membership &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Authentication Bypass via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1671</link><description>The Academist Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6. This is due to the academist_membership_check_facebook_user() function not properly verifying a user's identity prior to authenticating them. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any user, including site administrators.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 07:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12824 | Nokri – Job Board WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12824</link><description>The Nokri – Job Board WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. This is due to the plugin not properly checking for an empty token value prior updating their details like password. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's password, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 06:50:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13373 | Exertio Framework &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Password Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13373</link><description>The Exertio Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their password through the fl_forgot_pass_new() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 06:50:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1459 | Page Builder by SiteOrigin &amp;lt;= 2.31.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1459</link><description>The Page Builder by SiteOrigin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Embedded Video(PB) widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.31.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 06:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1502 | IP2Location Redirection &amp;lt;= 1.33.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Settings Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1502</link><description>The IP2Location Redirection plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'download_ip2location_redirection_backup' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.33.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 06:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1730 | Simple Download Counter &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1730</link><description>The Simple Download Counter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 2.0 via the 'simple_download_counter_download_handler'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including any local file on the server, such as wp-config.php or /etc/passwd.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 06:50:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27554 | ToDesktop before 2024-10-03, as used by Cursor before 2024-10-03 and other applications, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary comman...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27554</link><description>ToDesktop before 2024-10-03, as used by Cursor before 2024-10-03 and other applications, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the build server (e.g., read secrets from the desktopify config.prod.json file), and consequently deploy updates to any app, via a postinstall script in package.json. No exploitation occurred.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 06:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13901 | Counter Box: Add Engaging Countdowns, Timers &amp;amp; Counters to Your WordPress Site &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Authenticated (Administrator+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13901</link><description>The Counter Box: Add Engaging Countdowns, Timers &amp; Counters to Your WordPress Site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘content’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 05:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13518 | Simple:Press &amp;lt;= 6.10.11 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Unauthorized Post Editing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13518</link><description>The Simple:Press Forum plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.10.11. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'sp_save_edited_post' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify a forum post via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 04:32:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13559 | TemplatesNext ToolKit &amp;lt;= 3.2.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13559</link><description>The TemplatesNext ToolKit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tx_woo_wishlist_table' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 04:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13568 | Fluent Support – Helpdesk &amp;amp; Customer Support Ticket System &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13568</link><description>The Fluent Support – Helpdesk &amp; Customer Support Ticket System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.5 via the 'fluent-support' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/uploads/fluent-support directory which can contain file attachments included in support tickets.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 04:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13746 | Booking Calendar and Notification &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - Missing Authorization via wpcb_all_bookings, wpcb_update_booking_post, and wpcb_delete_posts Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13746</link><description>The Booking Calendar and Notification plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access, modification, and loss of data due to missing capability checks on the wpcb_all_bookings(), wpcb_update_booking_post(), and wpcb_delete_posts() functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract data, create or update bookings, or  delete arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 04:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13750 | Multilevel Referral Affiliate Plugin for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.27 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13750</link><description>The Multilevel Referral Affiliate Plugin for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'orderby' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.27 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 04:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9212 | SKU Generator for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9212</link><description>The SKU Generator for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 04:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9217 | Currency Switcher for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.16.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9217</link><description>The Currency Switcher for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.16.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 04:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0820 | Clicface Trombi &amp;lt;= 2.08 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via nom Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0820</link><description>The Clicface Trombi plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘nom’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.08 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 04:33:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13358 | BuddyPress WooCommerce My Account Integration. Create WooCommerce Member Pages &amp;lt;= 3.4.24 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13358</link><description>The BuddyPress WooCommerce My Account Integration. Create WooCommerce Member Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the wc4bp_delete_page() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.24. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugins page setting.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 03:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1780 | BuddyPress WooCommerce My Account Integration. Create WooCommerce Member Pages &amp;lt;= 3.4.25 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Limited Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1780</link><description>The BuddyPress WooCommerce My Account Integration. Create WooCommerce Member Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the wc4bp_delete_page() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.25. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugins page setting.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 03:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23115 | A Use After Free vulnerability on UniFi Protect Cameras could allow a Remote Code Execution (RCE) by a malicious actor with access to UniFi ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23115</link><description>A Use After Free vulnerability on UniFi Protect Cameras could allow a Remote Code Execution (RCE) by a malicious actor with access to UniFi Protect Cameras management network.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 03:06:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23116 | An Authentication Bypass vulnerability on UniFi Protect Application with Auto-Adopt Bridge Devices enabled could allow a malicious actor wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23116</link><description>An Authentication Bypass vulnerability on UniFi Protect Application with Auto-Adopt Bridge Devices enabled could allow a malicious actor with access to UniFi Protect Cameras adjacent network to take control of UniFi Protect Cameras.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 03:06:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23117 | An Insufficient Firmware Update Validation vulnerability could allow an authenticated malicious actor with access to UniFi Protect Cameras a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23117</link><description>An Insufficient Firmware Update Validation vulnerability could allow an authenticated malicious actor with access to UniFi Protect Cameras adjacent network to make unsupported changes to the camera system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 03:06:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23118 | An Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability could allow an authenticated malicious actor with access to UniFi Protect Cameras adjacent ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23118</link><description>An Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability could allow an authenticated malicious actor with access to UniFi Protect Cameras adjacent network to make unsupported changes to the camera system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 03:06:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23119 | An Improper Neutralization of Escape Sequences vulnerability could allow an Authentication Bypass with a Remote Code Execution (RCE) by a ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23119</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Escape Sequences vulnerability could allow an Authentication Bypass with a Remote Code Execution (RCE) by a malicious actor with access to UniFi Protect Cameras adjacent network.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 03:06:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27416 | Asking For Scratch Username And Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27416</link><description>Scratch-Coding-Hut.github.io is the website for Coding Hut. The website as of 28 February 2025 contained a sign in with scratch username and password form. Any user who used the sign in page would be susceptible to any other user signing into their account. As of time of publication, a fix is not available but work on a fix is underway. As a workaround, users should avoid signing in.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 00:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>