<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:45:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-27136 | Apache JSPWiki: Cross-site scripting vulnerability on upload page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27136</link><description>XSS in Upload page in Apache JSPWiki 2.12.1 and priors allows the attacker to execute javascript in the victim's browser and get some sensitive information about the victim.  Apache JSPWiki users should upgrade to 2.12.2 or later.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24554 | Bludit - Insecure Token Generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24554</link><description>Bludit uses predictable methods in combination with the MD5 hashing algorithm to generate sensitive tokens such as the API token and the user token. This allows attackers to authenticate against the Bludit API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24550 | Bludit - Remote Code Execution (RCE) through File API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24550</link><description>A security vulnerability has been identified in Bludit, allowing attackers with knowledge of the API token to upload arbitrary files through the File API which leads to arbitrary code execution on the server. This vulnerability arises from improper handling of file uploads, enabling malicious actors to upload and execute PHP files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24551 | Bludit - Remote Code Execution (RCE) through Image API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24551</link><description>A security vulnerability has been identified in Bludit, allowing authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code through the Image API. This vulnerability arises from improper handling of file uploads, enabling malicious actors to upload and execute PHP files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24552 | Bludit is Vulnerable to Session Fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24552</link><description>A session fixation vulnerability in Bludit allows an attacker to bypass the server's authentication if they can trick an administrator or any other user into authorizing a session ID of their choosing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24553 | Bludit uses SHA1 as Password Hashing Algorithm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24553</link><description>Bludit uses the SHA-1 hashing algorithm to compute password hashes. Thus, attackers could determine cleartext passwords with brute-force attacks due to the inherent speed of SHA-1. In addition, the salt that is computed by Bludit is generated with a non-cryptographically secure function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4460 | DoS Vulnerability in zenml-io/zenml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4460</link><description>A denial of service (DoS) vulnerability exists in zenml-io/zenml version 0.56.3 due to improper handling of line feed (`\n`) characters in component names. When a low-privileged user adds a component through the API endpoint `api/v1/workspaces/default/components` with a name containing a `\n` character, it leads to uncontrolled resource consumption. This vulnerability results in the inability of users to add new components in certain categories (e.g., 'Image Builder') and to register new stacks through the UI, thereby degrading the user experience and potentially rendering the ZenML Dashboard unusable. The issue does not affect component addition through the Web UI, as `\n` characters are properly escaped in that context. The vulnerability was tested on ZenML running in Docker, and it was observed in both Firefox and Chrome browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:10:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4899 | SEOPress &amp;lt; 7.8 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4899</link><description>The SEOPress  WordPress plugin before 7.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its Post settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 06:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4900 | SEOPress &amp;lt; 7.8 - Contributor+ Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4900</link><description>The SEOPress  WordPress plugin before 7.8 does not validate and escape one of its Post settings, which could allow contributor and above role to perform Open redirect attacks against any user viewing a malicious post</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 06:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4499 | CSRF Vulnerability in parisneo/lollms XTTS Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4499</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the XTTS server of parisneo/lollms version 9.6 due to a lax CORS policy. The vulnerability allows attackers to perform unauthorized actions by tricking a user into visiting a malicious webpage, which can then trigger arbitrary LoLLMS-XTTS API requests. This issue can lead to the reading and writing of audio files and, when combined with other vulnerabilities, could allow for the reading of arbitrary files on the system and writing files outside the permitted audio file location.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 03:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6280 | SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6280</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_settings. The manipulation of the argument img leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-269493 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 03:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6278 | lahirudanushka School Management System Subject Page subject.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6278</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file subject.php of the component Subject Page. The manipulation of the argument update leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269491.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6279 | lahirudanushka School Management System Exam Results Page examresults-par.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6279</link><description>A vulnerability was found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file examresults-par.php of the component Exam Results Page. The manipulation of the argument sid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269492.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6277 | lahirudanushka School Management System Student Page student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6277</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file student.php of the component Student Page. The manipulation of the argument update leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-269490 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6276 | lahirudanushka School Management System Teacher Page teacher.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6276</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file teacher.php of the component Teacher Page. The manipulation of the argument update leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-269489 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6274 | lahirudanushka School Management System Attendance Report Page attendancelist.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6274</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /attendancelist.php of the component Attendance Report Page. The manipulation of the argument aid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269487.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6275 | lahirudanushka School Management System Parent Page parent.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6275</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file parent.php of the component Parent Page. The manipulation of the argument update leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269488.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3121 | Remote Code Execution in create_conda_env function in parisneo/lollms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3121</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the create_conda_env function of the parisneo/lollms repository, version 5.9.0. The vulnerability arises from the use of shell=True in the subprocess.Popen function, which allows an attacker to inject arbitrary commands by manipulating the env_name and python_version parameters. This issue could lead to a serious security breach as demonstrated by the ability to execute the 'whoami' command among potentially other harmful commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 01:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39337 | Click Studios Passwordstate Core before 9.8 build 9858 allows Authentication Bypass.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39337</link><description>Click Studios Passwordstate Core before 9.8 build 9858 allows Authentication Bypass.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 23:18:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39334 | MENDELSON AS4 before 2024 B376 has a client-side vulnerability when a trading partner provides prepared XML data. When a victim opens the de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39334</link><description>MENDELSON AS4 before 2024 B376 has a client-side vulnerability when a trading partner provides prepared XML data. When a victim opens the details of this transaction in the client, files can be written to the computer on which the client process is running. (The server process is not affected.)</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 22:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6273 | SourceCodester Clinic Queuing System patient_side.php save_patient cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6273</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinic Queuing System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function save_patient of the file patient_side.php. The manipulation of the argument Full Name/Contact/Address leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-269485 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 22:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39331 | In Emacs before 29.4, org-link-expand-abbrev in lisp/ol.el expands a %(...) link abbrev even when it specifies an unsafe function, such as s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39331</link><description>In Emacs before 29.4, org-link-expand-abbrev in lisp/ol.el expands a %(...) link abbrev even when it specifies an unsafe function, such as shell-command-to-string. This affects Org Mode before 9.7.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 21:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4841 | Path Traversal in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4841</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui, specifically within the 'add_reference_to_local_mode' function due to the lack of input sanitization. This vulnerability affects versions v9.6 to the latest. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can predict the folders, subfolders, and files present on the victim's computer. The vulnerability is present in the way the application handles the 'path' parameter in HTTP requests to the '/add_reference_to_local_model' endpoint.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 14:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6269 | Ruijie RG-UAC HTTP POST Request sxh_vpnlic.php get_ip.addr_details command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6269</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Ruijie RG-UAC 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function get_ip.addr_details of the file /view/vpn/autovpn/sxh_vpnlic.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument indevice leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-269482 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6268 | lahirudanushka School Management System Login Page login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6268</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file login.php of the component Login Page. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269480.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 09:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6267 | SourceCodester Service Provider Management System System Info Page index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6267</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Service Provider Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file system_info/index.php of the component System Info Page. The manipulation of the argument System Name/System Short Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269479.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 06:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6266 | Pear Admin Boot loadDictItem sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6266</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Pear Admin Boot up to 2.0.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file /system/dictData/loadDictItem. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-269478 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 02:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38319 | IBM Security SOAR code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38319</link><description>IBM Security SOAR 51.0.2.0 could allow an authenticated user to execute malicious code loaded from a specially crafted script.  IBM X-Force ID:  294830.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 19:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5443 | Remote Code Execution via Path Traversal in parisneo/lollms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5443</link><description>CVE-2024-4320 describes a vulnerability in the parisneo/lollms software, specifically within the `ExtensionBuilder().build_extension()` function. The vulnerability arises from the `/mount_extension` endpoint, where a path traversal issue allows attackers to navigate beyond the intended directory structure. This is facilitated by the `data.category` and `data.folder` parameters accepting empty strings (`""`), which, due to inadequate input sanitization, can lead to the construction of a `package_path` that points to the root directory. Consequently, if an attacker can create a `config.yaml` file in a controllable path, this path can be appended to the `extensions` list and trigger the execution of `__init__.py` in the current directory, leading to remote code execution. The vulnerability affects versions up to 5.9.0, and has been addressed in version 9.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 16:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6253 | itsourcecode Online Food Ordering System purchase.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6253</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Food Ordering System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /purchase.php. The manipulation of the argument customer leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269420.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 14:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6252 | Zorlan SkyCaiji Task cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6252</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Zorlan SkyCaiji up to 2.8 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Task Handler. The manipulation of the argument onerror leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269419.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 12:26:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6251 | playSMS New Phonebook cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6251</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in playSMS 1.4.3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.php?app=main&amp;amp;inc=feature_phonebook&amp;amp;op=phonebook_list of the component New Phonebook Handler. The manipulation of the argument name/email leads to basic cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-269418 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 11:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38379 | Apache Allura: Stored authenticated XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38379</link><description>Apache Allura's neighborhood settings are vulnerable to a stored XSS attack.  Only neighborhood admins can access these settings, so the scope of risk is limited to configurations where neighborhood admins are not fully trusted.

This issue affects Apache Allura: from 1.4.0 through 1.17.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.17.1, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 09:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3593 | UberMenu &amp;lt;= 3.8.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3593</link><description>The UberMenu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the ubermenu_delete_all_item_settings and ubermenu_reset_settings functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete and reset the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 05:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5596 | ARMember Premium &amp;lt;= 6.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via multiple functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5596</link><description>The ARMember Premium plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 6.7. This is due to incorrectly implemented nonce validation function on multiple functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify, or delete user meta and plugin options which can lead to limited privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 05:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4940 | Open Redirect in gradio-app/gradio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4940</link><description>An open redirect vulnerability exists in the gradio-app/gradio, affecting the latest version. The vulnerability allows an attacker to redirect users to arbitrary websites, which can be exploited for phishing attacks, Cross-site Scripting (XSS), Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF), amongst others. This issue is due to improper validation of user-supplied input in the handling of URLs. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious URL that, when processed by the application, redirects the user to an attacker-controlled web page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 05:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21514 | This affects versions of the package opencart/opencart from 0.0.0. An SQL Injection issue was identified in the Divido payment extension for...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21514</link><description>This affects versions of the package opencart/opencart from 0.0.0. An SQL Injection issue was identified in the Divido payment extension for OpenCart, which is included by default in version 3.0.3.9. As an anonymous unauthenticated user, if the Divido payment module is installed (it does not have to be enabled), it is possible to exploit SQL injection to gain unauthorised access to the backend database. For any site which is vulnerable, any unauthenticated user could exploit this to dump the entire OpenCart database, including customer PII data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 05:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21515 | This affects versions of the package opencart/opencart from 4.0.0.0. A reflected XSS issue was identified in the filename parameter of the a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21515</link><description>This affects versions of the package opencart/opencart from 4.0.0.0. A reflected XSS issue was identified in the filename parameter of the admin tool/log route. An attacker could obtain a user's token by tricking the user to click on a maliciously crafted URL. The user is then prompted to login and redirected again upon authentication with the payload automatically executing. If the attacked user has admin privileges, this vulnerability could be used as the start of a chain of exploits like Zip Slip or arbitrary file write vulnerabilities in the admin functionality.&#13;&#13;**Notes:**&#13;&#13;1) This is only exploitable if the attacker knows the name or path of the admin directory. The name of the directory is "admin" by default but there is a pop-up in the dashboard warning users to rename it.&#13;&#13;2) The fix for this vulnerability is incomplete. The redirect is removed so that it is not possible for an attacker to control the redirect post admin login anymore, but it is still possible to exploit this issue in admin if the user is authenticated as an admin already.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 05:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21516 | This affects versions of the package opencart/opencart from 4.0.0.0. A reflected XSS issue was identified in the directory parameter of admi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21516</link><description>This affects versions of the package opencart/opencart from 4.0.0.0. A reflected XSS issue was identified in the directory parameter of admin common/filemanager.list route. An attacker could obtain a user's token by tricking the user to click on a maliciously crafted URL. The user is then prompted to login and redirected again upon authentication with the payload automatically executing. If the attacked user has admin privileges, this vulnerability could be used as the start of a chain of exploits like Zip Slip or arbitrary file write vulnerabilities in the admin functionality.&#13;&#13;**Notes:**&#13;&#13;1) This is only exploitable if the attacker knows the name or path of the admin directory. The name of the directory is "admin" by default but there is a pop-up in the dashboard warning users to rename it.&#13;&#13;2) The fix for this vulnerability is incomplete. The redirect is removed so that it is not possible for an attacker to control the redirect post admin login anymore, but it is still possible to exploit this issue in admin if the user is authenticated as an admin already.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 05:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21517 | This affects versions of the package opencart/opencart from 4.0.0.0. A reflected XSS issue was identified in the redirect parameter of custo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21517</link><description>This affects versions of the package opencart/opencart from 4.0.0.0. A reflected XSS issue was identified in the redirect parameter of customer account/login route. An attacker can inject arbitrary HTML and Javascript into the page response. As this vulnerability is present in the account functionality it could be used to target and attack customers of the OpenCart shop.&#13;&#13;**Notes:**&#13;&#13;1) The fix for this vulnerability is incomplete</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 05:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21518 | This affects versions of the package opencart/opencart from 4.0.0.0. A Zip Slip issue was identified via the marketplace installer due to im...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21518</link><description>This affects versions of the package opencart/opencart from 4.0.0.0. A Zip Slip issue was identified via the marketplace installer due to improper sanitization of the target path, allowing files within a malicious archive to traverse the filesystem and be extracted to arbitrary locations. An attacker can create arbitrary files in the web root of the application and overwrite other existing files by exploiting this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 05:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21519 | This affects versions of the package opencart/opencart from 4.0.0.0. An Arbitrary File Creation issue was identified via the database restor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21519</link><description>This affects versions of the package opencart/opencart from 4.0.0.0. An Arbitrary File Creation issue was identified via the database restoration functionality. By injecting PHP code into the database, an attacker with admin privileges can create a backup file with an arbitrary filename (including the extension), within /system/storage/backup.&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;&#13;It is less likely for the created file to be available within the web root, as part of the security recommendations for the application suggest moving the storage path outside of the web root.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 05:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4874 | Bricks Builder &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4874</link><description>The Bricks Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.8 via the postId parameter due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to modify posts and pages created by other users including admins. As a requirement for this, an admin would have to enable access to the editor specifically for such a user or enable it for all users with a certain user account type.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 04:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5965 | Mosaic &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5965</link><description>The Mosaic theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘link’ parameter within the theme's Button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 03:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5966 | Grey Opaque &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Download-Button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5966</link><description>The Grey Opaque theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter within the theme's Download-Button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 03:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2484 | Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle &amp;lt;= 2.10.34 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Services and Post Type Grid Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2484</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Services and Post Type Grid widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.34 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4313 | Table Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via _id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4313</link><description>The Table Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5346 | Flatsome | Multi-Purpose Responsive WooCommerce Theme &amp;lt;= 3.18.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Shortcodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5346</link><description>The Flatsome theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the UX Countdown, Video Button, UX Video, UX Slider, UX Sidebar, and UX Payment Icons shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 3.18.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5791 | Appointment Booking and Online Scheduling &amp;lt;= 4.4.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5791</link><description>The Online Booking &amp; Scheduling Calendar for WordPress by vcita plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'wp_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.2 due to missing authorization checks on processAction function, as well as insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts that will execute whenever a user accesses a wp-admin dashboard.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>