<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 05:53:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-0698 | code-projects Intern Membership Management System edit_students.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0698</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Intern Membership Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /intern/admin/edit_students.php. Such manipulation of the argument admin_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 05:53:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0697 | code-projects Intern Membership Management System edit_admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0697</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Intern Membership Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /intern/admin/edit_admin.php. This manipulation of the argument admin_id causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 05:04:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21427 | The installers for multiple products provided by PIONEER CORPORATION contain an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to insecurely...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21427</link><description>The installers for multiple products provided by PIONEER CORPORATION contain an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to insecurely loading Dynamic Link Libraries. As a result,  arbitrary code may be executed with the privileges of the running installer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0707 | Keycloak: keycloak authorization header parsing leading to potential security control bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0707</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. The Keycloak Authorization header parser is overly permissive regarding the formatting of the "Bearer" authentication scheme. It accepts non-standard characters (such as tabs) as separators and tolerates case variations that deviate from RFC 6750 specifications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25296 | WP Cost Estimation &amp;lt;= 9.642 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary File Upload/Delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25296</link><description>The WP Cost Estimation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads and deletion due to missing file type validation in the lfb_upload_form and lfb_removeFile AJAX actions in versions up to, and including, 9.642. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected sites server which may make remote code execution possible. Additionally, the attacker can also delete files on the server such as database configuration files, subsequently uploading their own database files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 02:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12640 | Folders – Unlimited Folders to Organize Media Library Folder, Pages, Posts, File Manager &amp;lt;= 3.1.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Author+) Media Replacement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12640</link><description>The Folders – Unlimited Folders to Organize Media Library Folder, Pages, Posts, File Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unauthorized Arbitrary Media Replacement in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.5. This is due to missing object-level authorization checks in the handle_folders_file_upload() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to replace arbitrary media files from the WordPress Media Library.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 02:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14275 | Jeg Elementor Kit &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14275</link><description>The Jeg Elementor Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization in the countdown widget's redirect functionality. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary JavaScript that will execute when an administrator or other user views the page containing the malicious countdown element.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 02:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25295 | WP Cost Estimation &amp;lt; 9.660 - Upload Directory Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25295</link><description>The WP Cost Estimation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Upload Directory Traversal in versions before 9.660 via the uploadFormFiles function. This allows attackers to overwrite any file with a whitelisted type on an affected site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 02:56:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21879 | Kanboard vulnerable to Open Redirect via protocol-relative URLs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21879</link><description>Kanboard is project management software focused on Kanban methodology. Versions 1.2.48 and below are vulnerable to an Open Redirect attack that allows malicious actors to redirect authenticated users to attacker-controlled websites. By crafting URLs such as //evil.com, attackers can bypass the filter_var($url, FILTER_VALIDATE_URL) validation check. This vulnerability could be exploited to conduct phishing attacks, steal user credentials, or distribute malware. The issue is fixed in version 1.2.49.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 02:56:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21880 | Kanboard LDAP Injection Vulnerability can Lead to User Enumeration and Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21880</link><description>Kanboard is project management software focused on Kanban methodology. Versions 1.2.48 and below have an LDAP Injection vulnerability in the LDAP authentication mechanism. User-supplied input is directly substituted into LDAP search filters without proper sanitization, allowing attackers to enumerate all LDAP users, discover sensitive user attributes, and perform targeted attacks against specific accounts. This issue is fixed in version 1.2.49.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 02:56:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21881 | Kanboard is Vulnerable to Reverse Proxy Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21881</link><description>Kanboard is project management software focused on Kanban methodology. Versions 1.2.48 and below is vulnerable to a critical authentication bypass when REVERSE_PROXY_AUTH is enabled. The application blindly trusts HTTP headers for user authentication without verifying the request originated from a trusted reverse proxy. An attacker can impersonate any user, including administrators, by simply sending a spoofed HTTP header. This issue is fixed in version 1.2.49.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 02:56:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21883 | Bokeh server applications have Incomplete Origin Validation in WebSockets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21883</link><description>Bokeh is an interactive visualization library written in Python. In versions 3.8.1 and below, if a server is configured with an allowlist (e.g., dashboard.corp), an attacker can register a domain like dashboard.corp.attacker.com (or use a subdomain if applicable) and lure a victim to visit it. The malicious site can then initiate a WebSocket connection to the vulnerable Bokeh server. Since the Origin header (e.g., http://dashboard.corp.attacker.com/) matches the allowlist according to the flawed logic, the connection is accepted. Once connected, the attacker can interact with the Bokeh server on behalf of the victim, potentially accessing sensitive data, or modifying visualizations. This issue is fixed in version 3.8.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 02:56:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21877 | n8n is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21877</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. In versions 0.121.2 and below, an authenticated attacker may be able to execute malicious code using the n8n service. This could result in full compromise and can impact both self-hosted and n8n Cloud instances. This issue is fixed in version 1.121.3. Administrators can reduce exposure by disabling the Git node and limiting access for untrusted users, but upgrading to the latest version is recommended.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21868 | Flag Forge has ReDoS Vulnerability in User Profile Lookup API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21868</link><description>Flag Forge is a Capture The Flag (CTF) platform. Versions 2.3.2 and below have a Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) vulnerability in the user profile API endpoint (/api/user/[username]). The application constructs a regular expression dynamically using unescaped user input (the username parameter). An attacker can exploit this by sending a specially crafted username containing regex meta-characters (e.g., deeply nested groups or quantifiers), causing the MongoDB regex engine to consume excessive CPU resources. This can lead to Denial of Service for other users. The issue is fixed in version 2.3.3. To workaround this issue, implement a Web Application Firewall (WAF) rule to block requests containing regex meta-characters in the URL path.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22035 | Greenshot Vulnerable to OS Command Injection via ExternalCommand Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22035</link><description>Greenshot is an open source Windows screenshot utility. Versions 1.3.310 and below arvulnerable to OS Command Injection through unsanitized filename processing. The FormatArguments method in ExternalCommandDestination.cs:269 uses string.Format() to insert user-controlled filenames directly into shell commands without sanitization, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary commands by crafting malicious filenames containing shell metacharacters. This issue is fixed in version 1.3.311.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21858 | n8n Vulnerable to Unauthenticated File Access via Improper Webhook Request Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21858</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Versions below 1.121.0 enable an attacker to access files on the underlying server through execution of certain form-based workflows. A vulnerable workflow could grant access to an unauthenticated remote attacker, resulting in exposure of sensitive information stored on the system and may enable further compromise depending on deployment configuration and workflow usage. This issue is fixed in version 1.121.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21875 | ClipBucket v5 Vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection through Channel Comments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21875</link><description>ClipBucket v5 is an open source video sharing platform. Versions 5.5.2-#187 and below allow an attacker to perform Blind SQL Injection through the add comment section within a channel. When adding a comment within a channel, there is a POST request to the /actions/ajax.php endpoint. The obj_id parameter within the POST request to /actions/ajax.php is then used within the user_exists function of the upload/includes/classes/user.class. php file as the $id parameter. It is then used within the count function of the upload/includes/classes/db.class. php file. The $id parameter is concatenated into the query without validation or sanitization, and a user-supplied input like 1' or 1=1-- - can be used to trigger the injection. This issue does not have a fix at the time of publication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:56:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15346 | wolfSSL Python library `CERT_REQUIRED` mode fails to enforce client certificate requirement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15346</link><description>A vulnerability in the handling of verify_mode = CERT_REQUIRED in the wolfssl Python package (wolfssl-py) causes client certificate requirements to not be fully enforced. 

Because the WOLFSSL_VERIFY_FAIL_IF_NO_PEER_CERT flag was not included, the behavior effectively matched CERT_OPTIONAL: a peer certificate was verified if presented, but connections were incorrectly authenticated when no client certificate was provided. 

This results in improper authentication, allowing attackers to bypass mutual TLS (mTLS) client authentication by omitting a client certificate during the TLS handshake. 

The issue affects versions up to and including 5.8.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21869 | llama.cpp has Out-of-bounds Write in llama-server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21869</link><description>llama.cpp is an inference of several LLM models in C/C++. In commits 55d4206c8 and prior, the n_discard parameter is parsed directly from JSON input in the llama.cpp server's completion endpoints without validation to ensure it's non-negative. When a negative value is supplied and the context fills up, llama_memory_seq_rm/add receives a reversed range and negative offset, causing out-of-bounds memory writes in the token evaluation loop. This deterministic memory corruption can crash the process or enable remote code execution (RCE). There is no fix at the time of publication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21695 | Titra API Contains Mass Assignment Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21695</link><description>Titra is open source project time tracking software. In versions 0.99.49 and below, an API has a Mass Assignment vulnerability which allows authenticated users to inject arbitrary fields into time entries, bypassing business logic controls via the customfields parameter. The affected endpoint uses the JavaScript spread operator (...customfields) to merge user-controlled input directly into the database document. While customfields is validated as an Object type, there is no validation of which keys are permitted inside that object. This allows attackers to overwrite protected fields such as userId, hours, and state. The issue is fixed in version 0.99.50.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21859 | Mailpit Proxy Endpoint is Vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21859</link><description>Mailpit is an email testing tool and API for developers. Versions 1.28.0 and below have a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the /proxy endpoint, allowing attackers to make requests to internal network resources. The /proxy endpoint validates http:// and https:// schemes, but it does not block internal IP addresses, enabling attackers to access internal services and APIs. This vulnerability is limited to HTTP GET requests with minimal headers. The issue is fixed in version 1.28.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20212 | FLIR Thermal Camera F/FC/PT/D 8.0.0.64 Information Disclosure via File Reading</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20212</link><description>FLIR Thermal Camera F/FC/PT/D firmware version 8.0.0.64 contains an information disclosure vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files through unverified input parameters. Attackers can exploit the /var/www/data/controllers/api/xml.php readFile() function to access local system files without authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20213 | FLIR Thermal Camera F/FC/PT/D Stream 8.0.0.64 Unauthenticated Stream Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20213</link><description>FLIR Thermal Camera F/FC/PT/D Stream firmware version 8.0.0.64 contains an unauthenticated vulnerability that allows remote attackers to access live camera streams without credentials. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability to view unauthorized thermal camera video feeds across multiple camera series without requiring any authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20214 | FLIR Thermal Camera F/FC/PT/D firmware version 8.0.0.64 Hard-Coded SSH Credentials Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20214</link><description>FLIR Thermal Camera F/FC/PT/D firmware version 8.0.0.64 contains hard-coded SSH credentials that cannot be changed through normal camera operations. Attackers can leverage these persistent, unmodifiable credentials to gain unauthorized remote access to the thermal camera system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20215 | FLIR Thermal Camera FC-S/PT firmware version 8.0.0.64 Authenticated OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20215</link><description>FLIR Thermal Camera FC-S/PT firmware version 8.0.0.64 contains an authenticated OS command injection vulnerability that allows attackers to execute shell commands with root privileges. Authenticated attackers can inject arbitrary shell commands through unvalidated input parameters to gain complete control of the thermal camera system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20216 | FLIR Thermal Camera PT-Series firmware version 8.0.0.64 Unauthenticated Remote Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20216</link><description>FLIR Thermal Camera PT-Series firmware version 8.0.0.64 contains multiple unauthenticated remote command injection vulnerabilities in the controllerFlirSystem.php script. Attackers can execute arbitrary system commands as root by exploiting unsanitized POST parameters in the execFlirSystem() function through shell_exec() calls. Exploitation evidence was observed by the Shadowserver Foundation on 2026-01-06 (UTC).</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25231 | devolo dLAN Cockpit 4.3.1 Unquoted Service Path Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25231</link><description>devolo dLAN Cockpit 4.3.1 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the 'DevoloNetworkService' that allows local non-privileged users to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the insecure service path configuration by inserting malicious code in the system root path to execute with elevated privileges during application startup or system reboot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25259 | Leica Geosystems GR10/GR25/GR30/GR50 GNSS 4.30.063 Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25259</link><description>Leica Geosystems GR10/GR25/GR30/GR50 GNSS 4.30.063 contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability that allows attackers to perform administrative actions without request validation. Attackers can trick logged-in users into executing unauthorized actions by crafting malicious web pages that submit requests to the application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25268 | NREL BEopt 2.8.0 Insecure Library Loading Arbitrary Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25268</link><description>NREL BEopt 2.8.0.0 contains a DLL hijacking vulnerability that allows attackers to load arbitrary libraries by tricking users into opening application files from remote shares. Attackers can exploit insecure library loading of sdl2.dll and libegl.dll by placing malicious libraries on WebDAV or SMB shares to execute unauthorized code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25270 | SOCA Access Control System 180612 Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via logged_page.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25270</link><description>SOCA Access Control System 180612 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the 'senddata' POST parameter of logged_page.php that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts. Attackers can exploit this weakness by sending crafted POST requests to execute arbitrary HTML and script code in a victim's browser session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25277 | FaceSentry Access Control System 6.4.8 Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via pluginInstall.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25277</link><description>FaceSentry Access Control System 6.4.8 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the 'msg' parameter of pluginInstall.php that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts. Attackers can exploit the unvalidated input to execute arbitrary JavaScript in victim browsers, potentially stealing authentication credentials and conducting phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25278 | FaceSentry Access Control System 6.4.8 Authentication Credentials MiTM Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25278</link><description>FaceSentry Access Control System 6.4.8 contains a cleartext transmission vulnerability that allows remote attackers to intercept authentication credentials. Attackers can perform man-in-the-middle attacks to capture HTTP cookie authentication information during network communication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25279 | FaceSentry Access Control System 6.4.8 Cleartext Password Storage Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25279</link><description>FaceSentry Access Control System 6.4.8 contains a cleartext password storage vulnerability that allows attackers to access unencrypted credentials in the device's SQLite database. Attackers can directly read sensitive login information stored in /faceGuard/database/FaceSentryWeb.sqlite without additional authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25280 | Yahei-PHP Prober 0.4.7 Remote HTML Injection via Speed Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25280</link><description>Yahei-PHP Prober 0.4.7 contains a remote HTML injection vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary HTML code through the 'speed' GET parameter. Attackers can inject malicious HTML code in the 'speed' parameter of prober.php to trigger cross-site scripting in user browser sessions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25282 | V-SOL GPON/EPON OLT Platform V2.03.62R_IPv6 v2.03 Open Redirect via bindProfile.html</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25282</link><description>V-SOL GPON/EPON OLT Platform v2.03 contains an open redirect vulnerability in the script that allows attackers to manipulate the 'parent' GET parameter. Attackers can craft malicious links that redirect logged-in users to arbitrary websites by exploiting improper input validation in the redirect mechanism.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25284 | V-SOL GPON/EPON OLT Platform V2.03.62R_IPv6 v2.03 Reflected Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25284</link><description>V-SOL GPON/EPON OLT Platform v2.03 contains multiple reflected cross-site scripting vulnerabilities due to improper input sanitization in various script parameters. Attackers can exploit these vulnerabilities by injecting malicious HTML and script code to execute arbitrary scripts in a victim's browser session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25289 | INIM Electronics SmartLiving SmartLAN/G/SI &amp;lt;=6.x Remote Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25289</link><description>SmartLiving SmartLAN &lt;=6.x contains an authenticated remote command injection vulnerability in the web.cgi binary through the 'par' POST parameter with the 'testemail' module. Attackers can exploit the unsanitized parameter and system() function call to execute arbitrary system commands with root privileges using default credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25290 | INIM Electronics Smartliving SmartLAN/G/SI &amp;lt;=6.x Unauthenticated SSRF via GetImage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25290</link><description>Smartliving SmartLAN/G/SI &lt;=6.x contains an unauthenticated server-side request forgery vulnerability in the GetImage functionality through the 'host' parameter. Attackers can exploit the onvif.cgi endpoint by specifying external domains to bypass firewalls and perform network enumeration through arbitrary HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25291 | INIM Electronics Smartliving SmartLAN/G/SI &amp;lt;=6.x Hard-coded Credentials Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25291</link><description>INIM Electronics Smartliving SmartLAN/G/SI &lt;=6.x contains hard-coded credentials in its Linux distribution image that cannot be changed through normal device operations. Attackers can exploit these persistent credentials to log in and gain unauthorized system access across multiple SmartLiving device models.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21694 | Titra APIs have Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21694</link><description>Titra is open source project time tracking software. Versions 0.99.49 and below have Improper Access Control, allowing users to view and edit other users' time entries in private projects they have not been granted access to. This issue is fixed in version 0.99.50.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7333 | bluelabsio records-mover Table Object sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7333</link><description>A weakness has been identified in bluelabsio records-mover up to 1.5.4. The affected element is an unknown function of the component Table Object Handler. This manipulation causes sql injection. The attack needs to be launched locally. Upgrading to version 1.6.0 is sufficient to fix this issue. Patch name: 3f8383aa89f45d861ca081e3e9fd2cc9d0b5dfaa. You should upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62224 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) for Android Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62224</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69262 | pnpm vulnerable to Command Injection via environment variable substitution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69262</link><description>pnpm is a package manager. Versions 6.25.0 through 10.26.2 have a Command Injection vulnerability when using environment variable substitution in .npmrc configuration files with tokenHelper settings. An attacker who can control environment variables during pnpm operations could achieve Remote Code Execution (RCE) in build environments. This issue is fixed in version 10.27.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21697 | axios4go&amp;#x27;s Race Condition in Shared HTTP Client Allows Proxy Configuration Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21697</link><description>axios4go is a Go HTTP client library. Prior to version 0.6.4, a race condition vulnerability exists in the shared HTTP client configuration. The global `defaultClient` is mutated during request execution without synchronization, directly modifying the shared `http.Client`'s `Transport`, `Timeout`, and `CheckRedirect` properties. Impacted applications include that that use axios4go with concurrent requests (multiple goroutines, `GetAsync`, `PostAsync`, etc.), those where different requests use different proxy configurations, and those that handle sensitive data (authentication credentials, tokens, API keys). Version 0.6.4 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21851 | MONAI has Path Traversal (Zip Slip) in NGC Private Bundle Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21851</link><description>MONAI (Medical Open Network for AI) is an AI toolkit for health care imaging. In versions up to and including 1.5.1, a Path Traversal (Zip Slip) vulnerability exists in MONAI's `_download_from_ngc_private()` function. The function uses `zipfile.ZipFile.extractall()` without path validation, while other similar download functions in the same codebase properly use the existing `safe_extract_member()` function. Commit 4014c8475626f20f158921ae0cf98ed259ae4d59 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21857 | Redaxo has Path Traversal in Backup Addon Leading to Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21857</link><description>REDAXO is a PHP-based content management system. Prior to version 5.20.2, authenticated users with backup permissions can read arbitrary files within the webroot via path traversal in the Backup addon's file export functionality. The Backup addon does not validate the `EXPDIR` POST parameter against the UI-generated allowlist of permitted directories. An attacker can supply relative paths containing `../` sequences (or even absolute paths inside the document root) to include any readable file in the generated `.tar.gz` archive. Version 5.20.2 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12776 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12776</link><description>The Report Builder component of the application stores user input directly in a web page and displays it to other users, which raised concerns about a possible Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack. Proper management of this functionality helps ensure a secure and seamless user experience.  Although the user input is not validated in the report creation, these scripts are not executed when the report is run by end users. The script is executed when the report is modified through the report builder by a user with edit permissions. 




The Report Builder is part of the WebConsole.  The WebConsole package is currently end of life, and is no longer maintained. We strongly recommend against installing or using it in any production environment. However, if you choose to install it, for example, to access functionality like the Report Builder, it must be deployed within a fully isolated network that has no access to sensitive data or internet connectivity. This is a critical security precaution, as the retired package may contain unpatched vulnerabilities and is no longer supported with updates or fixes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21441 | urllib3 vulnerable to decompression-bomb safeguard bypass when following HTTP redirects (streaming API)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21441</link><description>urllib3 is an HTTP client library for Python. urllib3's streaming API is designed for the efficient handling of large HTTP responses by reading the content in chunks, rather than loading the entire response body into memory at once. urllib3 can perform decoding or decompression based on the HTTP `Content-Encoding` header (e.g., `gzip`, `deflate`, `br`, or `zstd`). When using the streaming API, the library decompresses only the necessary bytes, enabling partial content consumption. Starting in version 1.22 and prior to version 2.6.3, for HTTP redirect responses, the library would read the entire response body to drain the connection and decompress the content unnecessarily. This decompression occurred even before any read methods were called, and configured read limits did not restrict the amount of decompressed data. As a result, there was no safeguard against decompression bombs. A malicious server could exploit this to trigger excessive resource consumption on the client. Applications and libraries are affected when they stream content from untrusted sources by setting `preload_content=False` when they do not disable redirects. Users should upgrade to at least urllib3 v2.6.3, in which the library does not decode content of redirect responses when `preload_content=False`. If upgrading is not immediately possible, disable redirects by setting `redirect=False` for requests to untrusted source.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22046 | iccDEV has heap-buffer-overflow in CIccProfileXml::ParseBasic() at IccXML/IccLibXML/IccProfileXml.cpp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22046</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have a heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability in `CIccProfileXml::ParseBasic()` at `IccXML/IccLibXML/IccProfileXml.cpp`. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22047 | iccDEV has heap-buffer-overflow in SIccCalcOp::Describe() at IccProfLib/IccMpeCalc.cpp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22047</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have a heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability in `SIccCalcOp::Describe()` at `IccProfLib/IccMpeCalc.cpp`. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21692 | iccDEV has Type Confusion in ToXmlCurve() at IccXML/IccLibXML/IccMpeXml.cpp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21692</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have a Type Confusion vulnerability in `ToXmlCurve()` at `IccXML/IccLibXML/IccMpeXml.cpp`. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21693 | iccDEV has Type Confusion in CIccSegmentedCurveXml::ToXml() at IccXML/IccLibXML/IccMpeXml.cpp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21693</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have a Type Confusion vulnerability in `CIccSegmentedCurveXml::ToXml()` at `IccXML/IccLibXML/IccMpeXml.cpp`. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69264 | pnpm v10+ Bypass &amp;quot;Dependency lifecycle scripts execution disabled by default&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69264</link><description>pnpm is a package manager. Versions 10.0.0 through 10.25 allow git-hosted dependencies to execute arbitrary code during pnpm install, circumventing the v10 security feature "Dependency lifecycle scripts execution disabled by default". While pnpm v10 blocks postinstall scripts via the onlyBuiltDependencies mechanism, git dependencies can still execute prepare, prepublish, and prepack scripts during the fetch phase, enabling remote code execution without user consent or approval. This issue is fixed in version 10.26.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21690 | iccDEV has Type Confusion in CIccTagXmlTagData::ToXml()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21690</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have a Type Confusion vulnerability in `CIccTagXmlTagData::ToXml()`. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21691 | iccDEV has Type Confusion in CIccTag:IsTypeCompressed()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21691</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have a Type Confusion vulnerability in `CIccTag:IsTypeCompressed()`. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 22:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21688 | iccDEV has Type Confusion in SIccCalcOp::ArgsPushed() at IccProfLib/IccMpeCalc.cpp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21688</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have a Type Confusion vulnerability in `SIccCalcOp::ArgsPushed()` at `IccProfLib/IccMpeCalc.cpp`. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21689 | iccDEV has Type Confusion in CIccProfileXml::ParseBasic() at IccXML/IccLibXML/IccProfileXml.cpp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21689</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have a Type Confusion vulnerability in `CIccProfileXml::ParseBasic()` at `IccXML/IccLibXML/IccProfileXml.cpp`. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69263 | pnpm Lockfile Integrity Bypass Allows Remote Dynamic Dependencies</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69263</link><description>pnpm is a package manager. Versions 10.26.2 and below store HTTP tarball dependencies (and git-hosted tarballs) in the lockfile without integrity hashes. This allows the remote server to serve different content on each install, even when a lockfile is committed. An attacker who publishes a package with an HTTP tarball dependency can serve different code to different users or CI/CD environments. The attack requires the victim to install a package that has an HTTP/git tarball in its dependency tree. The victim's lockfile provides no protection. This issue is fixed in version 10.26.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21685 | iccDEV has Undefined Behavior in CIccTagLut16::Read()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21685</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have Undefined Behavior in `CIccTagLut16::Read()`. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21686 | iccDEV has Undefined Behavior in CIccTagLutAtoB::Validate()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21686</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have Undefined Behavior in `CIccTagLutAtoB::Validate()`. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21687 | iccDEV has Undefined Behavior in CIccTagCurve::CIccTagCurve()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21687</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have Undefined Behavior in `CIccTagCurve::CIccTagCurve()`. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13151 | CVE-2025-13151</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13151</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow in libtasn1 version: v4.20.0. The function fails to validate the size of input data resulting in a buffer overflow in asn1_expend_octet_string.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69222 | LibreChat is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery due to missing restrictions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69222</link><description>LibreChat is a ChatGPT clone with additional features. Version 0.8.1-rc2 is prone to a server-side request forgery (SSRF)
vulnerability due to missing restrictions of the Actions feature in the default configuration. LibreChat enables users to configure agents with predefined instructions and actions that can interact with remote services via OpenAPI specifications, supporting various HTTP methods, parameters, and authentication methods including custom headers. By default, there are no restrictions on accessible services, which means agents can also access internal components like the RAG API included in the default Docker Compose setup. This issue is fixed in version 0.8.1-rc2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21683 | iccDEV has Type Confusion in icStatusCMM::CIccEvalCompare::EvaluateProfile()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21683</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have a Type Confusion vulnerability in `icStatusCMM::CIccEvalCompare::EvaluateProfile()`. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21684 | iccDEV has Undefined Behavior in CIccTagSpectralViewingConditions()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21684</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have Undefined Behavior in `CIccTagSpectralViewingConditions()`. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69221 | LibreChat has Insufficient Access Control for Agent Permission Queries</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69221</link><description>LibreChat is a ChatGPT clone with additional features. Version 0.8.1-rc2 does not enforce proper access control when
querying agent permissions. An authenticated attacker can read the permissions of arbitrary agents, even if they have no permissions for this agent. LibreChat allows the configuration of agents that have a predefined set of instructions and context. Private agents are not visible to other users. However, if an attacker knows the agent ID, they can read the permissions of the agent including the permissions individually assigned to other users. This issue is fixed in version 0.8.2-rc2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:02:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21682 | iccDEV has heap-buffer-overflow in CIccXmlArrayType::ParseText()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21682</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have a heap-buffer-overflow in `CIccXmlArrayType::ParseText()`. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:02:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69220 | LibreChat has Insufficient Access Control for Agent Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69220</link><description>LibreChat is a ChatGPT clone with additional features. Version 0.8.1-rc2 does not enforce proper access control for file uploads to an agents file context and file search. An authenticated attacker with access to the agent ID can change the behavior of arbitrary agents by uploading new files to the file context or file search, even if they have no permissions for this agent. This issue is fixed in version 0.8.2-rc2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21681 | iccDEV has Undefined Behavior runtime error: nan is outside the range .. IccProfLib/IccTagBasic.cpp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21681</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have a Undefined Behavior runtime error. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68705 | RustFS Path Traversal Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68705</link><description>RustFS is a distributed object storage system built in Rust. In versions 1.0.0-alpha.13 to 1.0.0-alpha.78, RustFS contains a path traversal vulnerability in the /rustfs/rpc/read_file_stream endpoint. This issue has been patched in version 1.0.0-alpha.79.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69255 | RustFS gRPC GetMetrics deserialization panic enables remote DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69255</link><description>RustFS is a distributed object storage system built in Rust. In versions 1.0.0-alpha.13 to 1.0.0-alpha.77, a malformed gRPC GetMetrics request causes get_metrics to unwrap() failed deserialization of metric_type/opts, panicking the handler thread and enabling remote denial of service of the metrics endpoint. This issue has been patched in version 1.0.0-alpha.78.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22184 | zlib &amp;lt;= 1.3.1.2 untgz Global Buffer Overflow in TGZfname()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22184</link><description>zlib versions up to and including 1.3.1.2 contain a global buffer overflow in the untgz utility. The TGZfname() function copies an attacker-supplied archive name from argv[] into a fixed-size 1024-byte static global buffer using an unbounded strcpy() call without length validation. Supplying an archive name longer than 1024 bytes results in an out-of-bounds write that can lead to memory corruption, denial of service, and potentially code execution depending on compiler, build flags, architecture, and memory layout. The overflow occurs prior to any archive parsing or validation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22185 | OpenLDAP &amp;lt;= 2.6.10 LMDB mdb_load Heap Buffer Underflow in readline()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22185</link><description>OpenLDAP Lightning Memory-Mapped Database (LMDB) mdb_load contains a heap buffer underflow vulnerability in the readline() function. When processing malformed input, an unsigned offset calculation can underflow a heap pointer, resulting in an out-of-bounds read of one byte before the allocated heap buffer. This may allow a local attacker to cause a denial of service and potentially disclose limited heap memory contents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22186 | Bio-Formats &amp;lt;= 8.3.0 XXE in Leica XLEF Metadata Parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22186</link><description>Bio-Formats versions up to and including 8.3.0 contain an XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in the Leica Microsystems metadata parsing component (e.g., XLEF). The parser uses an insecurely configured DocumentBuilderFactory when processing Leica XML-based metadata files, allowing external entity expansion and external DTD loading. A crafted metadata file can trigger outbound network requests (SSRF), access local system resources where readable, or cause a denial of service during XML parsing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22187 | Bio-Formats &amp;lt;= 8.3.0 Memoizer Unsafe Deserialization via .bfmemo Cache Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22187</link><description>Bio-Formats versions up to and including 8.3.0 perform unsafe Java deserialization of attacker-controlled memoization cache files (.bfmemo) during image processing. The loci.formats.Memoizer class automatically loads and deserializes memo files associated with images without validation, integrity checks, or trust enforcement. An attacker who can supply a crafted .bfmemo file alongside an image can trigger deserialization of untrusted data, which may result in denial of service, logic manipulation, or potentially remote code execution in environments where suitable gadget chains are present on the classpath.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22188 | Panda3D &amp;lt;= 1.10.16 Deploy-Stub Stack Exhaustion via Unbounded alloca()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22188</link><description>Panda3D versions up to and including 1.10.16 deploy-stub contains a denial of service vulnerability due to unbounded stack allocation. The deploy-stub executable allocates argv_copy and argv_copy2 using alloca() based directly on the attacker-controlled argc value without validation. Supplying a large number of command-line arguments can exhaust stack space and propagate uninitialized stack memory into Python interpreter initialization, resulting in a reliable crash and undefined behavior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22189 | Panda3D &amp;lt;= 1.10.16 egg-mkfont Stack Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22189</link><description>Panda3D versions up to and including 1.10.16 egg-mkfont contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability due to use of an unbounded sprintf() call with attacker-controlled input. When constructing glyph filenames, egg-mkfont formats a user-supplied glyph pattern (-gp) into a fixed-size stack buffer without length validation. Supplying an excessively long glyph pattern string can overflow the stack buffer, resulting in memory corruption and a deterministic crash. Depending on build configuration and execution environment, the overflow may also be exploitable for arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22190 | Panda3D &amp;lt;= 1.10.16 egg-mkfont Format String Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22190</link><description>Panda3D versions up to and including 1.10.16 egg-mkfont contains an uncontrolled format string vulnerability. The -gp (glyph pattern) command-line option is used directly as the format string for sprintf() with only a single argument supplied. If an attacker provides additional format specifiers, egg-mkfont may read unintended stack values and write the formatted output into generated .egg and .png files, resulting in disclosure of stack-resident memory and pointer values.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64305 | Columbia Weather Systems MicroServer Cleartext Storage in a File or on Disk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64305</link><description>MicroServer copies parts of the system firmware to an unencrypted external SD card on boot, which contains user and vendor secrets. An attacker can utilize these plaintext secrets to modify the vendor firmware, or gain admin access to the web portal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66620 | Columbia Weather Systems MicroServer Command Shell in Externally Accessible Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66620</link><description>An unused webshell in MicroServer allows unlimited login attempts, with sudo rights on certain files and directories. An attacker with admin access to MicroServer can gain limited shell access, enabling persistence through reverse shells, and the ability to modify or remove data stored in the file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61939 | Columbia Weather Systems MicroServer Improper Restriction of Communication Channel to Intended Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61939</link><description>An unused function in MicroServer can start a reverse SSH connection to a vendor registered domain, without mutual authentication. An attacker on the local network with admin access to the web server, and the ability to manipulate DNS responses, can redirect the SSH connection to an attacker controlled device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0670 | Stored XSS through a system message and a user-provided parameter in ProofreadPage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0670</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki - ProofreadPage Extension allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects MediaWiki - ProofreadPage Extension: 1.45, 1.44, 1.43, 1.39.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21854 | Tarkov Data Manager Authentication Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21854</link><description>The Tarkov Data Manager is a tool to manage the Tarkov item data. Prior to 02 January 2025, an authentication bypass vulnerability in the login endpoint allows any unauthenticated user to gain full admin access to the Tarkov Data Manager admin panel by exploiting a JavaScript prototype property access vulnerability, combined with loose equality type coercion. A series of fix commits on 02 January 2025 fixed this and other vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21855 | Tarkov Data Manager has Unauthenticated Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21855</link><description>The Tarkov Data Manager is a tool to manage the Tarkov item data. Prior to 02 January 2025, a reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the toast notification system allows any attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of a victim's browser session by crafting a malicious URL. A series of fix commits on 02 January 2025 fixed this and other vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21856 | Tarkov Data Manager has Authenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21856</link><description>The Tarkov Data Manager is a tool to manage the Tarkov item data. Prior to commit 9bdb3a75a98a7047b6d70144eb1da1655d6992a8, a time based blind SQL injection vulnerability in the webhook edit and scanner api endpoints that allow an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries against the MySQL database. Commit 9bdb3a75a98a7047b6d70144eb1da1655d6992a8 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61492 | A command injection vulnerability in the execute_command function of terminal-controller-mcp 0.1.7 allows attackers to execute arbitrary com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61492</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the execute_command function of terminal-controller-mcp 0.1.7 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0669 | Path Traversal vulnerability in CSS extension on certain web servers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0669</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki - CSS extension allows Path Traversal.This issue affects MediaWiki - CSS extension: 1.44, 1.43, 1.39.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21680 | iccDEV has Null Pointer Dereference in CIccProfile::CheckTagTypes()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21680</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have a NULL pointer dereference vulnerability. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0668 | VisualData extension: Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) via crafted user input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0668</link><description>Inefficient Regular Expression Complexity vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki - VisualData Extension allows Regular Expression Exponential Blowup.This issue affects MediaWiki - VisualData Extension: 1.45.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61782 | Open Redirect in OpenCTI&amp;#x27;s SAML Authentication Flow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61782</link><description>OpenCTI is an open source platform for managing cyber threat intelligence knowledge and observables. Prior to version 6.8.3, an open redirect vulnerability exists in the OpenCTI platform's SAML authentication endpoint (/auth/saml/callback). By manipulating the RelayState parameter, an attacker can force the server to issue a 302 redirect to any external URL, enabling phishing, credential theft, and arbitrary site redirection. This issue has been patched in version 6.8.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66560 | Quarkus REST has potential worker thread starvation when HTTP connection is closed while waiting to write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66560</link><description>Quarkus is a Cloud Native, (Linux) Container First framework for writing Java applications. Prior to versions 3.31.0, 3.27.2, and 3.20.5, a vulnerability exists in the HTTP layer of Quarkus REST related to response handling. When a response is being written, the framework waits for previously written response chunks to be fully transmitted before proceeding. If the client connection is dropped during this waiting period, the associated worker thread is never released and becomes permanently blocked. Under sustained or repeated occurrences, this can exhaust the available worker threads, leading to degraded performance, or complete unavailability of the application. This issue has been patched in versions 3.31.0, 3.27.2, and 3.20.5. A workaround involves implementing a health check that monitors the status and saturation of the worker thread pool to detect abnormal thread retention early.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4677 | Idle session timeout is not configured for multiple open ports</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4677</link><description>Insufficient Session Expiration vulnerability in ABB WebPro SNMP Card PowerValue, ABB WebPro SNMP Card PowerValue UL.This issue affects WebPro SNMP Card PowerValue: through 1.1.8.K; WebPro SNMP Card PowerValue UL: through 1.1.8.K.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58441 | Knowage is vulnerable to blind server-side request forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58441</link><description>Knowage is an open source analytics and business intelligence suite. Prior to version 8.1.37, there is a blind server-side request forgery vulnerability. The vulnerability allows attackers to send requests to arbitrary hosts/paths. Since the attacker is not able to read the response, the impact of this vulnerability is limited. However, an attacker should be able to leverage this vulnerability to scan the internal network. This issue has been patched in version 8.1.37.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21495 | Division by Zero in iccDEV TIFF Image Reader</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21495</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Prior to version 2.3.1.2, iccDEV is vulnerable to division by zero in the TIFF Image Reader. This issue has been patched in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21496 | NULL Pointer Dereference in iccDEV Signature Parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21496</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Prior to version 2.3.1.2, iccDEV is vulnerable to NULL pointer dereference via the signature parser. This issue has been patched in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21497 | NULL Pointer Dereference in iccDEV Unknown Tag Parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21497</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Prior to version 2.3.1.2, iccDEV is vulnerable to NULL pointer dereference via an unknown tag parser. This issue has been patched in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21498 | NULL Pointer Dereference in iccDEV XML Calculator Parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21498</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Prior to version 2.3.1.2, iccDEV is vulnerable to NULL pointer dereference via the XML calculator parser. This issue has been patched in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21499 | NULL Pointer Dereference in iccDEV XML Parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21499</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Prior to version 2.3.1.2, iccDEV is vulnerable to NULL pointer dereference via the XML parser. This issue has been patched in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21500 | Stack Overflow in iccDEV XML Calculator Macro Expansion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21500</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Prior to version 2.3.1.2, iccDEV is vulnerable to stack overflow in the XML calculator macro expansion. This issue has been patched in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21501 | Stack Overflow in iccDEV Calculator Parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21501</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Prior to version 2.3.1.2, iccDEV is vulnerable to stack overflow in the calculator parser. This issue has been patched in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21502 | NULL Pointer Dereference in iccDEV XML Tag Parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21502</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Prior to version 2.3.1.2, iccDEV is vulnerable to NULL pointer dereference via the XML tag parser. This issue has been patched in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21503 | iccDEV has Undefined Behavior - Null Pointer Passed to memcpy() in CIccTagSparseMatrixArray</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21503</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Prior to version 2.3.1.2, iccDEV has undefined behavior due to a null pointer passed to memcpy() in CIccTagSparseMatrixArray. This issue has been patched in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21504 | Heap Buffer Overflow in iccDEV ToneMap Parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21504</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Prior to version 2.3.1.2, iccDEV is vulnerable to heap buffer overflow in the ToneMap parser. This issue has been patched in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21505 | iccDEV has Undefined Behavior (UB) - Invalid Enum Value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21505</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Prior to version 2.3.1.2, iccDEV has undefined behavior due to an invalid enum value. This issue has been patched in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21506 | iccDEV is Vulnerable to Null Pointer Dereference in CIccProfileXml::ParseBasic() Leading to Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21506</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Prior to version 2.3.1.2, iccDEV is vulnerable to Null pointer dereference in CIccProfileXml::ParseBasic(), leading to denial of service. This issue has been patched in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21678 | iccDEV has heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability on IccTagXml()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21678</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Prior to version 2.3.1.2, iccDEV is vulnerable to heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability in IccTagXml(). This issue has been patched in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21679 | iccDEV has heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability in CIccLocalizedUnicode::GetText()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21679</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Prior to version 2.3.1.2, iccDEV is vulnerable to heap-buffer-overflow in CIccLocalizedUnicode::GetText(). This issue has been patched in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22539 | INFORMATION DISCLOSURE VIA CURL REQUESTS (OCPP)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22539</link><description>As the service interaction is performed without authentication, an attacker with some knowledge of the protocol could obtain information about the charger via OCPP v1.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4676 | Authentication bypass by brute forcing Authentication Headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4676</link><description>Incorrect Implementation of Authentication Algorithm vulnerability in ABB WebPro SNMP Card PowerValue, ABB WebPro SNMP Card PowerValue UL.This issue affects WebPro SNMP Card PowerValue: through 1.1.8.K; WebPro SNMP Card PowerValue UL: through 1.1.8.K.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:15:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0618 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Devolutions PowerShell Universal.This issue affects Powershell Universal: before 4.5.6, before 5.6.13.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0618</link><description>Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Devolutions PowerShell Universal.This issue affects Powershell Universal: before 4.5.6, before 5.6.13.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:15:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22537 | INFORMATION DISCLOSURE WITHIN THE OPERATING SYSTEM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22537</link><description>The lack of hardening of the system allows the user used to manage and maintain the charger to consult different files containing clear-text credentials or valuable information for an attacker.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:15:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4675 | Improper implementation of Modbus protocol leading to DOS attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4675</link><description>Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in ABB WebPro SNMP Card PowerValue, ABB WebPro SNMP Card PowerValue UL.This issue affects WebPro SNMP Card PowerValue: through 1.1.8.K; WebPro SNMP Card PowerValue UL: through 1.1.8.K.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:15:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61489 | A command injection vulnerability in the shell_exec function of sonirico mcp-shell v0.3.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61489</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the shell_exec function of sonirico mcp-shell v0.3.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via supplying a crafted command string.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66686 | A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Perch CMS version 3.2. An authenticated attacker with administrative privileges ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66686</link><description>A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Perch CMS version 3.2. An authenticated attacker with administrative privileges can inject malicious JavaScript code into the “Help button url” setting within the admin panel. The injected payload is stored and executed when any authenticated user clicks the Help button, potentially leading to session hijacking, information disclosure, privilege escalation, and unauthorized administrative actions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67366 | @sylphxltd/filesystem-mcp v0.5.8 is an MCP server that provides file content reading functionality. Version 0.5.8 of filesystem-mcp contains...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67366</link><description>@sylphxltd/filesystem-mcp v0.5.8 is an MCP server that provides file content reading functionality. Version 0.5.8 of filesystem-mcp contains a critical path traversal vulnerability in its "read_content" tool. This vulnerability arises from improper symlink handling in the path validation mechanism: the resolvePath function checks path validity before resolving symlinks, while fs.readFile resolves symlinks automatically during file access. This allows attackers to bypass directory restrictions by leveraging symlinks within the allowed directory that point to external files, enabling unauthorized access to files outside the intended operational scope.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22536 | PRIVILEGE ESCALATION VIA SUDO COMMAND</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22536</link><description>The absence of permissions control for the user XXX allows the current configuration in the sudoers file to escalate privileges without any restrictions</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67364 | fast-filesystem-mcp version 3.4.0 contains a critical path traversal vulnerability in its file operation tools including fast_read_file. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67364</link><description>fast-filesystem-mcp version 3.4.0 contains a critical path traversal vulnerability in its file operation tools including fast_read_file. This vulnerability arises from improper path validation that fails to resolve symbolic links to their actual physical paths. The safePath and isPathAllowed functions use path.resolve() which does not handle symlinks, allowing attackers to bypass directory access restrictions by creating symlinks within allowed directories that point to restricted system paths. When these symlinks are accessed through valid path references, the validation checks are circumvented, enabling access to unauthorized files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:52:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22535 | FRAIL SECURITY IN MQTT PROTOCOL ALLOWS AN ATTACKER MODIFY CRITICAL PARAMETERS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22535</link><description>An attacker with the ability to interact through the network and with access credentials, could, thanks to the unsecured (unencrypted) MQTT communications protocol, write on the server topics of the board that controls the MQTT communications</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:52:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65805 | OpenAirInterface CN5G AMF&lt;=v2.1.9 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in processing NAS messages. Unauthorized remote attackers can launch a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65805</link><description>OpenAirInterface CN5G AMF&lt;=v2.1.9 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in processing NAS messages. Unauthorized remote attackers can launch a denial-of-service attack and potentially execute malicious code by accessing port N1 and sending an imsi string longer than 1000 to AMF.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:52:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66786 | OpenAirInterface CN5G AMF&lt;=v2.0.1 There is a logical error when processing JSON format requests. Unauthorized remote attackers can send mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66786</link><description>OpenAirInterface CN5G AMF&lt;=v2.0.1 There is a logical error when processing JSON format requests. Unauthorized remote attackers can send malicious JSON data to AMF's SBI interface to launch a denial-of-service attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:52:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20026 | Multiple Cisco Products Snort 3 DCERPC Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20026</link><description>Multiple&amp;nbsp;Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the processing of DCE/RPC requests that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the Snort 3 Detection Engine to leak sensitive information or to restart, resulting in an interruption of packet inspection.

This vulnerability is due to an error in buffer handling logic when processing DCE/RPC requests, which can result in a buffer use-after-free read. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of DCE/RPC requests through an established connection that is inspected by Snort 3. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to unexpectedly restart the Snort 3 Detection Engine, which could cause a denial of service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:52:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20027 | Cisco Snort DCERPC Stub Data Out of Bounds Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20027</link><description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the processing of DCE/RPC requests that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the Snort 3 Detection Engine to leak sensitive information or to restart, resulting in an interruption of packet inspection.

This vulnerability is due to an error in buffer handling logic when processing DCE/RPC requests, which can result in a buffer out-of-bounds read. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of DCE/RPC requests through an established connection that is inspected by Snort 3. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain sensitive information in the Snort 3 data stream.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:52:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20029 | Cisco Identity Services Engine XML External Entity Processing Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20029</link><description>A vulnerability in the licensing features of&amp;nbsp;Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) and Cisco ISE Passive Identity Connector (ISE-PIC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative privileges to gain access to sensitive information.&amp;nbsp;

This vulnerability is due to improper parsing of XML that is processed by the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE and Cisco ISE-PIC. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a malicious file to the application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read arbitrary files from the underlying operating system that could include sensitive data that should otherwise be inaccessible even to administrators. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22544 | EXCHANGE OF CREDENTIALS IN CLEAR TEXT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22544</link><description>An attacker with a network connection could detect credentials in clear text.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12543 | Undertow-core: undertow http server fails to reject malformed host headers leading to potential cache poisoning and ssrf</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12543</link><description>A flaw was found in the Undertow HTTP server core, which is used in WildFly, JBoss EAP, and other Java applications. The Undertow library fails to properly validate the Host header in incoming HTTP requests.As a result, requests containing malformed or malicious Host headers are processed without rejection, enabling attackers to poison caches, perform internal network scans, or hijack user sessions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66837 | A file upload vulnerability in ARIS 10.0.23.0.3587512 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PDF file/Malware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66837</link><description>A file upload vulnerability in ARIS 10.0.23.0.3587512 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PDF file/Malware</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22543 | WEEK ENCODING FOR PASSWORDS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22543</link><description>The credentials required to access the device's web server are sent in base64 within the HTTP headers. Since base64 is not considered a strong cipher, an attacker could intercept the web request handling the login and obtain the credentials</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66838 | In Aris v10.0.23.0.3587512 and before, the file upload functionality does not enforce any rate limiting or throttling, allowing users to upl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66838</link><description>In Aris v10.0.23.0.3587512 and before, the file upload functionality does not enforce any rate limiting or throttling, allowing users to upload files at an unrestricted rate. An attacker can exploit this behavior to rapidly upload a large volume of files, potentially leading to resource exhaustion such as disk space depletion, increased server load, or degraded performance</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22542 | DENIAL OF SERVICE FOR CONCURRENT CONNECTIONS ON TELNET</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22542</link><description>An attacker with access to the system's internal network can cause a denial of service on the system by making two concurrent connections through the Telnet service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62327 | HCL DevOps Deploy is susceptible to insufficiently protected credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62327</link><description>In HCL DevOps Deploy 8.1.2.0 through 8.1.2.3, a user with LLM configuration privileges may be able to recover a credential previously saved for performing authenticated LLM Queries.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22541 | DENIAL OF SERVICE VIA ICMP PACKETS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22541</link><description>The massive sending of ICMP requests causes a denial of service on one of the boards from the EVCharger that allows control the EV interfaces. Since the board must be operating correctly for the charger to also function correctly.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49335 | WordPress External Media plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.36 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49335</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in minnur External Media allows Server Side Request Forgery.This issue affects External Media: from n/a through 1.0.36.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22540 | DENIAL OF SERVICE VIA ARP PACKETS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22540</link><description>The massive sending of ARP requests causes a denial of service on one board of the charger that allows control of the EV interfaces. Since the board must be operating correctly for the charger to also function correctly, the denial of service (DoS) results in a restart of the charger functionalities</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15479 | NGSurvey Enterprise 3.6.4 incorrect authorization exposes other users’ API keys and personal data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15479</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS, CWE-79) in the survey content and administration functionality in Data Illusion Zumbrunn NGSurvey Enterprise Edition 3.6.4 on all supported platforms (

on Windows and Linux servers ) allows authenticated remote users with survey creation or edit privileges to execute arbitrary JavaScript in other users’ browsers, steal session information and perform unauthorized actions on their behalf via crafted survey content that is rendered without proper output encoding.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6225 | Command injection in Kieback&amp;amp;Peter Neutrino-GLT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6225</link><description>Kieback&amp;amp;Peter Neutrino-GLT product is used for building management. It's web component "SM70 PHWEB" is vulnerable to shell command injection via login form. The injected commands would execute with low privileges. The vulnerability has been fixed in version 9.40.02</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46494 | WordPress WidgetKit Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 1.13.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46494</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themesgrove WidgetKit Pro allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WidgetKit Pro: from n/a through 1.13.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47552 | WordPress DZS Video Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 12.37 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47552</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Digital zoom studio DZS Video Gallery allows Object Injection.This issue affects DZS Video Gallery: from n/a through 12.37.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32303 | WordPress WPCHURCH plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.0 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32303</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Mojoomla WPCHURCH allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects WPCHURCH: from n/a through 2.7.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:24:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46256 | WordPress Advanced Database Cleaner PRO Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.10 - Limited .txt Path Traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46256</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in SigmaPlugin Advanced Database Cleaner PRO allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Advanced Database Cleaner PRO: from n/a through 3.2.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:24:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46434 | WordPress The Plus Addons for Elementor Pro plugin &amp;lt; 6.3.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46434</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in POSIMYTH Innovation The Plus Addons for Elementor Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects The Plus Addons for Elementor Pro: from n/a before 6.3.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31643 | WordPress WPCHURCH plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.0 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31643</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Dasinfomedia WPCHURCH allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects WPCHURCH: from n/a through 2.7.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32300 | WordPress DZS Video Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 12.25 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32300</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Digital zoom studio DZS Video Gallery allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects DZS Video Gallery: from n/a through 12.25.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69080 | WordPress Gecko theme &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69080</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in JanStudio Gecko allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Gecko: from n/a through 1.9.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69081 | WordPress Hope theme &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69081</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ThemeREX Group Hope charity-is-hope allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Hope: from n/a through 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69082 | WordPress Arlo theme &amp;lt;= 6.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69082</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Frenify Arlo arlo allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Arlo: from n/a through 6.0.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69333 | WordPress JetEngine plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.1.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69333</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Crocoblock JetEngine allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects JetEngine: from n/a through 3.8.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69344 | WordPress Oneline Lite theme &amp;lt;= 6.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69344</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThemeHunk Oneline Lite allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Oneline Lite: from n/a through 6.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68637 | Apache Uniffle: Insecure SSL Configuration in Uniffle HTTP Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68637</link><description>The Uniffle HTTP client is configured to trust all SSL certificates and

disables hostname verification by default. This insecure configuration
exposes all REST API communication between the Uniffle CLI/client and the
Uniffle Coordinator service to potential Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attacks.


This issue affects all versions from before 0.10.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.10.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13418 | Responsive Pricing Table &amp;lt;= 5.1.12 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13418</link><description>The Responsive Pricing Table plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'plan_icons' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13419 | Guest posting / Frontend Posting / Front Editor – WP Front User Submit &amp;lt;= 5.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Media Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13419</link><description>The Guest posting / Frontend Posting / Front Editor – WP Front User Submit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the '/wp-json/bfe/v1/revert' REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary media attachments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13667 | WP Recipe Manager &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;Skill Level&amp;#x27; Input Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13667</link><description>The WP Recipe Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Skill Level' input field in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13694 | AA Block country &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Unauthenticated IP Address Spoofing via X-Forwarded-For Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13694</link><description>The AA Block Country plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP Address Spoofing in versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to the plugin trusting user-supplied headers such as HTTP_X_FORWARDED_FOR to determine the client's IP address without proper validation or considering if the server is behind a trusted proxy. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass IP-based access restrictions by spoofing their IP address via the X-Forwarded-For header.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13722 | Fluent Forms &amp;lt;= 6.1.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Form Creation via AI Builder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13722</link><description>The Fluent Forms – Customizable Contact Forms, Survey, Quiz, &amp; Conversational Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.7. This is due to missing capability checks on the `fluentform_ai_create_form` AJAX action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create arbitrary forms via the publicly exposed AI builder.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13801 | Yoco Payments &amp;lt;= 3.8.8 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13801</link><description>The Yoco Payments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.8 via the file parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13841 | Smart App Banners &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;size&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;verticalalign&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13841</link><description>The Smart App Banners plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'size' and 'verticalalign' parameters of the 'app-store-download' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13847 | PhotoFade &amp;lt;= 0.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13847</link><description>The PhotoFade plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'time' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13848 | STM Gallery 1.9 &amp;lt;= 0.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13848</link><description>The STM Gallery 1.9 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'composicion' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13849 | Cool YT Player &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13849</link><description>The Cool YT Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'videoid' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13887 | AI BotKit &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13887</link><description>The AI BotKit – AI Chatbot &amp; Live Support for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' parameter in the `ai_botkit_widget` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13974 | Email Customizer for WooCommerce | Drag and Drop Email Templates Builder &amp;lt;= 2.6.7 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Email Template Content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13974</link><description>The Email Customizer for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via email template content in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in email templates that will execute when customers view transactional emails. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13990 | Mamurjor Employee Info &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Employee and Related Data Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13990</link><description>The Mamurjor Employee Info plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on multiple administrative functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create, update, or delete employee records, departments, designations, salary grades, education records, and salary payments via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14028 | Contact Us Simple Form &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Plugin Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14028</link><description>The Contact Us Simple Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14053 | Travel Bucket List &amp;lt;= 0.5.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14053</link><description>The Wish To Go plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcode attributes in all versions up to, and including, 0.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14057 | Multi-column Tag Map &amp;lt;= 17.0.39 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;mctm_css_conditional&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14057</link><description>The Multi-column Tag Map plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 17.0.39 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14070 | Reviewify &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary WooCommerce Coupon Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14070</link><description>The Reviewify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'send_test_email' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to create arbitrary WooCommerce discount coupons, potentially causing financial loss to the store.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14077 | Simcast &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14077</link><description>The Simcast plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the settingsPage function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14109 | AH Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;column&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14109</link><description>The AH Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'column' shortcode attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14110 | WP Js List Pages Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 1.21 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;class&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14110</link><description>The WP Js List Pages Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'class' shortcode attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14112 | Snillrik Restaurant &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;menu_style&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14112</link><description>The Snillrik Restaurant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'menu_style' shortcode attribute in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14113 | Viitor Button Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;link&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14113</link><description>The Viitor Button Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'link' shortcode attribute in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14114 | 1180px Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;class&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14114</link><description>The 1180px Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'class' shortcode attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14118 | Starred Review &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via PHP_SELF Variable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14118</link><description>The Starred Review plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the PHP_SELF variable in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14121 | EDD Download Info &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14121</link><description>The EDD Download Info plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'edd_download_info_link' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14122 | AD Sliding FAQ &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14122</link><description>The AD Sliding FAQ plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'sliding_faq' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14127 | Testimonial Master &amp;lt;= 0.2.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14127</link><description>The Testimonial Master plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` variable in all versions up to, and including, 0.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14128 | Stumble! for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14128</link><description>The Stumble! for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` variable in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14130 | Post Like Dislike &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14130</link><description>The Post Like Dislike plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` variable in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14131 | WP Widget Changer &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14131</link><description>The WP Widget Changer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` variable in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14144 | Mstoic Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;start&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14144</link><description>The Mstoic Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'start' parameter of the ms_youtube_embeds shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14145 | Niche Hero | Beautifully-designed blocks in seconds &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;spacing&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14145</link><description>The Niche Hero | Beautifully-designed blocks in seconds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'spacing' parameter of the nh_row shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14147 | Easy GitHub Gist Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;id&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14147</link><description>The Easy GitHub Gist Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' parameter of the gist shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14352 | Awesome Hotel Booking &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Incorrect Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Booking Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14352</link><description>The Awesome Hotel Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to incorrect authorization in the room-single.php shortcode handler in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to the plugin relying solely on nonce verification without capability checks. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify arbitrary booking records by obtaining a nonce from the public booking form.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14453 | My Album Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;style_css&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14453</link><description>The My Album Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'style_css' shortcode attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14460 | Piraeus Bank WooCommerce Payment Gateway &amp;lt;= 3.1.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Order Status Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14460</link><description>The Piraeus Bank WooCommerce Payment Gateway plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized order status modification in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.4. This is due to missing authorization checks on the payment callback endpoint handler when processing the 'fail' callback from the payment gateway. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change any order's status to 'failed' via the publicly accessible WooCommerce API endpoint by providing only the order ID (MerchantReference parameter), which can be easily enumerated as order IDs are sequential integers. This can cause significant business disruption including canceled shipments, inventory issues, and loss of revenue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14465 | Sticky Action Buttons &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14465</link><description>The Sticky Action Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the sabs_options_page_form_submit() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14626 | QR Code for WooCommerce order emails, PDF invoices, packing slips &amp;lt;= 1.9.42 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14626</link><description>The QR Code for WooCommerce order emails, PDF invoices, packing slips plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.42 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14796 | My Album Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Image Title</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14796</link><description>The My Album Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via image titles in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'attachment-&gt;title' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15058 | Responsive Pricing Table &amp;lt;= 5.1.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;table_currency&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15058</link><description>The Responsive Pricing Table plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'table_currency' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11877 | User Activity Log &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Unauthenticated Limited Options Update via Failed Login</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11877</link><description>The User Activity Log plugin is vulnerable to a limited options update in versions up to, and including, 2.2. The failed-login handler 'ual_shook_wp_login_failed' lacks a capability check and writes failed usernames directly into update_option() calls. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to push select site options from 0 to a non-zero value, allowing them to reopen registration or corrupt options like 'wp_user_roles', breaking wp-admin access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12030 | ACF to REST API &amp;lt;= 3.3.4 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Contributor+) ACF Field/Option Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12030</link><description>The ACF to REST API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.4. This is due to insufficient capability checks in the update_item_permissions_check() method, which only verifies that the current user has the edit_posts capability without checking object-specific permissions (e.g., edit_post($id), edit_user($id), manage_options). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to modify ACF fields on posts they do not own, any user account, comments, taxonomy terms, and even the global options page via the /wp-json/acf/v3/{type}/{id} endpoints, granted they can authenticate to the site.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12540 | ShareThis Dashboard for Google Analytics &amp;lt;= 3.2.4 - Unauthenticated Google Analytics Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12540</link><description>The ShareThis Dashboard for Google Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.4. This is due to the Google Analytics client_ID and client_secret being stored in plaintext in the publicly visible plugin source. This can allow unauthenticated attackers to craft a link to the sharethis.com server, which will share an authorization token for Google Analytics with a malicious website, if the attacker can trick an administrator logged into the website and Google Analytics to click the link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12958 | Rankology SEO and Analytics Tool &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Editor+) Header &amp;amp; Footer Code Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12958</link><description>The Rankology SEO and Analytics Tool plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to an incorrect capability check on the 'rankology_code_block' page in all versions up to, and including, 2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to add header and footer code blocks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13493 | Latest Registered Users &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via User Data Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13493</link><description>The Latest Registered Users plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized user data export in all versions up to, and including, 1.4. This is due to missing authorization and nonce validation in the rnd_handle_form_submit function hooked to both admin_post_my_simple_form and admin_post_nopriv_my_simple_form actions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export complete user details (excluding passwords and sensitive tokens) in CSV format via the 'action' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13496 | Moosend Landing Pages &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Option Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13496</link><description>The Moosend Landing Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the moosend_landings_auth_get function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete the 'moosend_landing_api_key' option value.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13497 | Recras WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;recrasname&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13497</link><description>The Recras WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'recrasname' shortcode attribute in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13519 | SVG Map Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update and Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13519</link><description>The SVG Map Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on multiple AJAX actions including 'save_data', 'delete_data', and 'add_popup'. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings, delete map data, and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13520 | MTCaptcha WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13520</link><description>The MTCaptcha WordPress Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the settings update functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin settings, including sensitive values like the private key, via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13521 | WP Status Notifier &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13521</link><description>The WP Status Notifier plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the settings update functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13527 | xShare &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to &amp;#x27;rs_plugin_reset&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13527</link><description>The xShare plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to missing nonce validation on the 'xshare_plugin_reset()' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13529 | Unify &amp;lt;= 3.4.9 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Option Deletion via &amp;#x27;unify_plugin_downgrade&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13529</link><description>The Unify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'init' action in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete specific plugin options via the 'unify_plugin_downgrade' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13531 | Stylish Order Form Builder &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;product_name&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13531</link><description>The Stylish Order Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'product_name' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:29:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14999 | Latest Tabs &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin&amp;#x27;s Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14999</link><description>The Latest Tabs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.5. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the settings update handler in admin-page.php. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:29:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15000 | Page Keys &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;page_key&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15000</link><description>The Page Keys plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘page_key’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:29:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15018 | Optional Email &amp;lt;= 1.3.11 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15018</link><description>The Optional Email plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.11. This is due to the plugin not restricting its 'random_password' filter to registration contexts, allowing the filter to affect password reset key generation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to set a known password reset key when initiating a password reset, reset the password of any user including administrators, and gain access to their accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15158 | WP Enable WebP &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15158</link><description>The WP Enable WebP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to improper file type validation in the 'wpse_file_and_ext_webp' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 08:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0980 | JSON RPC authentication bypass in Nokia SR Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0980</link><description>Nokia SR Linux is vulnerable to an authentication vulnerability allowing unauthorized access to the JSON-RPC service.  When exploited, an invalid validation allows JSON RPC access without providing valid authentication credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 07:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12449 | aBlocks – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12449</link><description>The aBlocks – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and disclosure of sensitive information due to missing capability checks on multiple AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to read plugin settings including block visibility, maintenance mode configuration, and third-party email marketing API keys, as well as read sensitive configuration data including API keys for email marketing services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 07:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13369 | Premmerce WooCommerce Customers Manager &amp;lt;= 1.1.14 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13369</link><description>The Premmerce WooCommerce Customers Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'money_spent_from', 'money_spent_to', 'registered_from', and 'registered_to' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick an administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 07:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14792 | Key Figures &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via kf_field_figure_default_color_render</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14792</link><description>The Key Figures plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the kf_field_figure_default_color_render function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 07:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14802 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.2.2 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Instructor+) Teacher Material Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14802</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized file deletion in versions up to, and including, 4.3.2.2 via the /wp-json/lp/v1/material/{file_id} REST API endpoint. This is due to a parameter mismatch between the DELETE operation and authorization check, where the endpoint uses file_id from the URL path but the permission callback validates item_id from the request body. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with teacher-level access, to delete arbitrary lesson material files uploaded by other teachers via sending a DELETE request with their own item_id (to pass authorization) while targeting another teacher's file_id.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 07:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31964 | HCL BigFix IVR is impacted by an improper service binding configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31964</link><description>Improper service binding configuration in internal service components in HCL BigFix IVR version 4.2 allows a privileged attacker to impact service availability via exposure of administrative services bound to external network interfaces instead of the local authentication interface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 07:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31963 | HCL BigFix IVR is impacted by improper authentication and missing CSRF protection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31963</link><description>Improper authentication and missing CSRF protection in the local setup interface component in HCL BigFix IVR version 4.2 allows a local attacker to perform unauthorized configuration changes via unauthenticated administrative configuration requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 07:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31962 | HCL BigFix IVR is impacted by an insufficient session expiration vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31962</link><description>Insufficient session expiration in the Web UI authentication component in HCL BigFix IVR version 4.2 allows an authenticated attacker to gain prolonged unauthorized access to protected API endpoints due to excessive expiration periods.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13371 | Money Space &amp;lt;= 2.13.9 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13371</link><description>The MoneySpace plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.13.9. This is due to the plugin storing full payment card details (PAN, card holder name, expiry month/year, and CVV) in WordPress post_meta using base64_encode(), and then embedding these values into the publicly accessible mspaylink page's inline JavaScript without any authentication or authorization check. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers who know or can guess an order_id to access the mspaylink endpoint and retrieve full credit card numbers and CVV codes directly from the HTML/JS response, constituting a severe PCI-DSS violation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13657 | HelpDesk contact form plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update via handle_query_args</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13657</link><description>The HelpDesk contact form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.5. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the handle_query_args() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's license ID and contact form ID settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14370 | Quote Comments &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14370</link><description>The Quote Comments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This is due to missing authorization checks in the quotecomments_add_admin function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary plugin options via the 'action' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14842 | Drag and Drop Multiple File Upload – Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 1.3.9.2 - Unauthenticated Limited Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14842</link><description>The Drag and Drop Multiple File Upload – Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to limited upload of files with a dangerous type in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.9.2. This is due to the plugin not blocking .phar and .svg files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary .phar or .svg files containing malicious PHP or JavaScript code. Malicious PHP code can be used to achieve remote code execution on the server via direct file access, if the server is configured to execute .phar files as PHP. The upload of .svg files allows for Stored Cross-Site Scripting under certain circumstances.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14845 | NS IE Compatibility Fixer &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14845</link><description>The NS IE Compatibility Fixer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.5. This is due to missing nonce validation on the settings update functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick an administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14867 | Flashcard Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 0.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Read via Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14867</link><description>The Flashcard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 0.9 via the 'source' attribute of the 'flashcard' shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14875 | HBLPAY Payment Gateway for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;cusdata&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14875</link><description>The HBLPAY Payment Gateway for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘cusdata’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14887 | twinklesmtp – Email Service Provider For WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.03 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Sender Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14887</link><description>The twinklesmtp – Email Service Provider For WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via plugin's sender settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.03 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14888 | Simple User Meta Editor &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via User Meta Value Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14888</link><description>The Simple User Meta Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the user meta value field in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14901 | Bit Form – Contact Form Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.21.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Workflow Replay</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14901</link><description>The Bit Form – Contact Form Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized workflow execution due to missing authorization in the triggerWorkFlow function in all versions up to, and including, 2.21.6. This is due to a logic flaw in the nonce verification where the security check only blocks requests when both the nonce verification fails and the user is logged in. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to replay form workflow executions and trigger all configured integrations including webhooks, email notifications, CRM integrations, and automation platforms via the bitforms_trigger_workflow AJAX action granted they can obtain the entry ID and log IDs from a legitimate form submission response.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14904 | Newsletter Email Subscribe &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14904</link><description>The Newsletter Email Subscribe plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 2.4. This is due to incorrect nonce validation on the nels_settings_page function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0656 | iPaymu Payment Gateway for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Missing Authentication to Unauthenticated Payment Bypass and Order Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0656</link><description>The iPaymu Payment Gateway for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authentication in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.2 via the 'check_ipaymu_response' function. This is due to the plugin not validating webhook request authenticity through signature verification or origin checks. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to mark WooCommerce orders as paid by sending crafted POST requests to the webhook endpoint without any payment occurring, as well as enumerate order IDs and obtain valid order keys via GET requests, exposing customer order PII including names, addresses, and purchased products.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14719 | Relevanssi (Free &amp;lt; 4.26.0, Premium &amp;lt; 2.29.0) - Contributor+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14719</link><description>The Relevanssi  WordPress plugin before 4.26.0, Relevanssi Premium WordPress plugin before 2.29.0 do not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing contributor and above roles to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14804 | Frontend File Manager &amp;lt; 23.5 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14804</link><description>The Frontend File Manager Plugin WordPress plugin before 23.5 did not validate a path parameter and ownership of the file, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscribers to delete arbitrary files on the server</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14835 | WP Photo Album Plus &amp;lt;= 9.1.05.008 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14835</link><description>The WP Photo Album Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘shortcode’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 9.1.05.008 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 05:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14468 | AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Comment Submission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14468</link><description>The AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.1.9. This is due to inverted nonce verification logic in the amp_theme_ajaxcomments AJAX handler, which rejects requests with VALID nonces and accepts requests with MISSING or INVALID nonces. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to submit comments on behalf of logged-in users via a forged request granted they can trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link, and the plugin's template mode is enabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15474 | AuntyFey Smart Combination Lock BLE Connection Flood DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15474</link><description>AuntyFey Smart Combination Lock firmware versions as of 2025-12-24 contain a vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker within Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) range to cause a denial of service by repeatedly initiating BLE connections. Sustained connection attempts interrupt keypad authentication input and repeatedly force the device into lockout states, preventing legitimate users from unlocking the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0650 | OpenFlagr &amp;lt;= 1.1.18 Authentication Bypass via Prefix Whitelist Path Normalization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0650</link><description>OpenFlagr versions prior to and including 1.1.18 contain an authentication bypass vulnerability in the HTTP middleware. Due to improper handling of path normalization in the whitelist logic, crafted requests can bypass authentication and access protected API endpoints without valid credentials. Unauthorized access may allow modification of feature flags and export of sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9611 | Microsoft Playwright MCP Server &amp;lt; 0.0.40 DNS Rebinding via Missing Origin Header Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9611</link><description>Microsoft Playwright MCP Server versions prior to 0.0.40 fails to validate the Origin header on incoming connections. This allows an attacker to perform a DNS rebinding attack via a victim’s web browser and send unauthorized requests to a locally running MCP server, resulting in unintended invocation of MCP tool endpoints.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14059 | EmailKit &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Read via Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14059</link><description>The EmailKit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read via Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.1. This is due to missing path validation in the create_template REST API endpoint where user-controlled input from the emailkit-editor-template parameter is passed directly to file_get_contents() without sanitization. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with Author-level permissions or higher to read arbitrary files on the server, including sensitive configuration files like /etc/passwd and wp-config.php, via the REST API. The file contents are stored in post meta and can be exfiltrated through MetForm's email confirmation feature.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14891 | Customer Reviews for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.93.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via displayName Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14891</link><description>The Customer Reviews for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'displayName' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.93.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with customer-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. While it is possible to invoke the AJAX action without authentication, the attacker would need to know a valid form ID, which requires them to place an order. This vulnerability can be exploited by unauthenticated attackers if guest checkout is enabled. However, the form ID still needs to be obtained through placing an order.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20893 | Origin validation error issue exists in Fujitsu Security Solution AuthConductor Client Basic V2 2.0.25.0 and earlier. If this vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20893</link><description>Origin validation error issue exists in Fujitsu Security Solution AuthConductor Client Basic V2 2.0.25.0 and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, an attacker who can log in to the Windows system where the affected product is installed may execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privilege and/or modify the registry value.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12648 | WP-Members Membership Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.4.4 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure via Unprotected Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12648</link><description>The WP-Members Membership Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized file access in versions up to, and including, 3.5.4.4. This is due to storing user-uploaded files in predictable directories (wp-content/uploads/wpmembers/user_files//) without implementing proper access controls beyond basic directory listing protection (.htaccess with Options -Indexes). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to directly access and download sensitive documents uploaded by site users via direct URL access, granted they can guess or enumerate user IDs and filenames.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 03:05:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14631 | Null Pointer Dereference Vulnerability in Malformed 802.11 Frame of TP-Link Archer BE400</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14631</link><description>A NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in TP-Link Archer BE400 V1(802.11 modules) allows 

an adjacent attacker to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) by triggering a device reboot.

This issue affects Archer BE400: xi 1.1.0 Build 20250710 rel.14914.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0649 | invoiceninja Migration Import Import.php copy server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0649</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in invoiceninja up to 5.12.38. The affected element is the function copy of the file /app/Jobs/Util/Import.php of the component Migration Import. The manipulation of the argument company_logo leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-14020 | carboneio carbone Formatter input.js prototype pollution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-14020</link><description>A weakness has been identified in carboneio carbone up to fbcd349077ad0e8748be73eab2a82ea92b6f8a7e. This impacts an unknown function of the file lib/input.js of the component Formatter Handler. Executing a manipulation can lead to improperly controlled modification of object prototype attributes. The attack can be launched remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is said to be difficult. Upgrading to version 3.5.6 will fix this issue. This patch is called 04f9feb24bfca23567706392f9ad2c53bbe4134e. You should upgrade the affected component. A successful exploitation can "only occur if the parent NodeJS application has the same security issue".</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0628 | Insufficient policy enforcement in WebView tag in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.192 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0628</link><description>Insufficient policy enforcement in WebView tag in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.192 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a malicious extension to inject scripts or HTML into a privileged page via a crafted Chrome Extension. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:11:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0643 | projectworlds House Rental and Property Listing Signup register.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0643</link><description>A flaw has been found in projectworlds House Rental and Property Listing 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /app/register.php?action=reg of the component Signup. This manipulation of the argument image causes unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:46:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47330 | Buffer Over-read in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47330</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing video packets received from the video firmware.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47331 | Buffer Over-read in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47331</link><description>Information disclosure while processing a firmware event.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47332 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47332</link><description>Memory corruption while processing a config call from userspace.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47333 | Use After Free in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47333</link><description>Memory corruption while handling buffer mapping operations in the cryptographic driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47334 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47334</link><description>Memory corruption while processing shared command buffer packet between camera userspace and kernel.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47335 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47335</link><description>Memory corruption while parsing clock configuration data for a specific hardware type.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47336 | Use After Free in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47336</link><description>Memory corruption while performing sensor register read operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47337 | Use After Free in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47337</link><description>Memory corruption while accessing a synchronization object during concurrent operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47339 | Use After Free in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47339</link><description>Memory corruption while deinitializing a HDCP session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47343 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47343</link><description>Memory corruption while processing a video session to set video parameters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47344 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47344</link><description>Memory corruption while handling sensor utility operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47345 | Reusing a Nonce, Key Pair in Encryption in Automotive Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47345</link><description>Cryptographic issue may occur while encrypting license data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47346 | Out-of-bounds Write in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47346</link><description>Memory corruption while processing a secure logging command in the trusted application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47348 | Use of Uninitialized Variable in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47348</link><description>Memory corruption while processing identity credential operations in the trusted application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:55:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47356 | Double Free in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47356</link><description>Memory Corruption when multiple threads concurrently access and modify shared resources.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:55:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47369 | Information Exposure in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47369</link><description>Information disclosure when a weak hashed value is returned to userland code in response to a IOCTL call to obtain a session ID.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:55:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47380 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47380</link><description>Memory corruption while preprocessing IOCTLs in sensors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47388 | Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47388</link><description>Memory corruption while passing pages to DSP with an unaligned starting address.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47393 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Automotive Linux OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47393</link><description>Memory corruption when accessing resources in kernel driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47394 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47394</link><description>Memory corruption when copying overlapping buffers during memory operations due to incorrect offset calculations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47395 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47395</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing a WLAN management frame with a Vendor Specific Information Element.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47396 | Double Free in Graphics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47396</link><description>Memory corruption occurs when a secure application is launched on a device with insufficient memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0642 | projectworlds House Rental and Property Listing complaint.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0642</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in projectworlds House Rental and Property Listing 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /app/complaint.php. The manipulation of the argument Name results in cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11235 | MOVEit Transfer REST API does not require current password in order to initiate the password change process</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11235</link><description>Unverified Password Change vulnerability in Progress MOVEit Transfer on Windows (REST API modules).This issue affects MOVEit Transfer: from 2023.1.0 before 2023.1.3, from 2023.0.0 before 2023.0.8, from 2022.1.0 before 2022.1.11, from 2022.0.0 before 2022.0.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15472 | TRENDnet TEW-811DRU httpd  uapply.cgi setDeviceURL  os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15472</link><description>A flaw has been found in TRENDnet TEW-811DRU 1.0.2.0. This affects the function setDeviceURL  of the file uapply.cgi of the component httpd . This manipulation of the argument DeviceURL causes os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14614 | Quartus® Prime Standard and Quartus® Prime Lite Security Advisory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14614</link><description>Insecure Temporary File vulnerability in Altera Quartus Prime Standard 

Installer (SFX)

 on Windows, Altera Quartus Prime Lite 

Installer (SFX)

 on Windows allows Explore for Predictable Temporary File Names.This issue affects Quartus Prime Standard: from 23.1 through 24.1; Quartus Prime Lite: from 23.1 through 24.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14625 | Quartus® Prime Standard and Quartus® Prime Lite Security Advisory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14625</link><description>Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability in Altera Quartus Prime Standard on Windows (Nios II Command Shell modules), Altera Quartus Prime Lite on Windows (Nios II Command Shell modules) allows Search Order Hijacking.This issue affects Quartus Prime Standard: from 19.1 through 24.1; Quartus Prime Lite: from 19.1 through 24.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14599 | Quartus® Prime Standard and Quartus® Prime Lite Security Advisory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14599</link><description>Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability in Altera Quartus Prime Standard 

Installer (SFX)

on Windows, Altera Quartus Prime Lite 

Installer (SFX)

 on Windows allows Search Order Hijacking.This issue affects Quartus Prime Standard: from 23.1 through 24.1; Quartus Prime Lite: from 23.1 through 24.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15471 | TRENDnet TEW-713RE formFSrvX os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15471</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in TRENDnet TEW-713RE 1.02. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /goformX/formFSrvX. The manipulation of the argument SZCMD results in os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14605 | Quartus Prime Pro Edition Advisory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14605</link><description>Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability in Altera Quartus Prime Pro on Windows (System Console modules) allows Search Order Hijacking.This issue affects Quartus Prime Pro: from 17.0 through 25.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14612 | Quartus Prime Pro Edition Advisory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14612</link><description>Insecure Temporary File vulnerability in Altera Quartus Prime Pro 

Installer (SFX)

 on Windows allows : Use of Predictable File Names.This issue affects Quartus Prime Pro: from 24.1 through 25.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14596 | Quartus Prime Pro Edition Installer Advisory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14596</link><description>Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability in Altera Quartus Prime Pro 

Installer (SFX) 

on Windows allows Search Order Hijacking.This issue affects Quartus Prime Pro: from 24.1 through 24.3.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31051 | WordPress Plant - Gardening &amp;amp; Houseplants WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31051</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in EngoTheme Plant - Gardening &amp; Houseplants WordPress Theme allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Plant - Gardening &amp; Houseplants WordPress Theme: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31642 | WordPress WPCHURCH plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31642</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dasinfomedia WPCHURCH allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WPCHURCH: from n/a through 2.7.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30996 | Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability in WordPress themes by Themify</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30996</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Themify Themify Sidepane WordPress Theme, Themify Themify Newsy, Themify Themify Folo, Themify Themify Edmin, Themify Bloggie, Themify Photobox, Themify Wigi, Themify Rezo, Themify Slide allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Themify Sidepane WordPress Theme: from n/a through 1.9.8; Themify Newsy: from n/a through 1.9.9; Themify Folo: from n/a through 1.9.6; Themify Edmin: from n/a through 2.0.0; Bloggie: from n/a through 2.0.8; Photobox: from n/a through 2.0.1; Wigi: from n/a through 2.0.1; Rezo: from n/a through 1.9.7; Slide: from n/a through 1.7.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:01:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13744 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed rendering of malicious HTML</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13744</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed attacker controlled HTML to be rendered by the Filter component (search) across GitHub that could be used to exfiltrate sensitive information. An attacker would require permissions to create or modify the names of milestones, issues, pull requests, or similar entities that are rendered in the vulnerable filter/search components. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.20 and was fixed in versions 3.19.1, and 3.18.2, 3.17.8, 3.16.11, 3.15.15, and 3.14.20. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29004 | Privilege Escalation Vulnerability in AA-Team WordPress plugins</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29004</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in AA-Team Premium Age Verification / Restriction for WordPress, AA-Team Responsive Coming Soon Landing Page / Holding Page for WordPress allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Premium Age Verification / Restriction for WordPress: from n/a through 3.0.2; Responsive Coming Soon Landing Page / Holding Page for WordPress: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30631 | Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in AA-Team WordPress plugins</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30631</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AA-Team Woocommerce Sales Funnel Builder, AA-Team Amazon Affiliates Addon for WPBakery Page Builder (formerly Visual Composer) allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Woocommerce Sales Funnel Builder: from n/a through 1.1; Amazon Affiliates Addon for WPBakery Page Builder (formerly Visual Composer): from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21492 | iccDEV ToneMap Writer has NULL Pointer Member Call</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21492</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. Versions prior to 2.3.1.2 have a NULL pointer member call vulnerability. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7048 | On affected platforms running Arista EOS with MACsec configuration, a specially crafted packet can cause the MACsec process to terminate unexpectedly. Continuous receipt of these packets with certain MACsec configurations can cause longer term disruption o</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7048</link><description>On affected platforms running Arista EOS with MACsec configuration, a specially crafted packet can cause the MACsec process to terminate unexpectedly. Continuous receipt of these packets with certain MACsec configurations can cause longer term disruption of dataplane traffic.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21490 | iccDEV has heap buffer overflow in CIccTagLut16::Validate()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21490</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. A vulnerability present in versions prior to 2.3.1.2 affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. It results in heap buffer overflow in `CIccTagLut16::Validate()`. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21491 | iccDEV has unicode buffer overflow in CIccTagTextDescription</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21491</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. A vulnerability present in versions prior to 2.3.1.2 affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. It results in unicode buffer overflow in `CIccTagTextDescription`. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0641 | TOTOLINK WA300 cstecgi.cgi sub_401510 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0641</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in TOTOLINK WA300 5.2cu.7112_B20190227. This vulnerability affects the function sub_401510 of the file cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument UPLOAD_FILENAME leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21494 | iccDEV has heap buffer overflow in CIccTagLut8::Validate()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21494</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of International Color Consortium (ICC) color management profiles. A vulnerability present in versions prior to 2.3.1.2 affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. It results in heap buffer overflow in `CIccTagLut8::Validate()`. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15382 | Client SCP Request Triggers Buffer Overread by 1 Byte</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15382</link><description>A heap buffer over-read vulnerability exists in the wolfSSH_CleanPath() function in wolfSSH. An authenticated remote attacker can trigger the issue via crafted SCP path input containing '/./' sequences, resulting in a heap over read by 1 byte.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32304 | WordPress WPCHURCH plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32304</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Mojoomla WPCHURCH allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects WPCHURCH: from n/a through 2.7.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14942 | Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14942</link><description>wolfSSH’s key exchange state machine can be manipulated to leak the client’s password in the clear, trick the client to send a bogus signature, or trick the client into skipping user authentication. This affects client applications with wolfSSH version 1.4.21 and earlier. Users of wolfSSH must update or apply the fix patch and it’s recommended to update credentials used. This fix is also recommended for wolfSSH server applications. While there aren’t any specific attacks on server applications, the same defect is present. Thanks to Aina Toky Rasoamanana of Valeo and Olivier Levillain of Telecom SudParis for the report.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39477 | WordPress InWave Jobs Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39477</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Sfwebservice InWave Jobs allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects InWave Jobs: from n/a through 3.5.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30547 | WordPress Header Image Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30547</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Shazdeh Header Image Slider header-image-slider allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Header Image Slider: from n/a through 0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31088 | WordPress AdsPlace&amp;#x27;r – Ad Manager, Inserter, AdSense Ads plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31088</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPShop.Ru AdsPlace'r – Ad Manager, Inserter, AdSense Ads allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects AdsPlace'r – Ad Manager, Inserter, AdSense Ads: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47553 | WordPress DZS Video Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 12.25 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47553</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Digital zoom studio DZS Video Gallery allows Object Injection.This issue affects DZS Video Gallery: from n/a through 12.25.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69083 | WordPress Frappé theme &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69083</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Elated-Themes Frappé allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Frappé: from n/a through 1.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69084 | WordPress Photo Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.7.26 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69084</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GT3 themes Photo Gallery allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Photo Gallery: from n/a through 2.7.7.26.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69085 | WordPress JobBank plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69085</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in e-plugins JobBank allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects JobBank: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69086 | WordPress Issabella theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69086</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Jwsthemes Issabella allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Issabella: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69327 | WordPress Car Rental Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69327</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in magepeopleteam Car Rental Manager car-rental-manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Car Rental Manager: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69331 | WordPress Theater for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 0.19 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69331</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jeroen Schmit Theater for WordPress theatre allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Theater for WordPress: from n/a through &lt;= 0.19.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69334 | WordPress Wishlist for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69334</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPFactory Wishlist for WooCommerce wish-list-for-woocommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Wishlist for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 3.3.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69335 | WordPress Team Showcase plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69335</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themepoints Team Showcase team-showcase allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Team Showcase: from n/a through &lt;= 2.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69336 | WordPress Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69336</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in bdthemes Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons ultimate-store-kit allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons: from n/a through &lt;= 2.9.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69341 | WordPress WeDesignTech Ultimate Booking Addon plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69341</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BuddhaThemes WeDesignTech Ultimate Booking Addon wedesigntech-ultimate-booking-addon allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WeDesignTech Ultimate Booking Addon: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69342 | WordPress Calafate theme &amp;lt;= 1.7.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69342</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in VanKarWai Calafate calafate allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Calafate: from n/a through &lt;= 1.7.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69345 | WordPress Post and Page Builder by BoldGrid plugin &amp;lt;= 1.27.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69345</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BoldGrid Post and Page Builder by BoldGrid post-and-page-builder allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Post and Page Builder by BoldGrid: from n/a through &lt;= 1.27.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69346 | WordPress AffiliateX plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.9.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69346</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPCenter AffiliateX affiliatex allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects AffiliateX: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.9.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69348 | WordPress The Events Calendar Countdown Addon plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.15 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69348</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CoolHappy The Events Calendar Countdown Addon countdown-for-the-events-calendar allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects The Events Calendar Countdown Addon: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.15.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69349 | WordPress RSS Feed Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69349</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Fahad Mahmood RSS Feed Widget rss-feed-widget allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects RSS Feed Widget: from n/a through &lt;= 3.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69350 | WordPress Accordion plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69350</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themepoints Accordion accordions-wp allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Accordion: from n/a through &lt;= 3.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69351 | WordPress Ninja Tables plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69351</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Shahjahan Jewel Ninja Tables ninja-tables allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Ninja Tables: from n/a through &lt;= 5.2.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69352 | WordPress The Events Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 6.15.12.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69352</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in StellarWP The Events Calendar the-events-calendar allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects The Events Calendar: from n/a through &lt;= 6.15.12.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69353 | WordPress Proxy &amp;amp; VPN Blocker plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69353</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Proxy &amp;amp; VPN Blocker Proxy &amp;amp; VPN Blocker proxy-vpn-blocker allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Proxy &amp;amp; VPN Blocker: from n/a through &lt;= 3.5.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69354 | WordPress Better Business Reviews plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69354</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BBR Plugins Better Business Reviews better-business-reviews allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Better Business Reviews: from n/a through &lt;= 0.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69355 | WordPress Tickera plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.6.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69355</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tickera Tickera tickera-event-ticketing-system allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Tickera: from n/a through &lt;= 3.5.6.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69356 | WordPress TheGem Theme Elements (for Elementor) plugin &amp;lt;= 5.11.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69356</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in CodexThemes TheGem Theme Elements (for Elementor) thegem-elements-elementor allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects TheGem Theme Elements (for Elementor): from n/a through &lt;= 5.11.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69357 | WordPress TheGem Theme Elements (for Elementor) plugin &amp;lt;= 5.11.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69357</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodexThemes TheGem Theme Elements (for Elementor) thegem-elements-elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects TheGem Theme Elements (for Elementor): from n/a through &lt;= 5.11.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69359 | WordPress Creator LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.12 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69359</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPFunnels Creator LMS creatorlms allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Creator LMS: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.12.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69360 | WordPress TheGem Theme Elements (for WPBakery) plugin &amp;lt;= 5.11.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69360</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodexThemes TheGem Theme Elements (for WPBakery) thegem-elements allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects TheGem Theme Elements (for WPBakery): from n/a through &lt;= 5.11.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69361 | WordPress Post Expirator plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69361</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in PublishPress Post Expirator post-expirator allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Post Expirator: from n/a through &lt;= 4.9.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69362 | WordPress UiChemy plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69362</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in POSIMYTH UiChemy uichemy allows Stored XSS.This issue affects UiChemy: from n/a through &lt;= 4.4.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69363 | WordPress Responsive Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69363</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CyberChimps Responsive Addons for Elementor responsive-addons-for-elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Responsive Addons for Elementor: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69364 | WordPress Breeze plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.21 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69364</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Cloudways Breeze breeze allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Breeze: from n/a through &lt;= 2.2.21.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36589 | Dell Unisphere for PowerMax, version(s) 9.2.4.x, contain(s) an Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability. A low pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36589</link><description>Dell Unisphere for PowerMax, version(s) 9.2.4.x, contain(s) an Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to unauthorized access to data and resources outside of the intended sphere of control.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60534 | Blue Access Cobalt v02.000.195 suffers from an authentication bypass vulnerability, which allows an attacker to selectively proxy requests i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60534</link><description>Blue Access Cobalt v02.000.195 suffers from an authentication bypass vulnerability, which allows an attacker to selectively proxy requests in order to operate functionality on the web application without the need to authenticate with legitimate credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63082 | Joomla! Core - [20260101] - Inadequate content filtering for data URLs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63082</link><description>Lack of input filtering leads to an XSS vector in the HTML filter code related to data URLs in img tags.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63083 | Joomla! Core - [20260102] - XSS vector in the pagebreak plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63083</link><description>Lack of output escaping leads to a XSS vector in the pagebreak plugin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59379 | DwyerOmega Isensix Advanced Remote Monitoring System (ARMS) 1.5.7 allows an attacker to retrieve sensitive information from the underlying S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59379</link><description>DwyerOmega Isensix Advanced Remote Monitoring System (ARMS) 1.5.7 allows an attacker to retrieve sensitive information from the underlying SQL database via Blind SQL Injection through the user parameter in the login page. This allows an attacker to steal credentials, which may be cleartext, from existing users (and admins) and use them to authenticate to the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36905 | FIBARO System Home Center 5.021 Remote File Inclusion via Proxy API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36905</link><description>FIBARO System Home Center 5.021 contains a remote file inclusion vulnerability in the undocumented proxy API that allows attackers to include arbitrary client-side scripts. Attackers can exploit the 'url' GET parameter to inject malicious JavaScript and potentially hijack user sessions or manipulate page content.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36906 | P5 FNIP-8x16A FNIP-4xSH 1.0.20 Cross-Site Request Forgery via User Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36906</link><description>P5 FNIP-8x16A FNIP-4xSH 1.0.20 contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability that allows attackers to perform administrative actions without user consent. Attackers can craft malicious web pages to add new admin users, change passwords, and modify system configurations by tricking authenticated users into loading a specially crafted form.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36907 | Extreme Networks Aerohive HiveOS &amp;lt;=11.x 11.x Unauthenticated Remote Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36907</link><description>Aerohive HiveOS contains a denial of service vulnerability in the NetConfig UI that allows unauthenticated attackers to render the web interface unusable. Attackers can send a crafted HTTP request to the action.php5 script with specific parameters to trigger a 5-minute service disruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36908 | Secure Computing SnapGear Management Console SG560 3.1.5 Cross-Site Request Forgery via Admin Users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36908</link><description>SnapGear Management Console SG560 version 3.1.5 contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability that allows attackers to perform administrative actions without user consent. Attackers can craft a malicious web page that automatically submits a form to create a new super user account with full administrative privileges when a logged-in user visits the page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36909 | Secure Computing SnapGear Management Console SG560 3.1.5 Arbitrary File Read/Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36909</link><description>SnapGear Management Console SG560 3.1.5 contains a file manipulation vulnerability that allows authenticated users to read, write, and delete files using the edit_config_files CGI script. Attackers can manipulate POST request parameters in /cgi-bin/cgix/edit_config_files to access and modify files outside the intended /etc/config/ directory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36910 | Cayin Signage Media Player 3.0 Authenticated Remote Command Injection via NTP Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36910</link><description>Cayin Signage Media Player 3.0 contains an authenticated remote command injection vulnerability in system.cgi and wizard_system.cgi pages. Attackers can exploit the 'NTP_Server_IP' parameter with default credentials to execute arbitrary shell commands as root.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36912 | Plexus anblick Digital Signage Management 3.1.13 Open Redirect via Pagina Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36912</link><description>Plexus anblick Digital Signage Management 3.1.13 contains an open redirect vulnerability in the 'PantallaLogin' script that allows attackers to manipulate the 'pagina' GET parameter. Attackers can craft malicious links that redirect users to arbitrary websites by exploiting improper input validation in the parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36913 | All-Dynamics Software enlogic:show 2.0.2 Session Fixation Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36913</link><description>All-Dynamics Software enlogic:show 2.0.2 contains a session fixation vulnerability that allows attackers to set a predefined PHP session identifier during the login process. Attackers can forge HTTP GET requests to welcome.php with a manipulated session token to bypass authentication and potentially execute cross-site request forgery attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36914 | QiHang Media Web Digital Signage 3.0.9 Cookie Authentication Credentials Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36914</link><description>QiHang Media Web Digital Signage 3.0.9 contains a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability that allows remote attackers to intercept user authentication credentials through cleartext cookie transmission. Attackers can perform man-in-the-middle attacks to capture and potentially misuse stored authentication credentials transmitted in an insecure manner.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36915 | Adtec Digital SignEdje Digital Signage Player v2.08.28 Default Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36915</link><description>Adtec Digital SignEdje Digital Signage Player v2.08.28 contains multiple hardcoded default credentials that allow unauthenticated remote access to web, telnet, and SSH interfaces. Attackers can exploit these credentials to gain root-level access and execute system commands across multiple Adtec Digital product versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36916 | TDM Digital Signage PC Player 4.1.0.4 Privilege Escalation via Insecure Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36916</link><description>TDM Digital Signage PC Player 4.1.0.4 contains an elevation of privileges vulnerability that allows authenticated users to modify executable files. Attackers can leverage the 'Modify' permissions for authenticated users to replace executable files with malicious binaries and gain elevated system access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36917 | iDS6 DSSPro Digital Signage System 6.2 Cleartext Password Disclosure via Cookie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36917</link><description>iDS6 DSSPro Digital Signage System 6.2 contains a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability that allows remote attackers to intercept authentication credentials through cleartext cookie transmission. Attackers can exploit the autoSave feature to capture user passwords during man-in-the-middle attacks on HTTP communications.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36918 | iDS6 DSSPro Digital Signage System 6.2 Cross-Site Request Forgery via User Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36918</link><description>iDS6 DSSPro Digital Signage System 6.2 contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability that allows attackers to perform administrative actions without request validation. Attackers can craft malicious web pages to trick logged-in administrators into adding unauthorized users by exploiting the lack of CSRF protections.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36920 | iDS6 DSSPro Digital Signage System 6.2 Privilege Escalation via Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36920</link><description>iDS6 DSSPro Digital Signage System 6.2 contains an improper access control vulnerability that allows authenticated users to elevate privileges through console JavaScript functions. Attackers can create users, modify roles and permissions, and potentially achieve full application takeover by exploiting insecure direct object references.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36921 | RED-V Super Digital Signage System 5.1.1 Log Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36921</link><description>RED-V Super Digital Signage System 5.1.1 contains an information disclosure vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to access sensitive webserver log files. Attackers can visit multiple endpoints to retrieve system resources and debug log information without authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36922 | Sony BRAVIA Digital Signage 1.7.8 Unauthenticated System API Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36922</link><description>Sony BRAVIA Digital Signage 1.7.8 contains an information disclosure vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to access sensitive system details through API endpoints. Attackers can retrieve network interface information, server configurations, and system metadata by sending requests to the exposed system API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36923 | Sony BRAVIA Digital Signage 1.7.8 Client-Side Protection Bypass via IDOR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36923</link><description>Sony BRAVIA Digital Signage 1.7.8 contains an insecure direct object reference vulnerability that allows attackers to bypass authorization controls. Attackers can access hidden system resources like '/#/content-creation' by manipulating client-side access restrictions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36924 | Sony BRAVIA Digital Signage 1.7.8 Unauthenticated Remote File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36924</link><description>Sony BRAVIA Digital Signage 1.7.8 contains a remote file inclusion vulnerability that allows attackers to inject arbitrary client-side scripts through the content material URL parameter. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability to hijack user sessions, execute cross-site scripting code, and modify display content by manipulating the input material type.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36925 | Arteco Web Client DVR/NVR Session ID Brute Force Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36925</link><description>Arteco Web Client DVR/NVR contains a session hijacking vulnerability with insufficient session ID complexity that allows remote attackers to bypass authentication. Attackers can brute force session IDs within a specific numeric range to obtain valid sessions and access live camera streams without authorization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65212 | An issue was discovered in NJHYST HY511 POE core before 2.1 and plugins before 0.1. The vulnerability stems from the device's insufficient c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65212</link><description>An issue was discovered in NJHYST HY511 POE core before 2.1 and plugins before 0.1. The vulnerability stems from the device's insufficient cookie verification, allowing an attacker to directly request the configuration file address and download the core configuration file without logging into the device management backend. By reading the corresponding username and self-decrypted MD5 password in the core configuration file, the attacker can directly log in to the backend, thereby bypassing the front-end backend login page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0640 | Tenda AC23 PowerSaveSet sscanf buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0640</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda AC23 16.03.07.52. This affects the function sscanf of the file /goform/PowerSaveSet. Executing a manipulation of the argument Time can lead to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14979 | Eddie VPN 2.24.6 - Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14979</link><description>AirVPN Eddie on MacOS contains an insecure XPC service that allows local, unprivileged users to escalate their privileges to root.This issue affects Eddie: 2.24.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60262 | An issue in H3C M102G HM1A0V200R010 wireless controller and BA1500L SWBA1A0V100R006 wireless access point, there is a misconfiguration vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60262</link><description>An issue in H3C M102G HM1A0V200R010 wireless controller and BA1500L SWBA1A0V100R006 wireless access point, there is a misconfiguration vulnerability about vsftpd. Through this vulnerability, all files uploaded anonymously via the FTP protocol is automatically owned by the root user and remote attackers could gain root-level control over the devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46696 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.0 Appliance and Application, version(s) versions 5.26 to 5.30, contain(s) an Execution with Unnecessary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46696</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.0 Appliance and Application, version(s) versions 5.26 to 5.30, contain(s) an Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14026 | Vulnerable Python version used in Forcepoint One DLP Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14026</link><description>Forcepoint One DLP Client, version 23.04.5642 (and possibly newer versions), includes a restricted version of Python 2.5.4 that prevents use of the ctypes library. ctypes is a foreign function interface (FFI) for Python, enabling calls to DLLs/shared libraries, memory allocation, and direct code execution. It was demonstrated that these restrictions could be bypassed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21493 | iccDEV has Type Confusion during XML Curve Serialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21493</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools for working with ICC color management profiles. Versions 2.3.1.1 and below are vulnerable to Type Confusion in its CIccSingleSampledeCurveXml class during XML Curve Serialization. This issue is fixed in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21488 | iccDEV has Out-of-bounds Read, Heap-based Buffer Overflow and Improper Null Termination</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21488</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools for working with ICC color management profiles. Versions 2.3.1.1 and below are vulnerable to Out-of-bounds Read, Heap-based Buffer Overflow and Improper Null Termination through its CIccTagText::Read function. This issue is fixed in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21489 | iccDEV has Out-of-bounds Read and Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21489</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools for working with ICC color management profiles. Versions 2.3.1.1 and below have Out-of-bounds Read and Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) vulnerabilities in its CIccCalculatorFunc::SequenceNeedTempReset function. This issue is fixed in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14552 | MediaPress &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Plugin&amp;#x27;s Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14552</link><description>The MediaPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's mpp-uploader shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9318 | Quiz and Survey Master (QSM) &amp;lt;= 10.3.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via `is_linking` Query Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9318</link><description>The Quiz and Survey Master (QSM) – Easy Quiz and Survey Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘is_linking’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 10.3.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9637 | Quiz and Survey Master (QSM) &amp;lt;= 10.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Unpublished, Private And Password-Protected Quiz Information Disclosure And Image Response Uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9637</link><description>The Quiz and Survey Master (QSM) – Easy Quiz and Survey Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data due to a missing capability and status checks on multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 10.3.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view the details of unpublished, private, or password-protected quizzes, as well as submit file responses to questions from those quizzes, which allow file upload.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13766 | MasterStudy LMS WordPress Plugin – for Online Courses and Education &amp;lt;= 3.7.6 Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Posts and Media Creation, Modification and Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13766</link><description>The MasterStudy LMS WordPress Plugin – for Online Courses and Education plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and deletion of data due to a missing capability checks on multiple REST API endpoints in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload or delete arbitrary media files, delete or modify posts, and create/manage course templates</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 08:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13964 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.2 - Missing Authentication to Unauthenticated Course Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13964</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the catch_lp_ajax function in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify course contents by adding/removing/updating/re-ordering sections or modifying section items.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 08:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5919 | Appointment Booking and Scheduling Calendar Plugin – WP Timetics &amp;lt;= 1.0.36 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Booking Details View And Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5919</link><description>The Appointment Booking and Scheduling Calendar Plugin – WP Timetics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data due to a missing capability check on the update and register_routes functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.36. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view and modify booking details.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 08:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9294 | Quiz And Survey Master &amp;lt;= 10.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Quiz Results Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9294</link><description>The Quiz and Survey Master (QSM) – Easy Quiz and Survey Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the qsm_dashboard_delete_result function in all versions up to, and including, 10.3.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete quiz results.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 08:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12067 | Table Field Add-on for ACF and SCF &amp;lt;= 1.3.30 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Table Cell Content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12067</link><description>The Table Field Add-on for ACF and SCF plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Table Cell Content in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 07:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13812 | GamiPress – Gamification plugin to reward points, achievements, badges &amp;amp; ranks in WordPress &amp;lt;= 7.6.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13812</link><description>The GamiPress – Gamification plugin to reward points, achievements, badges &amp; ranks in WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the gamipress_ajax_get_posts and gamipress_ajax_get_users functions in all versions up to, and including, 7.6.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to enumerate users, including their email addresses and to retrieve titles of private posts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 07:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14371 | TaxoPress &amp;lt;= 3.41.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Post Tag Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14371</link><description>The Tag, Category, and Taxonomy Manager – AI Autotagger with OpenAI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the taxopress_ai_add_post_term function in all versions up to, and including, 3.41.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to add or remove taxonomy terms (tags, categories) on any post, including ones they do not own.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 07:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13215 | Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme &amp;lt;= 2.17.13 - Unauthenticated Draft Posts Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13215</link><description>The Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.17.13 via the auxels_ajax_search due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract titles of draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 07:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4776 | Phlox &amp;lt;= 2.17.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via `data-caption` HTML Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4776</link><description>The Phlox theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `data-caption` HTML attribute in all versions up to, and including, 2.17.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21411 | Authentication bypass issue exists in OpenBlocks series versions prior to FW5.0.8, which may allow an attacker to bypass administrator authe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21411</link><description>Authentication bypass issue exists in OpenBlocks series versions prior to FW5.0.8, which may allow an attacker to bypass administrator authentication and change the password.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14120 | URL Image Importer &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14120</link><description>The URL Image Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7 due to insufficient sanitization of SVG files. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14438 | Xagio SEO &amp;lt;= 7.1.0.30 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14438</link><description>The Xagio SEO – AI Powered SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 7.1.0.30 via the 'pixabayDownloadImage' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14441 | Popupkit &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Subscriber Data Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14441</link><description>The Popupkit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary subscriber data deletion due to missing authorization on the DELETE `/subscribers` REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0. This is due to the `permission_callback` only validating wp_rest nonce without checking user capabilities. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary subscriber records.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14996 | AS Password Field In Default Registration Form &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14996</link><description>The AS Password Field In Default Registration Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their password. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14997 | BuddyPress Xprofile Custom Field Types &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14997</link><description>The BuddyPress Xprofile Custom Field Types plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the 'delete_field' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15001 | FS Registration Password &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15001</link><description>The FS Registration Password plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their password. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21486 | Use After Free and Heap-based Buffer Overflow and Integer Overflow or Wraparound and Out-of-bounds Write in iccDEV</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21486</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools for working with ICC color management profiles. Versions 2.3.1.1 and below contain Use After Free, Heap-based Buffer Overflow and Integer Overflow or Wraparound and Out-of-bounds Write vulnerabilities in its CIccSparseMatrix::CIccSparseMatrix function. This issue is fixed in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21487 | iccDEV has Out-of-bounds Read, Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset and Improper Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21487</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools for working with ICC color management profiles. Versions 2.3.1.1 and below have an Out-of-bounds Read, Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset and have Improper Input Validation in its CIccProfile::LoadTag function. This issue is fixed in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11370 | Depicter &amp;lt;= 4.0.7 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Display Rule Updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11370</link><description>The Popup and Slider Builder by Depicter – Add Email collecting Popup, Popup Modal, Coupon Popup, Image Slider, Carousel Slider, Post Slider Carousel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'store' function of the RulesAjaxController class in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update pop-up display settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11723 | Appointment Booking Calendar — Simply Schedule Appointments Booking Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.9.5 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11723</link><description>The Appointment Booking Calendar — Simply Schedule Appointments Booking Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.9.5 via the hash() function due to use of a hardcoded fall-back salt. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to generate a valid token across sites running the plugin that have not manually set a salt in the wp-config.php file and access booking information that will allow them to make modifications.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13409 | Form Vibes – Database Manager for Forms &amp;lt;= 1.4.13 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13409</link><description>The Form Vibes – Database Manager for Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'params' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.13 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13652 | CBX Bookmark &amp;amp; Favorite &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via `orderby` Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13652</link><description>The CBX Bookmark &amp; Favorite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to generic SQL Injection via the ‘orderby’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13746 | ForumWP – Forum &amp;amp; Discussion Board &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Display Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13746</link><description>The ForumWP – Forum &amp; Discussion Board plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the User's Display Name in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14034 | ilGhera Support System for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Ticket Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14034</link><description>The ilGhera Support System for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'delete_single_ticket_callback' and 'change_ticket_status_callback' functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary support tickets and modify their status.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14153 | Page Expire Popup/Redirection for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Author+) SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;id&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14153</link><description>The Page Expire Popup/Redirection for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the 'id' shortcode attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0604 | FastDup &amp;lt;= 2.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Path Traversal via &amp;#x27;dir_path&amp;#x27; REST Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0604</link><description>The FastDup – Fastest WordPress Migration &amp; Duplicator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 2.7 via the 'dir_path' parameter in the 'njt-fastdup/v1/template/directory-tree' REST API endpoint. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary directories on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21485 | iccDEV Undefined Behavior (UB) and Out of Memory in CIccProfile::LoadTag()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21485</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools for working with ICC color management profiles. Versions 2.3.1.1 and below are prone to have Undefined Behavior (UB) and Out of Memory errors. This issue is fixed in version 2.3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21676 | iccDEV has a Heap-based Buffer Overflow in its CIccMBB::Validate() function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21676</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools for working with ICC color management profiles. Versions 2.3.1 and below have a Heap-based Buffer Overflow in its CIccMBB::Validate function which checks tag data validity. This issue is fixed in version 2.3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21677 | iccDEV has Undefined Behavior in CIccCLUT::Init()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21677</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools for working with ICC color management profiles. Versions 2.3.1 and below have Undefined Behavior in its CIccCLUT::Init function which initializes and sets the size of a CLUT. This issue is fixed in version 2.3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12793 | An uncontrolled DLL loading path vulnerability exists in AsusSoftwareManagerAgent. A local attacker may influence the application to load a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12793</link><description>An uncontrolled DLL loading path vulnerability exists in AsusSoftwareManagerAgent. A local attacker may influence the application to load a DLL from an attacker-controlled location, potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.
Refer to the '

Security Update for MyASUS' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15364 | Download Manager &amp;lt;= 3.3.40 - Unauthenticated Limited Privilege Escalation via updatePassword</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15364</link><description>The Download Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.40. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their details like password. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change user's passwords, except administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15385 | Insufficient Verification of Data Authenticity vulnerability in TECNO Mobile com.Afmobi.Boomplayer allows Authentication Bypass.This issue a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15385</link><description>Insufficient Verification of Data Authenticity vulnerability in TECNO Mobile com.Afmobi.Boomplayer allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects com.Afmobi.Boomplayer: 7.4.63.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20760 | In Modem, there is a possible read of uninitialized heap data due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote denial of service, if ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20760</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible read of uninitialized heap data due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01676750; Issue ID: MSV-4653.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20761 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20761</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01311265; Issue ID: MSV-4655.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20762 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20762</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01685181; Issue ID: MSV-4760.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20778 | In display, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20778</link><description>In display, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10184870; Issue ID: MSV-4729.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20779 | In display, there is a possible use after free due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious acto...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20779</link><description>In display, there is a possible use after free due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10184084; Issue ID: MSV-4720.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20780 | In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious act...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20780</link><description>In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10184061; Issue ID: MSV-4712.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20781 | In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious act...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20781</link><description>In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10182914; Issue ID: MSV-4699.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20782 | In display, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20782</link><description>In display, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10182882; Issue ID: MSV-4685.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20783 | In display, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20783</link><description>In display, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10182882; Issue ID: MSV-4684.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20784 | In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20784</link><description>In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10182882; Issue ID: MSV-4683.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20785 | In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious act...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20785</link><description>In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10149882; Issue ID: MSV-4677.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20786 | In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious act...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20786</link><description>In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10149882; Issue ID: MSV-4673.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20787 | In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious act...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20787</link><description>In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10149879; Issue ID: MSV-4658.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20793 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20793</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01430930; Issue ID: MSV-4836.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20794 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20794</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01689259 / MOLY01586470; Issue ID: MSV-4847.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20795 | In KeyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20795</link><description>In KeyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10276761; Issue ID: MSV-5141.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20796 | In imgsys, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20796</link><description>In imgsys, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10314745; Issue ID: MSV-5553.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20797 | In battery, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20797</link><description>In battery, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10315812; Issue ID: MSV-5534.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20798 | In battery, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20798</link><description>In battery, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10315812; Issue ID: MSV-5533.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20799 | In c2ps, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20799</link><description>In c2ps, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10274607; Issue ID: MSV-5049.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20800 | In mminfra, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20800</link><description>In mminfra, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10267349; Issue ID: MSV-5033.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20801 | In seninf, there is a possible memory corruption due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20801</link><description>In seninf, there is a possible memory corruption due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10251210; Issue ID: MSV-4926.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20802 | In geniezone, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20802</link><description>In geniezone, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10238968; Issue ID: MSV-4914.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20803 | In dpe, there is a possible memory corruption due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20803</link><description>In dpe, there is a possible memory corruption due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10199779; Issue ID: MSV-4504.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20804 | In dpe, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor h...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20804</link><description>In dpe, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10198951; Issue ID: MSV-4503.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20805 | In dpe, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor h...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20805</link><description>In dpe, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10114696; Issue ID: MSV-4480.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20806 | In dpe, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor h...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20806</link><description>In dpe, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10114835; Issue ID: MSV-4479.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20807 | In dpe, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20807</link><description>In dpe, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10114841; Issue ID: MSV-4451.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21673 | iccDEV has Integer Overflow/Underflow in CIccXmlArrayType::ParseTextCountNum()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21673</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools for working with ICC color management profiles. Versions 2.3.1 and below have overflows and underflows in  CIccXmlArrayType::ParseTextCountNum(). This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. This issue is fixed in version 2.3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21674 | iccDEV has a Memory Leak in its CIccProfileXml::ParseTag() Error Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21674</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools for working with ICC color management profiles. Versions 2.3.1 and below contain a memory leak vulnerability in its XML MPE Parsing Path (iccFromXml). This issue is fixed in version 2.3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21675 | iccDEV has a Use After Free vulnerability in CIccCmm class via improper hint manager object deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21675</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools for working with ICC color management profiles. Versions 2.3.1 and below contain a Use After Free vulnerability in the CIccXform::Create() function, where it deletes the hint. This issue is fixed in version 2.3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68954 | Pterodactyl does not revoke SFTP access when server is deleted or permissions reduced</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68954</link><description>Pterodactyl is a free, open-source game server management panel. Versions 1.11.11 and below do not revoke active SFTP connections when a user is removed from a server instance or has their permissions changes with respect to file access over SFTP. This allows a user that was already connected to SFTP to remain connected and access files even after their permissions are revoked. A user must have been connected to SFTP at the time of their permissions being revoked in order for this vulnerability to be exploited. This issue is fixed in version 1.12.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 01:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69197 | Pterodactyl TOTPs can be reused during validity window</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69197</link><description>Pterodactyl is a free, open-source game server management panel. Versions 1.11.11 and below allow TOTP to be used multiple times during its validity window. Users with 2FA enabled are prompted to enter a token during sign-in, and afterward it is not sufficiently marked as used in the system. This allows an attacker who intercepts that token to use it in addition to a known username/password during the 60-second token validity window. The attacker must have intercepted a valid 2FA token (for example, during a screen share). This issue is fixed in version 1.12.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 01:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15444 | Crypt::Sodium::XS module versions prior to 0.000042, for Perl, include a vulnerable version of libsodium</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15444</link><description>Crypt::Sodium::XS module versions prior to 0.000042, for Perl, include a vulnerable version of libsodium

libsodium &lt;= 1.0.20 or a version of libsodium released before December 30, 2025 contains a vulnerability documented as CVE-2025-69277  https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69277 .

The libsodium vulnerability states:

In atypical use cases involving certain custom cryptography or untrusted data to crypto_core_ed25519_is_valid_point, mishandles checks for whether an elliptic curve point is valid because it sometimes allows points that aren't in the main cryptographic group.

0.000042 includes a version of libsodium updated to 1.0.20-stable, released January 3, 2026, which includes a fix for the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 01:27:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21507 | iccDEV is Vulnerable to Denial of Service via Infinite Loop in CalcProfileID()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21507</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools for working with ICC color management profiles. Versions 2.3.1 and below have an infinite loop in the IccProfile.cpp function, CalcProfileID. This issue is fixed in version 2.3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 01:27:26 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>