<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 18:53:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-22836 | In cases where a multi-tenant stack user is operating Foundry’s Linter service, and the user changes the linter name from the default value, the renamed value may be visible to the rest of the stack’s tenants.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22836</link><description>In cases where a multi-tenant stack user is operating Foundry’s Linter service, and the user changes a group name from the default value, the renamed value may be visible to the rest of the stack’s tenants.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 18:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24135 | Product Name and Product Code in the 'Add Product' section of Sourcecodester Product Inventory with Export to Excel 1.0 are vulnerable to XS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24135</link><description>Product Name and Product Code in the 'Add Product' section of Sourcecodester Product Inventory with Export to Excel 1.0 are vulnerable to XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 18:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1017 | Gabriels FTP Server denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1017</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Gabriels FTP Server 1.2. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation of the argument USERNAME leads to denial of service. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252287.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 18:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30970 | Gotham table and Forward App Path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30970</link><description>Gotham Table service and Forward App were found to be vulnerable to a Path traversal issue allowing an authenticated user to read arbitrary files on the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 18:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23940 | Trend Micro uiAirSupport, included in the Trend Micro Security 2023 family of consumer products, version 6.0.2092 and below is vulnerable to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23940</link><description>Trend Micro uiAirSupport, included in the Trend Micro Security 2023 family of consumer products, version 6.0.2092 and below is vulnerable to a DLL hijacking/proxying vulnerability, which if exploited could allow an attacker to impersonate and modify a library to execute code on the system and ultimately escalate privileges on an affected system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 18:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1016 | Solar FTP Server PASV Command denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1016</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Solar FTP Server 2.1.1/2.1.2. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component PASV Command Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-252286 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 17:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1011 | SourceCodester Employee Management System Leave delete-leave.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1011</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Employee Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file delete-leave.php of the component Leave Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252280.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 17:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40551 | Shim: out of bounds read when parsing mz binaries</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40551</link><description>A flaw was found in the MZ binary format in Shim. An out-of-bounds read may occur, leading to a crash or possible exposure of sensitive data during the system's boot phase.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23828 | Nginx-UI authenticated RCE through injecting into the application config via CRLF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23828</link><description>Nginx-UI is a web interface to manage Nginx configurations. It is vulnerable to an authenticated arbitrary command execution via CRLF attack when changing the value of test_config_cmd or start_cmd. This vulnerability exists due to an incomplete fix for CVE-2024-22197 and CVE-2024-22198. This vulnerability has been patched in version 2.0.0.beta.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1705 | Missing Authorization vulnerability in Forcepoint F|One SmartEdge Agent on Windows (bgAutoinstaller service modules) allows Privilege Escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1705</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Forcepoint F|One SmartEdge Agent on Windows (bgAutoinstaller service modules) allows Privilege Escalation, Functionality Bypass.This issue affects F|One SmartEdge Agent: before 1.7.0.230330-554.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40546 | Shim: out-of-bounds read printing error messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40546</link><description>A flaw was found in Shim when an error happened while creating a new ESL variable. If Shim fails to create the new variable, it tries to print an error message to the user; however, the number of parameters used by the logging function doesn't match the format string used by it, leading to a crash under certain circumstances.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40549 | Shim: out-of-bounds read in verify_buffer_authenticode() malformed pe file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40549</link><description>An out-of-bounds read flaw was found in Shim due to the lack of proper boundary verification during the load of a PE binary. This flaw allows an attacker to load a crafted PE binary, triggering the issue and crashing Shim, resulting in a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40550 | Shim: out-of-bound read in verify_buffer_sbat()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40550</link><description>An out-of-bounds read flaw was found in Shim when it tried to validate the SBAT information. This issue may expose sensitive data during the system's boot phase.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1009 | SourceCodester Employee Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1009</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument txtusername leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252278 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1010 | SourceCodester Employee Management System edit-profile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1010</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Employee Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file edit-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname/phone/date of birth/address/date of appointment leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252279.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0788 | SUPERAntiSpyware Pro X v10.0.1260 - Kernel-level API parameters manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0788</link><description>SUPERAntiSpyware Pro X v10.0.1260 is vulnerable to kernel-level API parameters manipulation and Denial of Service vulnerabilities by triggering the 0x9C402140 IOCTL code of the saskutil64.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23441 | Vba32 Antivirus v3.36.0 - Denial of Service (DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23441</link><description>Vba32 Antivirus v3.36.0 is vulnerable to a Denial of Service vulnerability by triggering the 0x2220A7 IOCTL code of the Vba32m64.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23827 | Nginx-UI arbitrary file write through the Import Certificate feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23827</link><description>Nginx-UI is a web interface to manage Nginx configurations. The Import Certificate feature allows arbitrary write into the system. The feature does not check if the provided user input is a certification/key and allows to write into arbitrary paths in the system. It's possible to leverage the vulnerability into a remote code execution overwriting the config file app.ini. Version 2.0.0.beta.12 fixed the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1007 | SourceCodester Employee Management System edit_profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1007</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file edit_profile.php. The manipulation of the argument txtfullname leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252276.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1008 | SourceCodester Employee Management System Profile Page edit-photo.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1008</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file edit-photo.php of the component Profile Page. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252277 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23826 | Uploading an image with a specific filename causes a server-side DoS </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23826</link><description>spbu_se_site is the website of the Department of System Programming of St. Petersburg State University. Before 2024.01.29, when uploading an avatar image, an authenticated user may intentionally use a large Unicode filename which would lead to a server-side denial of service under Windows. This is due to no limitation of the length of the filename and the costly use of the Unicode normalization with the form NFKD on Windows OS.  This vulnerability was fixed in the 2024.01.29 release.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23822 | Thruk Incorrect limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory (Path Traversal) (CWE-22)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23822</link><description>Thruk is a multibackend monitoring webinterface.  Prior to 3.12, the Thruk web monitoring application presents a vulnerability in a file upload form that allows a threat actor to arbitrarily upload files to the server to any path they desire and have permissions for. This vulnerability is known as Path Traversal or Directory Traversal. Version 3.12 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 15:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1006 | Shanxi Diankeyun Technology NODERP Cookie common.php improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1006</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shanxi Diankeyun Technology NODERP up to 6.0.2 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file application/index/common.php of the component Cookie Handler. The manipulation of the argument Nod_User_Id/Nod_User_Token leads to improper authentication. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252275. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 15:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1004 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi loginAuth stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1004</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. This affects the function loginAuth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252273 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 15:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1005 | Shanxi Diankeyun Technology NODERP log file access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1005</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Shanxi Diankeyun Technology NODERP up to 6.0.2 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /runtime/log. The manipulation leads to files or directories accessible. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252274 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 15:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40548 | Shim: interger overflow leads to heap buffer overflow in verify_sbat_section on 32-bits systems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40548</link><description>A buffer overflow was found in Shim in the 32-bit system. The overflow happens due to an addition operation involving a user-controlled value parsed from the PE binary being used by Shim. This value is further used for memory allocation operations, leading to a heap-based buffer overflow. This flaw causes memory corruption and can lead to a crash or data integrity issues during the boot phase.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5124 | PageLayer &amp;lt; 1.8.0 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5124</link><description>The Page Builder: Pagelayer WordPress plugin before 1.8.0 doesn't prevent attackers with administrator privileges from inserting malicious JavaScript inside a post's header or footer code, even when unfiltered_html is disallowed, such as in multi-site WordPress configurations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5943 | Wp-Adv-Quiz &amp;lt; 1.0.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5943</link><description>The Wp-Adv-Quiz WordPress plugin before 1.0.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5956 | Wp-Adv-Quiz &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS in Quiz Overview</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5956</link><description>The Wp-Adv-Quiz WordPress plugin through 1.0.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6165 | Restrict Usernames Emails Characters Plugin &amp;lt; 3.1.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6165</link><description>The Restrict Usernames Emails Characters WordPress plugin before 3.1.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6278 | Biteship for WooCommerce &amp;lt; 2.2.25 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6278</link><description>The Biteship: Plugin Ongkos Kirim Kurir Instant, Reguler, Kargo WordPress plugin before 2.2.25 does not sanitise and escape the biteship_error and biteship_message parameters before outputting them back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6279 | Woostify Sites Library &amp;lt; 1.4.8 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Options Update to DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6279</link><description>The Woostify Sites Library WordPress plugin before 1.4.8 does not have authorisation in an AJAX action, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber to update arbitrary blog options and set them to 'activated' which could lead to DoS when using a specific option name</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6389 | WordPress Toolbar &amp;lt;= 2.2.6 - Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6389</link><description>The WordPress Toolbar WordPress plugin through 2.2.6 redirects to any URL via the "wptbto" parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users to potentially malicious sites if they can successfully trick them into performing an action.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6390 | WordPress Users &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6390</link><description>The WordPress Users WordPress plugin through 1.4 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6391 | Custom User CSS &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6391</link><description>The Custom User CSS WordPress plugin through 0.2 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6503 | WP Plugin Lister &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Settings Update to Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6503</link><description>The WP Plugin Lister WordPress plugin through 2.1.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6530 | TJ Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 0.1.3 - Contributor+ Stored XSS via Shortcodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6530</link><description>The TJ Shortcodes WordPress plugin through 0.1.3 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6633 | Site Notes &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Admin Note Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6633</link><description>The Site Notes WordPress plugin through 2.0.0 does not have CSRF checks in some of its functionalities, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions, such as deleting administration notes, via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6946 | Autotitle for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Settings Update to Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6946</link><description>The Autotitle for WordPress plugin through 1.0.3 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7074 | WP Social Bookmark Menu &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7074</link><description>The WP SOCIAL BOOKMARK MENU WordPress plugin through 1.2 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7089 | Easy SVG Allow &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Author+ Stored XSS via SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7089</link><description>The Easy SVG Allow WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not sanitize uploaded SVG files, which could allow users with a role as low as Author to upload a malicious SVG containing XSS payloads.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7199 | Relevanssi (Free &amp;lt; 4.22.0, Premium &amp;lt; 2.25.0) - Unauthenticated Private/Draft Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7199</link><description>The Relevanssi WordPress plugin before 4.22.0, Relevanssi Premium WordPress plugin before 2.25.0 allows any unauthenticated user to read draft and private posts via a crafted request</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7200 | EventON &amp;lt; 4.4.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7200</link><description>The EventON WordPress plugin before 4.4.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7204 | WP STAGING WordPress Backup Plugin &amp;lt; 3.2.0 - Unauthorized Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7204</link><description>The WP STAGING WordPress Backup plugin before 3.2.0 allows access to cache files during the cloning process which provides</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1003 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setLanguageCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1003</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. Affected by this issue is the function setLanguageCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument lang leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252272. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22559 | LightCMS v2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Content Management - Articles field.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22559</link><description>LightCMS v2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Content Management - Articles field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23747 | The Moderna Sistemas ModernaNet Hospital Management System 2024 is susceptible to an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23747</link><description>The Moderna Sistemas ModernaNet Hospital Management System 2024 is susceptible to an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability. This vulnerability resides in the system's handling of user data access through a /Modernanet/LAUDO/LAU0000100/Laudo?id= URI. By manipulating this id parameter, an attacker can gain access to sensitive medical information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1002 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setIpPortFilterRules stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1002</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setIpPortFilterRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ePort leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252271. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1014 | Uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in SE-elektronic GmbH E-DDC3.3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1014</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in SE-elektronic GmbH E-DDC3.3 affecting versions 03.07.03 and higher. An attacker could interrupt the availability of the administration panel by sending multiple ICMP packets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1015 | Remote command execution vulnerability in SE-elektronic GmbH E-DDC3.3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1015</link><description>Remote command execution vulnerability in SE-elektronic GmbH E-DDC3.3 affecting versions 03.07.03 and higher. An attacker could send different commands from the operating system to the system via the web configuration functionality of the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1000 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setTracerouteCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1000</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setTracerouteCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument command leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252269 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:36:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1001 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi main stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1001</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. Affected is the function main of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252270 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0998 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setDiagnosisCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0998</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252267. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0999 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setParentalRules stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0999</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument eTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252268. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0997 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setOpModeCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0997</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setOpModeCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument pppoeUser leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252266 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 12:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29055 | Apache Kylin: Insufficiently protected credentials in config file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29055</link><description>In Apache Kylin version 2.0.0 to 4.0.3, there is a Server Config web interface that displays the content of file 'kylin.properties', that may contain serverside credentials. When the kylin service runs over HTTP (or other plain text protocol), it is possible for network sniffers to hijack the HTTP payload and get access to the content of kylin.properties and potentially the containing credentials.

To avoid this threat, users are recommended to 

  *  Always turn on HTTPS so that network payload is encrypted.

  *  Avoid putting credentials in kylin.properties, or at least not in plain text.
  *  Use network firewalls to protect the serverside such that it is not accessible to external attackers.

  *  Upgrade to version Apache Kylin 4.0.4, which filters out the sensitive content that goes to the Server Config web interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 12:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5378 | Stored XSS in SmodBIP and MegaBIP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5378</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in  MegaBIP and already unsupported SmodBIP software allows for Stored XSS.This issue affects SmodBIP in all versions and MegaBIP in versions up to 4.36.2 (newer versions were not tested; the vendor has not confirmed fixing the vulnerability).</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 11:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46838 | Linux: netback processing of zero-length transmit fragment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46838</link><description>Transmit requests in Xen's virtual network protocol can consist of
multiple parts.  While not really useful, except for the initial part
any of them may be of zero length, i.e. carry no data at all.  Besides a
certain initial portion of the to be transferred data, these parts are
directly translated into what Linux calls SKB fragments.  Such converted
request parts can, when for a particular SKB they are all of length
zero, lead to a de-reference of NULL in core networking code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 10:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23790 | Missing file type check in avatar picture upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23790</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in the upload functionality for user avatars allows functionality misuse due to missing check of filetypes.
This issue affects OTRS:  from 7.0.X through 7.0.48, from 8.0.X through 8.0.37, from 2023 through 2023.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23791 | Unnecessary data is written to log if issues during indexing occurs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23791</link><description>Insertion of debug information into log file during building the elastic search index allows reading of sensitive information from articles.This issue affects OTRS: from 7.0.X through 7.0.48, from 8.0.X through 8.0.37, from 2023.X through 2023.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0212 | Cloudflare WordPress plugin enables information disclosure of Cloudflare API (for low privileged users)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0212</link><description>The Cloudflare Wordpress plugin was found to be vulnerable to improper authentication. The vulnerability enables attackers with a lower privileged account to access data from the Cloudflare API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:22:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23792 | Insufficient access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23792</link><description>When adding attachments to ticket comments, 
another user can add attachments as well impersonating the orginal user. The attack requires a 
logged-in other user to know the UUID. While the legitimate user 
completes the comment, the malicious user can add more files to the 
comment.

This issue affects OTRS: from 7.0.X through 7.0.48, from 8.0.X through 8.0.37, from 2023.X through 2023.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:22:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24736 | The POP3 service in YahooPOPs (aka YPOPs!) 1.6 allows a remote denial of service (reboot) via a long string to TCP port 110, a related issue...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24736</link><description>The POP3 service in YahooPOPs (aka YPOPs!) 1.6 allows a remote denial of service (reboot) via a long string to TCP port 110, a related issue to CVE-2004-1558.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 03:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0996 | Tenda i9 httpd setcfm formSetCfm stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0996</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda i9 1.0.0.9(4122). This affects the function formSetCfm of the file /goform/setcfm of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument funcpara1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252261 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 02:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0995 | Tenda W6 httpd wifiSSIDset formwrlSSIDset stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0995</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W6 1.0.0.9(4122). It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formwrlSSIDset of the file /goform/wifiSSIDset of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument index leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252260. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 02:06:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0993 | Tenda i6 httpd WifiMacFilterGet formWifiMacFilterGet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0993</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda i6 1.0.0.9(3857). It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function formWifiMacFilterGet of the file /goform/WifiMacFilterGet of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument index leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252258 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 01:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0994 | Tenda W6 httpd setcfm formSetCfm stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0994</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W6 1.0.0.9(4122). It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetCfm of the file /goform/setcfm of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument funcpara1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252259. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 01:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0991 | Tenda i6 httpd setcfm formSetCfm stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0991</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda i6 1.0.0.9(3857) and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formSetCfm of the file /goform/setcfm of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument funcpara1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252256. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 01:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0992 | Tenda i6 httpd wifiSSIDset formwrlSSIDset stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0992</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda i6 1.0.0.9(3857) and classified as critical. This issue affects the function formwrlSSIDset of the file /goform/wifiSSIDset of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument index leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252257 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 01:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0989 | Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP Service.php del_sn_db path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0989</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP up to 1.0.4. Affected by this issue is the function del_sn_db of the file /application/index/controller/Service.php. The manipulation of the argument file leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252254 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0990 | Tenda i6 httpd setAutoPing formSetAutoPing stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0990</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda i6 1.0.0.9(3857). This affects the function formSetAutoPing of the file /goform/setAutoPing of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument ping1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252255. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0987 | Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP log neutralization for logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0987</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP up to 1.0.4. Affected is an unknown function of the file /runtime/log. The manipulation leads to improper output neutralization for logs. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252252. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0988 | Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP common.php checklogin improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0988</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP up to 1.0.4. Affected by this vulnerability is the function checklogin of the file /application/index/common.php. The manipulation of the argument App_User_id/App_user_Token leads to improper authentication. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252253 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0986 | Issabel PBX Asterisk-Cli os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0986</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Issabel PBX 4.0.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /index.php?menu=asterisk_cli of the component Asterisk-Cli. The manipulation of the argument Command leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252251. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 23:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23782 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in a-blog cms Ver.3.1.x series versions prior to Ver.3.1.7, Ver.3.0.x series versions prior to Ver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23782</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in a-blog cms Ver.3.1.x series versions prior to Ver.3.1.7, Ver.3.0.x series versions prior to Ver.3.0.29, Ver.2.11.x series versions prior to Ver.2.11.58, Ver.2.10.x series versions prior to Ver.2.10.50, and Ver.2.9.0 and earlier versions. If this vulnerability is exploited, a user with a contributor or higher privilege may execute an arbitrary script on the web browser of the user who accessed the website using the product.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 23:22:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6200 | Kernel: icmpv6 router advertisement packets, aka linux tcp/ip remote code execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6200</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux Kernel. Under certain conditions, an unauthenticated attacker from an adjacent network could send an ICMPv6 router advertisement packet, causing arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 12:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0841 | Kernel: hugetlbfs: null pointer dereference in hugetlbfs_fill_super function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0841</link><description>A null pointer dereference flaw was found in the hugetlbfs_fill_super function in the Linux kernel hugetlbfs (HugeTLB pages) functionality. This issue may allow a local user to crash the system or potentially escalate their privileges on the system.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 11:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23740 | An issue in Kap for macOS version 3.6.0 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilns...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23740</link><description>An issue in Kap for macOS version 3.6.0 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilnspectArguments settings.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 03:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23739 | An issue in Discord for macOS version 0.0.291 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNode...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23739</link><description>An issue in Discord for macOS version 0.0.291 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilnspectArguments settings.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 02:56:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23742 | An issue in Loom on macOS version 0.196.1 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23742</link><description>An issue in Loom on macOS version 0.196.1 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilnspectArguments settings.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 02:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23741 | An issue in Hyper on macOS version 3.4.1 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeCliln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23741</link><description>An issue in Hyper on macOS version 3.4.1 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilnspectArguments settings.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 02:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23743 | An issue in Notion for macOS version 3.1.0 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeCli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23743</link><description>An issue in Notion for macOS version 3.1.0 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilnspectArguments components.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 02:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23738 | An issue in Postman version 10.22 and before on macOS allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeCli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23738</link><description>An issue in Postman version 10.22 and before on macOS allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilnspectArguments settings.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0962 | obgm libcoap Configuration File coap_oscore.c get_split_entry stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0962</link><description>A vulnerability was found in obgm libcoap 4.3.4. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function get_split_entry of the file src/coap_oscore.c of the component Configuration File Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-252206 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 12:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0960 | flink-extended ai-flow workflow_command.py cloudpickle.loads deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0960</link><description>A vulnerability was found in flink-extended ai-flow 0.3.1. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cloudpickle.loads of the file \ai_flow\cli\commands\workflow_command.py. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252205 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 12:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0959 | StanfordVL GibsonEnv pposgd_fuse.py cloudpickle.load deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0959</link><description>A vulnerability was found in StanfordVL GibsonEnv 0.3.1. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function cloudpickle.load of the file gibson\utils\pposgd_fuse.py. The manipulation leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252204.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 10:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22861 | Integer overflow vulnerability in FFmpeg before n6.1, allows attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the avcodec/osq module.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22861</link><description>Integer overflow vulnerability in FFmpeg before n6.1, allows attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the avcodec/osq module.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 06:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0958 | CodeAstro Stock Management System Add Category index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0958</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Stock Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /index.php of the component Add Category Handler. The manipulation of the argument Category Name/Category Description leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252203.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 06:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22862 | Integer overflow vulnerability in FFmpeg before n6.1, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the JJPEG XL Parser.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22862</link><description>Integer overflow vulnerability in FFmpeg before n6.1, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the JJPEG XL Parser.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 06:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22860 | Integer overflow vulnerability in FFmpeg before n6.1, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the jpegxl_anim_read_packet comp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22860</link><description>Integer overflow vulnerability in FFmpeg before n6.1, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the jpegxl_anim_read_packet component in the JPEG XL Animation decoder.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 06:16:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48202 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sunlight CMS 8.0.1 allows an authenticated low-privileged user to escalate privileges via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48202</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sunlight CMS 8.0.1 allows an authenticated low-privileged user to escalate privileges via a crafted SVG file in the File Manager component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 05:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0618 | The Contact Form Plugin – Fastest Contact Form Builder Plugin for WordPress by Fluent Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0618</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin – Fastest Contact Form Builder Plugin for WordPress by Fluent Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via imported form titles in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 05:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48201 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sunlight CMS v.8.0.1, allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code and escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48201</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sunlight CMS v.8.0.1, allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code and escalate privileges via a crafted script to the Content text editor component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 05:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0697 | The Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and inclu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0697</link><description>The Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3 via the node_id parameter in the backuply_get_jstree function. This makes it possible for attackers with administrator privileges or higher to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 04:39:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0824 | The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Link Anything functionality in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0824</link><description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Link Anything functionality in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 04:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6497 | The WordPress Simple Shopping Cart plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the automatic redirect URL setting ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6497</link><description>The WordPress Simple Shopping Cart plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the automatic redirect URL setting in all versions up to and including 4.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 03:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0664 | The Meks Smart Social Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Meks Smart Social Widget in all versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0664</link><description>The Meks Smart Social Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Meks Smart Social Widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0667 | The Form Maker by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Drag &amp; Drop Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0667</link><description>The Form Maker by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Drag &amp; Drop Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.15.21. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'execute' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary methods in the 'BoosterController' class via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52389 | UTF32Encoding.cpp in POCO has a Poco::UTF32Encoding integer overflow and resultant stack buffer overflow because Poco::UTF32Encoding::conver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52389</link><description>UTF32Encoding.cpp in POCO has a Poco::UTF32Encoding integer overflow and resultant stack buffer overflow because Poco::UTF32Encoding::convert() and Poco::UTF32::queryConvert() may return a negative integer if a UTF-32 byte sequence evaluates to a value of 0x80000000 or higher. This is fixed in 1.11.8p2, 1.12.5p2, and 1.13.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 02:22:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6482 | Encryption key derived from static host information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6482</link><description>Use of encryption key derived from static information in Synaptics Fingerprint Driver allows 

an attacker to set up a TLS session with the fingerprint sensor and send restricted commands to the fingerprint sensor. This may 
allow an attacker, who has physical access to the sensor, to enroll a fingerprint into the 
template database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 00:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>