<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 16:36:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-2655 | SourceCodester AC Repair and Services System Users.php save_users sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2655</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester AC Repair and Services System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function save_users of the file /classes/Users.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 16:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29795 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Update Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29795</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 16:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29806 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29806</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 16:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2654 | SourceCodester AC Repair and Services System manage_service.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2654</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester AC Repair and Services System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/services/manage_service.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 16:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2653 | FoxCMS improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2653</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FoxCMS 1.25 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 15:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0927 | HFS+ filesystem heap overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0927</link><description>Attila Szász discovered that the HFS+ file system implementation in the Linux Kernel contained a heap overflow vulnerability. An attacker could use a specially crafted file system image that, when mounted, could cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 15:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2652 | SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System exposure of information through directory listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2652</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to exposure of information through directory listing. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to change the configuration settings. Multiple sub-directories are affected.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 15:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2651 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop admin exposure of information through directory listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2651</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /oews/admin/. The manipulation leads to exposure of information through directory listing. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to change the configuration settings. Multiple sub-directories are affected.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 14:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27553 | Apache Commons VFS: Possible path traversal issue when using NameScope.DESCENDENT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27553</link><description>Relative Path Traversal vulnerability in Apache Commons VFS before 2.10.0.

The FileObject API in Commons VFS has a 'resolveFile' method that
takes a 'scope' parameter. Specifying 'NameScope.DESCENDENT' promises that "an exception is thrown if the resolved file is not a descendent of
the base file". However, when the path contains encoded ".."
characters (for example, "%2E%2E/bar.txt"), it might return file objects that are not
a descendent of the base file, without throwing an exception.
This issue affects Apache Commons VFS: before 2.10.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.10.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 14:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2691 | Versions of the package nossrf before 1.0.4 are vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) where an attacker can provide a hostname th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2691</link><description>Versions of the package nossrf before 1.0.4 are vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) where an attacker can provide a hostname that resolves to a local or reserved IP address space and bypass the SSRF protection mechanism.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 14:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30474 | Apache Commons VFS: Failing to find an FTP file can reveal the URI&amp;#x27;s password in an error message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30474</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Apache Commons VFS.

The FtpFileObject class can throw an exception when a file is not found, revealing the original URI in its message, which may include a password. The fix is to mask the password in the exception message
This issue affects Apache Commons VFS: before 2.10.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.10.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 14:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2650 | PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System download-medical-cards.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2650</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /download-medical-cards.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 14:08:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2649 | PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System check-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2649</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /check-appointment.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 12:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2648 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System view-enquiry-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2648</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/view-enquiry-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 11:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2647 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2647</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /search.php. The manipulation of the argument Search leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 11:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2646 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System admin-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2646</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument contactnumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 09:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2645 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System product.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2645</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /product.php. The manipulation of the argument artname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 08:46:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2644 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System add-art-product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2644</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/add-art-product.php. The manipulation of the argument arttype leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 08:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2643 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System edit-art-type-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2643</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit-art-type-detail.php?editid=1. The manipulation of the argument arttype leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 07:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2642 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System edit-art-product-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2642</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit-art-product-detail.php?editid=2. The manipulation of the argument editide/sprice/description leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 07:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0718 | Nested Pages &amp;lt; 3.2.13 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0718</link><description>The Nested Pages WordPress plugin before 3.2.13 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributors to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 06:14:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1446 | Pods &amp;lt; 3.2.8.2 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1446</link><description>The Pods  WordPress plugin before 3.2.8.2 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 06:14:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2641 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System edit-artist-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2641</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-artist-detail.php?editid=1. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 04:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2640 | PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System appointment-bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2640</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /doctor/appointment-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 03:41:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2639 | JIZHICMS Article release.html improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2639</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in JIZHICMS up to 1.7.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /user/release.html of the component Article Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 03:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2638 | JIZHICMS Article release.html improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2638</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in JIZHICMS up to 1.7.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /user/release.html of the component Article Handler. The manipulation of the argument ishot with the input 1 leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 02:22:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2637 | JIZHICMS Account Profile Page userinfo.html improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2637</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in JIZHICMS up to 1.7.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/userinfo.html of the component Account Profile Page. The manipulation of the argument jifen leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2628 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System art-enquiry.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2628</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /art-enquiry.php. The manipulation of the argument eid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 21:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2627 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System contactus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2627</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/contactus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 21:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2626 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System edit_case.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2626</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file edit_case.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 20:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2625 | westboy CicadasCMS page sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2625</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in westboy CicadasCMS 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /system/cms/content/page. The manipulation of the argument orderField/orderDirection leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 20:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2624 | westboy CicadasCMS save sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2624</link><description>A vulnerability was found in westboy CicadasCMS 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /system/cms/content/save. The manipulation of the argument content/fujian/laiyuan leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 19:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2623 | westboy CicadasCMS save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2623</link><description>A vulnerability was found in westboy CicadasCMS 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /system/cms/content/save. The manipulation of the argument title/content/laiyuan leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 17:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2622 | aizuda snail-job Workflow-Task Management Module check-node-expression getRuntime deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2622</link><description>A vulnerability was found in aizuda snail-job 1.4.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function getRuntime of the file /snail-job/workflow/check-node-expression of the component Workflow-Task Management Module. The manipulation of the argument nodeExpression leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 17:16:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2621 | D-Link DAP-1620 storage check_dws_cookie stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2621</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DAP-1620 1.03 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function check_dws_cookie of the file /storage. The manipulation of the argument uid leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 16:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2620 | D-Link DAP-1620 Authentication storage mod_graph_auth_uri_handler stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2620</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DAP-1620 1.03 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function mod_graph_auth_uri_handler of the file /storage of the component Authentication Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 14:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2619 | D-Link DAP-1620 Cookie storage check_dws_cookie stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2619</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DAP-1620 1.03. This affects the function check_dws_cookie of the file /storage of the component Cookie Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 14:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2618 | D-Link DAP-1620 Path api set_ws_action heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2618</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DAP-1620 1.03. Affected by this issue is the function set_ws_action of the file /dws/api/ of the component Path Handler. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 13:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2186 | Recover WooCommerce Cart Abandonment, Newsletter, Email Marketing, Marketing Automation By FunnelKit &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;automationId&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2186</link><description>The Recover WooCommerce Cart Abandonment, Newsletter, Email Marketing, Marketing Automation By FunnelKit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘automationId’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 12:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2617 | yangyouwang 杨有旺 crud 简约后台管理系统 Department Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2617</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in yangyouwang 杨有旺 crud 简约后台管理系统 1.0.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Department Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 12:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26796 | Apache Oozie: XSS in Oozie Web Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26796</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apache Oozie.

This issue affects Apache Oozie: all versions.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 12:50:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1970 | Export and Import Users and Customers &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Server-Side Request Forgery via validate_file Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1970</link><description>The Export and Import Users and Customers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2 via the validate_file() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 11:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1971 | Export and Import Users and Customers &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) PHP Object Injection via form_data Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1971</link><description>The Export and Import Users and Customers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'form_data' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 11:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1972 | Export and Import Users and Customers &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Directory Traversal to Authenticated (Administrator+) Limited Arbitrary File Deletion via admin_log_page Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1972</link><description>The Export and Import Users and Customers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the admin_log_page() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to delete arbitrary log files on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 11:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1973 | Export and Import Users and Customers &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Directory Traversal to Authenticated (Administrator+) Limited Arbitrary File Read via download_file Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1973</link><description>The Export and Import Users and Customers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2 via the download_file() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary log files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 11:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2331 | GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform &amp;lt;= 3.22.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2331</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.22.1 via a misconfigured capability check in the 'permissionsCheck' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including reports detailing donors and donation amounts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 11:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2577 | Bitspecter Suite &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2577</link><description>The Bitspecter Suite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 11:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2616 | yangyouwang 杨有旺 crud 简约后台管理系统 Role Management Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2616</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in yangyouwang 杨有旺 crud 简约后台管理系统 1.0.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component Role Management Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 10:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13666 | Fluent Forms – Customizable Contact Forms, Survey, Quiz, &amp;amp; Conversational Form Builder &amp;lt;= 5.2.12 - IP-Spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13666</link><description>The Fluent Forms – Customizable Contact Forms, Survey, Quiz, &amp; Conversational Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP Address Spoofing in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.12 due to insufficient IP address validation and use of user-supplied HTTP headers as a primary method for IP retrieval. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers spoof their IP address and submit forms that may have IP-based restrictions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 08:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13768 | CITS Support svg, webp Media and TTF,OTF File Upload, Use Custom Fonts &amp;lt;= 4.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Font Assignment Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13768</link><description>The CITS Support svg, webp Media and TTF,OTF File Upload, Use Custom Fonts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the cits_assign_fonts_tab() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete font assignments via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13856 | Make Builder &amp;lt;= 1.1.10 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Server-Side Request Forgery via make_builder_ajax_subscribe Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13856</link><description>The Your Friendly Drag and Drop Page Builder — Make Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.10 via the make_builder_ajax_subscribe() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0807 | CITS Support svg, webp Media and TTF,OTF File Upload, Use Custom Fonts &amp;lt;= 4.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0807</link><description>The CITS Support svg, webp Media and TTF,OTF File Upload, Use Custom Fonts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the cits_settings_tab() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1311 | WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace – REST API &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1311</link><description>The WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace – REST API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in the update_delivery_status() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2303 | Block Logic &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2303</link><description>The Block Logic – Full Gutenberg Block Display Control plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8 via the block_logic_check_logic function. This is due to the unsafe evaluation of user-controlled input. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2477 | CryoKey &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;ckemail&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2477</link><description>The CryoKey plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘ckemail’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2478 | Code Clone &amp;lt;= 0.9 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via snippetId Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2478</link><description>The Code Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘snippetId’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2479 | Easy Custom Admin Bar &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via msg Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2479</link><description>The Easy Custom Admin Bar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘msg’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2482 | Gotcha | Gesture-based Captcha &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via menu Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2482</link><description>The Gotcha | Gesture-based Captcha plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'menu' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2484 | Multi Video Box &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via video_id and group_id Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2484</link><description>The Multi Video Box plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'video_id' and 'group_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13739 | Newsletters &amp;lt;= 4.9.9.7 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via To Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13739</link><description>The Newsletters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the "to" parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.9.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick an admin user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 04:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0723 | ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Groups and Communities &amp;lt;= 5.9.4.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0723</link><description>The ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Groups and Communities plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to blind and time-based SQL Injections via the rid and search parameters in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.4.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 04:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0724 | ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Groups and Communities &amp;lt;= 5.9.4.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0724</link><description>The ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Groups and Communities plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.4.5 via deserialization of untrusted input in the get_user_meta_fields_html function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 04:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1408 | ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Groups and Communities &amp;lt;= 5.9.4.4 - Missing Authorinzation to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Join Group Requests Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1408</link><description>The ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Groups and Communities plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the pm_decline_join_group_request and pm_approve_join_group_request functions in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.4.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to approve or decline join group requests which is normally should be available to administrators only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 04:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13737 | Motors – Car Dealer, Classifieds &amp;amp; Listing &amp;lt;= 1.4.57 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Deletion and Listing Template Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13737</link><description>The Motors – Car Dealer, Classifieds &amp; Listing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability checks on the motors_create_template and motors_delete_template functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.57. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary posts or create listing templates. This issue requires Elementor plugin to be installed, which is a required plugin for Motors Starter Theme.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 03:07:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30472 | Corosync through 3.1.9, if encryption is disabled or the attacker knows the encryption key, has a stack-based buffer overflow in orf_token_e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30472</link><description>Corosync through 3.1.9, if encryption is disabled or the attacker knows the encryption key, has a stack-based buffer overflow in orf_token_endian_convert in exec/totemsrp.c via a large UDP packet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 02:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2609 | MagnusBilling Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Login Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2609</link><description>Improper neutralization of input during web page generation vulnerability in MagnusSolution MagnusBilling login logging allows unauthenticated users to store HTML content in the viewable log component accessible at /mbilling/index.php/logUsers/read" cross-site scripting This vulnerability is associated with program files protected/components/MagnusLog.Php.

This issue affects MagnusBilling: through 7.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 22:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2610 | MagnusBilling Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Alarm Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2610</link><description>Improper neutralization of input during web page generation vulnerability in MagnusSolution MagnusBilling (Alarm Module modules) allows authenticated stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability is associated with program files protected/components/MagnusLog.Php.

This issue affects MagnusBilling: through 7.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 22:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26500 | VxWorks 7 USB Failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26500</link><description>: Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in Wind River Systems VxWorks 7 on VxWorks allows Excessive Allocation.  

Specifically crafted USB packets may lead to the system becoming unavailable

This issue affects VxWorks 7: from 22.06 through 24.03.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 22:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30204 | jwt-go allows excessive memory allocation during header parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30204</link><description>golang-jwt is a Go implementation of JSON Web Tokens. Prior to 
5.2.2 and 4.5.2, the function parse.ParseUnverified splits (via a call to strings.Split) its argument (which is untrusted data) on periods. As a result, in the face of a malicious request whose Authorization header consists of Bearer  followed by many period characters, a call to that function incurs allocations to the tune of O(n) bytes (where n stands for the length of the function's argument), with a constant factor of about 16. This issue is fixed in 5.2.2 and 4.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 21:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2608 | PHPGurukul Banquet Booking System view-user-queries.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2608</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Banquet Booking System 1.2. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/view-user-queries.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 21:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2606 | SourceCodester Best Church Management Software soulwinning_crud.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2606</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Church Management Software 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/app/soulwinning_crud.php. The manipulation of the argument photo/photo1 leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 21:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2607 | phplaozhang LzCMS-LaoZhangBoKeXiTong HTTP POST Request upimage.html unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2607</link><description>A vulnerability was found in phplaozhang LzCMS-LaoZhangBoKeXiTong up to 1.1.4. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/upload/upimage.html of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 21:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2604 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System edit_act.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2604</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file edit_act.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 20:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2603 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System deactivate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2603</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file deactivate.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 20:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2601 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System activate_reg.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2601</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file activate_reg.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 19:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2602 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System deactivate_reg.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2602</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file deactivate_reg.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 19:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25036 | Jalios JPlatform 10 Authenticated XML External Entity Injection (XXE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25036</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in Jalios JPlatform allows XML Injection.This issue affects all versions of JPlatform 10 before 10.0.8 (SP8).</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 19:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25035 | Jalios JPlatform 10 Multiple Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25035</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Jalios JPlatform 10 allows for Reflected XSS and Stored XSS.This issue affects JPlatform 10: before 10.0.8 (SP8), before 10.0.7 (SP7), before 10.0.6 (SP6) and Jalios Workplace 6.2, Jalios Workplace 6.1, Jalios Workplace 6.0, and Jalios Workplace 5.3 to 5.5</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 19:11:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53351 | Insecure permissions in pipecd v0.49 allow attackers to gain access to the service account's token, leading to escalation of privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53351</link><description>Insecure permissions in pipecd v0.49 allow attackers to gain access to the service account's token, leading to escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29223 | Linksys E5600 v1.1.0.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the pt parameter in the traceRoute function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29223</link><description>Linksys E5600 v1.1.0.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the pt parameter in the traceRoute function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53350 | Insecure permissions in kubeslice v1.3.1 allow attackers to gain access to the service account's token, leading to escalation of privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53350</link><description>Insecure permissions in kubeslice v1.3.1 allow attackers to gain access to the service account's token, leading to escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29226 | In Linksys E5600 V1.1.0.26, the \usr\share\lua\runtime.lua file contains a command injection vulnerability in the runtime.pingTest function ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29226</link><description>In Linksys E5600 V1.1.0.26, the \usr\share\lua\runtime.lua file contains a command injection vulnerability in the runtime.pingTest function via the pt["count"] parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29227 | In Linksys E5600 V1.1.0.26, the \usr\share\lua\runtime.lua file contains a command injection vulnerability in the runtime.pingTest function ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29227</link><description>In Linksys E5600 V1.1.0.26, the \usr\share\lua\runtime.lua file contains a command injection vulnerability in the runtime.pingTest function via the pt["pkgsize"] parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29230 | Linksys E5600 v1.1.0.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the runtime.emailReg function. The vulnerability can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29230</link><description>Linksys E5600 v1.1.0.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the runtime.emailReg function. The vulnerability can be triggered via the `pt["email"]` parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30349 | Horde IMP through 6.2.27, as used with Horde Application Framework through 5.2.23, allows XSS that leads to account takeover via a crafted t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30349</link><description>Horde IMP through 6.2.27, as used with Horde Application Framework through 5.2.23, allows XSS that leads to account takeover via a crafted text/html e-mail message with an onerror attribute (that may use base64-encoded JavaScript code), as exploited in the wild in March 2025.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-16151 | An improper neutralization of input during web page generation vulnerability [CWE-79] in FortiOS 6.4.1 and below, 6.2.9 and below may allow ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16151</link><description>An improper neutralization of input during web page generation vulnerability [CWE-79] in FortiOS 6.4.1 and below, 6.2.9 and below may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to either redirect users to malicious websites via a crafted "Host" header or to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser context.
This happens when the FortiGate has web filtering and category override enabled/configured.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43029 | IBM Storage Virtualize vSphere Remote Plug-in information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43029</link><description>IBM Storage Virtualize vSphere Remote Plug-in 1.0 and 1.1 could allow a remote user to obtain sensitive credential information after deployment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 15:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53349 | Insecure permissions in kuadrant v0.11.3 allow attackers to gain access to the service account's token, leading to escalation of privileges ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53349</link><description>Insecure permissions in kuadrant v0.11.3 allow attackers to gain access to the service account's token, leading to escalation of privileges via the secretes component in the k8s cluster</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 15:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53348 | LoxiLB v.0.9.7 and before is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control which allows attackers to obtain sensitive information and escalate priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53348</link><description>LoxiLB v.0.9.7 and before is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control which allows attackers to obtain sensitive information and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 15:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29641 | Phpgurukul Vehicle Record Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /index.php via the 'searchinputdata' parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29641</link><description>Phpgurukul Vehicle Record Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /index.php via the 'searchinputdata' parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 15:17:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-25635 | Content Manipulation with Certificate Validation Attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25635</link><description>An Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability in LibreOffice allowed 
an attacker to self sign an ODF document, with a signature untrusted by 
the target, then modify it to change the signature algorithm to an 
invalid (or unknown to LibreOffice) algorithm and LibreOffice would incorrectly present such a signature with an unknown algorithm as a 
valid signature issued by a trusted person


This issue affects LibreOffice: from 7.0 before 7.0.5, from 7.1 before 7.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 14:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30168 | Parse Server has an OAuth login vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30168</link><description>Parse Server is an open source backend that can be deployed to any infrastructure that can run Node.js. Prior to 7.5.2 and 8.0.2, the 3rd party authentication handling of Parse Server allows the authentication credentials of some specific authentication providers to be used across multiple Parse Server apps. For example, if a user signed up using the same authentication provider in two unrelated Parse Server apps, the credentials stored by one app can be used to authenticate the same user in the other app. Note that this only affects Parse Server apps that specifically use an affected 3rd party authentication provider for user authentication, for example by setting the Parse Server option auth to configure a Parse Server authentication adapter. The fix of this vulnerability requires to upgrade Parse Server to a version that includes the bug fix, as well as upgrade the client app to send a secure payload, which is different from the previous insecure payload. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.5.2 and 8.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 14:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29640 | Phpgurukul Human Metapneumovirus (HMPV) – Testing Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /patient-report.php via the param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29640</link><description>Phpgurukul Human Metapneumovirus (HMPV) – Testing Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /patient-report.php via the parameter searchdata..</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 14:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30157 | Envoy crashes when HTTP ext_proc processes local replies</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30157</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native high-performance edge/middle/service proxy. Prior to 1.33.1, 1.32.4, 1.31.6, and 1.30.10, Envoy's ext_proc HTTP filter is at risk of crashing if a local reply is sent to the external server due to the filter's life time issue. A known situation is the failure of a websocket handshake will trigger a local reply leading to the crash of Envoy. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.33.1, 1.32.4, 1.31.6, and 1.30.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 14:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29927 | Authorization Bypass in Next.js Middleware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29927</link><description>Next.js is a React framework for building full-stack web applications. Prior to 14.2.25 and 15.2.3, it is possible to bypass authorization checks within a Next.js application, if the authorization check occurs in middleware. If patching to a safe version is infeasible, it is recommend that you prevent external user requests which contain the x-middleware-subrequest header from reaching your Next.js application. This vulnerability is fixed in 14.2.25 and 15.2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 14:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2593 | FastCMS list sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2593</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FastCMS up to 0.1.5 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /api/client/article/list. The manipulation of the argument orderBy leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 14:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27612 | Libcontainer is affected by capabilities elevation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27612</link><description>libcontainer is a library for container control. Prior to libcontainer 0.5.3, while creating a tenant container, the tenant builder accepts a list of capabilities to be added in the spec of tenant container. The logic here adds the given capabilities to all capabilities of main container if present in spec, otherwise simply set provided capabilities as capabilities of the tenant container. However, setting inherited caps in any case for tenant container can lead to elevation of capabilities, similar to CVE-2022-29162. This does not affect youki binary itself. This is only applicable if you are using libcontainer directly and using the tenant builder.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 14:35:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24915 | When installing Nessus Agent to a non-default location on a Windows host, Nessus Agent versions prior to 10.8.3 did not enforce secure permi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24915</link><description>When installing Nessus Agent to a non-default location on a Windows host, Nessus Agent versions prior to 10.8.3 did not enforce secure permissions for sub-directories.  This could allow for local privilege escalation if users had not secured the directories in the non-default installation location.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 14:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2598 | AWS CDK CLI prints AWS credentials retrieved by custom credential plugins</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2598</link><description>When the AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK) Command Line Interface (AWS CDK CLI) is used with a credential plugin which returns an expiration property with the retrieved AWS credentials, the credentials are printed to the console output. To mitigate this issue, users should upgrade to version 2.178.2 or later and ensure any forked or derivative code is patched to incorporate the new fixes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 14:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2592 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp CSMLoader.cpp InternReadFile heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2592</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. This issue affects the function CSMImporter::InternReadFile of the file code/AssetLib/CSM/CSMLoader.cpp. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is named 2690e354da0c681db000cfd892a55226788f2743. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 14:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57490 | Guangzhou Hongfan Technology Co., LTD. iOffice20 has any user login vulnerability. An attacker can log in to any system account including th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57490</link><description>Guangzhou Hongfan Technology Co., LTD. iOffice20 has any user login vulnerability. An attacker can log in to any system account including the system administrator through a logical flaw.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 13:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2591 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp MDLLoader.cpp InternReadFile_Quake1 divide by zero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2591</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. This vulnerability affects the function MDLImporter::InternReadFile_Quake1 of the file code/AssetLib/MDL/MDLLoader.cpp. The manipulation of the argument skinwidth/skinheight leads to divide by zero. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is identified as ab66a1674fcfac87aaba4c8b900b315ebc3e7dbd. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 13:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2590 | code-projects Human Resource Management System recruitment.go UpdateRecruitmentById cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2590</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Human Resource Management System 1.0.1. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function UpdateRecruitmentById of the file \handler\recruitment.go. The manipulation of the argument c leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 13:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2589 | code-projects Human Resource Management System Account.go Index improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2589</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Human Resource Management System 1.0.1 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function Index of the file \handler\Account.go. The manipulation of the argument user_cookie leads to improper authorization. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 12:55:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2587 | Jinher OA C6 IncentivePlanFulfillAppprove.aspx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2587</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Jinher OA C6 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file IncentivePlanFulfillAppprove.aspx. The manipulation of the argument httpOID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 12:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2588 | Hercules Augeas fa.c re_case_expand null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2588</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Hercules Augeas 1.14.1 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function re_case_expand of the file src/fa.c. The manipulation of the argument re leads to null pointer dereference. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 12:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2597 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ITIUM 6050</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2597</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in ITIUM 6050 version 5.5.5.2-b3526 from Impact Technologies. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute malicious Javascript code via GET and POST requests to the ‘/index.php’ endpoint and injecting code into the ‘id_session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 11:55:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24920 | Unauthorized Bookmark Creation and Modification in Archived Channels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24920</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.2, 10.3.x &lt;= 10.3.3, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.8, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.0 fail to restrict bookmark creation and updates in archived channels, which allows authenticated users created or update bookmarked in archived channels</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 08:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25068 | Bypassing MFA Enforcement on Plugin Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25068</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.2, 10.3.x &lt;= 10.3.3, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.8, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.0 fail to enforce MFA on plugin endpoints, which allows authenticated attackers to bypass MFA protections via API requests to plugin-specific routes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 08:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25274 | Unauthorized Command Execution in Archived Channels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25274</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.2, 10.3.x &lt;= 10.3.3, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.8 fail to restrict command execution in archived channels, which allows authenticated users to run commands in archived channels.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 08:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27933 | Unauthorized Private-to-Public Channel Conversion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27933</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.2, 10.3.x &lt;= 10.3.3, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.8 fail to fail to enforce channel conversion restrictions, which allows members with permission to convert public channels to private ones to also convert private ones to public</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 08:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30179 | MFA Enforcement Bypass in Search APIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30179</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.2, 10.3.x &lt;= 10.3.3, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.8 fail to enforce MFA on certain search APIs, which allows authenticated attackers to bypass MFA protections via user search, channel search, or team search queries.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 08:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27715 | Auto-Enrollment of Team Admins into Private Channels without explicit consent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27715</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.8 fail to prompt for explicit approval before adding a team admin to a private channel, which team admins to joining private channels via crafted permalink links without explicit consent from them.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 08:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2584 | WebAssembly wabt binary-reader-interp.cc GetReturnCallDropKeepCount heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2584</link><description>A vulnerability was found in WebAssembly wabt 1.0.36. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function BinaryReaderInterp::GetReturnCallDropKeepCount of the file wabt/src/interp/binary-reader-interp.cc. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 07:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13903 | quickjs-ng QuickJS qjs quickjs.c JS_GetRuntime stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13903</link><description>A vulnerability was found in quickjs-ng QuickJS up to 0.8.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function JS_GetRuntime of the file quickjs.c of the component qjs. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 0.9.0 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 99c02eb45170775a9a679c32b45dd4000ea67aff. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 07:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30348 | encodeText in QDom in Qt before 6.8.0 has a complex algorithm involving XML string copy and inline replacement of parts of a string (with re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30348</link><description>encodeText in QDom in Qt before 6.8.0 has a complex algorithm involving XML string copy and inline replacement of parts of a string (with relocation of later data).</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 06:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2582 | SimpleMachines SMF ManageAttachments.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2582</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SimpleMachines SMF 2.1.4 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file ManageAttachments.php. The manipulation of the argument Notice leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 06:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2583 | SimpleMachines SMF ManageNews.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2583</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SimpleMachines SMF 2.1.4. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file ManageNews.php. The manipulation of the argument subject/message leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 06:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30346 | Varnish Cache before 7.6.2 and Varnish Enterprise before 6.0.13r10 allow client-side desync via HTTP/1 requests.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30346</link><description>Varnish Cache before 7.6.2 and Varnish Enterprise before 6.0.13r10 allow client-side desync via HTTP/1 requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 06:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30347 | Varnish Enterprise before 6.0.13r13 allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via an out-of-bounds read for range requests on ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30347</link><description>Varnish Enterprise before 6.0.13r13 allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via an out-of-bounds read for range requests on ephemeral MSE4 stevedore objects.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 06:44:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50053 | Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50053</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ServiceDesk Plus versions below 14920 , ServiceDesk Plus MSP and SupportCentre Plus versions below 14910 are vulnerable to Stored XSS in the task feature.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 06:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30342 | An XSS issue was discovered in OpenSlides before 4.2.5. When submitting descriptions such as Moderator Notes or Agenda Topics, an editor is ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30342</link><description>An XSS issue was discovered in OpenSlides before 4.2.5. When submitting descriptions such as Moderator Notes or Agenda Topics, an editor is shown that allows one to format the submitted text. This allows insertion of various HTML elements. When trying to insert a SCRIPT element, it is properly encoded when reflected; however, adding attributes to links is possible, which allows the injection of JavaScript via the onmouseover attribute and others. When a user moves the mouse over such a prepared link, JavaScript is executed in that user's session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 05:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30343 | A directory traversal issue was discovered in OpenSlides before 4.2.5. Files can be uploaded to OpenSlides meetings and organized in folders...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30343</link><description>A directory traversal issue was discovered in OpenSlides before 4.2.5. Files can be uploaded to OpenSlides meetings and organized in folders. The interface allows users to download a ZIP archive that contains all files in a folder and its subfolders. If an attacker specifies the title of a file or folder as a relative or absolute path (e.g., ../../../etc/passwd), the ZIP archive generated for download converts that title into a path. Depending on the extraction tool used by the user, this might overwrite files locally outside of the chosen directory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 05:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30344 | An issue was discovered in OpenSlides before 4.2.5. During login at the /system/auth/login/ endpoint, the system's response times differ dep...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30344</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenSlides before 4.2.5. During login at the /system/auth/login/ endpoint, the system's response times differ depending on whether a user exists in the system. The timing discrepancy stems from the omitted hashing of the password (e.g., more than 100 milliseconds).</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 05:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30345 | An issue was discovered in OpenSlides before 4.2.5. When creating new chats via the chat_group.create action, the user is able to specify th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30345</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenSlides before 4.2.5. When creating new chats via the chat_group.create action, the user is able to specify the name of the chat. Some HTML elements such as SCRIPT are filtered, whereas others are not. In most cases, HTML entities are encoded properly, but not when deleting chats or deleting messages in these chats. This potentially allows attackers to interfere with the layout of the rendered website, but it is unlikely that victims would click on deleted chats or deleted messages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 05:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2581 | xmedcon DICOM File malloc integer underflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2581</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in xmedcon 0.25.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function malloc of the component DICOM File Handler. The manipulation leads to integer underflow. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 0.25.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 05:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26336 | Dell Chassis Management Controller Firmware for Dell PowerEdge FX2, version(s) prior to 2.40.200.202101130302, and Dell Chassis Management C...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26336</link><description>Dell Chassis Management Controller Firmware for Dell PowerEdge FX2, version(s) prior to 2.40.200.202101130302, and Dell Chassis Management Controller Firmware for Dell PowerEdge VRTX version(s) prior to 3.41.200.202209300499, contain(s) a Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Remote execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 03:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2585 | EBM Technologies EBM Maintenance Center - SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2585</link><description>EBM Maintenance Center From EBM Technologies has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 02:39:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28207 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.3, macOS Monterey 12.6.4, macOS Big Sur 11.7.5. A plug...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28207</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.3, macOS Monterey 12.6.4, macOS Big Sur 11.7.5. A plug-in may be able to inherit app permissions and access user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 01:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29807 | Microsoft Dataverse Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29807</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 01:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29814 | Microsoft Partner Center Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29814</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 01:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>