<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 07:28:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-43884 | Bluetooth: MGMT: Add error handling to pair_device()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43884</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: MGMT: Add error handling to pair_device()

hci_conn_params_add() never checks for a NULL value and could lead to a NULL
pointer dereference causing a crash.

Fixed by adding error handling in the function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 07:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45241 | A traversal vulnerability in GeneralDocs.aspx in CentralSquare CryWolf (False Alarm Management) through 2024-08-09 allows unauthenticated at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45241</link><description>A traversal vulnerability in GeneralDocs.aspx in CentralSquare CryWolf (False Alarm Management) through 2024-08-09 allows unauthenticated attackers to read files outside of the working web directory via the rpt parameter, leading to the disclosure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 06:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45256 | An arbitrary file write issue in the exfiltration endpoint in BYOB (Build Your Own Botnet) 2.0 allows attackers to overwrite SQLite database...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45256</link><description>An arbitrary file write issue in the exfiltration endpoint in BYOB (Build Your Own Botnet) 2.0 allows attackers to overwrite SQLite databases and bypass authentication via an unauthenticated HTTP request with a crafted parameter. This occurs in file_add in api/files/routes.py.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 06:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41996 | Validating the order of the public keys in the Diffie-Hellman Key Agreement Protocol, when an approved safe prime is used, allows remote att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41996</link><description>Validating the order of the public keys in the Diffie-Hellman Key Agreement Protocol, when an approved safe prime is used, allows remote attackers (from the client side) to trigger unnecessarily expensive server-side DHE modular-exponentiation calculations. The client may cause asymmetric resource consumption. The basic attack scenario is that the client must claim that it can only communicate with DHE, and the server must be configured to allow DHE and validate the order of the public key.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 06:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6879 | Quiz and Survey Master (QSM) &amp;lt; 9.1.1 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6879</link><description>The Quiz and Survey Master (QSM)  WordPress plugin before 9.1.1 fails to validate and escape certain Quiz fields before displaying them on a page or post where the Quiz is embedded, which could allows contributor and above roles to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 06:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7313 | Shield Security &amp;lt; 20.0.6 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7313</link><description>The Shield Security  WordPress plugin before 20.0.6 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 06:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8073 | Command Injection Vulnerability in Hillstone Networks Web Application Firewall</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8073</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Hillstone Networks Hillstone Networks Web Application Firewall on 5.5R6 allows Command Injection.This issue affects Hillstone Networks Web Application Firewall: from 5.5R6-2.6.7 through 5.5R6-2.8.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 02:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8154 | SourceCodester QR Code Bookmark System Parameter update-bookmark.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8154</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester QR Code Bookmark System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /endpoint/update-bookmark.php of the component Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument tbl_bookmark_id/name/url leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 23:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8155 | ContiNew Admin tree sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8155</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in ContiNew Admin 3.2.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function top.continew.starter.extension.crud.controller.BaseController#tree of the file /api/system/dept/tree?sort=parentId%2Casc&amp;amp;sort=sort%2Casc. The manipulation of the argument sort leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 23:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8152 | SourceCodester QR Code Bookmark System Parameter add-bookmark.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8152</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester QR Code Bookmark System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /endpoint/add-bookmark.php of the component Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument name/url leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 22:42:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8153 | SourceCodester QR Code Bookmark System delete-bookmark.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8153</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester QR Code Bookmark System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /endpoint/delete-bookmark.php. The manipulation of the argument bookmark leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 22:42:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8150 | ContiNew Admin user sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8150</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ContiNew Admin 3.2.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function top.continew.starter.extension.crud.controller.BaseController#page of the file /api/system/user?deptId=1&amp;amp;page=1&amp;amp;size=10. The manipulation of the argument sort leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 22:17:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8151 | SourceCodester Interactive Map with Marker delete-mark.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8151</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Interactive Map with Marker 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /endpoint/delete-mark.php. The manipulation of the argument mark leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 22:17:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8158 | User impersonation for lib9p based 9p fileservers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8158</link><description>A bug in the 9p authentication implementation within lib9p allows an attacker with an existing valid user within the configured auth server to impersonate any other valid filesystem user.

This is due to lib9p not properly verifying that the uname given in the Tauth and Tattach 9p messages matches the client UID returned from the factotum authentication handshake.


The only filesystem making use of these functions within the base 9front systems is the experimental hjfs disk filesystem, other disk filesystems (cwfs and gefs) are not affected by this bug.

This bug was inherited from Plan 9 and is present in all versions of 9front and is remedied fully in commit 9645ae07eb66a59015e3e118d0024790c37400da.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 21:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45258 | The req package before 3.43.4 for Go may send an unintended request when a malformed URL is provided, because cleanHost in http.go intention...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45258</link><description>The req package before 3.43.4 for Go may send an unintended request when a malformed URL is provided, because cleanHost in http.go intentionally uses a "garbage in, garbage out" design.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 21:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48957 | PureVPN Linux client 2.0.2-Productions fails to properly handle DNS queries, allowing them to bypass the VPN tunnel and be sent directly to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48957</link><description>PureVPN Linux client 2.0.2-Productions fails to properly handle DNS queries, allowing them to bypass the VPN tunnel and be sent directly to the ISP or default DNS servers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 16:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8011 | Logitech Options+ on MacOS prior 1.72 allows a local attacker to inject dynamic library within Options+ runtime and abuse permissions grante...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8011</link><description>Logitech Options+ on MacOS prior 1.72 allows a local attacker to inject dynamic library within Options+ runtime and abuse permissions granted by the user to Options+ such as Camera.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 11:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8147 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8147</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /index.php?action=editPharmacist. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8146 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8146</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php?action=editSalesman. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 08:22:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42340 | CyberArk - CWE-602: Client-Side Enforcement of Server-Side Security</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42340</link><description>CyberArk - CWE-602: Client-Side Enforcement of Server-Side Security</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 07:27:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42337 | CyberArk -  CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42337</link><description>CyberArk -  CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 07:17:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42338 | CyberArk -  CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42338</link><description>CyberArk -  CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 07:17:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42339 | CyberArk -  CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42339</link><description>CyberArk -  CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 07:17:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8145 | ClassCMS Article admin cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8145</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in ClassCMS 4.8. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php/admin of the component Article Handler. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to basic cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 05:46:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8144 | ClassCMS Logo admin cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8144</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in ClassCMS 4.8. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php/admin of the component Logo Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 03:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8142 | SourceCodester Daily Calories Monitoring Tool delete-calorie.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8142</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Daily Calories Monitoring Tool 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /endpoint/delete-calorie.php. The manipulation of the argument calorie leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 02:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8141 | SourceCodester Daily Calories Monitoring Tool add-calorie.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8141</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Daily Calories Monitoring Tool 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /endpoint/add-calorie.php. The manipulation of the argument calorie_date/calorie_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 02:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45244 | Hyperledger Fabric through 2.5.9 does not verify that a request has a timestamp within the expected time window.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45244</link><description>Hyperledger Fabric through 2.5.9 does not verify that a request has a timestamp within the expected time window.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 01:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8140 | SourceCodester Task Progress Tracker update-task.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8140</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Task Progress Tracker 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file update-task.php. The manipulation of the argument task_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 01:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8139 | itsourcecode E-Commerce Website search_list.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8139</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode E-Commerce Website 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file search_list.php. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 01:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8138 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System Parameter index.php editManager sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8138</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0. Affected is the function editManager of the file /index.php?action=editManager of the component Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument id as part of String leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 01:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8137 | SourceCodester Record Management System search_user.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8137</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file search_user.php. The manipulation of the argument search leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 23:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45240 | The TikTok (aka com.zhiliaoapp.musically) application before 34.5.5 for Android allows the takeover of Lynxview JavaScript interfaces via de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45240</link><description>The TikTok (aka com.zhiliaoapp.musically) application before 34.5.5 for Android allows the takeover of Lynxview JavaScript interfaces via deeplink traversal (in the application's exposed WebView). (On Android 12 and later, this is only exploitable by third-party applications.)</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45234 | An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45234</link><description>An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync or RRDP) an ROA or a Manifest containing a signedAttrs encoded in non-canonical form. This bypasses Fort's BER decoder, reaching a point in the code that panics when faced with data not encoded in DER. Because Fort is an RPKI Relying Party, a panic can lead to Route Origin Validation unavailability, which can lead to compromised routing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45235 | An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45235</link><description>An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync or RRDP) a resource certificate containing an Authority Key Identifier extension that lacks the keyIdentifier field. Fort references this pointer without sanitizing it first. Because Fort is an RPKI Relying Party, a crash can lead to Route Origin Validation unavailability, which can lead to compromised routing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45236 | An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45236</link><description>An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync or RRDP) a signed object containing an empty signedAttributes field. Fort accesses the set's elements without sanitizing it first. Because Fort is an RPKI Relying Party, a crash can lead to Route Origin Validation unavailability, which can lead to compromised routing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45237 | An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45237</link><description>An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync or RRDP) a resource certificate containing a Key Usage extension composed of more than two bytes of data. Fort writes this string into a 2-byte buffer without properly sanitizing its length, leading to a buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45238 | An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45238</link><description>An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync or RRDP) a resource certificate containing a bit string that doesn't properly decode into a Subject Public Key. OpenSSL does not report this problem during parsing, and when compiled with OpenSSL libcrypto versions below 3, Fort recklessly dereferences the pointer. Because Fort is an RPKI Relying Party, a crash can lead to Route Origin Validation unavailability, which can lead to compromised routing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45239 | An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45239</link><description>An issue was discovered in Fort before 1.6.3. A malicious RPKI repository that descends from a (trusted) Trust Anchor can serve (via rsync or RRDP) an ROA or a Manifest containing a null eContent field. Fort dereferences the pointer without sanitizing it first. Because Fort is an RPKI Relying Party, a crash can lead to Route Origin Validation unavailability, which can lead to compromised routing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8136 | SourceCodester Record Management System sort1_user.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8136</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file sort1_user.php. The manipulation of the argument position leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8135 | Go-Tribe gotribe token.go Sign hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8135</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Go-Tribe gotribe up to cd3ccd32cd77852c9ea73f986eaf8c301cfb6310. Affected is the function Sign of the file pkg/token/token.go. The manipulation of the argument config.key leads to hard-coded credentials. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The patch is identified as 4fb9b9e80a2beedd09d9fde4b9cf5bd510baf18f. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 21:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8134 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 HTTP POST Request hd_config.cgi cgi_FMT_Std2R5_1st_DiskMGR command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8134</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function cgi_FMT_Std2R5_1st_DiskMGR of the file /cgi-bin/hd_config.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_source_dev leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 20:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8133 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 HTTP POST Request hd_config.cgi cgi_FMT_R5_SpareDsk_DiskMGR command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8133</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function cgi_FMT_R5_SpareDsk_DiskMGR of the file /cgi-bin/hd_config.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_source_dev leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 19:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8132 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 HTTP POST Request webdav_mgr.cgi webdav_mgr command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8132</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function webdav_mgr of the file /cgi-bin/webdav_mgr.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_path leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 18:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8131 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 HTTP POST Request apkg_mgr.cgi module_enable_disable command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8131</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function module_enable_disable of the file /cgi-bin/apkg_mgr.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_module_name leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 17:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8130 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 HTTP POST Request s3.cgi cgi_s3 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8130</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cgi_s3 of the file /cgi-bin/s3.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_a_key leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 16:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8129 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 HTTP POST Request s3.cgi cgi_s3_modify command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8129</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. Affected is the function cgi_s3_modify of the file /cgi-bin/s3.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_job_name leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 15:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7656 | Image Hotspot by DevVN &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Authenticated (Author+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7656</link><description>The Image Hotspot by DevVN plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'devvn_ihotspot_shortcode_func' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 11:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8128 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 HTTP POST Request webfile_mgr.cgi cgi_add_zip command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8128</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This issue affects the function cgi_add_zip of the file /cgi-bin/webfile_mgr.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument path leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 11:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43915 | IBM App Connect Enterprise Certified Container</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43915</link><description>IBM App Connect Enterprise Certified Container 5.0, 7.1, 7.2, 8.0, 8.1, 8.2, 9.0, 9.1, 9.2, 10.0, 10.1, 11.0, 11.1, 11.2, 11.3, 11.4, 11.5, 11.6, 12.0, and 12.1 does not limit calls to unshare in running Pods.  This can allow a user with access to execute commands in a running Pod to elevate their user privileges.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 11:28:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8127 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 HTTP POST Request webfile_mgr.cgi cgi_unzip command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8127</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This vulnerability affects the function cgi_unzip of the file /cgi-bin/webfile_mgr.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument path leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 09:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7351 | Simple Job Board &amp;lt;= 2.12.3 - Authenticated (Editor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7351</link><description>The Simple Job Board plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.3 via deserialization of untrusted input when editing job applications. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 07:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6499 | WordPress Button Plugin MaxButtons &amp;lt;= 9.7.8 - Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6499</link><description>The WordPress Button Plugin MaxButtons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to information exposure in all versions up to, and including, 9.7.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain the full path to instances, which they may be able to use in combination with other vulnerabilities or to simplify reconnaissance work. On its own, this information is of very limited use.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 03:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2254 | RT Easy Builder – Advanced addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2254</link><description>The RT Easy Builder – Advanced addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 02:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6631 | ImageRecycle pdf &amp;amp; image compression &amp;lt;= 3.1.14 - Missing Authorization in Several AJAX Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6631</link><description>The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on several AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.14. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to perform unauthorized actions, such as updating plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 02:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8120 | ImageRecycle pdf &amp;amp; image compression &amp;lt;= 3.1.14 - Cross-Site Request in Several AJAX Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8120</link><description>The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.14. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on several functions in the class/class-image-otimizer.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings along with performing other actions via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 02:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-0926 | Custom Permalinks &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 - Authenticated(Editor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0926</link><description>The Custom Permalinks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including, 2.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on tag names. This allows authenticated users, with editor-level permissions or greater to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page, even when 'unfiltered_html' has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 02:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6987 | String Locator &amp;lt;= 2.6.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6987</link><description>The String locator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'sql-column' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This required WP_DEBUG to be enabled in order to be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 02:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7568 | Favicon Generator &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7568</link><description>The Favicon Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.5. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the output_sub_admin_page_0 function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files on the server via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. The plugin author deleted the functionality of the plugin to patch this issue and close the plugin, we recommend seeking an alternative to this plugin.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 02:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>