<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 07:45:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-15235 | Quanta Computer｜QOCA aim AI Medical Cloud Platform - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15235</link><description>QOCA aim AI Medical Cloud Platform developed by Quanta Computer has a Missing Authorization vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to modify specific network packet parameters, enabling certain system functions to access other users' files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 07:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0580 | SourceCodester API Key Manager App Import Key cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0580</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester API Key Manager App 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Import Key Handler. Performing a manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 07:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15462 | UTT 进取 520W ConfigAdvideo strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15462</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. This issue affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/ConfigAdvideo. The manipulation of the argument timestart leads to buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 07:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15461 | UTT 进取 520W formTaskEdit strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15461</link><description>A flaw has been found in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. This vulnerability affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/formTaskEdit. Executing a manipulation of the argument selDateType can lead to buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 06:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14124 | Team &amp;lt; 5.0.11 - Unauthenticated SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14124</link><description>The Team  WordPress plugin before 5.0.11 does not properly sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement via an AJAX action available to unauthenticated users, leading to a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 06:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15460 | UTT 进取 520W formPptpClientConfig strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15460</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. This affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/formPptpClientConfig. Performing a manipulation of the argument EncryptionMode results in buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 06:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9543 | FlexTable Google Sheets Connector &amp;lt; 3.19.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9543</link><description>The FlexTable  WordPress plugin before 3.19.2 does not sanitise and escape the imported links from Google Sheet cells, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 06:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15459 | UTT 进取 520W formUser strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15459</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. Affected by this issue is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formUser. Such manipulation of the argument passwd1 leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 05:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15458 | bg5sbk MiniCMS Article post-edit.php improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15458</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in bg5sbk MiniCMS up to 1.8. This affects an unknown function of the file /mc-admin/post-edit.php of the component Article Handler. Executing a manipulation can lead to improper authentication. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 05:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15457 | bg5sbk MiniCMS Trash File Restore post.php improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15457</link><description>A vulnerability was found in bg5sbk MiniCMS up to 1.8. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /minicms/mc-admin/post.php of the component Trash File Restore Handler. Performing a manipulation results in improper authentication. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 05:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15456 | bg5sbk MiniCMS Publish page-edit.php improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15456</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in bg5sbk MiniCMS up to 1.8. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /mc-admin/page-edit.php of the component Publish Page Handler. Such manipulation leads to improper authentication. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The existence of this vulnerability is still disputed at present. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 05:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15455 | bg5sbk MiniCMS File Recovery Request page.php delete_page improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15455</link><description>A flaw has been found in bg5sbk MiniCMS up to 1.8. Impacted is the function delete_page of the file /minicms/mc-admin/page.php of the component File Recovery Request Handler. This manipulation causes improper authentication. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15453 | milvus HTTP Endpoint expr.go expr.Exec deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15453</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in milvus up to 2.6.7. This vulnerability affects the function expr.Exec of the file pkg/util/expr/expr.go of the component HTTP Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument code leads to deserialization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. A fix is planned for the next release 2.6.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15454 | zhanglun lettura RSS ContentRender.tsx cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15454</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in zhanglun lettura up to 0.1.22. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file src/components/ArticleView/ContentRender.tsx of the component RSS Handler. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. The patch is identified as 67213093db9923e828a6e3fd8696a998c85da2d4. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15451 | xnx3 wangmarket System Variables variableSave.do cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15451</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in xnx3 wangmarket up to 4.9. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/system/variableSave.do of the component System Variables Page. Performing a manipulation of the argument Description results in cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15452 | xnx3 wangmarket Backend Variable Search variableList.do variableList cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15452</link><description>A weakness has been identified in xnx3 wangmarket up to 4.9. This affects the function variableList of the file /admin/system/variableList.do of the component Backend Variable Search. Executing a manipulation of the argument Description can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15450 | sfturing hosp_order orderHos findOrderHosNum sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15450</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in sfturing hosp_order up to 627f426331da8086ce8fff2017d65b1ddef384f8. Affected by this vulnerability is the function findOrderHosNum of the file /ssm_pro/orderHos/. Such manipulation of the argument hospitalAddress/hospitalName leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 01:59:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15449 | cld378632668 JavaMall MinioController.java delete path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15449</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in cld378632668 JavaMall up to 994f1e2b019378ec9444cdf3fce2d5b5f72d28f0. Affected is the function delete of the file src/main/java/com/macro/mall/controller/MinioController.java. This manipulation of the argument objectName causes path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 01:59:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15448 | cld378632668 JavaMall MinioController.java upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15448</link><description>A vulnerability was found in cld378632668 JavaMall up to 994f1e2b019378ec9444cdf3fce2d5b5f72d28f0. This impacts the function Upload of the file src/main/java/com/macro/mall/controller/MinioController.java. The manipulation results in unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 01:59:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5591 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in Kentico Xperience 13</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5591</link><description>Kentico Xperience 13 is vulnerable to a stored cross-site scripting attack via a form component, allowing an attacker to hijack a victim user’s session and perform actions in their security context.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 01:59:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15447 | Seeyon Zhiyuan OA Web Application System assetsService.j%73p sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15447</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Seeyon Zhiyuan OA Web Application System up to 20251223. This affects an unknown function of the file /assetsGroupReport/assetsService.j%73p. The manipulation of the argument unitCode leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 23:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15446 | Seeyon Zhiyuan OA Web Application System fixedAssetsList.j%73p sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15446</link><description>A flaw has been found in Seeyon Zhiyuan OA Web Application System up to 20251223. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /assetsGroupReport/fixedAssetsList.j%73p. Executing a manipulation of the argument unitCode can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 23:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0579 | code-projects Online Product Reservation System POST Parameter edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0579</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Product Reservation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /handgunner-administrator/edit.php of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument prod_id/name/price/model/serial results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 12:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0578 | code-projects Online Product Reservation System delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0578</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Online Product Reservation System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /handgunner-administrator/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 12:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15443 | CRMEB product_export sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15443</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in CRMEB up to 5.6.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /adminapi/product/product_export. Such manipulation of the argument cate_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 11:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15442 | CRMEB product_list sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15442</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in CRMEB up to 5.6.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /adminapi/export/product_list. This manipulation of the argument cate_id causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 11:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0577 | code-projects Online Product Reservation System prod.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0577</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Online Product Reservation System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /handgunner-administrator/prod.php. Executing manipulation can lead to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14830 | JFrog Artifactory Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14830</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in JFrog Artifactory (Workers) allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Artifactory (Workers): from &gt;=7.94.0 through &lt;7.117.10.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0576 | code-projects Online Product Reservation System Parameter prod.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0576</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Online Product Reservation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /handgunner-administrator/prod.php of the component Parameter Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument cat/price/name/model/serial results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0575 | code-projects Online Product Reservation System Administrator Login adminlogin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0575</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Online Product Reservation System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /handgunner-administrator/adminlogin.php of the component Administrator Login. Such manipulation of the argument emailadd/pass leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 06:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0574 | yeqifu warehouse Request UserController.java saveUserRole improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0574</link><description>A weakness has been identified in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. This affects the function saveUserRole of the file warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\UserController.java of the component Request Handler. This manipulation causes improper authorization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery. Therefore, version details for affected or updated releases cannot be specified.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 03:10:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15115 | Petlibro Smart Pet Feeder Platform through 1.7.31 Authentication Bypass via API endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15115</link><description>Petlibro Smart Pet Feeder Platform versions up to 1.7.31 contains an authentication bypass vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to access any user account by exploiting OAuth token validation flaws in the social login system. Attackers can send requests to /member/auth/thirdLogin with arbitrary Google IDs and phoneBrand parameters to obtain full session tokens and account access without proper OAuth verification.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 23:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3646 | Petlibro Smart Pet Feeder Platform through 1.7.31 Authorization Bypass via Device Share API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3646</link><description>Petlibro Smart Pet Feeder Platform versions up to 1.7.31 contains an authorization bypass vulnerability that allows unauthorized users to add users as shared owners to any device by exploiting missing permission checks. Attackers can send requests to the device share API to gain unauthorized access to devices and view owner information without proper authorization validation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 23:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3652 | Petlibro Smart Pet Feeder Platform through 1.7.31 Audio Information Disclosure via API endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3652</link><description>Petlibro Smart Pet Feeder Platform versions up to 1.7.31 contains an information disclosure vulnerability that allows unauthorized access to private audio recordings by exploiting sequential audio IDs and insecure assignment endpoints. Attackers can send requests to /device/deviceAudio/use with arbitrary audio IDs to assign recordings to any device, then retrieve audio URLs to access other users' private recordings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 23:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3653 | Petlibro Smart Pet Feeder through 1.7.31 Platform Improper Access Control via API endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3653</link><description>Petlibro Smart Pet Feeder Platform versions up to 1.7.31 contains an improper access control vulnerability that allows unauthorized device manipulation by accepting arbitrary serial numbers without ownership verification. Attackers can control any device by sending serial numbers to device control APIs to change feeding schedules, trigger manual feeds, access camera feeds, and modify device settings without authorization checks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 23:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3654 | Petlibro Smart Pet Feeder Platform through 1.7.31 Information Disclosure via API endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3654</link><description>Petlibro Smart Pet Feeder Platform versions up to 1.7.31 contains an information disclosure vulnerability that allows unauthorized access to device hardware information by exploiting insecure API endpoints. Attackers can retrieve device serial numbers and MAC addresses through /device/devicePetRelation/getBoundDevices using pet IDs, enabling full device control without proper authorization checks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 23:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3660 | Petlibro Smart Pet Feeder Platform through 1.7.31 Broken Access Control via API endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3660</link><description>Petlibro Smart Pet Feeder Platform versions up to 1.7.31 contains a broken access control vulnerability that allows authenticated users to access other users' pet data by exploiting missing ownership verification. Attackers can send requests to /member/pet/detailV2 with arbitrary pet IDs to retrieve sensitive information including pet details, member IDs, and avatar URLs without proper authorization checks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 23:45:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21484 | AnythingLLM Vulnerable to Username Enumeration w/ Password Recovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21484</link><description>AnythingLLM is an application that turns pieces of content into context that any LLM can use as references during chatting. Prior to commit e287fab56089cf8fcea9ba579a3ecdeca0daa313, the password recovery endpoint returns different error messages depending on whether a username exists, so enabling username enumeration. Commit e287fab56089cf8fcea9ba579a3ecdeca0daa313 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 02:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64124 | Nuvation Energy Multi-Stack Controller OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64124</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Nuvation Energy Multi-Stack Controller (MSC) allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects Multi-Stack Controller (MSC): before 2.5.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 02:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64125 | Nuvation Energy nCloud Client-to-Client Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64125</link><description>A vulnerability in Nuvation Energy nCloud VPN Service allowed Network Boundary Bridging.This issue affected the nCloud VPN Service and was fixed on 2025-12-1 (December, 2025). End users do not have to take any action to mitigate the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 02:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>