<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 05:34:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-37528 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability affects HCL BigFix Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37528</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Web Reports component of HCL BigFix Platform can possibly allow an attack to exploit an application parameter during execution of the Save Report.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 05:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1200 | Jspxcms information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1200</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Jspxcms 10.2.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /template/1/default/. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252698 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 02:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31004 | IBM Security Access Manager Container gain access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31004</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow a remote attacker to gain access to the underlying system using man in the middle techniques.  IBM X-Force ID:  254765.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31006 | IBM Security Access Manager Container denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31006</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) is vulnerable to a denial of service attacks on the DSC server.  IBM X-Force ID:  254776.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32327 | IBM Security Access Manager Container XML external entity injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32327</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) is vulnerable to an XML External Entity Injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.  IBM X-Force ID:  254783.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32329 | IBM Security Access Manager Container improper file validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32329</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow a user to download files from an incorrect repository due to improper file validation.  IBM X-Force ID:  254972.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43016 | IBM Security Access Manager Container unauthorized access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43016</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow a remote user to log into the server due to a user account with an empty password.  IBM X-Force ID:  266154.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30999 | IBM Security Access Manager denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30999</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow an attacker to cause a denial of service due to uncontrolled resource consumption.  IBM X-Force ID:  254651.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31005 | IBM Security Access Manager Container privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31005</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow a local user to escalate their privileges due to an improper security configuration.  IBM X-Force ID:  254767.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1199 | CodeAstro Employee Task Management System attendance-info.php denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1199</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CodeAstro Employee Task Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file \employee-tasks-php\attendance-info.php. The manipulation of the argument aten_id leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252697 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1198 | openBI Phar User.php addxinzhi deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1198</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in openBI up to 6.0.3. Affected is the function addxinzhi of the file application/controllers/User.php of the component Phar Handler. The manipulation of the argument outimgurl leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252696.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 23:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1197 | SourceCodester Testimonial Page Manager HTTP GET Request delete-testimonial.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1197</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Testimonial Page Manager 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file delete-testimonial.php of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument testimony leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252695.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 22:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1196 | SourceCodester Testimonial Page Manager HTTP POST Request add-testimonial.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1196</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Testimonial Page Manager 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file add-testimonial.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument name/description/testimony leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-252694 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 22:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1195 | iTop VPN IOCTL ITopVpnCallbackProcess.sys denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1195</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in iTop VPN up to 4.0.0.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality in the library ITopVpnCallbackProcess.sys of the component IOCTL Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack needs to be approached locally. The identifier VDB-252685 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 21:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23553 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability affects HCL BigFix Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23553</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Web Reports component of HCL BigFix Platform exists due to missing a specific http header attribute.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 21:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1194 | Armcode AlienIP Locate Host denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1194</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Armcode AlienIP 2.41. Affected is an unknown function of the component Locate Host Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252684. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 21:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1193 | Navicat MySQL Conecction denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1193</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Navicat 12.0.29. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component MySQL Conecction Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252683. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 20:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37531 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability affects HCL BigFix Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37531</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Web Reports component of HCL BigFix Platform can possibly allow an attacker to execute malicious javascript code into a form field of a webpage by a user with privileged access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 20:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37530 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability affects HCL BigFix Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37530</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Web Reports component of HCL BigFix Platform can possibly allow an attacker to execute malicious javascript code into a webpage trying to retrieve cookie stored information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 20:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1192 | South River WebDrive New Secure WebDAV denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1192</link><description>A vulnerability was found in South River WebDrive 18.00.5057. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component New Secure WebDAV. The manipulation leads to denial of service. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252682 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 20:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37529 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability affects HCL BigFix Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37529</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Web Reports component of HCL BigFix Platform can possibly allow an attacker to execute malicious javascript code into a webpage trying to retrieve cookie stored information.  This is not the same vulnerability as identified in CVE-2023-37530.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 19:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1191 | Hyper CdCatalog HCF File denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1191</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Hyper CdCatalog 2.3.1. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component HCF File Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252681 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 19:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25006 | XenForo before 2.2.14 allows Directory Traversal (with write access) by an authenticated user who has permissions to administer styles, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25006</link><description>XenForo before 2.2.14 allows Directory Traversal (with write access) by an authenticated user who has permissions to administer styles, and uses a ZIP archive for Styles Import.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 19:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1190 | Global Scape CuteFTP denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1190</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Global Scape CuteFTP 9.3.0.3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation of the argument Host/Username/Password leads to denial of service. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252680. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 19:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1189 | AMPPS Encryption Passphrase denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1189</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in AMPPS 2.7 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Encryption Passphrase Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252679. NOTE: The vendor explains that AMPPS 4.0 is a complete overhaul and the code was re-written.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 18:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37527 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability affects HCL BigFix Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37527</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Web Reports component of HCL BigFix Platform can possibly allow an attacker to execute malicious javascript code in the application session or in database, via remote injection, while rendering content in a web page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 18:18:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1188 | Rizone Soft Notepad3 Encryption Passphrase denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1188</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Rizone Soft Notepad3 1.0.2.350. Affected is an unknown function of the component Encryption Passphrase Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252678 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 18:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1187 | Munsoft Easy Outlook Express Recovery Registration Key denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1187</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Munsoft Easy Outlook Express Recovery 2.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Registration Key Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252677 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 17:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1186 | Munsoft Easy Archive Recovery Registration Key denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1186</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Munsoft Easy Archive Recovery 2.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Registration Key Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252676. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 17:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23635 | AntiSamy malicious input can provoke XSS when preserving comments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23635</link><description>AntiSamy is a library for performing fast, configurable cleansing of HTML coming from untrusted sources. Prior to 1.7.5, there is a potential for a mutation XSS (mXSS) vulnerability in AntiSamy caused by flawed parsing of the HTML being sanitized. To be subject to this vulnerability the `preserveComments` directive must be enabled in your policy file. As a result, certain crafty inputs can result in elements in comment tags being interpreted as executable when using AntiSamy's sanitized output. Patched in AntiSamy 1.7.5 and later.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24560 | Vyper external calls can overflow return data to return input buffer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24560</link><description>Vyper is a Pythonic Smart Contract Language for the Ethereum Virtual Machine. When calls to external contracts are made, we write the input buffer starting at byte 28, and allocate the return buffer to start at byte 0 (overlapping with the input buffer). When checking RETURNDATASIZE for dynamic types, the size is compared only to the minimum allowed size for that type, and not to the returned value's length. As a result, malformed return data can cause the contract to mistake data from the input buffer for returndata.  When the called contract returns invalid ABIv2 encoded data, the calling contract can read different invalid data (from the dirty buffer) than the called contract returned.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45036 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45036</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45037 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45037</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47561 | Photo Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47561</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect Photo Station. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Photo Station 6.4.2 ( 2023/12/15 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47562 | Photo Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47562</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect Photo Station. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Photo Station 6.4.2 ( 2023/12/15 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47564 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47564</link><description>An incorrect permission assignment for critical resource vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to read or modify the resource via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
Qsync Central 4.4.0.15 ( 2024/01/04 ) and later
Qsync Central 4.3.0.11 ( 2024/01/11 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47566 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47566</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47567 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47567</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47568 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47568</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50359 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50359</link><description>An unchecked return value vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow local authenticated administrators to place the system in a state that could lead to a crash or other unintended behaviors via unspecified vectors.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-29504 | Dell BSAFE Crypto-C Micro Edition, versions before 4.1.5, and Dell BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, versions before 4.5.2, contain a Missing Requi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29504</link><description>Dell BSAFE Crypto-C Micro Edition, versions before 4.1.5, and Dell BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, versions before 4.5.2, contain a Missing Required Cryptographic Step Vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32967 | QTS, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32967</link><description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to bypass intended access restrictions via a network.
QTS 5.x, QuTS hero are not affected.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39297 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39297</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39302 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39302</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39303 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39303</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to compromise the security of the system via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41273 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41273</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.2.2533 build 20230926 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.2.2534 build 20230927 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41274 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41274</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.2.2533 build 20230926 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.2.2534 build 20230927 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41275 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41275</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.2.2533 build 20230926 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.2.2534 build 20230927 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41276 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41276</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.2.2533 build 20230926 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.2.2534 build 20230927 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41277 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41277</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.2.2533 build 20230926 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.2.2534 build 20230927 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41278 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41278</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.2.2533 build 20230926 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.2.2534 build 20230927 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41279 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41279</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.2.2533 build 20230926 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.2.2534 build 20230927 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41280 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41280</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.2.2533 build 20230926 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.2.2534 build 20230927 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41281 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41281</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41282 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41282</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41283 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41283</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41292 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41292</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45025 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45025</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45026 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45026</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to read the contents of unexpected files and expose sensitive data via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45027 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45027</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to read the contents of unexpected files and expose sensitive data via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45028 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45028</link><description>An uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45035 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45035</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24470 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in flusity-CMS v.2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the update_post.php co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24470</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in flusity-CMS v.2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the update_post.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-21575 | Dell BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, versions before 4.5.2, contain an Observable Timing Discrepancy Vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21575</link><description>Dell BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, versions before 4.5.2, contain an Observable Timing Discrepancy Vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24160 | MRCMS 3.0 contains a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via /admin/system/saveinfo.do.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24160</link><description>MRCMS 3.0 contains a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via /admin/system/saveinfo.do.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51838 | Ylianst MeshCentral 1.1.16 suffers from Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51838</link><description>Ylianst MeshCentral 1.1.16 suffers from Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24161 | MRCMS 3.0 contains an Arbitrary File Read vulnerability in /admin/file/edit.do as the incoming path parameter is not filtered.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24161</link><description>MRCMS 3.0 contains an Arbitrary File Read vulnerability in /admin/file/edit.do as the incoming path parameter is not filtered.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22107 | An issue was discovered in GTB Central Console 15.17.1-30814.NG. The method systemSettingsDnsDataAction at /opt/webapp/src/AppBundle/Control...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22107</link><description>An issue was discovered in GTB Central Console 15.17.1-30814.NG. The method systemSettingsDnsDataAction at /opt/webapp/src/AppBundle/Controller/React/SystemSettingsController.php is vulnerable to command injection via the /old/react/v1/api/system/dns/data endpoint. An authenticated attacker can abuse it to inject an arbitrary command and compromise the platform.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22108 | An issue was discovered in GTB Central Console 15.17.1-30814.NG. The method setTermsHashAction at /opt/webapp/lib/PureApi/CCApi.class.php is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22108</link><description>An issue was discovered in GTB Central Console 15.17.1-30814.NG. The method setTermsHashAction at /opt/webapp/lib/PureApi/CCApi.class.php is vulnerable to an unauthenticated SQL injection via /ccapi.php that an attacker can abuse in order to change the Administrator password to a known value.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:43:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24757 | open-irs .env Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24757</link><description>open-irs is an issue response robot that reponds to issues in the installed repository. The `.env` file was accidentally uploaded when working with git actions. This problem is fixed in 1.0.1. Discontinuing all sensitive keys and turning into secrets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:43:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34381 | Dell BSAFE SSL-J version 7.0 and all versions prior to 6.5, and Dell BSAFE Crypto-J versions prior to 6.2.6.1 contain an unmaintained third-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34381</link><description>Dell BSAFE SSL-J version 7.0 and all versions prior to 6.5, and Dell BSAFE Crypto-J versions prior to 6.2.6.1 contain an unmaintained third-party component vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the compromise of the impacted system. This is a Critical vulnerability and Dell recommends customers to upgrade at the earliest opportunity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1185 | Nsasoft NBMonitor Network Bandwidth Monitor Registration denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1185</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Nsasoft NBMonitor Network Bandwidth Monitor 1.6.5.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Registration Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252675. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23831 | Privilege escalation through CSRF attack on &amp;#x27;setup.pl&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23831</link><description>LedgerSMB is a free web-based double-entry accounting system. When a LedgerSMB database administrator has an active session in /setup.pl, an attacker can trick the admin into clicking on a link which automatically submits a request to setup.pl without the admin's consent.  This request can be used to create a new user account with full application (/login.pl) privileges, leading to privilege escalation.  The vulnerability is patched in versions 1.10.30 and 1.11.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24029 | JFinalCMS 5.0.0 is vulnerable to SQL injection via /admin/content/data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24029</link><description>JFinalCMS 5.0.0 is vulnerable to SQL injection via /admin/content/data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24760 | Mailcow Docker Container Exposure to Local Network</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24760</link><description>mailcow is a dockerized email package, with multiple containers linked in one bridged network. A security vulnerability has been identified in mailcow affecting versions &lt; 2024-01c. This vulnerability potentially allows attackers on the same subnet to connect to exposed ports of a Docker container, even when the port is bound to 127.0.0.1. The vulnerability has been addressed by implementing additional iptables/nftables rules. These rules drop packets for Docker containers on ports 3306, 6379, 8983, and 12345, where the input interface is not `br-mailcow` and the output interface is `br-mailcow`.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6387 | Incorrect buffer parsing in Bluetooth LE sample code may lead to buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6387</link><description>A potential buffer overflow exists in the Bluetooth LE HCI CPC sample application in the Gecko SDK which may result in a denial of service or remote code execution</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23824 | mailcow ipixel flood attack leads to Denial of Service in admin page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23824</link><description>mailcow is a dockerized email package, with multiple containers linked in one bridged network. The application is vulnerable to pixel flood attack, once the payload has been successfully uploaded in the logo the application goes slow and doesn't respond in the admin page. It is tested on the versions 2023-12a and prior and patched in version 2024-01.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38273 | IBM Cloud Pak System information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38273</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak System 2.3.1.1, 2.3.2.0, and 2.3.3.7 uses an inadequate account lockout setting that could allow a remote attacker to brute force account credentials.  IBM X-Force ID:  260733.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 14:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47142 | IBM Tivoli Application Dependency Discovery Manager privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47142</link><description>IBM Tivoli Application Dependency Discovery Manager 7.3.0.0 through 7.3.0.10 could allow an attacker on the organization's local network to escalate their privileges due to unauthorized API access.  IBM X-Force ID:  270267.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:26:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47144 | IBM Tivoli Application Dependency Discovery Manager cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47144</link><description>IBM Tivoli Application Dependency Discovery Manager 7.3.0.0 through 7.3.0.10 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  270271.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6676 | Cross Site Request Forgery in National Keep&amp;#x27;s CyberMath</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6676</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in National Keep Cyber Security Services CyberMath allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects CyberMath: from v1.4 before v1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0269 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0269</link><description>ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions 7270 and below are vulnerable to the Authenticated SQL injection in File-Summary DrillDown. This issue has been fixed and released in version 7271.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47143 | IBM Tivoli Application Dependency Discovery Manager HOST header injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47143</link><description>IBM Tivoli Application Dependency Discovery Manager 7.3.0.0 through 7.3.0.10 is vulnerable to HTTP header injection, caused by improper validation of input by the HOST headers.  This could allow an attacker to conduct various attacks against the vulnerable system, including cross-site scripting, cache poisoning or session hijacking.  IBM X-Force ID:  270270.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:05:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1184 | Nsasoft Network Sleuth Registration denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1184</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Nsasoft Network Sleuth 3.0.0.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Registration Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252674 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:05:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47148 | IBM Storage Protect Plus Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47148</link><description>IBM Storage Protect Plus Server 10.1.0 through 10.1.15.2 Admin Console could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information due to improper validation of unsecured endpoints which could be used in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  270599.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:05:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6675 | Malicious File Upload in National Keep&amp;#x27;s CyberMath</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6675</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in National Keep Cyber Security Services CyberMath allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects CyberMath: from v.1.4 before v.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:05:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6673 | Reflected XSS in National Keep&amp;#x27;s CyberMath</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6673</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in National Keep Cyber Security Services CyberMath allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects CyberMath: from v.1.4 before v.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0253 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0253</link><description>ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions 7270 and below are vulnerable to the Authenticated SQL injection in home Graph-Data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6672 | Stored XSS in National Keep&amp;#x27;s CyberMath</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6672</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in National Keep Cyber Security Services CyberMath allows Stored XSS.This issue affects CyberMath: from v1.4 before v1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1201 | PanteraSoft HDD Health search path or unquoted item vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1201</link><description>Search path or unquoted item vulnerability in HDD Health affecting versions 4.2.0.112 and earlier. This vulnerability could allow a local attacker to store a malicious executable file within the unquoted search path, resulting in privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0844 | The Popup More Popups, Lightboxes, and more popup modules plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in version 2.1.6 via th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0844</link><description>The Popup More Popups, Lightboxes, and more popup modules plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in version 2.1.6 via the ycfChangeElementData() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files ending with "Form.php" on the server , allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 11:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0963 | The Calculated Fields Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's CP_CALCULATED_FIELDS shortcode...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0963</link><description>The Calculated Fields Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's CP_CALCULATED_FIELDS shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.52 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied 'location' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 11:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50488 | An issue in Blurams Lumi Security Camera (A31C) v23.0406.435.4120 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50488</link><description>An issue in Blurams Lumi Security Camera (A31C) v23.0406.435.4120 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 10:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51820 | An issue in Blurams Lumi Security Camera (A31C) v.2.3.38.12558 allows a physically proximate attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51820</link><description>An issue in Blurams Lumi Security Camera (A31C) v.2.3.38.12558 allows a physically proximate attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 10:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24388 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in XunRuiCMS versions v4.6.2 and before, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24388</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in XunRuiCMS versions v4.6.2 and before, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via crafted malicious requests to the background login.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51072 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the NOC component of Nagios XI version up to and including 2024R1 allows low-privileged...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51072</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the NOC component of Nagios XI version up to and including 2024R1 allows low-privileged users to execute malicious HTML or JavaScript code via the audio file upload functionality from the Operation Center section. This allows any authenticated user to execute arbitrary JavaScript code on behalf of other users, including the administrators.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39611 | An issue in Software FX Chart FX 7 version 7.0.4962.20829 allows attackers to enumerate and read files from the local filesystem by sending ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39611</link><description>An issue in Software FX Chart FX 7 version 7.0.4962.20829 allows attackers to enumerate and read files from the local filesystem by sending crafted web requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0338 | Buffer Overflow Vulnerability in XAMPP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0338</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability has been found in XAMPP affecting version 8.2.4 and earlier. An attacker could execute arbitrary code through a long file debug argument that controls the Structured Exception Handler (SEH).</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23895 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Cups Easy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23895</link><description>A vulnerability has been reported in Cups Easy (Purchase &amp; Inventory), version 1.0, whereby user-controlled inputs are not sufficiently encoded, resulting in a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via /cupseasylive/locationcreate.php, in the locationid parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted URL to an authenticated user and steal their session cookie credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48645 | An issue was discovered in the Archibus app 4.0.3 for iOS. It uses a local database that is synchronized with a Web central server instance ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48645</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Archibus app 4.0.3 for iOS. It uses a local database that is synchronized with a Web central server instance every time the application is opened, or when the refresh button is used. There is a SQL injection in the search work request feature in the Maintenance module of the app. This allows performing queries on the local database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:17:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22851 | Directory Traversal Vulnerability in LiveConfig before v.2.5.2 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted reques...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22851</link><description>Directory Traversal Vulnerability in LiveConfig before v.2.5.2 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request to the /static/ endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 08:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24524 | Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in flusity-CMS v.2.33, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the add_menu.ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24524</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in flusity-CMS v.2.33, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the add_menu.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 08:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22281 | Zip Slip Vulnerability in B&amp;amp;R Automation Studio Project Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22281</link><description>: Relative Path Traversal vulnerability in B&amp;R Industrial Automation Automation Studio allows Relative Path Traversal.This issue affects Automation Studio: from 4.0 through 4.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 07:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-24682 | Automation Studio and PVI Multiple unquoted service path vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-24682</link><description>Unquoted Search Path or Element vulnerability in B&amp;R Industrial Automation Automation Studio, B&amp;R Industrial Automation NET/PVI allows Target Programs with Elevated Privileges.This issue affects Automation Studio: from 4.0 through 4.6, from 4.7.0 before 4.7.7 SP, from 4.8.0 before 4.8.6 SP, from 4.9.0 before 4.9.4 SP; NET/PVI: from 4.0 through 4.6, from 4.7.0 before 4.7.7, from 4.8.0 before 4.8.6, from 4.9.0 before 4.9.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 07:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-24681 | Automation Studio and PVI Multiple incorrect permission assignments for services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-24681</link><description>Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in B&amp;R Industrial Automation Automation Studio allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Automation Studio: from 4.6.0 through 4.6.X, from 4.7.0 before 4.7.7 SP, from 4.8.0 before 4.8.6 SP, from 4.9.0 before 4.9.4 SP.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 07:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22282 | RCE in B&amp;amp;R Automation Studio with crafted project files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22282</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in B&amp;R Industrial Automation Automation Studio allows Local Execution of Code.This issue affects Automation Studio: from 4.0 through 4.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21780 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in HOME SPOT CUBE2 V102 and earlier. Processing a specially crafted command may result in a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21780</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in HOME SPOT CUBE2 V102 and earlier. Processing a specially crafted command may result in a denial of service (DoS) condition. Note that the affected products are no longer supported.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23978 | Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in HOME SPOT CUBE2 V102 and earlier. By processing invalid values, arbitrary code may be exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23978</link><description>Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in HOME SPOT CUBE2 V102 and earlier. By processing invalid values, arbitrary code may be executed. Note that the affected products are no longer supported.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43756 | Dsoftbus has an out-of-bounds read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43756</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.4 and prior versions allow a local attacker causes information leak through out-of-bounds Read.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45734 | Dsoftbus has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45734</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.4 and prior versions allow an adjacent attacker arbitrary code execution through out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49118 | Dsoftbus has an out-of-bounds read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49118</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.4 and prior versions allow a local attacker causes information leak through out-of-bounds Read.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0285 | Dsoftbus has an improper input validation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0285</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause DOS through improper input.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21845 | Dsoftbus has an integer overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21845</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause heap overflow through  integer overflow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21851 | Dsoftbus has an integer overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21851</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause heap overflow through  integer overflow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21860 | Dsoftbus has a use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21860</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions

allow an adjacent attacker arbitrary code execution in any apps through use after free.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21863 | Dsoftbus has an improper input validation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21863</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause DOS through improper input.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1143 | Central Dogma versions prior to 0.64.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), which could allow for the leakage of user sessions and s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1143</link><description>Central Dogma versions prior to 0.64.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), which could allow for the leakage of user sessions and subsequent authentication bypass.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46045 | Graphviz 2.36 before 10.0.0 has an out-of-bounds read via a crafted config6a file. NOTE: exploitability may be uncommon because this file is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46045</link><description>Graphviz 2.36 before 10.0.0 has an out-of-bounds read via a crafted config6a file. NOTE: exploitability may be uncommon because this file is typically owned by root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 05:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1047 | The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1047</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the register_reference() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.28. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the connected API keys.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 05:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1162 | The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.29. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1162</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.29. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the register_reference() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers  to update the connected API keys via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 05:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21485 | Versions of the package dash-core-components before 2.13.0; all versions of the package dash-core-components; versions of the package dash b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21485</link><description>Versions of the package dash-core-components before 2.13.0; all versions of the package dash-core-components; versions of the package dash before 2.15.0; all versions of the package dash-html-components; versions of the package dash-html-components before 2.0.16 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) when the href of the a tag is controlled by an adversary. An authenticated attacker who stores a view that exploits this vulnerability could steal the data that's visible to another user who opens that view - not just the data already included on the page, but they could also, in theory, make additional requests and access other data accessible to this user. In some cases, they could also steal the access tokens of that user, which would allow the attacker to act as that user, including viewing other apps and resources hosted on the same server.&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;&#13;This is only exploitable in Dash apps that include some mechanism to store user input to be reloaded by a different user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 05:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24482 | Aprktool before 2.9.3 on Windows allows ../ and /.. directory traversal.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24482</link><description>Aprktool before 2.9.3 on Windows allows ../ and /.. directory traversal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 05:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0685 | The Ninja Forms Contact Form – The Drag and Drop Form Builder for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Second Order SQL Injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0685</link><description>The Ninja Forms Contact Form – The Drag and Drop Form Builder for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Second Order SQL Injection via the email address value submitted through forms in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject SQL in their email address that will append additional into the already existing query when an administrator triggers a personal data export.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 04:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1073 | The SlimStat Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'filter_array' parameter in all versions up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1073</link><description>The SlimStat Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'filter_array' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 04:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38020 | IBM SOAR QRadar Plugin App log injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38020</link><description>IBM SOAR QRadar Plugin App 1.0 through 5.0.3 could allow an authenticated user to manipulate output written to log files.  IBM X-Force ID:  260576.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 03:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38019 | IBM SOAR QRadar Plugin App directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38019</link><description>IBM SOAR QRadar Plugin App 1.0 through 5.0.3 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  260575.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 03:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38263 | IBM SOAR QRadar Plugin App improper access controls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38263</link><description>IBM SOAR QRadar Plugin App 1.0 through 5.0.3 could allow an authenticated user to perform unauthorized actions due to improper access controls.  IBM X-Force ID:  260577.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 03:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-40744 | IBM Aspera Faspex cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40744</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.6 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  236441.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 03:16:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46159 | IBM Storage Ceph denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46159</link><description>IBM Storage Ceph 5.3z1, 5.3z5, and 6.1z1 could allow an authenticated user on the network to cause a denial of service from RGW.  IBM X-Force ID:  268906.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22320 | IBM Operational Decision Manager code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22320</link><description>IBM Operational Decision Manager 8.10.3, 8.10.4, 8.10.5.1, 8.11, 8.11.0.1, and 8.12.0.1 could allow a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on the system, caused by an unsafe deserialization. By sending specially crafted request, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.  IBM X-Force ID:  279146.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22319 | IBM Operational Decision Manager LDAP injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22319</link><description>IBM Operational Decision Manager 8.10.3, 8.10.4, 8.10.5.1, 8.11, 8.11.0.1, and 8.12.0.1 could allow a remote attacker to conduct an LDAP injection. By sending a request with a specially crafted request, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to inject unsanitized content into the LDAP filter.  IBM X-Force ID:  279145.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22533 | Before Beetl v3.15.12, the rendering template has a server-side template injection (SSTI) vulnerability. When the incoming template is contr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22533</link><description>Before Beetl v3.15.12, the rendering template has a server-side template injection (SSTI) vulnerability. When the incoming template is controllable, it will be filtered by the DefaultNativeSecurityManager blacklist. Because blacklist filtering is not strict, the blacklist can be bypassed, leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32333 | IBM Maximo Asset Management improper access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32333</link><description>IBM Maximo Asset Management 7.6.1.3 could allow a remote attacker to log into the admin panel due to improper access controls.  IBM X-Force ID:  255073.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22779 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in Kihron ServerRPExposer v.1.0.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22779</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in Kihron ServerRPExposer v.1.0.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the loadServerPack in ServerResourcePackProviderMixin.java.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46344 | A vulnerability in Solar-Log Base 15 Firmware 6.0.1 Build 161, and possibly other Solar-Log Base products, allows an attacker to escalate th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46344</link><description>A vulnerability in Solar-Log Base 15 Firmware 6.0.1 Build 161, and possibly other Solar-Log Base products, allows an attacker to escalate their privileges by exploiting a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the switch group function under /#ilang=DE&amp;b=c_smartenergy_swgroups in the web portal. The vulnerability can be exploited to gain the rights of an installer or PM, which can then be used to gain administrative access to the web portal and execute further attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48792 | Zoho ManageEngine ADAudit Plus through 7250 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the report export option.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48792</link><description>Zoho ManageEngine ADAudit Plus through 7250 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the report export option.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22899 | Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the syncNtpTime func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22899</link><description>Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the syncNtpTime function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22900 | Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the setNetworkCardIn...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22900</link><description>Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the setNetworkCardInfo function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22901 | Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to use default MYSQL credentials.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22901</link><description>Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to use default MYSQL credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:05:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22902 | Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to be configured with default root credentials.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22902</link><description>Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to be configured with default root credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:05:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22903 | Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the deleteUpdateAPK ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22903</link><description>Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the deleteUpdateAPK function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:05:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23746 | Miro Desktop 0.8.18 on macOS allows Electron code injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23746</link><description>Miro Desktop 0.8.18 on macOS allows Electron code injection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:05:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48793 | Zoho ManageEngine ADAudit Plus through 7250 allows SQL Injection in the aggregate report feature.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48793</link><description>Zoho ManageEngine ADAudit Plus through 7250 allows SQL Injection in the aggregate report feature.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50328 | IBM PowerSC information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50328</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 may allow a remote attacker to view session identifiers passed via URL query strings.  IBM X-Force ID:  275110.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50934 | IBM PowerSC improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50934</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 uses single-factor authentication which can lead to unnecessary risk of compromise when compared with the benefits of a dual-factor authentication scheme.  IBM X-Force ID:  275114.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50935 | IBM PowerSC forced browsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50935</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 fails to properly restrict access to a URL or resource, which may allow a remote attacker to obtain unauthorized access to application functionality and/or resources.  IBM X-Force ID:  275115.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50938 | IBM PowerSC clickjacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50938</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 could allow a remote attacker to hijack the clicking action of the victim. By persuading a victim to visit a malicious Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to hijack the victim's click actions and possibly launch further attacks against the victim.  IBM X-Force ID:  275128.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50941 | IBM PowerSC session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50941</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 does not provide logout functionality, which could allow an authenticated user to gain access to an unauthorized user using session fixation.  IBM X-Force ID:  275131.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50962 | IBM PowerSC information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50962</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 MFA does not implement the "HTTP Strict Transport Security" (HSTS) web security policy mechanism.  IBM X-Force ID:  276004.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50327 | IBM PowerSC weak security</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50327</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 uses insecure HTTP methods which could allow a remote attacker to perform unauthorized file request modification.  IBM X-Force ID:  275109.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50936 | IBM PowerSC session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50936</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 does not invalidate session after logout which could allow an authenticated user to impersonate another user on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  275116.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50940 | IBM PowerSC cross-resource origin sharing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50940</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 uses Cross-Origin Resource Sharing (CORS) which could allow an attacker to carry out privileged actions and retrieve sensitive information as the domain name is not being limited to only trusted domains.  IBM X-Force ID:  275130.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50326 | IBM PowerSC information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50326</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 uses an inadequate account lockout setting that could allow a remote attacker to brute force account credentials.  IBM X-Force ID:  275107.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50933 | IBM PowerSC HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50933</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 is vulnerable to HTML injection. A remote attacker could inject malicious HTML code, which when viewed, would be executed in the victim's Web browser within the security context of the hosting site.  IBM X-Force ID:  275113.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50937 | IBM PowerSC information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50937</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  275117.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21399 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21399</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:48:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50939 | IBM PowerSC information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50939</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  275129.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 23:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21866 | Generation of Error Message Containing Sensitive Information in Rapid SCADA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21866</link><description>In Rapid Software LLC's Rapid SCADA versions prior to Version 5.8.4, the affected product responds back with an error message containing sensitive data if it receives a specific malformed request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 23:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21764 | Use of Hard-Coded Credentials in Rapid SCADA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21764</link><description>In Rapid Software LLC's Rapid SCADA versions prior to Version 5.8.4, the product uses hard-coded credentials, which may allow an attacker to connect to a specific port.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 23:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21869 | Plaintext Storage of a Password in Rapid SCADA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21869</link><description>In Rapid Software LLC's Rapid SCADA versions prior to Version 5.8.4, the affected product stores plaintext credentials in various places. This may allow an attacker with local access to see them.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 23:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21794 | Open Redirect in Rapid SCADA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21794</link><description>In Rapid Software LLC's Rapid SCADA versions prior to Version 5.8.4, an attacker can redirect users to malicious pages through the login page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 23:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22016 | Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource in Rapid SCADA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22016</link><description>In Rapid Software LLC's Rapid SCADA versions prior to Version 5.8.4, an authorized user can write directly to the Scada directory. This may allow privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 23:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22096 | Relative Path Traversal in Rapid SCADA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22096</link><description>In Rapid Software LLC's Rapid SCADA versions prior to Version 5.8.4, an attacker can append path traversal characters to the filename when using a specific command, allowing them to read arbitrary files from the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 23:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21852 | Rapid SCADA Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21852</link><description>In Rapid Software LLC's Rapid SCADA versions prior to Version 5.8.4, an attacker can supply a malicious configuration file by utilizing a Zip Slip vulnerability in the unpacking routine to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 23:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36496 | Delegated Admin Virtual Attribute Provider Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36496</link><description>Delegated Admin Privilege virtual attribute provider plugin, when enabled, allows an authenticated user to elevate their permissions in the Directory Server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 23:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22927 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the func parameter in eyoucms v.1.6.5 allows a remote attacker to run arbitrary code via crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22927</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the func parameter in eyoucms v.1.6.5 allows a remote attacker to run arbitrary code via crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 23:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23033 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in the path parameter in eyoucms v.1.6.5 allows a remote attacker to run arbitrary code via crafted URL.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23033</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in the path parameter in eyoucms v.1.6.5 allows a remote attacker to run arbitrary code via crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 23:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23032 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in num parameter in eyoucms v.1.6.5 allows a remote attacker to run arbitrary code via crafted URL.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23032</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in num parameter in eyoucms v.1.6.5 allows a remote attacker to run arbitrary code via crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 22:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23034 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in the input parameter in eyoucms v.1.6.5 allows a remote attacker to run arbitrary code via crafted URL.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23034</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in the input parameter in eyoucms v.1.6.5 allows a remote attacker to run arbitrary code via crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 22:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23031 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in is_water parameter in eyoucms v.1.6.5 allows a remote attacker to run arbitrary code via crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23031</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in is_water parameter in eyoucms v.1.6.5 allows a remote attacker to run arbitrary code via crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 22:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24756 | Crafatar path traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24756</link><description>Crafatar serves Minecraft avatars based on the skin for use in external applications. Files outside of the `lib/public/` directory can be requested from the server. Instances running behind Cloudflare (including crafatar.com) are not affected. Instances using the Docker container as shown in the README are affected, but only files within the container can be read. By default, all of the files within the container can also be found in this repository and are not confidential. This vulnerability is patched in 2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 22:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47867 | MachineSense FeverWarn Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47867</link><description>MachineSense FeverWarn devices are configured as Wi-Fi hosts in a way that attackers within range could connect to the device's web services and compromise the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 22:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49610 | MachineSense FeverWarn Improper Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49610</link><description>MachineSense FeverWarn Raspberry Pi-based devices lack input sanitization, which could allow an attacker on an adjacent network to send a message running commands or could overflow the stack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 22:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46706 | MachineSense FeverWarn Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46706</link><description>Multiple MachineSense devices have credentials unable to be changed by the user or administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 22:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49115 | MachineSense FeverWarn Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49115</link><description>MachineSense devices use unauthenticated MQTT messaging to monitor devices and remote viewing of sensor data by users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 22:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49617 | MachineSense FeverWarn Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49617</link><description>The MachineSense application programmable interface (API) is improperly protected and can be accessed without authentication. A remote attacker could retrieve and modify sensitive information without any authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 22:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6221 | MachineSense FeverWarn  Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6221</link><description>The cloud provider MachineSense uses for integration and deployment for multiple MachineSense devices, such as the programmable logic controller (PLC), PumpSense, PowerAnalyzer, FeverWarn, and others is insufficiently protected against unauthorized access. An attacker with access to the internal procedures could view source code, secret credentials, and more.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 22:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47256 | ConnectWise ScreenConnect through 23.8.4 allows local users to connect to arbitrary relay servers via implicit trust of proxy settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47256</link><description>ConnectWise ScreenConnect through 23.8.4 allows local users to connect to arbitrary relay servers via implicit trust of proxy settings</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 22:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47257 | ConnectWise ScreenConnect through 23.8.4 allows man-in-the-middle attackers to achieve remote code execution via crafted messages.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47257</link><description>ConnectWise ScreenConnect through 23.8.4 allows man-in-the-middle attackers to achieve remote code execution via crafted messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 22:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4472 | Cryptographically weak PRNG in Opinio 7.22</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4472</link><description>Objectplanet Opinio version 7.22 and prior uses a cryptographically weak pseudo-random number generator (PRNG) coupled to a predictable seed, which could lead to an unauthenticated account takeover of any user on the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 22:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24755 | discourse-group-membership-ip-block is exposing potentially sensitive custom fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24755</link><description>discourse-group-membership-ip-block is a discourse plugin that adds support for adding users to groups based on their IP address. discourse-group-membership-ip-block was sending all group custom fields to the client, including group custom fields from other plugins which may expect their custom fields to remain secret.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 22:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0325 | Command Injection in Helix Sync</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0325</link><description>In Helix Sync versions prior to 2024.1, a local command injection was identified.  Reported by Bryan Riggins.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 22:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1040 | Use of weak hash in Gessler GmbH WEB-MASTER </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1040</link><description>Gessler GmbH WEB-MASTER user account is stored using a weak hashing algorithm. The attacker can restore the passwords by breaking the hashes stored on the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 21:49:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1039 | Use of weak credentials in Gessler GmbH WEB-MASTER</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1039</link><description>Gessler GmbH WEB-MASTER has a restoration account that uses weak hard coded credentials and if exploited could allow an attacker control over the web management of the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 21:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24041 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Travel Journal Using PHP and MySQL with Source Code v1.0 allows attackers to execute ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24041</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Travel Journal Using PHP and MySQL with Source Code v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the location parameter at /travel-journal/write-journal.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 20:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24945 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Travel Journal Using PHP and MySQL with Source Code v1.0 allows attackers to execute ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24945</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Travel Journal Using PHP and MySQL with Source Code v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Share Your Moments parameter at /travel-journal/write-journal.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 20:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23052 | An issue in WuKongOpenSource WukongCRM v.72crm_9.0.1_20191202 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the parseObject() funct...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23052</link><description>An issue in WuKongOpenSource WukongCRM v.72crm_9.0.1_20191202 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the parseObject() function in the fastjson component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 20:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22936 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Parents &amp; Student Portal in Genesis School Management Systems in Genesis AIMS Student Informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22936</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Parents &amp; Student Portal in Genesis School Management Systems in Genesis AIMS Student Information Systems v.3053 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the message parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 20:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22939 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in FlyCms v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the system/article/category_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22939</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in FlyCms v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the system/article/category_edit component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 19:53:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51835 | An issue in TRENDnet TEW-822DRE v.1.03B02 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the parameters ipv4_ping in the /boafrm/form...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51835</link><description>An issue in TRENDnet TEW-822DRE v.1.03B02 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the parameters ipv4_ping in the /boafrm/formSystemCheck.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 19:53:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24569 | `ZipSecurity#isBelowCurrentDirectory` is vulnerable to partial-path traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24569</link><description>The Pixee Java Code Security Toolkit is a set of security APIs meant to help secure Java code. `ZipSecurity#isBelowCurrentDirectory` is vulnerable to a partial-path traversal bypass. To be vulnerable to the bypass, the application must use toolkit version &lt;=1.1.1, use ZipSecurity as a guard against path traversal, and have an exploit path. Although the control still protects attackers from escaping the application path into higher level directories (e.g., /etc/), it will allow "escaping" into sibling paths. For example, if your running path is /my/app/path you an attacker could navigate into /my/app/path-something-else. This vulnerability is patched in 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 19:10:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5841 | OpenEXR Heap Overflow in Scanline Deep Data Parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5841</link><description>Due to a failure in validating the number of scanline samples of a OpenEXR file containing deep scanline data, Academy Software Foundation OpenEX image parsing library version 3.2.1 and prior is susceptible to a heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 18:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1167 | SEW-EURODRIVE MOVITOOLS MotionStudio Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1167</link><description>When SEW-EURODRIVE MOVITOOLS MotionStudio processes XML information unrestricted file access can occur.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 18:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24570 | Statamic account takeover via XSS and password reset link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24570</link><description>Statamic is a Laravel and Git powered CMS. HTML files crafted to look like jpg files are able to be uploaded, allowing for XSS. This affects the front-end forms with asset fields without any mime type validation, asset fields in the control panel, and asset browser in the control panel. Additionally, if the XSS is crafted in a specific way, the "copy password reset link" feature may be exploited to gain access to a user's password reset token and gain access to their account. The authorized user is required to execute the XSS in order for the vulnerability to occur. In versions 4.46.0 and 3.4.17, the XSS vulnerability has been patched, and the copy password reset link functionality has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 16:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24561 | Vyper bounds check on built-in `slice()` function can be overflowed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24561</link><description>Vyper is a pythonic Smart Contract Language for the ethereum virtual machine. In versions 0.3.10 and earlier, the bounds check for slices does not account for the ability for start + length to overflow when the values aren't literals. If a slice() function uses a non-literal argument for the start or length variable, this creates the ability for an attacker to overflow the bounds check. This issue can be used to do OOB access to storage, memory or calldata addresses. It can also be used to corrupt the length slot of the respective array.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 16:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24557 | Moby classic builder cache poisoning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24557</link><description>Moby is an open-source project created by Docker to enable software containerization. The classic builder cache system is prone to cache poisoning if the image is built FROM scratch. Also, changes to some instructions (most important being HEALTHCHECK and ONBUILD) would not cause a cache miss. An attacker with the knowledge of the Dockerfile someone is using could poison their cache by making them pull a specially crafted image that would be considered as a valid cache candidate for some build steps. 23.0+ users are only affected if they explicitly opted out of Buildkit (DOCKER_BUILDKIT=0 environment variable) or are using the /build API endpoint. All users on versions older than 23.0 could be impacted. Image build API endpoint (/build) and ImageBuild function from github.com/docker/docker/client is also affected as it the uses classic builder by default. Patches are included in 24.0.9 and 25.0.2 releases.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 16:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23832 | Mastodon Remote user impersonation and takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23832</link><description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub Mastodon allows configuration of LDAP for authentication. Due to insufficient origin validation in all Mastodon, attackers can impersonate and take over any remote account. Every Mastodon version prior to 3.5.17 is vulnerable, as well as 4.0.x versions prior to 4.0.13, 4.1.x version prior to 4.1.13, and 4.2.x versions prior to 4.2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 16:27:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24752 | Bref Uploaded Files Not Deleted in Event-Driven Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24752</link><description>Bref enable serverless PHP on AWS Lambda. When Bref is used with the Event-Driven Function runtime and the handler is a `RequestHandlerInterface`, then the Lambda event is converted to a PSR7 object. During the conversion process, if the request is a MultiPart, each part is parsed and for each which contains a file, it is extracted and saved in `/tmp` with a random filename starting with `bref_upload_`. The flow mimics what plain PHP does but it does not delete the temporary files when the request has been processed. An attacker could fill the Lambda instance disk by performing multiple MultiPart requests containing files. This vulnerability is patched in 2.1.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 16:27:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24753 | Bref Multiple Value Headers Not Supported in ApiGatewayFormatV2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24753</link><description>Bref enable serverless PHP on AWS Lambda. When Bref is used in combination with an API Gateway with the v2 format, it does not handle multiple values headers. If PHP generates a response with two headers having the same key but different values only the latest one is kept. If an application relies on multiple headers with the same key being set for security reasons, then Bref would lower the application security. For example, if an application sets multiple `Content-Security-Policy` headers, then Bref would just reflect the latest one. This vulnerability is patched in 2.1.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 16:27:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24754 | Bref Body Parsing Inconsistency in Event-Driven Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24754</link><description>Bref enable serverless PHP on AWS Lambda. When Bref is used with the Event-Driven Function runtime and the handler is a `RequestHandlerInterface`, then the Lambda event is converted to a PSR7 object. During the conversion process, if the request is a MultiPart, each part is parsed and its content added in the `$files` or `$parsedBody` arrays. The conversion process produces a different output compared to the one of plain PHP when keys ending with and open square bracket ([) are used. Based on the application logic the difference in the body parsing might lead to vulnerabilities and/or undefined behaviors. This vulnerability is patched in 2.1.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22433 | Dell Data Protection Search 19.2.0 and above contain an exposed password opportunity in plain text when using LdapSettings.get_ldap_info in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22433</link><description>Dell Data Protection Search 19.2.0 and above contain an exposed password opportunity in plain text when using LdapSettings.get_ldap_info in DP Search. A remote unauthorized unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability leading to a loss of Confidentiality, Integrity, Protection, and remote takeover of the system. This is a high-severity vulnerability as it allows an attacker to take complete control of DP Search to affect downstream protected devices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 16:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23328 | The Dataease datasource exists deserialization and arbitrary file read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23328</link><description>Dataease is an open source data visualization analysis tool. A deserialization vulnerability exists in the DataEase datasource, which can be exploited to execute arbitrary code. The location of the vulnerability code is `core/core-backend/src/main/java/io/dataease/datasource/type/Mysql.java.` The blacklist of mysql jdbc attacks can be bypassed and attackers can further exploit it for deserialized execution or reading arbitrary files. This vulnerability is patched in 1.18.15 and 2.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 15:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51446 | GLPI LDAP Injection during authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51446</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package. When authentication is made against a LDAP, the authentication form can be used to perform LDAP injection. Upgrade to 10.0.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 15:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23645 | GLPI reflected XSS in reports pages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23645</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package. A malicious URL can be used to execute XSS on reports pages.  Upgrade to 10.0.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 15:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1141 | Glance-store: glance store access key logged in debug log level</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1141</link><description>A vulnerability was found in python-glance-store. The issue occurs when the package logs the access_key for the glance-store when the DEBUG log level is enabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 14:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6078 | OS Command Injection vulnerability affecting BIOVIA Materials Studio products from Release BIOVIA 2021 through Release BIOVIA 2023</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6078</link><description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability exists in BIOVIA Materials Studio products from Release BIOVIA 2021 through Release BIOVIA 2023. Upload of a specially crafted perl script can lead to arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 13:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0935 | Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability affecting DELMIA Apriso Release 2019 through Release 2024</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0935</link><description>An insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability is affecting DELMIA Apriso Release 2019 through Release 2024</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 13:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24059 | springboot-manager v1.6 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload. The system does not filter the suffixes of uploaded files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24059</link><description>springboot-manager v1.6 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload. The system does not filter the suffixes of uploaded files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 13:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24060 | springboot-manager v1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /sys/user.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24060</link><description>springboot-manager v1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /sys/user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 13:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24061 | springboot-manager v1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /sysContent/add.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24061</link><description>springboot-manager v1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /sysContent/add.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 13:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24062 | springboot-manager v1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /sys/role.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24062</link><description>springboot-manager v1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /sys/role.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 13:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51506 | WordPress WPCS Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51506</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in realmag777 WPCS – WordPress Currency Switcher Professional allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WPCS – WordPress Currency Switcher Professional: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51509 | WordPress RegistrationMagic Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.4.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51509</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Metagauss RegistrationMagic – Custom Registration Forms, User Registration, Payment, and User Login allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects RegistrationMagic – Custom Registration Forms, User Registration, Payment, and User Login: from n/a through 5.2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51514 | WordPress CBX Bookmark &amp;amp; Favorite Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51514</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Codeboxr Team CBX Bookmark &amp; Favorite allows Stored XSS.This issue affects CBX Bookmark &amp; Favorite: from n/a through 1.7.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51520 | WordPress Booking Calendar Plugin &amp;lt; 9.7.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51520</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPdevelop / Oplugins WP Booking Calendar allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Booking Calendar: from n/a before 9.7.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:19:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51532 | WordPress Icegram Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.19 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51532</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Icegram Icegram Engage – WordPress Lead Generation, Popup Builder, CTA, Optins and Email List Building allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Icegram Engage – WordPress Lead Generation, Popup Builder, CTA, Optins and Email List Building: from n/a through 3.1.19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51693 | WordPress Themify Icons Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51693</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themify Icons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Themify Icons: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51694 | WordPress Embed Privacy Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51694</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Epiphyt Embed Privacy allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Embed Privacy: from n/a through 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51695 | WordPress Everest Forms Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51695</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPEverest Everest Forms – Build Contact Forms, Surveys, Polls, Application Forms, and more with Ease! allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Everest Forms – Build Contact Forms, Surveys, Polls, Application Forms, and more with Ease!: from n/a through 2.0.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51690 | WordPress Advanced iFrame Plugin &amp;lt;= 2023.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51690</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Advanced iFrame allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Advanced iFrame: from n/a through 2023.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:11:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51691 | WordPress wpDiscuz Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6.12 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51691</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in gVectors Team Comments – wpDiscuz allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Comments – wpDiscuz: from n/a through 7.6.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:11:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51689 | WordPress Easy Video Player Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51689</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in naa986 Easy Video Player allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Easy Video Player: from n/a through 1.2.2.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51684 | WordPress Easy Digital Downloads Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51684</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Easy Digital Downloads Easy Digital Downloads – Sell Digital Files (eCommerce Store &amp; Payments Made Easy) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Easy Digital Downloads – Sell Digital Files (eCommerce Store &amp; Payments Made Easy): from n/a through 3.2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51685 | WordPress WP Review Slider Plugin &amp;lt;= 12.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51685</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LJ Apps WP Review Slider allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Review Slider: from n/a through 12.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51534 | WordPress Brave Popup Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51534</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Brave Brave – Create Popup, Optins, Lead Generation, Survey, Sticky Elements &amp; Interactive Content allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Brave – Create Popup, Optins, Lead Generation, Survey, Sticky Elements &amp; Interactive Content: from n/a through 0.6.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51536 | WordPress CRM Perks Forms Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51536</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CRM Perks CRM Perks Forms – WordPress Form Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects CRM Perks Forms – WordPress Form Builder: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51677 | WordPress Schema &amp;amp; Structured Data for WP &amp;amp; AMP Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.23 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51677</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Magazine3 Schema &amp; Structured Data for WP &amp; AMP allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Schema &amp; Structured Data for WP &amp; AMP: from n/a through 1.23.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51666 | WordPress Related Post Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.53 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51666</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PickPlugins Related Post allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Related Post: from n/a through 2.0.53.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51669 | WordPress Product Code for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51669</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Artios Media Product Code for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Product Code for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.4.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51674 | WordPress Advanced Access Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.9.18 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51674</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AAM Advanced Access Manager – Restricted Content, Users &amp; Roles, Enhanced Security and More allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Advanced Access Manager – Restricted Content, Users &amp; Roles, Enhanced Security and More: from n/a through 6.9.18.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51540 | WordPress Custom 404 Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.10.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51540</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kunal Nagar Custom 404 Pro allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Custom 404 Pro: from n/a through 3.10.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51548 | WordPress SlickNav Mobile Menu Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51548</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Neil Gee SlickNav Mobile Menu allows Stored XSS.This issue affects SlickNav Mobile Menu: from n/a through 1.9.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52118 | WordPress WP User Profile Avatar Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52118</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Event Manager WP User Profile Avatar allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP User Profile Avatar: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52175 | WordPress Auto Amazon Links Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52175</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Michael Uno (miunosoft) Auto Amazon Links – Amazon Associates Affiliate Plugin allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Auto Amazon Links – Amazon Associates Affiliate Plugin: from n/a through 5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52188 | WordPress Footer Putter Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.17 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52188</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Russell Jamieson Footer Putter allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Footer Putter: from n/a through 1.17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52189 | WordPress Ideal Interactive Map Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52189</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jhayghost Ideal Interactive Map allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ideal Interactive Map: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:00:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52191 | WordPress Infogram Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52191</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Torbjon Infogram – Add charts, maps and infographics allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Infogram – Add charts, maps and infographics: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:00:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52192 | WordPress Keap Official Opt-in Forms Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52192</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Keap Keap Official Opt-in Forms allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Keap Official Opt-in Forms: from n/a through 1.0.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52193 | WordPress Page Builder: Live Composer Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.23 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52193</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Live Composer Team Page Builder: Live Composer allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Page Builder: Live Composer: from n/a through 1.5.23.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22430 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.x through 9.6.0.x contains an incorrect default permissions vulnerability. A local low privileges malicio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22430</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.x through 9.6.0.x contains an incorrect default permissions vulnerability. A local low privileges malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22449 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 9.0.0.x through 9.6.0.x contains a missing authentication for critical function vulnerability. A low privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22449</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 9.0.0.x through 9.6.0.x contains a missing authentication for critical function vulnerability. A low privileged local malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain elevated access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52194 | WordPress oEmbed Gist Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52194</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Takayuki Miyauchi oEmbed Gist allows Stored XSS.This issue affects oEmbed Gist: from n/a through 4.9.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52195 | WordPress Posts to Page Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52195</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Posts to Page Kerry James allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Kerry James: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21750 | WordPress Shortcodes Finder Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21750</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Scribit Shortcodes Finder allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Shortcodes Finder: from n/a through 1.5.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22148 | WordPress WP Smart Editor Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22148</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Smart Editor JoomUnited allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects JoomUnited: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37621 | An issue in Fronius Datalogger Web v.2.0.5-4, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37621</link><description>An issue in Fronius Datalogger Web v.2.0.5-4, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 08:32:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51939 | An issue in the cp_bbs_sig function in relic/src/cp/relic_cp_bbs.c of Relic relic-toolkit 0.6.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51939</link><description>An issue in the cp_bbs_sig function in relic/src/cp/relic_cp_bbs.c of Relic relic-toolkit 0.6.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and escalate privileges via the cp_bbs_sig function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 06:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22859 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in livewire before v3.0.4, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code getCsrfToken fu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22859</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in livewire before v3.0.4, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code getCsrfToken function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 06:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24548 | Payment EX Ver1.1.5b and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to obtain the information of the user who purchases merchandise us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24548</link><description>Payment EX Ver1.1.5b and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to obtain the information of the user who purchases merchandise using Payment EX.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 06:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0907 | The NEX-Forms – Ultimate Form Builder – Contact forms and much more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0907</link><description>The NEX-Forms – Ultimate Form Builder – Contact forms and much more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the restore_records() function in all versions up to, and including, 8.5.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to restore records.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 04:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1129 | The NEX-Forms – Ultimate Form Builder – Contact forms and much more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1129</link><description>The NEX-Forms – Ultimate Form Builder – Contact forms and much more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the set_starred() function in all versions up to, and including, 8.5.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to mark records as starred.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 04:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1130 | The NEX-Forms – Ultimate Form Builder – Contact forms and much more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1130</link><description>The NEX-Forms – Ultimate Form Builder – Contact forms and much more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the set_read() function in all versions up to, and including, 8.5.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to mark records as read.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 04:32:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23941 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Group Office prior to v6.6.182, prior to v6.7.64 and prior to v6.8.31, which may allow a remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23941</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Group Office prior to v6.6.182, prior to v6.7.64 and prior to v6.8.31, which may allow a remote authenticated attacker to execute an arbitrary script on the web browser of the user who is logging in to the product.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 04:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7069 | The Advanced iFrame plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'advanced_iframe' shortcode in all ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7069</link><description>The Advanced iFrame plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'advanced_iframe' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2023.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 03:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0831 | Vault May Expose Sensitive Information When Configuring An Audit Log Device</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0831</link><description>Vault and Vault Enterprise (“Vault”) may expose sensitive information when enabling an audit device which specifies the `log_raw` option, which may log sensitive information to other audit devices, regardless of whether they are configured to use `log_raw`.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 02:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>