<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 12:52:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-3421 | SourceCodester Online Courseware deactivatestud.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3421</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file admin/deactivatestud.php. The manipulation of the argument selector leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259593 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 12:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3420 | SourceCodester Online Courseware saveedit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3420</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/saveedit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259592.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3419 | SourceCodester Online Courseware edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3419</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/edit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259591.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 10:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3418 | SourceCodester Online Courseware deactivateteach.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3418</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin/deactivateteach.php. The manipulation of the argument selector leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259590 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 09:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52716 | Vulnerability of starting activities in the background in the ActivityManagerService (AMS) module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52716</link><description>Vulnerability of starting activities in the background in the ActivityManagerService (AMS) module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 09:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52717 | Permission verification vulnerability in the lock screen module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52717</link><description>Permission verification vulnerability in the lock screen module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 09:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4438 | kyivstarteam react-native-sms-user-consent SmsUserConsentModule.kt registerReceiver improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4438</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in kyivstarteam react-native-sms-user-consent up to 1.1.4 on Android. Affected by this issue is the function registerReceiver of the file android/src/main/java/ua/kyivstar/reactnativesmsuserconsent/SmsUserConsentModule.kt. The manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. Attacking locally is a requirement. Upgrading to version 1.1.5 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 5423dcb0cd3e4d573b5520a71fa08aa279e4c3c7. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259508.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 09:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52715 | The SystemUI module has a vulnerability in permission management.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52715</link><description>The SystemUI module has a vulnerability in permission management.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 09:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52382 | Vulnerability of improper control over foreground service notifications in the notification module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52382</link><description>Vulnerability of improper control over foreground service notifications in the notification module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52714 | Vulnerability of defects introduced in the design process in the hwnff module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52714</link><description>Vulnerability of defects introduced in the design process in the hwnff module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52713 | Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52713</link><description>Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30418 | Vulnerability of insufficient permission verification in the app management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30418</link><description>Vulnerability of insufficient permission verification in the app management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:30:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30416 | Use After Free (UAF) vulnerability in the underlying driver module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30416</link><description>Use After Free (UAF) vulnerability in the underlying driver module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30417 | Path traversal vulnerability in the Bluetooth-based sharing module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30417</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability in the Bluetooth-based sharing module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30413 | Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30413</link><description>Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30414 | Command injection vulnerability in the AccountManager module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30414</link><description>Command injection vulnerability in the AccountManager module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30415 | Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30415</link><description>Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3417 | SourceCodester Online Courseware saveeditt.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3417</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/saveeditt.php. The manipulation of the argument contact leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259589 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 05:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3416 | SourceCodester Online Courseware editt.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3416</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file admin/editt.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259588.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 03:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6877 | The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Store...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6877</link><description>The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the Content-Type field of error messages when retrieving an invalid RSS feed. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 02:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3415 | SourceCodester Human Resource Information System addbranches_process.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3415</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Human Resource Information System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file Superadmin_Dashboard/process/addbranches_process.php. The manipulation of the argument branches_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259584.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 23:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3414 | SourceCodester Human Resource Information System addcorporate_process.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3414</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Human Resource Information System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file Superadmin_Dashboard/process/addcorporate_process.php. The manipulation of the argument corporate_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259583.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 20:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3413 | SourceCodester Human Resource Information System login_process.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3413</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Human Resource Information System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file initialize/login_process.php. The manipulation of the argument hr_email/hr_password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259582 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 18:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28741 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in EginDemirbilek NorthStar C2 v1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the login.php co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28741</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in EginDemirbilek NorthStar C2 v1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the login.php component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 18:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27620 | An issue in Ladder v.0.0.1 thru v.0.0.21 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request to the API.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27620</link><description>An issue in Ladder v.0.0.1 thru v.0.0.21 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request to the API.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 18:17:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0406 | Mholt/archiver: path traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0406</link><description>A flaw was discovered in the mholt/archiver package. This flaw allows an attacker to create a specially crafted tar file, which, when unpacked, may allow access to restricted files or directories. This issue can allow the creation or overwriting of files with the user's or application's privileges using the library.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 16:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3156 | Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3156</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 14:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3158 | Use after free in Bookmarks in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3158</link><description>Use after free in Bookmarks in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 14:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3159 | Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform arbitrary read/write via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3159</link><description>Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform arbitrary read/write via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 14:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3378 | iboss Secure Web Gateway Login Portal login cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3378</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in iboss Secure Web Gateway up to 10.1 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /login of the component Login Portal. The manipulation of the argument redirectUrl leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 10.2.0.160 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-259501 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 12:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3377 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3377</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /classes/SystemSettings.php?f=update_settings. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259498 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 12:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24746 | Apache NimBLE: Denial of service in NimBLE Bluetooth stack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24746</link><description>Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in Apache NimBLE. 

Specially crafted GATT operation can cause infinite loop in GATT server leading to denial of service in Bluetooth stack or device.

This issue affects Apache NimBLE: through 1.6.0.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.7.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 12:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25029 | IBM Personal Communications code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25029</link><description>IBM Personal Communications 14.0.6 through 15.0.1 includes a Windows service that is vulnerable to remote code execution (RCE) and local privilege escalation (LPE). The vulnerability allows any unprivileged user with network access to a target computer to run commands with full privileges in the context of NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM. This allows for a low privileged attacker to move laterally to affected systems and to escalate their privileges.  IBM X-Force ID:  281619.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22328 | IBM Maximo Application Suite information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22328</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite 8.10 and 8.11 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  279950.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3376 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System config.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3376</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file config.php. The manipulation of the argument url leads to execution after redirect. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259497 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3369 | code-projects Car Rental add-vehicle.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3369</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Car Rental 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file add-vehicle.php. The manipulation of the argument Upload Image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259490 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3366 | Xuxueli xxl-job Template JdkSerializeTool.java deserialize injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3366</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Xuxueli xxl-job up to 2.4.1. This vulnerability affects the function deserialize of the file com/xxl/job/core/util/JdkSerializeTool.java of the component Template Handler. The manipulation leads to injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259480.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 10:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3365 | SourceCodester Online Library System controller.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3365</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/users/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument user_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259469 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 09:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3364 | SourceCodester Online Library System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3364</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file admin/books/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259468.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 09:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2132 | The Ultimate Bootstrap Elements for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Widget in all ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2132</link><description>The Ultimate Bootstrap Elements for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 08:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2296 | The Photo Gallery by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Image Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG file up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2296</link><description>The Photo Gallery by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Image Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG file uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 08:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3363 | SourceCodester Online Library System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3363</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file admin/borrowed/index.php. The manipulation of the argument BookPublisher/BookTitle leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259467.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 08:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0837 | The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter G...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0837</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter Grid) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the image URL parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 07:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1428 | The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter G...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1428</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter Grid) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘element_pack_wrapper_link’ attribute of the Trailer Box widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 07:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2458 | The Powerkit – Supercharge your WordPress Site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2458</link><description>The Powerkit – Supercharge your WordPress Site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 07:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2949 | The Carousel, Slider, Gallery by WP Carousel – Image Carousel &amp; Photo Gallery, Post Carousel &amp; Post Grid, Product Carousel &amp; Product Grid fo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2949</link><description>The Carousel, Slider, Gallery by WP Carousel – Image Carousel &amp; Photo Gallery, Post Carousel &amp; Post Grid, Product Carousel &amp; Product Grid for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the carousel widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 06:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3362 | SourceCodester Online Library System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3362</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/books/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument IBSN leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259466 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 06:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2471 | The FooGallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via image attachment fields (such as 'Title', 'Alt Text', '...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2471</link><description>The FooGallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via image attachment fields (such as 'Title', 'Alt Text', 'Custom URL', 'Custom Class', and 'Override Type') in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 05:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3361 | SourceCodester Online Library System deweydecimal.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3361</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/books/deweydecimal.php. The manipulation of the argument category leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259465 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 05:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21506 | Versions of the package pymongo before 4.6.3 are vulnerable to Out-of-bounds Read in the bson module. Using the crafted payload the attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21506</link><description>Versions of the package pymongo before 4.6.3 are vulnerable to Out-of-bounds Read in the bson module. Using the crafted payload the attacker could force the parser to deserialize unmanaged memory. The parser tries to interpret bytes next to buffer and throws an exception with string. If the following bytes are not printable UTF-8 the parser throws an exception with a single byte.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 05:10:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2444 | Inline Related Posts &amp;lt; 3.5.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2444</link><description>The Inline Related Posts WordPress plugin before 3.5.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 05:10:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3360 | SourceCodester Online Library System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3360</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin/books/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259464.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 04:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3359 | SourceCodester Online Library System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3359</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument user_email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259463.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 04:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3358 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3358</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument to leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259462 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1385 | The WP-Stateless – Google Cloud Storage plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1385</link><description>The WP-Stateless – Google Cloud Storage plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the dismiss_notices() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary option values to the current time, which may completely take a site offline.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2656 | The Email Subscribers by Icegram Express – Email Marketing, Newsletters, Automation for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2656</link><description>The Email Subscribers by Icegram Express – Email Marketing, Newsletters, Automation for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a CSV import in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2950 | The BoldGrid Easy SEO – Simple and Effective SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and inclu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2950</link><description>The BoldGrid Easy SEO – Simple and Effective SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.14 via meta information (og:description) This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view the first 130 characters of a password protected post which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3216 | The WooCommerce PDF Invoices, Packing Slips, Delivery Notes and Shipping Labels plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modificat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3216</link><description>The WooCommerce PDF Invoices, Packing Slips, Delivery Notes and Shipping Labels plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the wt_pklist_reset_settings() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset all of the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3245 | The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor pl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3245</link><description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Youtube block in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 02:41:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1994 | The Image Watermark plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the waterma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1994</link><description>The Image Watermark plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the watermark_action_ajax() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to apply and remove watermarks from images.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 02:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3357 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3357</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file admin/mod_reports/index.php. The manipulation of the argument end leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259461 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 21:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3356 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3356</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/mod_settings/controller.php?action=add. The manipulation of the argument type leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259460.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 21:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30977 | An issue in Secnet Security Network Intelligent AC Management System v.1.02.040 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the passw...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30977</link><description>An issue in Secnet Security Network Intelligent AC Management System v.1.02.040 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the password component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 21:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25493 | A potential vulnerability was reported in the BIOS update tool driver for some Desktop, Smart Edge, Smart Office, and ThinkStation products ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25493</link><description>A potential vulnerability was reported in the BIOS update tool driver for some Desktop, Smart Edge, Smart Office, and ThinkStation products that could allow a local user with elevated privileges to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25494 | A potential vulnerability were reported in the BIOS of some Desktop, Smart Edge, and ThinkStation products that could allow a local attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25494</link><description>A potential vulnerability were reported in the BIOS of some Desktop, Smart Edge, and ThinkStation products that could allow a local attacker with elevated privileges to write to NVRAM variables.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4605 | A valid authenticated Lenovo XClarity Administrator (LXCA) user can potentially leverage an unauthenticated API endpoint to retrieve system ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4605</link><description>A valid authenticated Lenovo XClarity Administrator (LXCA) user can potentially leverage an unauthenticated API endpoint to retrieve system event information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5912 | A potential memory leakage vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Notebook products that may allow a local attacker with elevated privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5912</link><description>A potential memory leakage vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Notebook products that may allow a local attacker with elevated privileges to write to NVRAM variables.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23592 | An authentication bypass vulnerability was reported in Lenovo devices with Synaptics fingerprint readers that could allow an attacker with p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23592</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability was reported in Lenovo devices with Synaptics fingerprint readers that could allow an attacker with physical access to replay fingerprints and bypass Windows Hello authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27908 | A buffer overflow vulnerability was reported in the HTTPS service of some Lenovo Printers that could result in denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27908</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was reported in the HTTPS service of some Lenovo Printers that could result in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27909 | A denial of service vulnerability was reported in the HTTPS service of some Lenovo Printers that could result in a system reboot.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27909</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability was reported in the HTTPS service of some Lenovo Printers that could result in a system reboot.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27910 | A vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker to reboot the printer without authenticati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27910</link><description>A vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker to reboot the printer without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27911 | A vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker to obtain the administrator password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27911</link><description>A vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Printers that could allow an unauthenticated attacker to obtain the administrator password.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27912 | A denial of service vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Printers that could allow an attacker to cause the device to crash by sending ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27912</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Printers that could allow an attacker to cause the device to crash by sending crafted LPD packets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3355 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3355</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/mod_users/controller.php?action=add. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259459.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27231 | In tmu_get_tr_stats of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27231</link><description>In tmu_get_tr_stats of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27232 | In asn1_ec_pkey_parse of asn1_common.c, there is a possible OOB read due to a missing null check. This could lead to local information discl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27232</link><description>In asn1_ec_pkey_parse of asn1_common.c, there is a possible OOB read due to a missing null check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29738 | In gov_init, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29738</link><description>In gov_init, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29739 | In tmu_get_temp_lut of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29739</link><description>In tmu_get_temp_lut of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29740 | In tmu_set_table of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29740</link><description>In tmu_set_table of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29741 | In pblS2mpuResume of s2mpu.c, there is a possible mitigation bypass due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29741</link><description>In pblS2mpuResume of s2mpu.c, there is a possible mitigation bypass due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29742 | In apply_minlock_constraint of dvfs.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local inform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29742</link><description>In apply_minlock_constraint of dvfs.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29743 | In tmu_set_temp_lut of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29743</link><description>In tmu_set_temp_lut of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29744 | In tmu_get_gov_time_windows, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29744</link><description>In tmu_get_gov_time_windows, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29745 | there is a possible Information Disclosure due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29745</link><description>there is a possible Information Disclosure due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29746 | In lpm_req_handler of lpm.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29746</link><description>In lpm_req_handler of lpm.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29747 | In _dvfs_get_lv of dvfs.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing null check. This could lead to local information disclosu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29747</link><description>In _dvfs_get_lv of dvfs.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing null check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29748 | there is a possible way to bypass  due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29748</link><description>there is a possible way to bypass  due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29749 | In tmu_set_tr_thresholds of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29749</link><description>In tmu_set_tr_thresholds of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29750 | In km_exp_did_inner of kmv.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29750</link><description>In km_exp_did_inner of kmv.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29751 | In asn1_ec_pkey_parse_p384 of asn1_common.c, there is a possible OOB Read due to a missing null check. This could lead to local information ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29751</link><description>In asn1_ec_pkey_parse_p384 of asn1_common.c, there is a possible OOB Read due to a missing null check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29752 | In tmu_set_tr_num_thresholds of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29752</link><description>In tmu_set_tr_num_thresholds of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29753 | In tmu_set_control_temp_step of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29753</link><description>In tmu_set_control_temp_step of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29754 | In TMU_IPC_GET_TABLE, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29754</link><description>In TMU_IPC_GET_TABLE, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29755 | In tmu_get_pi of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29755</link><description>In tmu_get_pi of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29756 | In afe_callback of q6afe.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29756</link><description>In afe_callback of q6afe.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29757 | there is a possible permission bypass due to Debug certs being allowlisted. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29757</link><description>there is a possible permission bypass due to Debug certs being allowlisted. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29782 | In tmu_get_tr_num_thresholds of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local inform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29782</link><description>In tmu_get_tr_num_thresholds of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29783 | In tmu_get_tr_thresholds, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclos...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29783</link><description>In tmu_get_tr_thresholds, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3354 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3354</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin/mod_users/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259458 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 20:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2312 | GRUB2 does not call the module fini functions on exit, leading to Debian/Ubuntu's peimage GRUB2 module leaving UEFI system table hooks after...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2312</link><description>GRUB2 does not call the module fini functions on exit, leading to Debian/Ubuntu's peimage GRUB2 module leaving UEFI system table hooks after exit. This lead to a use-after-free condition, and could possibly lead to secure boot bypass.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 19:51:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3353 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3353</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/mod_reports/index.php. The manipulation of the argument categ/end leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259457 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 19:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3352 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3352</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file admin/mod_comments/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259456.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 19:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0081 | NVIDIA NeMo framework for Ubuntu contains a vulnerability in tools/asr_webapp where an attacker may cause an allocation of resources without...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0081</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo framework for Ubuntu contains a vulnerability in tools/asr_webapp where an attacker may cause an allocation of resources without limits or throttling. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a server-side denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 18:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22004 | Unchecked length in Trusted Application on Google Nest Wifi Pro, leading to out of bounds read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22004</link><description>Due to length check, an attacker with privilege access on a Linux Nonsecure operating system can trigger a vulnerability and leak the secure memory from the Trusted Application</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 18:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3351 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3351</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file admin/mod_roomtype/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259455.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 18:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28065 | In Unify CP IP Phone firmware 1.10.4.3, files are not encrypted and contain sensitive information such as the root password hash.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28065</link><description>In Unify CP IP Phone firmware 1.10.4.3, files are not encrypted and contain sensitive information such as the root password hash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 18:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0076 | NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump and nvdisasm where an attacker may cause a crash by tricking a u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0076</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump and nvdisasm where an attacker may cause a crash by tricking a user into reading a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0080 | NVIDIA nvTIFF Library for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where improper input validation might enable an attacker to use a speci...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0080</link><description>NVIDIA nvTIFF Library for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where improper input validation might enable an attacker to use a specially crafted input file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31028 | NVIDIA nvJPEG2000 Library for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where improper input validation might enable an attacker to use a s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31028</link><description>NVIDIA nvJPEG2000 Library for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where improper input validation might enable an attacker to use a specially crafted input file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:55:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0072 | NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump and nvdisasm where an attacker may cause a crash by tricking a u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0072</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump and nvdisasm where an attacker may cause a crash by tricking a user into reading a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31851 | A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Java version of CData Sync &lt; 23.4.8843 when running using the embedded Jetty server, which coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31851</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Java version of CData Sync &lt; 23.4.8843 when running using the embedded Jetty server, which could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to gain access to sensitive information and perform limited actions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31848 | A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Java version of CData API Server &lt; 23.4.8844 when running using the embedded Jetty server, whic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31848</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Java version of CData API Server &lt; 23.4.8844 when running using the embedded Jetty server, which could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to gain complete administrative access to the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31849 | A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Java version of CData Connect &lt; 23.4.8846 when running using the embedded Jetty server, which c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31849</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Java version of CData Connect &lt; 23.4.8846 when running using the embedded Jetty server, which could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to gain complete administrative access to the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31850 | A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Java version of CData Arc &lt; 23.4.8839 when running using the embedded Jetty server, which could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31850</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Java version of CData Arc &lt; 23.4.8839 when running using the embedded Jetty server, which could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to gain access to sensitive information and perform limited actions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3350 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3350</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/mod_room/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259454 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3349 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3349</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259453 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3348 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3348</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file booking/index.php. The manipulation of the argument log_email/log_pword leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259452.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3347 | SourceCodester Airline Ticket Reservation System activate_jet_details_form_handler.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3347</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Airline Ticket Reservation System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file activate_jet_details_form_handler.php. The manipulation of the argument jet_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259451.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:12:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3346 | Byzro Smart S80 webmailattach.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3346</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Byzro Smart S80 up to 20240328. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /log/webmailattach.php. The manipulation of the argument mail_file_path leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259450 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48426 | Chromecast Bootloader &amp;amp; Kernel-level code-execution including compromise of user-data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48426</link><description>u-boot bug that allows for u-boot shell and interrupt over UART</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31220 | Sunshine vulnerable to remote unauthenticated arbitrary file read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31220</link><description>Sunshine is a self-hosted game stream host for Moonlight. Starting in version 0.16.0 and prior to version 0.18.0, an attacker may be able to remotely read arbitrary files without authentication due to a path traversal vulnerability. Users who exposed the Sunshine configuration web user interface outside of localhost may be affected, depending on firewall configuration. To exploit vulnerability, attacker could make an http/s request to the `node_modules` endpoint if user exposed Sunshine config web server to internet or attacker is on the LAN. Version 0.18.0 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, one may block access to Sunshine via firewall.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:07:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31213 | InstantCMS Open Redirect vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31213</link><description>InstantCMS is a free and open source content management system. An open redirect was found in the ICMS2 application version 2.16.2 when being redirected after modifying one's own user profile. An attacker could trick a victim into visiting their web application, thinking they are still present on the ICMS2 application. They could then host a website stating "To update your profile, please enter your password," upon which the user may type their password and send it to the attacker. As of time of publication, a patched version is not available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 14:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31218 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function in Webhood backend</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31218</link><description>Webhood is a self-hosted URL scanner used analyzing phishing and malicious sites. Webhood's backend container images in versions 0.9.0 and earlier are subject to Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to send a HTTP request to the database (Pocketbase) admin API to create an admin account. The Pocketbase admin API does not check for authentication/authorization when creating an admin account when no admin accounts have been added. In its default deployment, Webhood does not create a database admin account. Therefore, unless users have manually created an admin account in the database, an admin account will not exist in the deployment and the deployment is vulnerable. Versions starting from 0.9.1 are patched. The patch creates a randomly generated admin account if admin accounts have not already been created i.e. the vulnerability is exploitable in the deployment. As a workaround, users can disable access to URL path starting with `/api/admins` entirely. With this workaround, the vulnerability is not exploitable via network.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 14:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31852 | LLVM before 18.1.3 generates code in which the LR register can be overwritten without data being saved to the stack, and thus there can some...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31852</link><description>LLVM before 18.1.3 generates code in which the LR register can be overwritten without data being saved to the stack, and thus there can sometimes be an exploitable error in the flow of control. This affects the ARM backend and can be demonstrated with Clang. NOTE: the vendor perspective is "we don't have strong objections for a CVE to be created ... It does seem that the likelihood of this miscompile enabling an exploit remains very low, because the miscompile resulting in this JOP gadget is such that the function is most likely to crash on most valid inputs to the function. So, if this function is covered by any testing, the miscompile is most likely to be discovered before the binary is shipped to production."</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 14:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49965 | SpaceX Starlink Wi-Fi router Gen 2 before 2023.48.0 allows XSS via the ssid and password parameters on the Setup Page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49965</link><description>SpaceX Starlink Wi-Fi router Gen 2 before 2023.48.0 allows XSS via the ssid and password parameters on the Setup Page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 13:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2380 | XSS in graph rendering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2380</link><description>Stored XSS in graph rendering in Checkmk &lt;2.3.0b4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 13:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5692 | WordPress Core is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including,  6.4.3 via the redirect_guess_404_permalink...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5692</link><description>WordPress Core is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including,  6.4.3 via the redirect_guess_404_permalink function. This can allow unauthenticated attackers to expose the slug of a custom post whose 'publicly_queryable' post status has been set to 'false'.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 13:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2499 | The Squelch Tabs and Accordions Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'accordions' s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2499</link><description>The Squelch Tabs and Accordions Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'accordions' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 13:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31083 | Xorg-x11-server: user-after-free in procrenderaddglyphs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31083</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability was found in the ProcRenderAddGlyphs() function of Xorg servers. This issue occurs when AllocateGlyph() is called to store new glyphs sent by the client to the X server, potentially resulting in multiple entries pointing to the same non-refcounted glyphs. Consequently, ProcRenderAddGlyphs() may free a glyph, leading to a use-after-free scenario when the same glyph pointer is subsequently accessed. This flaw allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on the system by sending a specially crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6522 | Information Disclosure in ExtremePacs&amp;#x27;s Extreme XDS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6522</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in ExtremePacs Extreme XDS allows Collect Data as Provided by Users.This issue affects Extreme XDS: before 3914.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 11:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6523 | IDOR in ExtremePacs&amp;#x27;s Extreme XDS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6523</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in ExtremePacs Extreme XDS allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects Extreme XDS: before 3914.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 11:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2447 | Mattermost versions 8.1.x before 8.1.11, 9.3.x before 9.3.3, 9.4.x before 9.4.4, and 9.5.x before 9.5.2 fail to authenticate the source of c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2447</link><description>Mattermost versions 8.1.x before 8.1.11, 9.3.x before 9.3.3, 9.4.x before 9.4.4, and 9.5.x before 9.5.2 fail to authenticate the source of certain types of post actions, allowing an authenticated attacker to create posts as other users via a crafted post action.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 09:07:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26810 | vfio/pci: Lock external INTx masking ops</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26810</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vfio/pci: Lock external INTx masking ops

Mask operations through config space changes to DisINTx may race INTx
configuration changes via ioctl.  Create wrappers that add locking for
paths outside of the core interrupt code.

In particular, irq_type is updated holding igate, therefore testing
is_intx() requires holding igate.  For example clearing DisINTx from
config space can otherwise race changes of the interrupt configuration.

This aligns interfaces which may trigger the INTx eventfd into two
camps, one side serialized by igate and the other only enabled while
INTx is configured.  A subsequent patch introduces synchronization for
the latter flows.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 08:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26812 | vfio/pci: Create persistent INTx handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26812</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vfio/pci: Create persistent INTx handler

A vulnerability exists where the eventfd for INTx signaling can be
deconfigured, which unregisters the IRQ handler but still allows
eventfds to be signaled with a NULL context through the SET_IRQS ioctl
or through unmask irqfd if the device interrupt is pending.

Ideally this could be solved with some additional locking; the igate
mutex serializes the ioctl and config space accesses, and the interrupt
handler is unregistered relative to the trigger, but the irqfd path
runs asynchronous to those.  The igate mutex cannot be acquired from the
atomic context of the eventfd wake function.  Disabling the irqfd
relative to the eventfd registration is potentially incompatible with
existing userspace.

As a result, the solution implemented here moves configuration of the
INTx interrupt handler to track the lifetime of the INTx context object
and irq_type configuration, rather than registration of a particular
trigger eventfd.  Synchronization is added between the ioctl path and
eventfd_signal() wrapper such that the eventfd trigger can be
dynamically updated relative to in-flight interrupts or irqfd callbacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 08:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26813 | vfio/platform: Create persistent IRQ handlers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26813</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vfio/platform: Create persistent IRQ handlers

The vfio-platform SET_IRQS ioctl currently allows loopback triggering of
an interrupt before a signaling eventfd has been configured by the user,
which thereby allows a NULL pointer dereference.

Rather than register the IRQ relative to a valid trigger, register all
IRQs in a disabled state in the device open path.  This allows mask
operations on the IRQ to nest within the overall enable state governed
by a valid eventfd signal.  This decouples @masked, protected by the
@locked spinlock from @trigger, protected via the @igate mutex.

In doing so, it's guaranteed that changes to @trigger cannot race the
IRQ handlers because the IRQ handler is synchronously disabled before
modifying the trigger, and loopback triggering of the IRQ via ioctl is
safe due to serialization with trigger changes via igate.

For compatibility, request_irq() failures are maintained to be local to
the SET_IRQS ioctl rather than a fatal error in the open device path.
This allows, for example, a userspace driver with polling mode support
to continue to work regardless of moving the request_irq() call site.
This necessarily blocks all SET_IRQS access to the failed index.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 08:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26814 | vfio/fsl-mc: Block calling interrupt handler without trigger</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26814</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vfio/fsl-mc: Block calling interrupt handler without trigger

The eventfd_ctx trigger pointer of the vfio_fsl_mc_irq object is
initially NULL and may become NULL if the user sets the trigger
eventfd to -1.  The interrupt handler itself is guaranteed that
trigger is always valid between request_irq() and free_irq(), but
the loopback testing mechanisms to invoke the handler function
need to test the trigger.  The triggering and setting ioctl paths
both make use of igate and are therefore mutually exclusive.

The vfio-fsl-mc driver does not make use of irqfds, nor does it
support any sort of masking operations, therefore unlike vfio-pci
and vfio-platform, the flow can remain essentially unchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 08:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27437 | vfio/pci: Disable auto-enable of exclusive INTx IRQ</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27437</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vfio/pci: Disable auto-enable of exclusive INTx IRQ

Currently for devices requiring masking at the irqchip for INTx, ie.
devices without DisINTx support, the IRQ is enabled in request_irq()
and subsequently disabled as necessary to align with the masked status
flag.  This presents a window where the interrupt could fire between
these events, resulting in the IRQ incrementing the disable depth twice.
This would be unrecoverable for a user since the masked flag prevents
nested enables through vfio.

Instead, invert the logic using IRQF_NO_AUTOEN such that exclusive INTx
is never auto-enabled, then unmask as required.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 08:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21848 | Users maintain access to active call after being removed from a channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21848</link><description>Improper Access Control in Mattermost Server versions 8.1.x before 8.1.11 allows an attacker that is in a channel with an active call to keep participating in the call even if they are removed from the channel</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 08:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28949 | DoS via a large number of User Preferences</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28949</link><description>Mattermost Server versions 9.5.x before 9.5.2, 9.4.x before 9.4.4, 9.3.x before 9.3.3, 8.1.x before 8.1.11 don't limit the number of user preferences which allows an attacker to send a large number of user preferences potentially causing denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 08:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29221 | Invite ID available to team admins even without the &amp;quot;Add Members&amp;quot; permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29221</link><description>Improper Access Control in Mattermost Server versions 9.5.x before 9.5.2, 9.4.x before 9.4.4, 9.3.x before 9.3.3, 8.1.x before 8.1.11 lacked proper access control in the `/api/v4/users/me/teams` endpoint allowing a team admin to get the invite ID of their team, thus allowing them to invite users, even if the "Add Members" permission was explicitly removed from team admins.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 08:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30849 | Arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Sourcecodester Complete E-Commerce Site v1.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30849</link><description>Arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Sourcecodester Complete E-Commerce Site v1.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via filename parameter in admin/products_photo.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 07:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2115 | The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2115</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the filter_users functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to elevate their privileges to that of a teacher via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 07:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3217 | The WP Directory Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'attribute_value' and 'attribute_id' parameters in all vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3217</link><description>The WP Directory Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'attribute_value' and 'attribute_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 07:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30891 | A command injection vulnerability exists in /goform/exeCommand in Tenda AC18 v15.03.05.05, which allows attackers to construct cmdinput para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30891</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in /goform/exeCommand in Tenda AC18 v15.03.05.05, which allows attackers to construct cmdinput parameters for arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 07:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26329 | Chilkat before v9.5.0.98, allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via predictable PRNG in ChilkatRand::randomBytes function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26329</link><description>Chilkat before v9.5.0.98, allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via predictable PRNG in ChilkatRand::randomBytes function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 07:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29863 | A race condition in the installer executable in Qlik Qlikview before versions May 2022 SR3 (12.70.20300) and May 2023 SR2 (12,80.20200) may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29863</link><description>A race condition in the installer executable in Qlik Qlikview before versions May 2022 SR3 (12.70.20300) and May 2023 SR2 (12,80.20200) may allow an existing lower privileged user to cause code to be executed in the context of a Windows Administrator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 06:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52235 | SpaceX Starlink Wi-Fi router GEN 2 before 2023.53.0 and Starlink Dish before 07dd2798-ff15-4722-a9ee-de28928aed34 allow CSRF (e.g., for a re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52235</link><description>SpaceX Starlink Wi-Fi router GEN 2 before 2023.53.0 and Starlink Dish before 07dd2798-ff15-4722-a9ee-de28928aed34 allow CSRF (e.g., for a reboot) via a DNS Rebinding attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 06:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27448 | MailDev 2 through 2.1.0 allows Remote Code Execution via a crafted Content-ID header for an e-mail attachment, leading to lib/mailserver.js ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27448</link><description>MailDev 2 through 2.1.0 allows Remote Code Execution via a crafted Content-ID header for an e-mail attachment, leading to lib/mailserver.js writing arbitrary code into the routes.js file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 06:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29672 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in zly2006 Reden before v.0.2.514 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the DEBUG_RTC_REQ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29672</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in zly2006 Reden before v.0.2.514 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the DEBUG_RTC_REQUEST_SYNC_DATA in KeyCallbacks.kt.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 05:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22363 | SheetJS Community Edition before 0.20.2 is vulnerable.to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22363</link><description>SheetJS Community Edition before 0.20.2 is vulnerable.to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS).</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 05:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2509 | Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks &amp;lt; 3.2.26 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2509</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks  WordPress plugin before 3.2.26 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 05:07:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5973 | Truncated port name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5973</link><description>Brocade
 Web Interface in Brocade Fabric OS v9.x and before v9.2.0 does not 
properly represent the portName to the user if the portName contains 
reserved characters. This could allow an authenticated user to alter the
 UI of the Brocade Switch and change ports display.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 02:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3321 | SourceCodester eLearning System Maintenance Module cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3321</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester eLearning System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Maintenance Module. The manipulation of the argument Subject Code/Description leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259389 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 01:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3320 | SourceCodester eLearning System cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3320</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester eLearning System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation of the argument page leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259388.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:29:40 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>