<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:44:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-22956 | OPSI before 4.3 allows any client to retrieve any ProductPropertyState, including those of other clients. This can lead to privilege escalat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22956</link><description>OPSI before 4.3 allows any client to retrieve any ProductPropertyState, including those of other clients. This can lead to privilege escalation if any ProductPropertyState contains a secret only intended to be accessible by a subset of clients. One example of this is a domain join account password for the windomain package.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3212 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows access to already freed memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3212</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user process to perform valid GPU memory processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r49p4, from r50p0 through r51p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r49p4, from r50p0 through r54p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r49p4, from r50p0 through r54p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10093 | D-Link DIR-852 Device Configuration getcfg.php phpcgi_main information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10093</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-852 up to 1.00CN B09. Affected by this vulnerability is the function phpcgi_main of the file /getcfg.php of the component Device Configuration Handler. Such manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 12:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40641 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the Multi-purpose Inventory Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40641</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability stored in Multi-Purpose Inventory Management System, consisting of a stored XSS due to lack of proper validation of user input by sending a POST request using the product_name parameter in /Controller_Products/update. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal their cookie session details.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 11:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10092 | Jinher OA XML Type xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10092</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Jinher OA up to 1.2. This impacts an unknown function of the file /c6/Jhsoft.Web.projectmanage/TaskManage/AddTask.aspx/?Type=add of the component XML Handler. The manipulation results in xml external entity reference. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 11:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40642 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in WebWork</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40642</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WebWork, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code through the 'q' and 'engine' request parameters in /search.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 11:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10091 | Jinher OA XML Type xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10091</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Jinher OA up to 1.2. This affects an unknown function of the file /c6/Jhsoft.Web.projectmanage/ProjectManage/XmlHttp.aspx/?Type=add of the component XML Handler. The manipulation leads to xml external entity reference. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 11:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5993 | Path Traversal in ITCube CRM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5993</link><description>ITCube CRM in versions from 2023.2 through 2025.2 is vulnerable to path traversal. Unauthenticated remote attacker is able to exploit vulnerable parameter fileName and construct payloads that allow to download any file accessible by the the web server process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2014-125128 | 'sanitize-html' prior to version 1.0.3 is vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS). The function 'naughtyHref' doesn't properly validate the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125128</link><description>'sanitize-html' prior to version 1.0.3 is vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS). The function 'naughtyHref' doesn't properly validate the hyperreference (`href`) attribute in anchor tags (`&lt;a&gt;`), allowing bypasses that contain different casings, whitespace characters, or hexadecimal encodings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25225 | `sanitize-html` prior to version 2.0.0-beta is vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS). The `sanitizeHtml()` function in `index.js` does no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25225</link><description>`sanitize-html` prior to version 2.0.0-beta is vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS). The `sanitizeHtml()` function in `index.js` does not sanitize content when using the custom `transformTags` option, which is intended to convert attribute values into text. As a result, malicious input can be transformed into executable code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10090 | Jinher OA GetTreeDate.aspx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10090</link><description>A flaw has been found in Jinher OA up to 1.2. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /C6/Jhsoft.Web.departments/GetTreeDate.aspx. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 09:49:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58782 | Apache Jackrabbit Core, Apache Jackrabbit JCR Commons: JNDI injection risk with JndiRepositoryFactory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58782</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache Jackrabbit Core and Apache Jackrabbit JCR Commons.

This issue affects Apache Jackrabbit Core: from 1.0.0 through 2.22.1; Apache Jackrabbit JCR Commons: from 1.0.0 through 2.22.1.

Deployments that accept JNDI URIs for JCR lookup from untrusted users allows them to inject malicious JNDI references, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution through deserialization of untrusted data.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.22.2. JCR lookup through JNDI has been disabled by default in 2.22.2. Users of this feature need to enable it explicitly and are adviced to review their use of JNDI URI for JCR lookup.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 09:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10088 | SourceCodester Time Tracker index.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10088</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Time Tracker 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /index.html. Performing manipulation of the argument project-name results in cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 07:22:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10087 | SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software profit_report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10087</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/profit_report.php. Such manipulation of the argument product_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 06:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41664 | Improper Permission Handling Enables Unauthorized Access to Firmware and Certificates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41664</link><description>A low-privileged remote attacker could gain unauthorized access to critical resources, such as firmware and certificates, due to improper permission handling during the runtime of services (e.g., FTP/SFTP). This access could allow the attacker to escalate privileges and modify firmware.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 06:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41682 | Credential Disclosure via Insecure Storage on Charge Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41682</link><description>An authenticated, low-privileged attacker can obtain credentials stored on the charge controller including the manufacturer password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 06:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41708 | Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Data via Insecure HTTP Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41708</link><description>Due to an unsecure default configuration HTTP is used instead of HTTPS for the web interface. An unauthenticated attacker on the same network could exploit this to learn sensitive data during transmission.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 06:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10086 | fuyang_lipengjun platform AdPositionController queryAll improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10086</link><description>A weakness has been identified in fuyang_lipengjun platform 1.0.0. This issue affects the function queryAll of the file /adposition/queryAll of the component AdPositionController. This manipulation causes improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. Affects another part than CVE-2025-9936.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 06:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8085 | Ditty &amp;lt; 3.1.58 - Unauthenticated SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8085</link><description>The Ditty  WordPress plugin before 3.1.58 lacks authorization and authentication for requests to its displayItems endpoint, allowing unauthenticated visitors to make requests to arbitrary URLs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 06:21:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10085 | SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software manage_website.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10085</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file manage_website.php. The manipulation results in unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 05:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10084 | elunez eladmin SysLogController 1 queryErrorLogDetail improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10084</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in elunez eladmin up to 2.7. This affects the function queryErrorLogDetail of the file /api/logs/error/1 of the component SysLogController. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 05:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58422 | RICOH Streamline NX versions 3.5.1 to 24R3 are vulnerable to tampering with operation history. If an attacker can perform a man-in-the-middl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58422</link><description>RICOH Streamline NX versions 3.5.1 to 24R3 are vulnerable to tampering with operation history. If an attacker can perform a man-in-the-middle attack, they may alter the values of HTTP requests, which could result in tampering with the operation history of the product’s management tool.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10083 | SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software profile.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10083</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/profile.php. Executing manipulation can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10082 | SourceCodester Online Polling System manage-admins.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10082</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Polling System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/manage-admins.php. Such manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:14:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10081 | SourceCodester Pet Management System profile.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10081</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Pet Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/profile.php. This manipulation of the argument website_image causes unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 03:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10080 | running-elephant Datart API AESUtil.java getTokensecret hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10080</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in running-elephant Datart up to 1.0.0-rc3. Affected by this issue is the function getTokensecret of the file datart/security/src/main/java/datart/security/util/AESUtil.java of the component API. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 03:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10079 | PHPGurukul Small CRM get-quote.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10079</link><description>A flaw has been found in PHPGurukul Small CRM 4.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /get-quote.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Contact can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 03:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10078 | SourceCodester Online Polling System candidates.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10078</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Online Polling System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/candidates.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 02:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10077 | SourceCodester Online Polling System registeracc.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10077</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SourceCodester Online Polling System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /registeracc.php. Such manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 02:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10076 | SourceCodester Online Polling System manage-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10076</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Online Polling System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /manage-profile.php. This manipulation of the argument email causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 01:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10075 | SourceCodester Online Polling System manage-profile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10075</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in SourceCodester Online Polling System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /manage-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument firstname results in cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 01:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10074 | Portabilis i-Educar tipos cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10074</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /usuarios/tipos/. The manipulation of the argument Tipos de Usuário/Descrição leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 01:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10073 | Portabilis i-Educar turma improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10073</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /module/Api/turma. Executing manipulation can lead to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 23:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10072 | Portabilis i-Educar enturmar access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10072</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /matricula/[ID_STUDENT]/enturmar/. Performing manipulation results in improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 23:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10071 | Portabilis i-Educar cancelar-enturmacao-em-lote access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10071</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /cancelar-enturmacao-em-lote/. Such manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 22:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10070 | Portabilis i-Educar enturmacao-em-lote access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10070</link><description>A flaw has been found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This affects an unknown part of the file /enturmacao-em-lote/. This manipulation causes improper access controls. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 22:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48042 | Before action hooks may execute in certain scenarios despite a request being forbidden</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48042</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in ash-project ash allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This vulnerability is associated with program files lib/ash/actions/create/bulk.ex, lib/ash/actions/destroy/bulk.ex, lib/ash/actions/update/bulk.ex and program routines 'Elixir.Ash.Actions.Create.Bulk':run/5, 'Elixir.Ash.Actions.Destroy.Bulk':run/6, 'Elixir.Ash.Actions.Update.Bulk:run'/6.

This issue affects ash: from pkg:hex/ash before pkg:hex/ash@3.5.39, before 3.5.39, before 5d1b6a5d00771fd468a509778637527b5218be9a.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39727 | mm: swap: fix potential buffer overflow in setup_clusters()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39727</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: swap: fix potential buffer overflow in setup_clusters()

In setup_swap_map(), we only ensure badpages are in range (0, last_page]. 
As maxpages might be &lt; last_page, setup_clusters() will encounter a buffer
overflow when a badpage is &gt;= maxpages.

Only call inc_cluster_info_page() for badpage which is &lt; maxpages to fix
the issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 15:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39729 | crypto: ccp - Fix dereferencing uninitialized error pointer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39729</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: ccp - Fix dereferencing uninitialized error pointer

Fix below smatch warnings:
drivers/crypto/ccp/sev-dev.c:1312 __sev_platform_init_locked()
error: we previously assumed 'error' could be null</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 15:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39730 | NFS: Fix filehandle bounds checking in nfs_fh_to_dentry()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39730</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

NFS: Fix filehandle bounds checking in nfs_fh_to_dentry()

The function needs to check the minimal filehandle length before it can
access the embedded filehandle.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 15:30:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39731 | f2fs: vm_unmap_ram() may be called from an invalid context</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39731</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

f2fs: vm_unmap_ram() may be called from an invalid context

When testing F2FS with xfstests using UFS backed virtual disks the
kernel complains sometimes that f2fs_release_decomp_mem() calls
vm_unmap_ram() from an invalid context. Example trace from
f2fs/007 test:

f2fs/007 5s ...  [12:59:38][    8.902525] run fstests f2fs/007
[   11.468026] BUG: sleeping function called from invalid context at mm/vmalloc.c:2978
[   11.471849] in_atomic(): 1, irqs_disabled(): 1, non_block: 0, pid: 68, name: irq/22-ufshcd
[   11.475357] preempt_count: 1, expected: 0
[   11.476970] RCU nest depth: 0, expected: 0
[   11.478531] CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 68 Comm: irq/22-ufshcd Tainted: G        W           6.16.0-rc5-xfstests-ufs-g40f92e79b0aa #9 PREEMPT(none)
[   11.478535] Tainted: [W]=WARN
[   11.478536] Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS 1.16.3-debian-1.16.3-2 04/01/2014
[   11.478537] Call Trace:
[   11.478543]  
[   11.478545]  dump_stack_lvl+0x4e/0x70
[   11.478554]  __might_resched.cold+0xaf/0xbe
[   11.478557]  vm_unmap_ram+0x21/0xb0
[   11.478560]  f2fs_release_decomp_mem+0x59/0x80
[   11.478563]  f2fs_free_dic+0x18/0x1a0
[   11.478565]  f2fs_finish_read_bio+0xd7/0x290
[   11.478570]  blk_update_request+0xec/0x3b0
[   11.478574]  ? sbitmap_queue_clear+0x3b/0x60
[   11.478576]  scsi_end_request+0x27/0x1a0
[   11.478582]  scsi_io_completion+0x40/0x300
[   11.478583]  ufshcd_mcq_poll_cqe_lock+0xa3/0xe0
[   11.478588]  ufshcd_sl_intr+0x194/0x1f0
[   11.478592]  ufshcd_threaded_intr+0x68/0xb0
[   11.478594]  ? __pfx_irq_thread_fn+0x10/0x10
[   11.478599]  irq_thread_fn+0x20/0x60
[   11.478602]  ? __pfx_irq_thread_fn+0x10/0x10
[   11.478603]  irq_thread+0xb9/0x180
[   11.478605]  ? __pfx_irq_thread_dtor+0x10/0x10
[   11.478607]  ? __pfx_irq_thread+0x10/0x10
[   11.478609]  kthread+0x10a/0x230
[   11.478614]  ? __pfx_kthread+0x10/0x10
[   11.478615]  ret_from_fork+0x7e/0xd0
[   11.478619]  ? __pfx_kthread+0x10/0x10
[   11.478621]  ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30
[   11.478623]  

This patch modifies in_task() check inside f2fs_read_end_io() to also
check if interrupts are disabled. This ensures that pages are unmapped
asynchronously in an interrupt handler.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 15:30:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39732 | wifi: ath11k: fix sleeping-in-atomic in ath11k_mac_op_set_bitrate_mask()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39732</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: ath11k: fix sleeping-in-atomic in ath11k_mac_op_set_bitrate_mask()

ath11k_mac_disable_peer_fixed_rate() is passed as the iterator to
ieee80211_iterate_stations_atomic(). Note in this case the iterator is
required to be atomic, however ath11k_mac_disable_peer_fixed_rate() does
not follow it as it might sleep. Consequently below warning is seen:

BUG: sleeping function called from invalid context at wmi.c:304
Call Trace:
 
 dump_stack_lvl
 __might_resched.cold
 ath11k_wmi_cmd_send
 ath11k_wmi_set_peer_param
 ath11k_mac_disable_peer_fixed_rate
 ieee80211_iterate_stations_atomic
 ath11k_mac_op_set_bitrate_mask.cold

Change to ieee80211_iterate_stations_mtx() to fix this issue.

Tested-on: WCN6855 hw2.0 PCI WLAN.HSP.1.1-03125-QCAHSPSWPL_V1_V2_SILICONZ_LITE-3.6510.30</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 15:30:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39733 | team: replace team lock with rtnl lock</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39733</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

team: replace team lock with rtnl lock

syszbot reports various ordering issues for lower instance locks and
team lock. Switch to using rtnl lock for protecting team device,
similar to bonding. Based on the patch by Tetsuo Handa.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 15:30:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39734 | Revert &amp;quot;fs/ntfs3: Replace inode_trylock with inode_lock&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39734</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Revert "fs/ntfs3: Replace inode_trylock with inode_lock"

This reverts commit 69505fe98f198ee813898cbcaf6770949636430b.

Initially, conditional lock acquisition was removed to fix an xfstest bug
that was observed during internal testing. The deadlock reported by syzbot
is resolved by reintroducing conditional acquisition. The xfstest bug no
longer occurs on kernel version 6.16-rc1 during internal testing. I
assume that changes in other modules may have contributed to this.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 15:30:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10068 | itsourcecode Online Discussion Forum add_views.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10068</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Online Discussion Forum 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/admin_forum/add_views.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 04:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10067 | itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System empty_table.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10067</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /inventory/main/vendors/datatables/unit_testing/templates/empty_table.php. Performing manipulation of the argument scripts results in cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 02:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10066 | itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System dymanic_table.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10066</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /inventory/main/vendors/datatables/unit_testing/templates/dymanic_table.php. Such manipulation of the argument scripts leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 02:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10064 | itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System dom_data_two_headers.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10064</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /inventory/main/vendors/datatables/unit_testing/templates/dom_data_two_headers.php. The manipulation of the argument scripts results in cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 01:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10065 | itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System dom_data_th.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10065</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /inventory/main/vendors/datatables/unit_testing/templates/dom_data_th.php. This manipulation of the argument scripts causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 01:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36100 | IBM MQ information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36100</link><description>IBM MQ LTS 9.1.0.0 through 9.1.0.29, 9.2.0.0 through 9.2.0.36, 9.3.0.0 through 9.3.0.30 and 9.4.0.0 through 9.4.0.12 and IBM MQ CD 9.3.0.0 through 9.3.5.1 and 9.4.0.0 through 9.4.3.0  Java and JMS stores a password in client configuration files when trace is enabled which can be read by a local user.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 01:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10063 | itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System deferred_table.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10063</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /inventory/main/vendors/datatables/unit_testing/templates/deferred_table.php. The manipulation of the argument scripts leads to cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 23:14:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10062 | itsourcecode Student Information Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10062</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Student Information Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/login.php. Executing manipulation of the argument uname can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 22:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58443 | FOG&amp;#x27;s authentication bypass leads to full SQL DB dump</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58443</link><description>FOG is a free open-source cloning/imaging/rescue suite/inventory management system. Versions 1.5.10.1673 and below contain an authentication bypass vulnerability. It is possible for an attacker to perform an unauthenticated DB dump where they could pull a full SQL DB without credentials. A fix is expected to be released 9/15/2025. To address this vulnerability immediately, upgrade to the latest version of either the dev-branch or working-1.6 branch. This will patch the issue for users concerned about immediate exposure. See the FOG Project documentation for step-by-step upgrade instructions: https://docs.fogproject.org/en/latest/install-fog-server#choosing-a-fog-version.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 20:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58445 | Atlantis Exposes Service Version Publicly on /status API Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58445</link><description>Atlantis is a self-hosted golang application that listens for Terraform pull request events via webhooks. All versions of Atlantis publicly expose detailed version information through its /status endpoint. This information disclosure could allow attackers to identify and target known vulnerabilities associated with the specific versions, potentially compromising the service's security posture. This issue does not currently have a fix.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 19:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58446 | xgrammar vulnerable to denial of service by huge enum grammar</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58446</link><description>xgrammar is an open-source library for efficient, flexible, and portable structured generation. A grammar optimizer introduced in 0.1.23 processes large grammars (&gt;100k characters) at very low rates, and can be used for DOS of model providers. This issue is fixed in version 0.1.24.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 19:22:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58438 | internetarchive is vulnerable to Directory Traversal through file downloads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58438</link><description>internetarchive is a Python and Command-Line Interface to Archive.org In versions 5.5.0 and below, there is a directory traversal (path traversal) vulnerability in the File.download() method of the internetarchive library. The file.download() method does not properly sanitize user-supplied filenames or validate the final download path. A maliciously crafted filename could contain path traversal sequences (e.g., ../../../../windows/system32/file.txt) or illegal characters that, when processed, would cause the file to be written outside of the intended target directory. An attacker could potentially overwrite critical system files or application configuration files, leading to a denial of service, privilege escalation, or remote code execution, depending on the context in which the library is used.  The vulnerability is particularly critical for users on Windows systems, but all operating systems are affected. This issue is fixed in version 5.5.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 18:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0032 | Improper cleanup in AMD CPU microcode patch loading could allow an attacker with local administrator privilege to load malicious CPU microco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0032</link><description>Improper cleanup in AMD CPU microcode patch loading could allow an attacker with local administrator privilege to load malicious CPU microcode, potentially resulting in loss of integrity of x86 instruction execution.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 18:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0034 | Insufficient parameter sanitization in TEE SOC Driver could allow an attacker to issue a malformed DRV_SOC_CMD_ID_SRIOV_SPATIAL_PART and cau...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0034</link><description>Insufficient parameter sanitization in TEE SOC Driver could allow an attacker to issue a malformed DRV_SOC_CMD_ID_SRIOV_SPATIAL_PART and cause read or write past the end of allocated arrays, potentially resulting in a loss of platform integrity or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 18:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0010 | An out of bounds write in the Linux graphics driver could allow an attacker to overflow the buffer potentially resulting in loss of confiden...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0010</link><description>An out of bounds write in the Linux graphics driver could allow an attacker to overflow the buffer potentially resulting in loss of confidentiality, integrity, or availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 18:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0011 | Improper removal of sensitive information before storage or transfer in AMD Crash Defender could allow an attacker to obtain kernel address ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0011</link><description>Improper removal of sensitive information before storage or transfer in AMD Crash Defender could allow an attacker to obtain kernel address information potentially resulting in loss of confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 18:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0009 | A NULL pointer dereference in AMD Crash Defender could allow an attacker to write a NULL output to a log file potentially resulting in a sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0009</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference in AMD Crash Defender could allow an attacker to write a NULL output to a log file potentially resulting in a system crash and loss of availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 18:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36354 | Improper input validation for DIMM serial presence detect (SPD) metadata could allow an attacker with physical access, ring0 access on a sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36354</link><description>Improper input validation for DIMM serial presence detect (SPD) metadata could allow an attacker with physical access, ring0 access on a system with a non-compliant DIMM, or control over the Root of Trust for BIOS update, to bypass SMM isolation potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution at the SMM level.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 18:13:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36352 | Improper input validation in the AMD Graphics Driver could allow an attacker to supply a specially crafted pointer, potentially leading to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36352</link><description>Improper input validation in the AMD Graphics Driver could allow an attacker to supply a specially crafted pointer, potentially leading to arbitrary writes or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 18:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36342 | Improper input validation in the GPU driver could allow an attacker to exploit a heap overflow potentially resulting in arbitrary code execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36342</link><description>Improper input validation in the GPU driver could allow an attacker to exploit a heap overflow potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 17:53:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36346 | Improper input validation in AMD Power Management Firmware (PMFW) could allow a privileged attacker from Guest VM to send arbitrary input da...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36346</link><description>Improper input validation in AMD Power Management Firmware (PMFW) could allow a privileged attacker from Guest VM to send arbitrary input data potentially causing a GPU Reset condition.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 17:53:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36331 | Improper initialization of CPU cache memory could allow a privileged attacker with hypervisor access to overwrite SEV-SNP guest memory resul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36331</link><description>Improper initialization of CPU cache memory could allow a privileged attacker with hypervisor access to overwrite SEV-SNP guest memory resulting in loss of data integrity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 17:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21970 | Improper validation of an array index in the AND power Management Firmware could allow a privileged attacker to corrupt AGESA memory potenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21970</link><description>Improper validation of an array index in the AND power Management Firmware could allow a privileged attacker to corrupt AGESA memory potentially leading to a loss of integrity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 17:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36326 | Missing authorization in AMD RomArmor could allow an attacker to bypass ROMArmor protections during system resume from a standby state, pote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36326</link><description>Missing authorization in AMD RomArmor could allow an attacker to bypass ROMArmor protections during system resume from a standby state, potentially resulting in a loss of confidentiality and integrity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 17:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21947 | Improper input validation in the system management mode (SMM) could allow a privileged attacker to overwrite arbitrary memory potentially re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21947</link><description>Improper input validation in the system management mode (SMM) could allow a privileged attacker to overwrite arbitrary memory potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution at the SMM level.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 17:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31365 | An integer overflow in the SMU could allow a privileged attacker to potentially write memory beyond the end of the reserved dRAM area result...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31365</link><description>An integer overflow in the SMU could allow a privileged attacker to potentially write memory beyond the end of the reserved dRAM area resulting in loss of integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 17:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31330 | An out-of-bounds read in the ASP could allow a privileged attacker with access to a malicious bootloader to potentially read sensitive memor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31330</link><description>An out-of-bounds read in the ASP could allow a privileged attacker with access to a malicious bootloader to potentially read sensitive memory resulting in loss of confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 17:10:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31351 | Improper restriction of operations in the IOMMU could allow a malicious hypervisor to access guest private memory resulting in loss of integ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31351</link><description>Improper restriction of operations in the IOMMU could allow a malicious hypervisor to access guest private memory resulting in loss of integrity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 17:10:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31326 | Use of an uninitialized variable in the ASP could allow an attacker to access leftover data from a trusted execution environment (TEE) drive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31326</link><description>Use of an uninitialized variable in the ASP could allow an attacker to access leftover data from a trusted execution environment (TEE) driver, potentially leading to loss of confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31325 | Improper isolation of shared resources on System-on-a-chip (SOC) could a privileged attacker to tamper with the contents of the PSP reserved...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31325</link><description>Improper isolation of shared resources on System-on-a-chip (SOC) could a privileged attacker to tamper with the contents of the PSP reserved DRAM region potentially resulting in loss of confidentiality and integrity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:46:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31322 | Type confusion in the ASP could allow an attacker to pass a malformed argument to the Reliability, Availability, and Serviceability trusted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31322</link><description>Type confusion in the ASP could allow an attacker to pass a malformed argument to the Reliability, Availability, and Serviceability trusted application (RAS TA) potentially leading to a read or write to shared memory resulting in loss of confidentiality, integrity, or availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31306 | Improper validation of an array index in the AMD graphics driver software could allow an attacker to pass malformed arguments to the dynamic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31306</link><description>Improper validation of an array index in the AMD graphics driver software could allow an attacker to pass malformed arguments to the dynamic power management (DPM) functions resulting in an out of bounds read and loss of availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20516 | Improper handling of insufficiency privileges in the ASP could allow a privileged attacker to modify Translation Map Registers (TMRs) potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20516</link><description>Improper handling of insufficiency privileges in the ASP could allow a privileged attacker to modify Translation Map Registers (TMRs) potentially resulting in loss of confidentiality or integrity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46750 | Failure to validate the address and size in TEE (Trusted Execution Environment) may allow a malicious x86 attacker to send malformed message...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46750</link><description>Failure to validate the address and size in TEE (Trusted Execution Environment) may allow a malicious x86 attacker to send malformed messages to the graphics mailbox resulting in an overlap of a TMR (Trusted Memory Region) that was previously allocated by the ASP bootloader leading to a potential loss of integrity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-26377 | Insufficient parameter validation while allocating process space in the Trusted OS (TOS) may allow for a malicious userspace process to trig...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26377</link><description>Insufficient parameter validation while allocating process space in the Trusted OS (TOS) may allow for a malicious userspace process to trigger an integer overflow, leading to a potential denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 15:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10034 | D-Link DIR-825 httpd ping6_response.cg get_ping6_app_stat buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10034</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-825 1.08.01. This impacts the function get_ping6_app_stat of the file ping6_response.cg of the component httpd. Performing manipulation of the argument ping6_ipaddr results in buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 14:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10033 | itsourcecode Online Discussion Forum admin sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10033</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Online Discussion Forum 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin. Such manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 13:13:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10032 | Campcodes Grocery Sales and Inventory System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10032</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Campcodes Grocery Sales and Inventory System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument page results in cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 12:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10031 | Campcodes Grocery Sales and Inventory System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10031</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Campcodes Grocery Sales and Inventory System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_sales. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 12:17:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10030 | Campcodes Grocery Sales and Inventory System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10030</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Grocery Sales and Inventory System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ajax.php?action=save_receiving. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10029 | itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System complex_header_2.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10029</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /inventory/main/vendors/datatables/unit_testing/templates/complex_header_2.php. Performing manipulation of the argument scripts results in cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 08:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9961 | Authenticated RCE by CWMP binary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9961</link><description>An authenticated attacker may remotely execute arbitrary code via the CWMP binary on the devices AX10 and AX1500. 

The exploit can only be conducted via a Man-In-The-Middle (MITM) attack. 

This issue affects AX10 V1/V1.2/V2/V2.6/V3/V3.6: before 1.2.1; AX1500 V1/V1.20/V1.26/V1.60/V1.80/V2.60/V3.6: before 1.3.11.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 07:10:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10046 | ELEX WooCommerce Google Shopping (Google Product Feed) &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Inejction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10046</link><description>The ELEX WooCommerce Google Shopping (Google Product Feed) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'file_to_delete' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 06:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10028 | itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System 6776.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10028</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /inventory/main/vendors/datatables/unit_testing/templates/6776.php. Such manipulation of the argument scripts leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 06:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6757 | Recent Posts Widget Extended &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via rpwe Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6757</link><description>The Recent Posts Widget Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'rpwe' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 04:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7040 | Cloud SAML SSO &amp;lt;= 1.0.19 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Settings Modification via set_organization_settings Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7040</link><description>The Cloud SAML SSO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'set_organization_settings' action of the csso_handle_actions() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.19. The handler reads client-supplied POST parameters for organization settings and passes them directly to update_option() without any check of the user’s capabilities or a CSRF nonce. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change critical configuration (including toggling signing and encryption), potentially breaking the SSO flow and causing a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 03:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7045 | Cloud SAML SSO &amp;lt;= 1.0.19 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Identity Provider Deletion via delete_config Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7045</link><description>The Cloud SAML SSO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Identity Provider Deletion due to a missing capability check on the delete_config action of the csso_handle_actions() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.19. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete any configured IdP, breaking the SSO authentication flow and causing a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 03:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8149 | aThemes Addons for Elementor Lite &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8149</link><description>The aThemes Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Countdown widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 03:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8564 | SKT Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8564</link><description>The SKT Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 03:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8722 | Content Views &amp;lt;= 4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Grid and List Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8722</link><description>The Content Views plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Grid and List widgets in all versions up to, and including, 4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 03:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9126 | Smart Table Builder &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9126</link><description>The Smart Table Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 03:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9442 | StreamWeasels Kick Integration &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via vodsChannel Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9442</link><description>The StreamWeasels Kick Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘vodsChannel’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 03:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9493 | Admin Menu Editor &amp;lt;= 1.14 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via placeholder Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9493</link><description>The Admin Menu Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘placeholder’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 03:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58437 | Coder&amp;#x27;s privilege escalation vulnerability could lead to a cross workspace compromise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58437</link><description>Coder allows organizations to provision remote development environments via Terraform. In versions 2.22.0 through 2.24.3, 2.25.0  and 2.25.1, Coder can be compromised through insecure session handling in prebuilt workspaces. Coder automatically generates a session token for a user when a workspace is started. It is automatically exposed via coder_workspace_owner.session_token. Prebuilt workspaces are initially owned by a built-in prebuilds system user. When a prebuilt workspace is claimed, a new session token is generated for the user that claimed the workspace, but the previous session token for the prebuilds user was not expired. Any Coder workspace templates that persist this automatically generated session token are potentially impacted. This is fixed in versions 2.24.4 and 2.25.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10003 | UsersWP – Front-end login form, User Registration, User Profile &amp;amp; Members Directory plugin for WP &amp;lt;= 1.2.44 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10003</link><description>The UsersWP – Front-end login form, User Registration, User Profile &amp; Members Directory plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘upload_file_remove’ function and 'htmlvar' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.44 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 02:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58374 | Roo Code: Auto-approve allows npm install execution of malicious postinstall scripts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58374</link><description>Roo Code is an AI-powered autonomous coding agent that lives in users' editors. Versions 3.25.23 and below contain a default list of allowed commands that do not need manual approval if auto-approve is enabled, and npm install is included in that list. Because npm install executes lifecycle scripts, if a repository’s package.json file contains a malicious postinstall script, it would be executed automatically without user approval. This means that enabling auto-approved commands and opening a malicious repo could result in arbitrary code execution. This is fixed in version 3.26.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 02:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8359 | AdForest &amp;lt;= 6.0.9 - Authentication Bypass to Admin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8359</link><description>The AdForest theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.9. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a user's identity prior to authenticating them. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as other users, including administrators, without access to a password.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 02:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8360 | LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.5.5.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8360</link><description>The LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several of the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 02:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9085 | User Registration &amp;amp; Membership &amp;lt;= 4.3.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9085</link><description>The User Registration &amp; Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 's' parameter in version 4.3.0. This is due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 02:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9515 | Multi Step Form &amp;lt;= 1.7.25 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9515</link><description>The Multi Step Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation via the import functionality in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.25. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 02:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9853 | Optio Dentistry &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9853</link><description>The Optio Dentistry plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'optio-lightbox' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 02:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6067 | Easy Social Feed – Social Photos Gallery – Post Feed – Like Box &amp;lt;= 6.6.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6067</link><description>The Easy Social Feed – Social Photos Gallery – Post Feed – Like Box plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `data-caption` and `data-linktext` parameters in all versions up to, and including, 6.6.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 02:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7366 | Rehub &amp;lt;= 19.9.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via re_filterpost</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7366</link><description>The The REHub - Price Comparison, Multi Vendor Marketplace Wordpress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 19.9.7. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 02:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7368 | Rehub &amp;lt;= 19.9.7 - Unauthenticated Password Protected Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7368</link><description>The REHub - Price Comparison, Multi Vendor Marketplace Wordpress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 19.9.7 via the 'ajax_action_re_getfullcontent' function due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract data from password protected posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 02:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9849 | Html Social share buttons &amp;lt;= 2.1.16 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9849</link><description>The Html Social share buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'zm_sh_btn' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.16 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 02:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58439 | ERP: Possibility of SQL injection due to missing validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58439</link><description>ERP is a free and open source Enterprise Resource Planning tool. In versions below 14.89.2 and 15.0.0 through 15.75.1, lack of validation of parameters left certain endpoints vulnerable to error-based SQL Injection. Some information like version could be retrieved. This issue is fixed in versions 14.89.2 and 15.76.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>