<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:26:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-22795 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Forescout SecureConnector v.11.3.06.0063 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the Rechec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22795</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Forescout SecureConnector v.11.3.06.0063 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the Recheck Compliance Status component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23764 | Certain WithSecure products allow Local Privilege Escalation. This affects WithSecure Client Security 15 and later, WithSecure Server Securi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23764</link><description>Certain WithSecure products allow Local Privilege Escalation. This affects WithSecure Client Security 15 and later, WithSecure Server Security 15 and later, WithSecure Email and Server Security 15 and later, and WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection 17 and later.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24215 | An issue in the component /cgi-bin/GetJsonValue.cgi of Cellinx NVT Web Server 5.0.0.014 allows attackers to leak configuration information v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24215</link><description>An issue in the component /cgi-bin/GetJsonValue.cgi of Cellinx NVT Web Server 5.0.0.014 allows attackers to leak configuration information via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24213 | Supabase PostgreSQL v15.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /pg_meta/default/query.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24213</link><description>Supabase PostgreSQL v15.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /pg_meta/default/query.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24321 | An issue in Dlink DIR-816A2 v.1.10CNB05 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the wizardstep4_ssid_2 parameter in the sub_4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24321</link><description>An issue in Dlink DIR-816A2 v.1.10CNB05 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the wizardstep4_ssid_2 parameter in the sub_42DA54 function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:09:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50061 | PrestaShop Op'art Easy Redirect &gt;= 1.3.8 and &lt;= 1.3.12 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via Oparteasyredirect::hookActionDispatcher().</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50061</link><description>PrestaShop Op'art Easy Redirect &gt;= 1.3.8 and &lt;= 1.3.12 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via Oparteasyredirect::hookActionDispatcher().</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:09:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25190 | l8w8jwt 2.2.1 uses memcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25190</link><description>l8w8jwt 2.2.1 uses memcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing side channel.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25189 | libjwt 1.15.3 uses strcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25189</link><description>libjwt 1.15.3 uses strcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing side channel.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25191 | php-jwt 1.0.0 uses strcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25191</link><description>php-jwt 1.0.0 uses strcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing side channel.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42282 | An issue in NPM IP Package v.1.1.8 and before allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the isPublic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42282</link><description>An issue in NPM IP Package v.1.1.8 and before allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the isPublic() function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47020 | Multiple Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) chaining in NCR Terminal Handler v.1.5.1 allows privileges to be escalated by an attacker through...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47020</link><description>Multiple Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) chaining in NCR Terminal Handler v.1.5.1 allows privileges to be escalated by an attacker through a crafted request involving user account creation and adding the user to an administrator group. This is exploited by an undisclosed function in the WSDL that lacks security controls and can accept custom content types.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24834 | WordPress BEAR Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24834</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in realmag777 BEAR – Bulk Editor and Products Manager Professional for WooCommerce by Pluginus.Net allows Stored XSS.This issue affects BEAR – Bulk Editor and Products Manager Professional for WooCommerce by Pluginus.Net: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1150 | Improper validation of update packages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1150</link><description>Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature vulnerability in Snow Software Inventory Agent on Unix allows File Manipulation through Snow Update Packages.This issue affects Inventory Agent: through 7.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24836 | WordPress GDPR Data Request Form Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24836</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Audrasjb GDPR Data Request Form allows Stored XSS.This issue affects GDPR Data Request Form: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24871 | WordPress Blocksy Theme &amp;lt;= 2.0.19 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24871</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Creative Themes Blocksy allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Blocksy: from n/a through 2.0.19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7169 | Impersonate vendor signed Powershell scripts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7169</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in Snow Software Snow Inventory Agent on Windows allows Signature Spoof.This issue affects Snow Inventory Agent: through 6.14.5. Customers advised to upgrade to version 7.0</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0985 | PostgreSQL non-owner REFRESH MATERIALIZED VIEW CONCURRENTLY executes arbitrary SQL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0985</link><description>Late privilege drop in REFRESH MATERIALIZED VIEW CONCURRENTLY in PostgreSQL allows an object creator to execute arbitrary SQL functions as the command issuer. The command intends to run SQL functions as the owner of the materialized view, enabling safe refresh of untrusted materialized views. The victim is a superuser or member of one of the attacker's roles. The attack requires luring the victim into running REFRESH MATERIALIZED VIEW CONCURRENTLY on the attacker's materialized view. As part of exploiting this vulnerability, the attacker creates functions that use CREATE RULE to convert the internally-built temporary table to a view. Versions before PostgreSQL 15.6, 14.11, 13.14, and 12.18 are affected. The only known exploit does not work in PostgreSQL 16 and later. For defense in depth, PostgreSQL 16.2 adds the protections that older branches are using to fix their vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1149 | Improper validation of update packages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1149</link><description>Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature vulnerability in Snow Software Inventory Agent on MacOS, Snow Software Inventory Agent on Windows, Snow Software Inventory Agent on Linux allows File Manipulation through Snow Update Packages.This issue affects Inventory Agent: through 6.12.0; Inventory Agent: through 6.14.5; Inventory Agent: through 6.7.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24877 | WordPress Wonder Slider Lite Plugin &amp;lt;= 13.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24877</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Magic Hills Pty Ltd Wonder Slider Lite allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Wonder Slider Lite: from n/a through 13.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24878 | WordPress Portugal CTT Tracking for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24878</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PT Woo Plugins (by Webdados) Portugal CTT Tracking for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Portugal CTT Tracking for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1312 | Kernel: race condition leads to use after free during vma lock in lock_vma_under_rcu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1312</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the Linux kernel's Memory Management subsystem when a user wins two races at the same time with a fail in the mas_prev_slot function. This issue could allow a local user to crash the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 12:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24113 | xxl-job =&lt; 2.4.1 has a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability, which causes low-privileged users to control executor to RCE.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24113</link><description>xxl-job =&lt; 2.4.1 has a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability, which causes low-privileged users to control executor to RCE.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 12:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24879 | WordPress Link Library Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.5.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24879</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Yannick Lefebvre Link Library allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Link Library: from n/a through 7.5.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 12:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24880 | WordPress Apollo13 Framework Extensions Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24880</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apollo13Themes Apollo13 Framework Extensions allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Apollo13 Framework Extensions: from n/a through 1.9.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 12:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6519 | Seeing admin password hash value in Mia Technology&amp;#x27;s Mia-Med</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6519</link><description>Exposure of Data Element to Wrong Session vulnerability in Mia Technology Inc. MİA-MED allows Read Sensitive Strings Within an Executable.This issue affects MİA-MED: before 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6518 | Password Disclosure in Mia Technology&amp;#x27;s Mia-Med</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6518</link><description>Plaintext Storage of a Password vulnerability in Mia Technology Inc. MİA-MED allows Read Sensitive Strings Within an Executable.This issue affects MİA-MED: before 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6517 | Seeing the SMS Verification Code in Mia Technology&amp;#x27;s Mia-Med</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6517</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information Due to Incompatible Policies vulnerability in Mia Technology Inc. MİA-MED allows Collect Data as Provided by Users.This issue affects MİA-MED: before 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6564 | Improper Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6564</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE Premium and Ultimate affecting versions 16.4.3, 16.5.3, and 16.6.1. In projects using subgroups to define who can push and/or merge to protected branches, there may have been instances in which subgroup members with the Developer role were able to push or merge to protected branches.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24881 | WordPress WP SMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24881</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VeronaLabs WP SMS – Messaging &amp; SMS Notification for WordPress, WooCommerce, GravityForms, etc allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP SMS – Messaging &amp; SMS Notification for WordPress, WooCommerce, GravityForms, etc: from n/a through 6.5.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24885 | WordPress Woocommerce Vietnam Checkout Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24885</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Lê Văn Toản Woocommerce Vietnam Checkout allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Woocommerce Vietnam Checkout: from n/a through 2.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24886 | WordPress Product Labels For Woocommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24886</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Acowebs Product Labels For Woocommerce (Sale Badges) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Product Labels For Woocommerce (Sale Badges): from n/a through 1.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 10:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6515 | IDOR in Mia Technology&amp;#x27;s Mia-Med</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6515</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Mia Technology Inc. MİA-MED allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects MİA-MED: before 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 09:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22464 | Dell EMC AppSync, versions from 4.2.0.0 to 4.6.0.0 including all Service Pack releases, contain an exposure of sensitive information vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22464</link><description>Dell EMC AppSync, versions from 4.2.0.0 to 4.6.0.0 including all Service Pack releases, contain an exposure of sensitive information vulnerability in AppSync server logs. A high privileged remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of certain user credentials. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the vulnerable system with privileges of the compromised account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 09:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23452 | Apache bRPC: HTTP request smuggling vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23452</link><description>Request smuggling vulnerability in HTTP server in Apache bRPC 0.9.5~1.7.0 on all platforms allows attacker to smuggle request.

Vulnerability Cause Description：

The http_parser does not comply with the RFC-7230 HTTP 1.1 specification.

Attack scenario:
If a message is received with both a Transfer-Encoding and a Content-Length header field, such a message might indicate an attempt to perform request smuggling or response splitting.
One particular attack scenario is that a bRPC made http server on the backend receiving requests in one persistent connection from frontend server that uses TE to parse request with the logic that 'chunk' is contained in the TE field. in that case an attacker can smuggle a request into the connection to the backend server. 

Solution:
You can choose one solution from below:
1. Upgrade bRPC to version 1.8.0, which fixes this issue. Download link:  https://github.com/apache/brpc/releases/tag/1.8.0
 2. Apply this patch:  https://github.com/apache/brpc/pull/2518</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 09:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0965 | The Simple Page Access Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0965</link><description>The Simple Page Access Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.21 via the REST API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the plugin's page restriction and view page content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 08:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1207 | The WP Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'calendar_request_params[dates_ddmmyy_csv]' parameter in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1207</link><description>The WP Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'calendar_request_params[dates_ddmmyy_csv]' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 9.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 08:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24034 | Setor Informatica S.I.L version 3.0 is vulnerable to Open Redirect via the hprinter parameter, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24034</link><description>Setor Informatica S.I.L version 3.0 is vulnerable to Open Redirect via the hprinter parameter, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 08:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24091 | Yealink Meeting Server before v26.0.0.66 was discovered to contain an OS command injection vulnerability via the file upload interface.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24091</link><description>Yealink Meeting Server before v26.0.0.66 was discovered to contain an OS command injection vulnerability via the file upload interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:53:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0511 | The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0511</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.87. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the wpr_update_form_action_meta function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to post metadata via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24216 | Zentao v18.0 to v18.10 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the checkConnection method of /app/zentao/m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24216</link><description>Zentao v18.0 to v18.10 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the checkConnection method of /app/zentao/module/repo/model.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24202 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in /upgrade/control.php of ZenTao Community Edition v18.10, ZenTao Biz v8.10, and ZenTao Max v4.10 al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24202</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in /upgrade/control.php of ZenTao Community Edition v18.10, ZenTao Biz v8.10, and ZenTao Max v4.10 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted .txt file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 04:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25148 | In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 15, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25148</link><description>In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 15, and older unsupported versions the `doAsUserId` URL parameter may get leaked when creating linked content using the WYSIWYG editor and while impersonating a user. This may allow remote authenticated users to impersonate a user after accessing the linked content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:51:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25146 | Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 18, and o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25146</link><description>Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 18, and older unsupported versions returns with different responses depending on whether a site does not exist or if the user does not have permission to access the site, which allows remote attackers to discover the existence of sites by enumerating URLs. This vulnerability occurs if locale.prepend.friendly.url.style=2 and if a custom 404 page is used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5665 | The Payment Forms for Paystack plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5665</link><description>The Payment Forms for Paystack plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25144 | The IFrame widget in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.26, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 27, 7.3 before...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25144</link><description>The IFrame widget in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.26, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 27, 7.3 before update 6, 7.2 before fix pack 19, and older unsupported versions does not check the URL of the IFrame, which allows remote authenticated users to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) via a self referencing IFrame.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47798 | Account lockout in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.3.0, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.2 before fix pack 5, and older unsu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47798</link><description>Account lockout in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.3.0, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.2 before fix pack 5, and older unsupported versions does not invalidate existing user sessions, which allows remote authenticated users to remain authenticated after an account has been locked.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22394 | An improper authentication vulnerability has been identified in SonicWall SonicOS SSL-VPN feature, which in specific conditions could allow ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22394</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability has been identified in SonicWall SonicOS SSL-VPN feature, which in specific conditions could allow a remote attacker to bypass authentication. 

This issue affects only firmware version SonicOS 7.1.1-7040.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24003 | jshERP v3.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. The com.jsh.erp.controller.DepotHeadController: com.jsh.erp.utils.BaseResponseInfo findInOutMate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24003</link><description>jshERP v3.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. The com.jsh.erp.controller.DepotHeadController: com.jsh.erp.utils.BaseResponseInfo findInOutMaterialCount() function of jshERP does not filter `column` and `order` parameters well enough, and an attacker can construct malicious payload to bypass jshERP's protection mechanism in `safeSqlParse` method for sql injection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24014 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass crafted offset, limit, and sort param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24014</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /novel/author/list</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24017 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass crafted offset, limit, and sort param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24017</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /common/dict/list</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24021 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior. An attacker can pass specially crafted offset, limit, and sort para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24021</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior. An attacker can pass specially crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /novel/userFeedback/list.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48974 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Axigen WebMail v.10.5.7 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted scrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48974</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Axigen WebMail v.10.5.7 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script to the serverName_input parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24018 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass in crafted offset, limit, and sort pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24018</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass in crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /system/dataPerm/list</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24025 | An arbitrary File upload vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior at com.java2nb.common.controller.FileController: upload(). ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24025</link><description>An arbitrary File upload vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior at com.java2nb.common.controller.FileController: upload(). An attacker can pass in specially crafted filename parameter to perform arbitrary File download.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24350 | File Upload vulnerability in Software Publico e-Sic Livre v.2.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the extens...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24350</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in Software Publico e-Sic Livre v.2.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the extension filtering component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24023 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior. An attacker can pass specially crafted offset, limit, and sort para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24023</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior. An attacker can pass specially crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /novel/bookContent/list.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:02:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24024 | An arbitrary File download vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior at com.java2nb.common.controller.FileController: fileDown...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24024</link><description>An arbitrary File download vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior at com.java2nb.common.controller.FileController: fileDownload(). An attacker can pass in specially crafted filePath and fieName parameters to perform arbitrary File download.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:02:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24026 | An arbitrary File upload vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions at com.java2nb.system.controller.SysUserController...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24026</link><description>An arbitrary File upload vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions at com.java2nb.system.controller.SysUserController: uploadImg(). An attacker can pass in specially crafted filename parameter to perform arbitrary File download.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:02:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6736 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6736</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 11.3 before 16.6.7, all versions starting from 16.7 before 16.7.5, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a client-side denial of service using malicious crafted content in the CODEOWNERS file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6840 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6840</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.4 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows a maintainer to change the name of a protected branch that bypasses the security policy added to block MR.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1066 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1066</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 13.3.0 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows an attacker to do a resource exhaustion using GraphQL `vulnerabilitiesCountByDay`</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24806 | Improper Domain Lookup that potentially leads to SSRF attacks in libuv</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24806</link><description>libuv is a multi-platform support library with a focus on asynchronous I/O. The `uv_getaddrinfo` function in `src/unix/getaddrinfo.c` (and its windows counterpart `src/win/getaddrinfo.c`), truncates hostnames to 256 characters before calling `getaddrinfo`. This behavior can be exploited to create addresses like `0x00007f000001`, which are considered valid by `getaddrinfo` and could allow an attacker to craft payloads that resolve to unintended IP addresses, bypassing developer checks. The vulnerability arises due to how the `hostname_ascii` variable (with a length of 256 bytes) is handled in `uv_getaddrinfo` and subsequently in `uv__idna_toascii`. When the hostname exceeds 256 characters, it gets truncated without a terminating null byte. As a result attackers may be able to access internal APIs or for websites (similar to MySpace) that allows users to have `username.example.com` pages. Internal services that crawl or cache these user pages can be exposed to SSRF attacks if a malicious user chooses a long vulnerable username. This issue has been addressed in release version 1.48.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 21:53:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23448 | APM Server Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23448</link><description>An issue was discovered whereby APM Server could log at ERROR level, a response from Elasticsearch indicating that indexing the document failed and that response would contain parts of the original document. Depending on the nature of the document that the APM Server attempted to ingest, this could lead to the insertion of sensitive or private information in the APM Server logs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 21:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6356 | Kernel: null pointer dereference in nvmet_tcp_build_iovec</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6356</link><description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's NVMe driver. This issue may allow an unauthenticated malicious actor to send a set of crafted TCP packages when using NVMe over TCP, leading the NVMe driver to a NULL pointer dereference in the NVMe driver and causing kernel panic and a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 21:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6535 | Kernel: null pointer dereference in nvmet_tcp_execute_request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6535</link><description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's NVMe driver. This issue may allow an unauthenticated malicious actor to send a set of crafted TCP packages when using NVMe over TCP, leading the NVMe driver to a NULL pointer dereference in the NVMe driver, causing kernel panic and a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6536 | Kernel: null pointer dereference in __nvmet_req_complete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6536</link><description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's NVMe driver. This issue may allow an unauthenticated malicious actor to send a set of crafted TCP packages when using NVMe over TCP, leading the NVMe driver to a NULL pointer dereference in the NVMe driver, causing kernel panic and a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38995 | An issue in SCHUHFRIED v.8.22.00 allows remote attacker to obtain the database password via crafted curl command.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38995</link><description>An issue in SCHUHFRIED v.8.22.00 allows remote attacker to obtain the database password via crafted curl command.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 19:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24488 | An issue in Shenzen Tenda Technology CP3V2.0 V11.10.00.2311090948 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the password c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24488</link><description>An issue in Shenzen Tenda Technology CP3V2.0 V11.10.00.2311090948 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the password component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 19:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23769 | Improper privilege control for the named pipe in Samsung Magician PC Software 8.0.0 (for Windows) allows a local attacker to read privileged...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23769</link><description>Improper privilege control for the named pipe in Samsung Magician PC Software 8.0.0 (for Windows) allows a local attacker to read privileged data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 19:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24823 | graylog2-server Session Fixation vulnerability through cookie injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24823</link><description>Graylog is a free and open log management platform. Starting in version 4.3.0 and prior to versions 5.1.11 and 5.2.4, reauthenticating with an existing session cookie would re-use that session id, even if for different user credentials. In this case, the pre-existing session could be used to gain elevated access to an existing Graylog login session, provided the malicious user could successfully inject their session cookie into someone else's browser. The complexity of such an attack is high, because it requires presenting a spoofed login screen and injection of a session cookie into an existing browser, potentially through a cross-site scripting attack. No such attack has been discovered. Graylog 5.1.11 and 5.2.4, and any versions of the 6.0 development branch, contain patches to not re-use sessions under any circumstances. Some workarounds are available. Using short session expiration and explicit log outs of unused sessions can help limiting the attack vector. Unpatched this vulnerability exists, but is relatively hard to exploit. A proxy could be leveraged to clear the `authentication` cookie for the Graylog server URL for the `/api/system/sessions` endpoint, as that is the only one vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 17:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24824 | graylog2-server vulnerable to instantiation of arbitrary classes triggered by API request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24824</link><description>Graylog is a free and open log management platform. Starting in version 2.0.0 and prior to versions 5.1.11 and 5.2.4, arbitrary classes can be loaded and instantiated using a HTTP PUT request to the `/api/system/cluster_config/` endpoint. Graylog's cluster config system uses fully qualified class names as config keys. To validate the existence of the requested class before using them, Graylog loads the class using the class loader. If a user with the appropriate permissions performs the request, arbitrary classes with 1-arg String constructors can be instantiated. This will execute arbitrary code that is run during class instantiation. In the specific use case of `java.io.File`, the behavior of the internal web-server stack will lead to information exposure by including the entire file content in the response to the REST request. Versions 5.1.11 and 5.2.4 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 17:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24822 | Pimcore Admin Classic Bundle permissions are not getting checked when working with tags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24822</link><description>Pimcore's Admin Classic Bundle provides a backend user interface for Pimcore. Prior to version 1.3.3, an attacker can create, delete etc. tags without having the permission to do so. A fix is available in version 1.3.3. As a workaround, one may apply the patch manually.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 17:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24563 | Vyper array negative index vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24563</link><description>Vyper is a Pythonic Smart Contract Language for the Ethereum Virtual Machine. Arrays can be keyed by a signed integer, while they are defined for unsigned integers only. The typechecker doesn't throw when spotting the usage of an `int` as an index for an array. The typechecker allows the usage of signed integers to be used as indexes to arrays. The vulnerability is present in different forms in all versions, including `0.3.10`. For ints, the 2's complement representation is used. Because the array was declared very large, the bounds checking will pass Negative values will simply be represented as very large numbers. As of time of publication, a fixed version does not exist.

There are three potential vulnerability classes: unpredictable behavior, accessing inaccessible elements and denial of service. Class 1: If it is possible to index an array with a negative integer without reverting, this is most likely not anticipated by the developer and such accesses can cause unpredictable behavior for the contract. Class 2: If a contract has an invariant in the form `assert index &lt; x`, the developer will suppose that no elements on indexes `y | y &gt;= x` are accessible. However, by using negative indexes, this can be bypassed. Class 3: If the index is dependent on the state of the contract, this poses a risk of denial of service. If the state of the contract can be manipulated in such way that the index will be forced to be negative, the array access can always revert (because most likely the array won't be declared extremely large). However, all these the scenarios are highly unlikely. Most likely behavior is a revert on the bounds check.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 17:14:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24816 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in samples with enabled the preview feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24816</link><description>CKEditor4 is an open source what-you-see-is-what-you-get HTML editor. A cross-site scripting vulnerability vulnerability has been discovered in versions prior to 4.24.0-lts in samples that use the `preview` feature. All integrators that use these samples in the production code can be affected. The vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code by abusing the misconfigured preview feature. It affects all users using the CKEditor 4 at version &lt; 4.24.0-lts with affected samples used in a production environment. A fix is available in version 4.24.0-lts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 17:14:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24706 | WordPress WP-CFM Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24706</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Forum One WP-CFM wp-cfm.This issue affects WP-CFM: from n/a through 1.7.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:53:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47700 | IBM Storage Virtualize improper certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47700</link><description>IBM SAN Volume Controller, IBM Storwize, IBM FlashSystem and IBM Storage Virtualize 8.6 products could allow a remote attacker to spoof a trusted system that would not be correctly validated by the Storwize server.  This could lead to a user connecting to a malicious host, believing that it was a trusted system and deceived into accepting spoofed data.  IBM X-Force ID:  271016.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20290 | A vulnerability in the OLE2 file format parser of ClamAV could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20290</link><description>A vulnerability in the OLE2 file format parser of ClamAV could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an incorrect check for end-of-string values during scanning, which may result in a heap buffer over-read. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted file containing OLE2 content to be scanned by ClamAV on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ClamAV scanning process to terminate, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected software and consuming available system resources.&#13;
&#13; For a description of this vulnerability, see the ClamAV blog .</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23806 | HID Global Reader Configuration Cards Improper Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23806</link><description>Sensitive data can be extracted from HID iCLASS SE reader configuration cards. This could include credential and device administrator keys.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31002 | IBM Security Access Manager Container information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31002</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 temporarily stores sensitive information in files that could be accessed by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  254657.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32328 | IBM Security Verify Access information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32328</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 uses insecure protocols in some instances that could allow an attacker on the network to take control of the server.  IBM X-Force Id:  254957.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32330 | IBM Security Verify Access man in the middle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32330</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 uses insecure calls that could allow an attacker on the network to take control of the server.  IBM X-Force ID:  254977.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38369 | IBM Security Access Manager Container information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38369</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 does not require that docker images should have strong passwords by default, which makes it easier for attackers to compromise user accounts.  IBM X-Force ID:  261196.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43017 | IBM Security Verify Access man in the middle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43017</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 could allow a privileged user to install a configuration file that could allow remote access.  IBM X-Force ID:  266155.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20252 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an unauthenticated, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20252</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks that perform arbitrary actions on an affected device. &#13;
&#13; Note: "Cisco Expressway Series" refers to Cisco Expressway Control (Expressway-C) devices and Cisco Expressway Edge (Expressway-E) devices.&#13;
&#13; For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details ["#details"] section of this advisory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20254 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an unauthenticated, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20254</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks that perform arbitrary actions on an affected device. &#13;
&#13; Note: "Cisco Expressway Series" refers to Cisco Expressway Control (Expressway-C) devices and Cisco Expressway Edge (Expressway-E) devices.&#13;
&#13; For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details ["#details"] section of this advisory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20255 | A vulnerability in the SOAP API of Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server could allow an unauthenticated,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20255</link><description>A vulnerability in the SOAP API of Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the REST API to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected system to reload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22012 | In TBD of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22012</link><description>In TBD of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24815 | CKEditor4 Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability caused by incorrect CDATA detection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24815</link><description>CKEditor4 is an open source what-you-see-is-what-you-get HTML editor. A cross-site scripting vulnerability has been discovered in the core HTML parsing module in versions of CKEditor4 prior to 4.24.0-lts. It may affect all editor instances that enabled full-page editing mode or enabled CDATA elements in Advanced Content Filtering configuration (defaults to `script` and `style` elements). The vulnerability allows attackers to inject malformed HTML content bypassing Advanced Content Filtering mechanism, which could result in executing JavaScript code. An attacker could abuse faulty CDATA content detection and use it to prepare an intentional attack on the editor. A fix is available in version 4.24.0-lts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24812 | Frappe Authenticated Reflected Cross site scripting (XSS) in portal pages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24812</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework that uses Python and MariaDB on the server side and a tightly integrated client side library. Prior to versions 14.59.0 and 15.5.0, portal pages are susceptible to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) which can be used to inject malicious JS code if user clicks on a malicious link. This vulnerability has been patched in versions 14.59.0 and 15.5.0. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25145 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Portal Search module's Search Result app in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.11, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25145</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Portal Search module's Search Result app in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.11, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 8, 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML into the Search Result app's search result if highlighting is disabled by adding any searchable content (e.g., blog, message board message, web content article) to the application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24771 | Open Forms potential multi-factor authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24771</link><description>Open Forms allows users create and publish smart forms. Versions prior to 2.2.9, 2.3.7, 2.4.5, and 2.5.2 contain a non-exploitable multi-factor authentication weakness. Superusers who have their credentials (username + password) compromised could potentially have the second-factor authentication bypassed if an attacker somehow managed to authenticate to Open Forms. The maintainers of Open Forms do not believe it is or has been possible to perform this login. However, if this were possible, the victim's account may be abused to view (potentially sensitive) submission data or have been used to impersonate other staff accounts to view and/or modify data. Three mitigating factors to help prevent exploitation include: the usual login page (at `/admin/login/`) does not fully log in the user until the second factor was succesfully provided; the additional non-MFA protected login page at `/api/v2/api-authlogin/` was misconfigured and could not be used to log in; and there are no additional ways to log in. This also requires credentials of a superuser to be compromised to be exploitable. Versions 2.2.9, 2.3.7, 2.4.5, and 2.5.2 contain the following patches to address these weaknesses: Move and only enable the API auth endpoints (`/api/v2/api-auth/login/`) with `settings.DEBUG = True`. `settings.DEBUG = True` is insecure and should never be applied in production settings. Additionally, apply a custom permission check to the hijack flow to only allow second-factor-verified superusers to perform user hijacking.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 14:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24811 | Products.SQLAlchemyDA  vulnerable to unauthenticated arbitrary SQL query execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24811</link><description>SQLAlchemyDA is a generic database adapter for ZSQL methods. A vulnerability found in versions prior to 2.2 allows unauthenticated execution of arbitrary SQL statements on the database to which the SQLAlchemyDA instance is connected. All users are affected. The problem has been patched in version 2.2. There is no workaround for the problem.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 14:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25143 | The Document and Media widget In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.3.6, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25143</link><description>The Document and Media widget In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.3.6, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 13, and older unsupported versions, does not limit resource consumption when generating a preview image, which allows remote authenticated users to cause a denial of service (memory consumption) via crafted PNG images.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 14:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24130 | Mail2World v12 Business Control Center was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Usr parameter ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24130</link><description>Mail2World v12 Business Control Center was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Usr parameter at resellercenter/login.asp.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 14:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24131 | SuperWebMailer v9.31.0.01799 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulenrability via the component api.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24131</link><description>SuperWebMailer v9.31.0.01799 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulenrability via the component api.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 14:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24133 | Atmail v6.6.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the username parameter on the login page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24133</link><description>Atmail v6.6.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the username parameter on the login page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 14:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25200 | Espruino 2v20 (commit fcc9ba4) was discovered to contain a Stack Overflow via the jspeFactorFunctionCall at src/jsparse.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25200</link><description>Espruino 2v20 (commit fcc9ba4) was discovered to contain a Stack Overflow via the jspeFactorFunctionCall at src/jsparse.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 13:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25201 | Espruino 2v20 (commit fcc9ba4) was discovered to contain an Out-of-bounds Read via jsvStringIteratorPrintfCallback at src/jsvar.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25201</link><description>Espruino 2v20 (commit fcc9ba4) was discovered to contain an Out-of-bounds Read via jsvStringIteratorPrintfCallback at src/jsvar.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 13:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24186 | Jsish v3.5.0 (commit 42c694c) was discovered to contain a stack-overflow via the component IterGetKeysCallback at /jsish/src/jsiValue.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24186</link><description>Jsish v3.5.0 (commit 42c694c) was discovered to contain a stack-overflow via the component IterGetKeysCallback at /jsish/src/jsiValue.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 13:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24188 | Jsish v3.5.0 was discovered to contain a heap-buffer-overflow in ./src/jsiUtils.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24188</link><description>Jsish v3.5.0 was discovered to contain a heap-buffer-overflow in ./src/jsiUtils.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 13:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24189 | Jsish v3.5.0 (commit 42c694c) was discovered to contain a use-after-free via the SplitChar at ./src/jsiUtils.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24189</link><description>Jsish v3.5.0 (commit 42c694c) was discovered to contain a use-after-free via the SplitChar at ./src/jsiUtils.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 13:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39196 | Apache Ozone: Missing mutual TLS authentication in one of the service internal Ozone Storage Container Manager endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39196</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Apache Ozone.

The vulnerability allows an attacker to download metadata internal to the Storage Container Manager service without proper authentication.
The attacker is not allowed to do any modification within the Ozone Storage Container Manager service using this vulnerability.
The accessible metadata does not contain sensitive information that can be used to exploit the system later on, and the accessible data does not make it possible to gain access to actual user data within Ozone.
This issue affects Apache Ozone: 1.2.0 and subsequent releases up until 1.3.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.4.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 13:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1109 | The Podlove Podcast Publisher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the ini...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1109</link><description>The Podlove Podcast Publisher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the init_download() and init() functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.11. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export the plugin's tracking data and podcast information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 11:09:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1110 | The Podlove Podcast Publisher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1110</link><description>The Podlove Podcast Publisher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the init() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.11. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to import the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 11:09:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1118 | The Podlove Subscribe button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to UNION-based SQL Injection via the 'button' attribute of the podlove-subsc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1118</link><description>The Podlove Subscribe button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to UNION-based SQL Injection via the 'button' attribute of the podlove-subscribe-button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.10 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 11:09:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51437 | Apache Pulsar: Timing attack in SASL token signature verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51437</link><description>Observable timing discrepancy vulnerability in Apache Pulsar SASL Authentication Provider can allow an attacker to forge a SASL Role Token that will pass signature verification.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.11.3, 3.0.2, or 3.1.1 which fixes the issue. Users should also consider updating the configured secret in the `saslJaasServerRoleTokenSignerSecretPath` file.

Any component matching an above version running the SASL Authentication Provider is affected. That includes the Pulsar Broker, Proxy, Websocket Proxy, or Function Worker.

2.11 Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 2.11.3.
3.0 Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 3.0.2.
3.1 Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 3.1.1.
Any users running Pulsar 2.8, 2.9, 2.10, and earlier should upgrade to one of the above patched versions.

For additional details on this attack vector, please refer to  https://codahale.com/a-lesson-in-timing-attacks/ .</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24303 | SQL Injection vulnerability in HiPresta "Gift Wrapping Pro" (hiadvancedgiftwrapping) module for PrestaShop before version 1.4.1, allows remo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24303</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in HiPresta "Gift Wrapping Pro" (hiadvancedgiftwrapping) module for PrestaShop before version 1.4.1, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the HiAdvancedGiftWrappingGiftWrappingModuleFrontController::addGiftWrappingCartValue() method.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24311 | Path Traversal vulnerability in Linea Grafica "Multilingual and Multistore Sitemap Pro - SEO" (lgsitemaps) module for PrestaShop before vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24311</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in Linea Grafica "Multilingual and Multistore Sitemap Pro - SEO" (lgsitemaps) module for PrestaShop before version 1.6.6, a guest can download personal information without restriction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 08:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46914 | SQL Injection vulnerability in RM bookingcalendar module for PrestaShop versions 2.7.9 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46914</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in RM bookingcalendar module for PrestaShop versions 2.7.9 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information via ics_export.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 08:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24304 | In the module "Mailjet" (mailjet) from Mailjet for PrestaShop before versions 3.5.1, a guest can download technical information without rest...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24304</link><description>In the module "Mailjet" (mailjet) from Mailjet for PrestaShop before versions 3.5.1, a guest can download technical information without restriction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 08:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40355 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Axigen versions 10.3.3.0 before 10.3.3.59, 10.4.0 before 10.4.19, and 10.5.0 before 10.5.5, allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40355</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Axigen versions 10.3.3.0 before 10.3.3.59, 10.4.0 before 10.4.19, and 10.5.0 before 10.5.5, allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the logic for switching between the Standard and Ajax versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0977 | The Timeline Widget For Elementor (Elementor Timeline, Vertical &amp; Horizontal Timeline) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Si...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0977</link><description>The Timeline Widget For Elementor (Elementor Timeline, Vertical &amp; Horizontal Timeline) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via image URLs in the plugin's timeline widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page, changes the slideshow type, and then changes it back to an image.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1078 | The Quiz Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ays_quick_st...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1078</link><description>The Quiz Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ays_quick_start() and add_question_rows() functions in all versions up to, and including, 6.5.2.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to create arbitrary quizzes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1079 | The Quiz Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the ays_show_results()...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1079</link><description>The Quiz Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the ays_show_results() function in all versions up to, and including, 6.5.2.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to fetch arbitrary quiz results which can contain PII.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0628 | The WP RSS Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.23.5 via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0628</link><description>The WP RSS Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.23.5 via the RSS feed source in admin settings. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1037 | The All-In-One Security (AIOS) – Security and Firewall plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tab' pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1037</link><description>The All-In-One Security (AIOS) – Security and Firewall plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tab' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1055 | The PowerPack Addons for Elementor (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scriptin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1055</link><description>The PowerPack Addons for Elementor (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's buttons in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied URL values. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 06:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0256 | The Starbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Profile Display Name and Social Settings in all versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0256</link><description>The Starbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Profile Display Name and Social Settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 04:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23447 | Elastic Network Drive Connector Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23447</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Windows Network Drive Connector when using Document Level Security to assign permissions to a file, with explicit allow write and deny read. Although the document is not accessible to the user in Network Drive it is visible in search applications to the user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 03:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23446 | Kibana Broken Access Control issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23446</link><description>An issue was discovered by Elastic, whereby the Detection Engine Search API does not respect Document-level security (DLS) or Field-level security (FLS) when querying the .alerts-security.alerts-{space_id} indices. Users who are authorized to call this API may obtain unauthorized access to documents if their roles are configured with DLS or FLS against the aforementioned index.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 03:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6388 | Suite CRM v7.14.2 - SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6388</link><description>Suite CRM version 7.14.2 allows making arbitrary HTTP requests through

the vulnerable server. This is possible because the application is vulnerable

to SSRF.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 02:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0849 | Leanote 2.7.0 - Local File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0849</link><description>Leanote version 2.7.0 allows obtaining arbitrary local files. This is possible

because the application is vulnerable to LFR.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 02:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24810 | WiX is vulnerable to DLL redirection attacks that allow the attacker to escalate privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24810</link><description>WiX toolset lets developers create installers for Windows Installer, the Windows installation engine. The .be TEMP folder is vulnerable to DLL redirection attacks that allow the attacker to escalate privileges. This impacts any installer built with the WiX installer framework. This issue has been patched in version 4.0.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 02:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1269 | SourceCodester Product Management System supplier.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1269</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Product Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /supplier.php. The manipulation of the argument supplier_name/supplier_contact leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-253012.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 02:03:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1268 | CodeAstro Restaurant POS System update_product.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1268</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in CodeAstro Restaurant POS System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file update_product.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-253011.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 02:03:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1267 | CodeAstro Restaurant POS System create_account.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1267</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in CodeAstro Restaurant POS System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file create_account.php. The manipulation of the argument Full Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-253010 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 01:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22021 | Vulnerability CVE-2024-22021 allows a Veeam Recovery Orchestrator user with a low privileged role (Plan Author) to retrieve plans from a Sco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22021</link><description>Vulnerability CVE-2024-22021 allows a Veeam Recovery Orchestrator user with a low privileged role (Plan Author) to retrieve plans from a Scope other than the one they are assigned to.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 01:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22022 | Vulnerability CVE-2024-22022 allows a Veeam Recovery Orchestrator user that has been assigned a low-privileged role to access the NTLM hash ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22022</link><description>Vulnerability CVE-2024-22022 allows a Veeam Recovery Orchestrator user that has been assigned a low-privileged role to access the NTLM hash of the service account used by the Veeam Orchestrator Server Service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 01:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1266 | CodeAstro University Management System Student Registration Form st_reg.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1266</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in CodeAstro University Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /st_reg.php of the component Student Registration Form. The manipulation of the argument Address leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-253009 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 01:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24019 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass in crafted offset, limit, and sort pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24019</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass in crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /system/roleDataPerm/list</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1265 | CodeAstro University Management System Attendance Management att_add.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1265</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in CodeAstro University Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /att_add.php of the component Attendance Management. The manipulation of the argument Student Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-253008.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24001 | jshERP v3.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. via the com.jsh.erp.controller.DepotHeadController: com.jsh.erp.utils.BaseResponseInfo findalloc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24001</link><description>jshERP v3.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. via the com.jsh.erp.controller.DepotHeadController: com.jsh.erp.utils.BaseResponseInfo findallocationDetail() function of jshERP which allows an attacker to construct malicious payload to bypass jshERP's protection mechanism.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 23:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24002 | jshERP v3.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. The com.jsh.erp.controller.MaterialController: com.jsh.erp.utils.BaseResponseInfo getListWithSto...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24002</link><description>jshERP v3.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. The com.jsh.erp.controller.MaterialController: com.jsh.erp.utils.BaseResponseInfo getListWithStock() function of jshERP does not filter `column` and `order` parameters well enough, and an attacker can construct malicious payload to bypass jshERP's protection mechanism in `safeSqlParse` method for sql injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 23:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0971 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists where an authenticated, low-privileged remote attacker could potentially alter scan DB content.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0971</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists where an authenticated, low-privileged remote attacker could potentially alter scan DB content.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 23:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0955 | Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0955</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability exists where an authenticated, remote attacker with administrator privileges on the Nessus application could alter Nessus proxy settings, which could lead to the execution of remote arbitrary scripts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 23:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24004 | jshERP v3.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. The com.jsh.erp.controller.DepotHeadController: com.jsh.erp.utils.BaseResponseInfo findInOutDeta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24004</link><description>jshERP v3.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. The com.jsh.erp.controller.DepotHeadController: com.jsh.erp.utils.BaseResponseInfo findInOutDetail() function of jshERP does not filter `column` and `order` parameters well enough, and an attacker can construct malicious payload to bypass jshERP's protection mechanism in `safeSqlParse` method for sql injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 23:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1264 | Juanpao JPShop UploadsController.php actionUpdate unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1264</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Juanpao JPShop up to 1.5.02 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function actionUpdate of the file /api/controllers/common/UploadsController.php. The manipulation of the argument imgage leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-253003.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 23:35:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1283 | Heap buffer overflow in Skia in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.160 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1283</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in Skia in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.160 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 23:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1284 | Use after free in Mojo in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.160 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1284</link><description>Use after free in Mojo in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.160 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 23:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22388 | HID Global Encoders Improper Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22388</link><description>Certain configuration available in the communication channel for encoders could expose sensitive data when reader configuration cards are programmed. This data could include credential and device administration keys.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 23:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1263 | Juanpao JPShop API PosterController.php actionUpdate unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1263</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Juanpao JPShop up to 1.5.02. Affected is the function actionUpdate of the file /api/controllers/merchant/shop/PosterController.php of the component API. The manipulation of the argument pic_url leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-253002 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 23:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1262 | Juanpao JPShop API MaterialController.php actionUpdate unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1262</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Juanpao JPShop up to 1.5.02. This issue affects the function actionUpdate of the file /api/controllers/merchant/design/MaterialController.php of the component API. The manipulation of the argument pic_url leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-253001 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 22:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24255 | A Race Condition discovered in geofence.cpp and mission_feasibility_checker.cpp in PX4 Autopilot 1.14 and earlier allows attackers to send d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24255</link><description>A Race Condition discovered in geofence.cpp and mission_feasibility_checker.cpp in PX4 Autopilot 1.14 and earlier allows attackers to send drones on unintended missions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 22:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1261 | Juanpao JPShop API ComboController.php actionIndex unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1261</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Juanpao JPShop up to 1.5.02. This vulnerability affects the function actionIndex of the file /api/controllers/merchant/app/ComboController.php of the component API. The manipulation of the argument pic_url leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-253000.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 22:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24254 | PX4 Autopilot 1.14 and earlier, due to the lack of synchronization mechanism for loading geofence data, has a Race Condition vulnerability i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24254</link><description>PX4 Autopilot 1.14 and earlier, due to the lack of synchronization mechanism for loading geofence data, has a Race Condition vulnerability in the geofence.cpp and mission_feasibility_checker.cpp. This will result in the drone uploading overlapping geofences and mission routes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 22:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24680 | An issue was discovered in Django 3.2 before 3.2.24, 4.2 before 4.2.10, and Django 5.0 before 5.0.2. The intcomma template filter was subjec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24680</link><description>An issue was discovered in Django 3.2 before 3.2.24, 4.2 before 4.2.10, and Django 5.0 before 5.0.2. The intcomma template filter was subject to a potential denial-of-service attack when used with very long strings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 22:08:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40143 | Westermo Lynx </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40143</link><description>An attacker with access to the Westermo Lynx web application that has the vulnerable software could introduce arbitrary JavaScript by injecting a cross-site scripting payload into the "forward.0.domain" parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45735 | Westermo Lynx Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45735</link><description>A potential attacker with access to the Westermo Lynx device may be able to execute malicious code that could affect the correct functioning of the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22520 | An issue discovered in Dronetag Drone Scanner 1.5.2 allows attackers to impersonate other drones via transmission of crafted data packets.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22520</link><description>An issue discovered in Dronetag Drone Scanner 1.5.2 allows attackers to impersonate other drones via transmission of crafted data packets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45222 | Westermo Lynx Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45222</link><description>An attacker with access to the web application that has the vulnerable software could introduce arbitrary JavaScript by injecting a cross-site scripting payload into the "autorefresh" parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45213 |  Westermo Lynx Permissive Cross-domain Policy with Untrusted Domains</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45213</link><description>A potential attacker with access to the Westermo Lynx device would be able to execute malicious code that could affect the correct functioning of the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22519 | An issue discovered in OpenDroneID OSM 3.5.1 allows attackers to impersonate other drones via transmission of crafted data packets.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22519</link><description>An issue discovered in OpenDroneID OSM 3.5.1 allows attackers to impersonate other drones via transmission of crafted data packets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24577 | libgit2 is vulnerable to arbitrary code execution due to heap corruption in `git_index_add`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24577</link><description>libgit2 is a portable C implementation of the Git core methods provided as a linkable library with a solid API, allowing to build Git functionality into your application. Using well-crafted inputs to `git_index_add` can cause heap corruption that could be leveraged for arbitrary code execution. There is an issue in the `has_dir_name` function in `src/libgit2/index.c`, which frees an entry that should not be freed. The freed entry is later used and overwritten with potentially bad actor-controlled data leading to controlled heap corruption. Depending on the application that uses libgit2, this could lead to arbitrary code execution. This issue has been patched in version 1.6.5 and 1.7.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42765 | Westermo Lynx Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42765</link><description>An attacker with access to the vulnerable software could introduce arbitrary JavaScript by injecting a cross-site scripting payload into the "username" parameter in the SNMP configuration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1260 | Juanpao JPShop API ComboController.php actionIndex unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1260</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Juanpao JPShop up to 1.5.02. This affects the function actionIndex of the file /api/controllers/admin/app/ComboController.php of the component API. The manipulation of the argument pic_url leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252999.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40544 | Westermo Lynx Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40544</link><description>An attacker with access to the network where the affected devices are located could maliciously actions to obtain, via a sniffer, sensitive information exchanged via TCP communications.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:35:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24575 | libgit2 is vulnerable to a denial of service attack in `git_revparse_single` </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24575</link><description>libgit2 is a portable C implementation of the Git core methods provided as a linkable library with a solid API, allowing to build Git functionality into your application. Using well-crafted inputs to `git_revparse_single` can cause the function to enter an infinite loop, potentially causing a Denial of Service attack in the calling application. The revparse function in `src/libgit2/revparse.c` uses a loop to parse the user-provided spec string. There is an edge-case during parsing that allows a bad actor to force the loop conditions to access arbitrary memory. Potentially, this could also leak memory if the extracted rev spec is reflected back to the attacker. As such, libgit2 versions before 1.4.0 are not affected. Users should upgrade to version 1.6.5 or 1.7.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45227 | Westermo Lynx Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45227</link><description>An attacker with access to the web application with vulnerable software could introduce arbitrary JavaScript by injecting a cross-site scripting payload into the "dns.0.server" parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38579 | Westermo Lynx 206-F2G Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38579</link><description>The cross-site request forgery token in the request may be predictable or easily guessable allowing attackers to craft a malicious request, which could be triggered by a victim unknowingly. In a successful CSRF attack, the attacker could lead the victim user to carry out an action unintentionally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1259 | Juanpao JPShop API AppController.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1259</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Juanpao JPShop up to 1.5.02. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/controllers/admin/app/AppController.php of the component API. The manipulation of the argument app_pic_url leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252998 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22514 | An issue discovered in iSpyConnect.com Agent DVR 5.1.6.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary files by restoring a crafted backup file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22514</link><description>An issue discovered in iSpyConnect.com Agent DVR 5.1.6.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary files by restoring a crafted backup file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:13:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22515 | Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability in iSpyConnect.com Agent DVR 5.1.6.0 allows attackers to upload arbitrary files via the upload audio ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22515</link><description>Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability in iSpyConnect.com Agent DVR 5.1.6.0 allows attackers to upload arbitrary files via the upload audio component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 20:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1258 | Juanpao JPShop API params.php hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1258</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Juanpao JPShop up to 1.5.02. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file api/config/params.php of the component API. The manipulation of the argument JWT_KEY_ADMIN leads to use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252997 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 20:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1257 | Jspxcms find_text.do cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1257</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Jspxcms 10.2.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /ext/collect/find_text.do. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252996.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 20:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22241 | Aria Operations for Networks contains a cross site scripting vulnerability. A malicious actor with admin privileges can inject a malicious p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22241</link><description>Aria Operations for Networks contains a cross site scripting vulnerability. A malicious actor with admin privileges can inject a malicious payload into the login banner and takeover the user account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 19:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22239 | Aria Operations for Networks contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A console user with access to Aria Operations for Networks...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22239</link><description>Aria Operations for Networks contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A console user with access to Aria Operations for Networks may exploit this vulnerability to escalate privileges to gain regular shell access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 19:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22240 | Aria Operations for Networks contains a local file read vulnerability. A malicious actor with admin privileges may exploit this vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22240</link><description>Aria Operations for Networks contains a local file read vulnerability. A malicious actor with admin privileges may exploit this vulnerability leading to unauthorized access to sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 19:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22237 | Aria Operations for Networks contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A console user with access to Aria Operations for Networks...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22237</link><description>Aria Operations for Networks contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A console user with access to Aria Operations for Networks may exploit this vulnerability to escalate privileges to gain root access to the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 19:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22238 | Aria Operations for Networks contains a cross site scripting vulnerability. A malicious actor with admin privileges may be able to inject ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22238</link><description>Aria Operations for Networks contains a cross site scripting vulnerability. A malicious actor with admin privileges may be able to inject malicious code into user profile configurations due to improper input sanitization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 19:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1256 | Jspxcms filter_text.do cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1256</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Jspxcms 10.2.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ext/collect/filter_text.do. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252995.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 19:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1255 | sepidz SepidzDigitalMenu Waiters information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1255</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in sepidz SepidzDigitalMenu up to 7.1.0728.1 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Waiters. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252994 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 19:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1254 | Beijing Baichuo Smart S20 Management Platform sysmanageajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1254</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Beijing Baichuo Smart S20 Management Platform up to 20231120. This affects an unknown part of the file /sysmanage/sysmanageajax.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252993 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 18:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40545 | PingFederate OAuth client_secret_jwt Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40545</link><description>Authentication bypass when an OAuth2 Client is using client_secret_jwt as its authentication method on affected 11.3 versions via specially crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 17:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1048 | Grub2: grub2-set-bootflag can be abused by local (pseudo-)users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1048</link><description>A flaw was found in the grub2-set-bootflag utility of grub2. After the fix of CVE-2019-14865, grub2-set-bootflag will create a temporary file with the new grubenv content and rename it to the original grubenv file. If the program is killed before the rename operation, the temporary file will not be removed and may fill the filesystem when invoked multiple times, resulting in a filesystem out of free inodes or blocks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 17:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1253 | Beijing Baichuo Smart S40 Management Platform Import web.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1253</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Beijing Baichuo Smart S40 Management Platform up to 20240126. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /useratte/web.php of the component Import Handler. The manipulation of the argument file_upload leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252992. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 17:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1252 | Tongda OA 2017 delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1252</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /general/attendance/manage/ask_duty/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument ASK_DUTY_ID leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252991.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36498 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability exists in the PPTP client functionality of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigabit VPN Router 1.3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36498</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability exists in the PPTP client functionality of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigabit VPN Router 1.3.0 build 20230322 Rel.70591. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to arbitrary command injection. An attacker can make an authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability and gain access to an unrestricted shell.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42664 | A post authentication command injection vulnerability exists when setting up the PPTP global configuration of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigabit V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42664</link><description>A post authentication command injection vulnerability exists when setting up the PPTP global configuration of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigabit VPN Router 1.3.0 build 20230322 Rel.70591. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to arbitrary command injection. An attacker can make an authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43482 | A command execution vulnerability exists in the guest resource functionality of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigabit VPN Router 1.3.0 build 20230322...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43482</link><description>A command execution vulnerability exists in the guest resource functionality of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigabit VPN Router 1.3.0 build 20230322 Rel.70591. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to arbitrary command execution. An attacker can make an authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46683 | A  post authentication command injection vulnerability exists when configuring the wireguard VPN functionality of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46683</link><description>A  post authentication command injection vulnerability exists when configuring the wireguard VPN functionality of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigabit VPN Router 1.3.0 build 20230322 Rel.70591. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to arbitrary command injection . An attacker can make an authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47167 | A post authentication command injection vulnerability exists in the GRE policy functionality of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigabit VPN Router 1.3....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47167</link><description>A post authentication command injection vulnerability exists in the GRE policy functionality of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigabit VPN Router 1.3.0 build 20230322 Rel.70591. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to arbitrary command injection. An attacker can make an authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47209 | A post authentication command injection vulnerability exists in the ipsec policy functionality of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigabit VPN Router 1....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47209</link><description>A post authentication command injection vulnerability exists in the ipsec policy functionality of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigabit VPN Router 1.3.0 build 20230322 Rel.70591. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to arbitrary command injection. An attacker can make an authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47617 | A post authentication command injection vulnerability exists when configuring the web group member of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigabit VPN Route...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47617</link><description>A post authentication command injection vulnerability exists when configuring the web group member of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigabit VPN Router 1.3.0 build 20230322 Rel.70591. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to arbitrary command injection. An attacker can make an authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47618 | A post authentication command execution vulnerability exists in the web filtering functionality of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigabit VPN Router 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47618</link><description>A post authentication command execution vulnerability exists in the web filtering functionality of Tp-Link ER7206 Omada Gigabit VPN Router 1.3.0 build 20230322 Rel.70591. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to arbitrary command execution. An attacker can make an authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22331 | IBM UrbanCode Deploy information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22331</link><description>IBM UrbanCode Deploy (UCD) 7.0 through 7.0.5.19, 7.1 through 7.1.2.15, 7.2 through 7.2.3.8, 7.3 through 7.3.2.3, and IBM UrbanCode Deploy (UCD) - IBM DevOps Deploy 8.0.0.0 could disclose sensitive user information when installing the Windows agent.  IBM X-Force ID:  279971.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46183 | IBM PowerVM Hypervisor information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46183</link><description>IBM PowerVM Hypervisor FW950.00 through FW950.90, FW1020.00 through FW1020.40, and FW1030.00 through FW1030.30 could allow a system administrator to obtain sensitive partition information.  IBM X-Force ID:  269695.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:10:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24000 | jshERP v3.3 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload. The jshERP-boot/systemConfig/upload interface does not check the uploaded file type, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24000</link><description>jshERP v3.3 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload. The jshERP-boot/systemConfig/upload interface does not check the uploaded file type, and the biz parameter can be spliced into the upload path, resulting in arbitrary file uploads with controllable paths.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:10:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35188 | SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35188</link><description>SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability was found using a create statement in the SolarWinds Platform. This vulnerability requires user authentication to be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50395 | SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50395</link><description>SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability was found using an update statement in the SolarWinds Platform. This vulnerability requires user authentication to be exploited</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1251 | Tongda OA 2017 delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1251</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.10. Affected is an unknown function of the file /general/email/outbox/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument DELETE_STR leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252990 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23344 | Tuleap&amp;#x27;s content of artifacts might be readable by unauthorized users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23344</link><description>Tuleap is an Open Source Suite to improve management of software developments and collaboration. Some users might get access to restricted information when a process validates the permissions of multiple users (e.g. mail notifications). This issue has been patched in version 15.4.99.140 of Tuleap Community Edition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24013 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass crafted offset, limit, and sort param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24013</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /novel/pay/list</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 15:55:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24015 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass in crafted offset, limit, and sort pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24015</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass in crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL via /sys/user/exit</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 15:55:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24291 | An issue in the component /member/index/login of yzmcms v7.0 allows attackers to direct users to malicious sites via a crafted URL.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24291</link><description>An issue in the component /member/index/login of yzmcms v7.0 allows attackers to direct users to malicious sites via a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 15:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24593 | A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in all versions of the api and web server components of Allegro AI’s ClearML platform allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24593</link><description>A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in all versions of the api and web server components of Allegro AI’s ClearML platform allows a remote attacker to impersonate a user by sending API requests via maliciously crafted html. Exploitation of the vulnerability allows an attacker to compromise confidential workspaces and files, leak sensitive information, and target instances of the ClearML platform within closed off networks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 14:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24594 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in all versions of the web server component of Allegro AI’s ClearML platform allows a remote atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24594</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in all versions of the web server component of Allegro AI’s ClearML platform allows a remote attacker to execute a JavaScript payload when a user views the Debug Samples tab in the web UI.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 14:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24590 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in version 0.17.0 or newer of Allegro AI’s ClearML platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded art...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24590</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in version 0.17.0 or newer of Allegro AI’s ClearML platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded artifact to run arbitrary code on an end user’s system when interacted with.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 14:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24591 | A path traversal vulnerability in version 1.4.0 or newer of Allegro AI’s ClearML platform enables a maliciously uploaded dataset to write lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24591</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in version 1.4.0 or newer of Allegro AI’s ClearML platform enables a maliciously uploaded dataset to write local or remote files to an arbitrary location on an end user’s system when interacted with.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 14:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24592 | Lack of authentication in all versions of the fileserver component of Allegro AI’s ClearML platform allows a remote attacker to arbitrarily ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24592</link><description>Lack of authentication in all versions of the fileserver component of Allegro AI’s ClearML platform allows a remote attacker to arbitrarily access, create, modify and delete files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 14:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0911 | Indent: heap-based buffer overflow in set_buf_break()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0911</link><description>A flaw was found in Indent. This issue may allow a local user to use a specially-crafted file to trigger a heap-based buffer overflow, which can lead to an application crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 14:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0690 | Ansible-core: possible information leak in tasks that ignore ansible_no_log configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0690</link><description>An information disclosure flaw was found in ansible-core due to a failure to respect the ANSIBLE_NO_LOG configuration in some scenarios. It was discovered that information is still included in the output in certain tasks, such as loop items. Depending on the task, this issue may include sensitive information, such as decrypted secret values.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 12:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23673 | Apache Sling Servlets Resolver: Malicious code execution via path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23673</link><description>Malicious code execution via path traversal in Apache Software Foundation Apache Sling Servlets Resolver.This issue affects all version of Apache Sling Servlets Resolver before 2.11.0. However, whether a system is vulnerable to this attack depends on the exact configuration of the system.
If the system is vulnerable, a user with write access to the repository might be able to trick the Sling Servlet Resolver to load a previously uploaded script. 

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.11.0, which fixes this issue. It is recommended to upgrade, regardless of whether your system configuration currently allows this attack or not.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 10:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23917 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2023.11.3 authentication bypass leading to RCE was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23917</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2023.11.3 authentication bypass leading to RCE was possible</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24936 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2023.11.2 access control at the S3 Artifact Storage plugin endpoint was missed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24936</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2023.11.2 access control at the S3 Artifact Storage plugin endpoint was missed</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24937 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2023.11.2 stored XSS via agent distribution was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24937</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2023.11.2 stored XSS via agent distribution was possible</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24938 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2023.11.2 limited directory traversal was possible in the Kotlin DSL documentation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24938</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2023.11.2 limited directory traversal was possible in the Kotlin DSL documentation</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24939 | In JetBrains Rider before 2023.3.3 logging of environment variables containing secret values was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24939</link><description>In JetBrains Rider before 2023.3.3 logging of environment variables containing secret values was possible</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24940 | In JetBrains IntelliJ IDEA before 2023.3.3 path traversal was possible when unpacking archives</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24940</link><description>In JetBrains IntelliJ IDEA before 2023.3.3 path traversal was possible when unpacking archives</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24941 | In JetBrains IntelliJ IDEA before 2023.3.3 a plugin for JetBrains Space was able to send an authentication token to an inappropriate URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24941</link><description>In JetBrains IntelliJ IDEA before 2023.3.3 a plugin for JetBrains Space was able to send an authentication token to an inappropriate URL</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24942 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2023.11.3 path traversal allowed reading data within JAR archives</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24942</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2023.11.3 path traversal allowed reading data within JAR archives</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24943 | In JetBrains Toolbox App before 2.2 a DoS attack was possible via a malicious SVG image</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24943</link><description>In JetBrains Toolbox App before 2.2 a DoS attack was possible via a malicious SVG image</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4503 | Eap-galleon: custom provisioning creates unsecured http-invoker</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4503</link><description>An improper initialization vulnerability was found in Galleon. When using Galleon to provision custom EAP or EAP-XP servers, the servers are created unsecured. This issue could allow an attacker to access remote HTTP services available from the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 08:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0684 | Coreutils: heap overflow in split --line-bytes with very long lines</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0684</link><description>A flaw was found in the GNU coreutils "split" program. A heap overflow with user-controlled data of multiple hundred bytes in length could occur in the line_bytes_split() function, potentially leading to an application crash and denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 08:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25140 | A default installation of RustDesk 1.2.3 on Windows places a WDKTestCert certificate under Trusted Root Certification Authorities with Enhan...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25140</link><description>A default installation of RustDesk 1.2.3 on Windows places a WDKTestCert certificate under Trusted Root Certification Authorities with Enhanced Key Usage of Code Signing (1.3.6.1.5.5.7.3.3), valid from 2023 until 2033. This is potentially unwanted, e.g., because there is no public documentation of security measures for the private key, and arbitrary software could be signed if the private key were to be compromised. NOTE: the vendor's position is "we do not have EV cert, so we use test cert as a workaround." Insertion into Trusted Root Certification Authorities was the originally intended behavior, and the UI ensured that the certificate installation step (checked by default) was visible to the user before proceeding with the product installation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 08:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32479 | Dell Encryption, Dell Endpoint Security Suite Enterprise, and Dell Security Management Server versions prior to 11.9.0 contain privilege esc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32479</link><description>Dell Encryption, Dell Endpoint Security Suite Enterprise, and Dell Security Management Server versions prior to 11.9.0 contain privilege escalation vulnerability due to improper ACL of the non-default installation directory. A local malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability by replacing binaries in installed directory and taking reverse shell of the system leading to Privilege Escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 08:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32454 | DUP framework version 4.9.4.36 and prior contains insecure operation on Windows junction/Mount point vulnerability. A local malicious standa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32454</link><description>DUP framework version 4.9.4.36 and prior contains insecure operation on Windows junction/Mount point vulnerability. A local malicious standard user could exploit the vulnerability to create arbitrary files, leading to denial of service</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 08:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32474 | Dell Display Manager application, version 2.1.1.17 and prior, contain an insecure operation on windows junction/mount point. A local malicio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32474</link><description>Dell Display Manager application, version 2.1.1.17 and prior, contain an insecure operation on windows junction/mount point. A local malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability during installation leading to arbitrary folder or file deletion</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 08:00:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32451 | Dell Display Manager application, version 2.1.1.17, contains a vulnerability that low privilege user can execute malicious code during insta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32451</link><description>Dell Display Manager application, version 2.1.1.17, contains a vulnerability that low privilege user can execute malicious code during installation and uninstallation</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 07:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28063 | Dell BIOS contains a Signed to Unsigned Conversion Error vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with admin privileges could pot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28063</link><description>Dell BIOS contains a Signed to Unsigned Conversion Error vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with admin privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 07:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22365 | linux-pam (aka Linux PAM) before 1.6.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (blocked login process) via mkfifo because the openat c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22365</link><description>linux-pam (aka Linux PAM) before 1.6.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (blocked login process) via mkfifo because the openat call (for protect_dir) lacks O_DIRECTORY.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 07:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52239 | The XML parser in Magic xpi Integration Platform 4.13.4 allows XXE attacks, e.g., via onItemImport.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52239</link><description>The XML parser in Magic xpi Integration Platform 4.13.4 allows XXE attacks, e.g., via onItemImport.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 07:18:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28049 | Dell Command | Monitor, versions prior to 10.9, contain an arbitrary folder deletion vulnerability. A locally authenticated malicious user m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28049</link><description>Dell Command | Monitor, versions prior to 10.9, contain an arbitrary folder deletion vulnerability. A locally authenticated malicious user may exploit this vulnerability in order to perform a privileged arbitrary file delete.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 06:48:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25543 | Dell Power Manager, versions prior to 3.14, contain an Improper Authorization vulnerability in DPM service. A low privileged malicious user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25543</link><description>Dell Power Manager, versions prior to 3.14, contain an Improper Authorization vulnerability in DPM service. A low privileged malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability in order to elevate privileges on the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 06:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33046 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in Trusted Execution Environment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33046</link><description>Memory corruption in Trusted Execution Environment while deinitializing an object used for license validation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33049 | Improper Release of Memory Before Removing Last Reference in Multi-Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33049</link><description>Transient DOS in Multi-Mode Call Processor due to UE failure because of heap leakage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33057 | Improper Input Validation in Multi-Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33057</link><description>Transient DOS in Multi-Mode Call Processor while processing UE policy container.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33058 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Modem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33058</link><description>Information disclosure in Modem while processing SIB5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33060 | Buffer Over-read in Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33060</link><description>Transient DOS in Core when DDR memory check is called while DDR is not initialized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33064 | Buffer Over-read in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33064</link><description>Transient DOS in Audio when invoking callback function of ASM driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33065 | Buffer Over-read in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33065</link><description>Information disclosure in Audio while accessing AVCS services from ADSP payload.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33067 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33067</link><description>Memory corruption in Audio while calling START command on host voice PCM multiple times for the same RX or TX tap points.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33068 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33068</link><description>Memory corruption in Audio while processing IIR config data from AFE calibration block.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33069 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33069</link><description>Memory corruption in Audio while processing the calibration data returned from ACDB loader.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33072 | Buffer copy without checking size of Input in Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33072</link><description>Memory corruption in Core while processing control functions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33076 | Configuration Issue in Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33076</link><description>Memory corruption in Core when updating rollback version for TA and OTA feature is enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33077 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33077</link><description>Memory corruption in HLOS while converting from authorization token to HIDL vector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43513 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in PCIe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43513</link><description>Memory corruption while processing the event ring, the context read pointer is untrusted to HLOS and when it is passed with arbitrary values, may point to address in the middle of ring element.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43516 | Use of out-of-range pointer offset in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43516</link><description>Memory corruption when malformed message payload is received from firmware.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43517 | Improper Access Control in Automotive Multimedia</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43517</link><description>Memory corruption in Automotive Multimedia due to improper access control in HAB.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43518 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43518</link><description>Memory corruption in video while parsing invalid mp2 clip.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43519 | Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43519</link><description>Memory corruption in video while parsing the Videoinfo, when the size of atom is greater than the videoinfo size.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43520 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow in WLAN HOST</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43520</link><description>Memory corruption when AP includes TID to link mapping IE in the beacons and STA is parsing the beacon TID to link mapping IE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43522 | NULL Pointer Dereference in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43522</link><description>Transient DOS while key unwrapping process, when the given encrypted key is empty or NULL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43523 | Reachable Assertion in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43523</link><description>Transient DOS while processing 11AZ RTT management action frame received through OTA.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43532 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in Display</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43532</link><description>Memory corruption while reading ACPI config through the user mode app.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43533 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43533</link><description>Transient DOS in WLAN Firmware when the length of received beacon is less than length of ieee802.11 beacon frame.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43534 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in WLAN HOST</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43534</link><description>Memory corruption while validating the TID to Link Mapping action request frame, when a station connects to an access point.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43535 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Display</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43535</link><description>Memory corruption when negative display IDs are sent as input while processing DISPLAYESCAPE event trigger.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43536 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43536</link><description>Transient DOS while parse fils IE with length equal to 1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 05:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23304 | Cybozu KUNAI for Android 3.0.20 to 3.0.21 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition by performin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23304</link><description>Cybozu KUNAI for Android 3.0.20 to 3.0.21 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition by performing certain operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 04:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24808 | pyLoad open redirect vulnerability due to improper validation of the is_safe_url function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24808</link><description>pyLoad is an open-source Download Manager written in pure Python. There is an open redirect vulnerability due to incorrect validation of input values when redirecting users after login. pyLoad is validating URLs via the `get_redirect_url` function when redirecting users at login. This vulnerability has been patched with commit fe94451.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 03:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20810 | Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in Smart Suggestions prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows attackers to get sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20810</link><description>Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in Smart Suggestions prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows attackers to get sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20811 | Improper caller verification in GameOptimizer prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to configure GameOptimizer.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20811</link><description>Improper caller verification in GameOptimizer prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to configure GameOptimizer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20812 | Out-of-bounds Write in padmd_vld_htbl of libpadm.so prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20812</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write in padmd_vld_htbl of libpadm.so prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:30:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20813 | Out-of-bounds Write in padmd_vld_qtbl of libpadm.so prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20813</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write in padmd_vld_qtbl of libpadm.so prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:30:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20814 | Out-of-bounds Read in padmd_vld_ac_prog_refine of libpadm.so prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows attacker access unauthorized information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20814</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read in padmd_vld_ac_prog_refine of libpadm.so prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows attacker access unauthorized information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:30:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20815 | Improper authentication vulnerability in onCharacteristicReadRequest in Auto Hotspot prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows adjacent attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20815</link><description>Improper authentication vulnerability in onCharacteristicReadRequest in Auto Hotspot prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows adjacent attackers connect to victim&amp;#39;s mobile hotspot without user awareness.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:30:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20816 | Improper authentication vulnerability in onCharacteristicWriteRequest in Auto Hotspot prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows adjacent attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20816</link><description>Improper authentication vulnerability in onCharacteristicWriteRequest in Auto Hotspot prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows adjacent attackers connect to victim&amp;#39;s mobile hotspot without user awareness.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:30:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20817 | Out out bounds Write vulnerabilities in svc1td_vld_slh of libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to trigger buf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20817</link><description>Out out bounds Write vulnerabilities in svc1td_vld_slh of libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to trigger buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:30:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20818 | Out out bounds Write vulnerabilities in svc1td_vld_elh of libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to trigger buf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20818</link><description>Out out bounds Write vulnerabilities in svc1td_vld_elh of libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to trigger buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:30:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20819 | Out out bounds Write vulnerabilities in svc1td_vld_plh_ap of libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to trigger ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20819</link><description>Out out bounds Write vulnerabilities in svc1td_vld_plh_ap of libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to trigger buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:30:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20820 | Improper input validation in bootloader prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows attacker to cause an Out-Of-Bounds read.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20820</link><description>Improper input validation in bootloader prior to SMR Feb-2024 Release 1 allows attacker to cause an Out-Of-Bounds read.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:30:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20822 | Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in AccountActivity of Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.63.6 allows local attackers to access sensit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20822</link><description>Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in AccountActivity of Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.63.6 allows local attackers to access sensitive information via implicit intent.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20823 | Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in SamsungAccount of Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.63.6 allows local attackers to access sensiti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20823</link><description>Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in SamsungAccount of Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.63.6 allows local attackers to access sensitive information via implicit intent.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20824 | Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in VoiceSearch of Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.63.6 allows local attackers to access sensitive ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20824</link><description>Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in VoiceSearch of Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.63.6 allows local attackers to access sensitive information via implicit intent.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20825 | Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in IAP of Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.63.6 allows local attackers to access sensitive informat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20825</link><description>Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in IAP of Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.63.6 allows local attackers to access sensitive information via implicit intent.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20826 | Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in UPHelper library prior to version 4.0.0 allows local attackers to access sensitive information vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20826</link><description>Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in UPHelper library prior to version 4.0.0 allows local attackers to access sensitive information via implicit intent.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20827 | Improper access control vulnerability in Samsung Gallery prior to version 14.5.04.4 allows physical attackers to access the picture using ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20827</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in Samsung Gallery prior to version 14.5.04.4 allows physical attackers to access the picture using physical keyboard on the lockscreen.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20828 | Improper authorization verification vulnerability in Samsung Internet prior to version 24.0 allows physical attackers to access files downlo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20828</link><description>Improper authorization verification vulnerability in Samsung Internet prior to version 24.0 allows physical attackers to access files downloaded in SecretMode without proper authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22852 | D-Link Go-RT-AC750 GORTAC750_A1_FW_v101b03 contains a stack-based buffer overflow via the function genacgi_main. This vulnerability allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22852</link><description>D-Link Go-RT-AC750 GORTAC750_A1_FW_v101b03 contains a stack-based buffer overflow via the function genacgi_main. This vulnerability allows attackers to enable telnet service via a specially crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:03:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22853 | D-LINK Go-RT-AC750 GORTAC750_A1_FW_v101b03 has a hardcoded password for the Alphanetworks account, which allows remote attackers to obtain r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22853</link><description>D-LINK Go-RT-AC750 GORTAC750_A1_FW_v101b03 has a hardcoded password for the Alphanetworks account, which allows remote attackers to obtain root access via a telnet session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:03:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46359 | An OS command injection vulnerability in Hardy Barth cPH2 eCharge Ladestation v1.87.0 and earlier, may allow an unauthenticated remote attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46359</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability in Hardy Barth cPH2 eCharge Ladestation v1.87.0 and earlier, may allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the system via a specifically crafted arguments passed to the connectivity check feature.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 01:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46360 | Hardy Barth cPH2 eCharge Ladestation v1.87.0 and earlier is vulnerable to Execution with Unnecessary Privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46360</link><description>Hardy Barth cPH2 eCharge Ladestation v1.87.0 and earlier is vulnerable to Execution with Unnecessary Privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 01:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47022 | An issue in NCR Terminal Handler v.1.5.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the payload parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47022</link><description>An issue in NCR Terminal Handler v.1.5.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the payload parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 01:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24112 | xmall v1.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the orderDir parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24112</link><description>xmall v1.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the orderDir parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 01:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47353 | An issue in the com.oneed.dvr.service.DownloadFirmwareService component of IMOU GO v1.0.11 allows attackers to force the download of arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47353</link><description>An issue in the com.oneed.dvr.service.DownloadFirmwareService component of IMOU GO v1.0.11 allows attackers to force the download of arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47889 | The Android application BINHDRM26 com.bdrm.superreboot 1.0.3, exposes several critical actions through its exported broadcast receivers. The...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47889</link><description>The Android application BINHDRM26 com.bdrm.superreboot 1.0.3, exposes several critical actions through its exported broadcast receivers. These exposed actions can allow any app on the device to send unauthorized broadcasts, leading to unintended consequences. The vulnerability is particularly concerning because these actions include powering off, system reboot &amp; entering recovery mode.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6229 | Buffer overflow in CPCA PDL Resource Download process of Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6229</link><description>Buffer overflow in CPCA PDL Resource Download process of Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code.*: Satera LBP670C Series/Satera MF750C Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in Japan. Color imageCLASS LBP674C/Color imageCLASS X LBP1333C/Color imageCLASS MF750C Series/Color imageCLASS X MF1333C Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in US. i-SENSYS LBP673Cdw/C1333P/i-SENSYS MF750C Series/C1333i Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6230 | Buffer overflow in the Address Book password process in authentication of Mobile Device Function of Office Multifunction Printers and Laser ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6230</link><description>Buffer overflow in the Address Book password process in authentication of Mobile Device Function of Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code.*: Satera LBP670C Series/Satera MF750C Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in Japan. Color imageCLASS LBP674C/Color imageCLASS X LBP1333C/Color imageCLASS MF750C Series/Color imageCLASS X MF1333C Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in US. i-SENSYS LBP673Cdw/C1333P/i-SENSYS MF750C Series/C1333i Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6231 | Buffer overflow in WSD probe request process of Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the netwo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6231</link><description>Buffer overflow in WSD probe request process of Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code.*: Satera LBP670C Series/Satera MF750C Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in Japan. Color imageCLASS LBP674C/Color imageCLASS X LBP1333C/Color imageCLASS MF750C Series/Color imageCLASS X MF1333C Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in US. i-SENSYS LBP673Cdw/C1333P/i-SENSYS MF750C Series/C1333i Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6232 | Buffer overflow in the Address Book username process in authentication of Mobile Device Function of Office Multifunction Printers and Laser ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6232</link><description>Buffer overflow in the Address Book username process in authentication of Mobile Device Function of Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code.*: Satera LBP670C Series/Satera MF750C Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in Japan. Color imageCLASS LBP674C/Color imageCLASS X LBP1333C/Color imageCLASS MF750C Series/Color imageCLASS X MF1333C Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in US. i-SENSYS LBP673Cdw/C1333P/i-SENSYS MF750C Series/C1333i Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6233 | Buffer overflow in SLP attribute request process of Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6233</link><description>Buffer overflow in SLP attribute request process of Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code.*: Satera LBP670C Series/Satera MF750C Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in Japan. Color imageCLASS LBP674C/Color imageCLASS X LBP1333C/Color imageCLASS MF750C Series/Color imageCLASS X MF1333C Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in US. i-SENSYS LBP673Cdw/C1333P/i-SENSYS MF750C Series/C1333i Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6234 | Buffer overflow in CPCA Color LUT Resource Download process of Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6234</link><description>Buffer overflow in CPCA Color LUT Resource Download process of Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code.*: Satera LBP670C Series/Satera MF750C Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in Japan. Color imageCLASS LBP674C/Color imageCLASS X LBP1333C/Color imageCLASS MF750C Series/Color imageCLASS X MF1333C Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in US. i-SENSYS LBP673Cdw/C1333P/i-SENSYS MF750C Series/C1333i Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0244 | Buffer overflow in CPCA PCFAX number process of Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the netwo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0244</link><description>Buffer overflow in CPCA PCFAX number process of Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code.*:Satera MF750C Series firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in Japan. Color imageCLASS MF750C Series/Color imageCLASS X MF1333C firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in US. i-SENSYS MF754Cdw/C1333iF firmware v03.07 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22773 | Intelbras Roteador ACtion RF 1200 1.2.2 esposes the Password in Cookie resulting in Login Bypass.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22773</link><description>Intelbras Roteador ACtion RF 1200 1.2.2 esposes the Password in Cookie resulting in Login Bypass.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47354 | An issue in the PowerOffWidgetReceiver function of Super Reboot (Root) Recovery v1.0.3 allows attackers to arbitrarily reset or power off th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47354</link><description>An issue in the PowerOffWidgetReceiver function of Super Reboot (Root) Recovery v1.0.3 allows attackers to arbitrarily reset or power off the device via a crafted intent</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24398 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in Stimulsoft GmbH Stimulsoft Dashboard.JS before v.2024.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24398</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in Stimulsoft GmbH Stimulsoft Dashboard.JS before v.2024.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the fileName parameter of the Save function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>