<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 19:00:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-55585 | moPS App Engine 1.8.618 has incorrect access control.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55585</link><description>moPS App Engine 1.8.618 has incorrect access control.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 19:00:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5840 | SourceCodester Client Database Management System user_update_customer_order.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5840</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Client Database Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /user_update_customer_order.php. The manipulation of the argument uploaded_file leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 18:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5839 | Tenda AC9 POST Request AdvSetLanip fromadvsetlanip buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5839</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda AC9 15.03.02.13. Affected by this issue is the function fromadvsetlanip of the file /goform/AdvSetLanip of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument lanMask leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 17:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5838 | PHPGurukul Employee Record Management System adminprofile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5838</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Employee Record Management System 1.3. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/adminprofile.php. The manipulation of the argument AdminName leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 16:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5837 | PHPGurukul Employee Record Management System allemployees.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5837</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Employee Record Management System 1.3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/allemployees.php. The manipulation of the argument delid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 14:15:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49619 | Skyvern through 0.1.85 has a Jinja runtime leak in sdk/workflow/models/block.py.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49619</link><description>Skyvern through 0.1.85 has a Jinja runtime leak in sdk/workflow/models/block.py.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 13:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5836 | Tenda AC9 POST Request SetIPTVCfg formSetIptv command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5836</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC9 15.03.02.13. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function formSetIptv of the file /goform/SetIPTVCfg of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument list leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 13:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9993 | Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp;amp; WooCommerce Builders &amp;lt;= 6.1.12 - Authenticated(Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Event Calendar Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9993</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Addon, Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the eael_event_details_text parameter of Event Calendar Widget in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 11:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9994 | Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp;amp; WooCommerce Builders &amp;lt;= 6.1.12 - Authenticated(Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Pricing Table Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9994</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Addon, Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the eael_pricing_item_tooltip_content parameter of the Pricing Table Widget in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 11:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5528 | Social Sharing Plugin – Sassy Social Share &amp;lt;= 3.3.75 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;heateor_mastodon_share&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5528</link><description>The Social Sharing Plugin – Sassy Social Share plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the heateor_mastodon_share parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.75 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action, such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 11:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5568 | WpEvently &amp;lt;= 4.4.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5568</link><description>The WpEvently plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple parameters in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 11:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5303 | LTL Freight Quotes – Freightview Edition &amp;lt;= 1.0.11, LTL Freight Quotes – Daylight Edition &amp;lt;=2.2.6 and LTL Freight Quotes – Day &amp;amp; Ross Edition &amp;lt;= 2.1.10 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via `expiry_date` Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5303</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – Freightview Edition, LTL Freight Quotes – Daylight Edition and LTL Freight Quotes – Day &amp; Ross Edition plugins for WordPress are vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the expiry_date parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.11, 2.2.6 and 2.1.10 respectively, due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 08:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5399 | WebSocket endless loop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5399</link><description>Due to a mistake in libcurl's WebSocket code, a malicious server can send a
particularly crafted packet which makes libcurl get trapped in an endless
busy-loop.

There is no other way for the application to escape or exit this loop other
than killing the thread/process.

This might be used to DoS libcurl-using application.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 07:57:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47601 | WordPress MaxiBlocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Arbitrary Option Update to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47601</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Christiaan Pieterse MaxiBlocks allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects MaxiBlocks: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 04:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5814 | Profiler – What Slowing Down Your WP &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Missing Authentication to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Plugin Reactivation via State Restoration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5814</link><description>The Profiler – What Slowing Down Your WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the wpsd_plugin_control() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reactivate previously deactivated plugins after accessing the "Profiler" page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 04:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49128 | Jackson-core Vulnerable to Memory Disclosure via Source Snippet in JsonLocation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49128</link><description>Jackson-core contains core low-level incremental ("streaming") parser and generator abstractions used by Jackson Data Processor. Starting in version 2.0.0 and prior to version 2.13.0, a flaw in jackson-core's `JsonLocation._appendSourceDesc` method allows up to 500 bytes of unintended memory content to be included in exception messages. When parsing JSON from a byte array with an offset and length, the exception message incorrectly reads from the beginning of the array instead of the logical payload start. This results in possible information disclosure in systems using pooled or reused buffers, like Netty or Vert.x. This issue was silently fixed in jackson-core version 2.13.0, released on September 30, 2021, via PR #652. All users should upgrade to version 2.13.0 or later. If upgrading is not immediately possible, applications can mitigate the issue by disabling exception message exposure to clients to avoid returning parsing exception messages in HTTP responses and/or disabling source inclusion in exceptions to prevent Jackson from embedding any source content in exception messages, avoiding leakage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 21:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49127 | Kafbat UI vulnerable to Remote Code Execution by JMX in Metrices Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49127</link><description>Kafbat UI is a web user interface for managing Apache Kafka clusters. An unsafe deserialization vulnerability in version 1.0.0 allows any unauthenticated user to execute arbitrary code on the server. Version 1.1.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 20:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5798 | Tenda AC8 SetSysTimeCfg fromSetSysTime stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5798</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.09. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function fromSetSysTime of the file /goform/SetSysTimeCfg. The manipulation of the argument timeType leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5799 | Tenda AC8 WifiExtraSet fromSetWirelessRepeat stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5799</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.09. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function fromSetWirelessRepeat of the file /goform/WifiExtraSet. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5796 | code-projects Laundry System edit_type.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5796</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Laundry System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /data/edit_type.php. The manipulation of the argument Type leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5797 | Laundry Laundry System insert_type.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5797</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Laundry Laundry System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /data/insert_type.php. The manipulation of the argument Type leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2766 | 70mai A510 Use of Default Password Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2766</link><description>70mai A510 Use of Default Password Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of 70mai A510. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the default configuration of user accounts. The configuration contains default password. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication and execute arbitrary code in the context of the root. Was ZDI-CAN-24996.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3485 | Allegra extractFileFromZip Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3485</link><description>Allegra extractFileFromZip Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Allegra. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the extractFileFromZip method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26524.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5473 | GIMP ICO File Parsing Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5473</link><description>GIMP ICO File Parsing Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of GIMP. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of ICO files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an integer overflow before writing to memory. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26752.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5474 | 2BrightSparks SyncBackFree Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5474</link><description>2BrightSparks SyncBackFree Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of 2BrightSparks SyncBackFree. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. User interaction on the part of an administrator is also required.

The specific flaw exists within the Mirror functionality. By creating a junction, an attacker can abuse the service to delete arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-26962.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5480 | Action1 Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5480</link><description>Action1 Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Action1.  An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of OpenSSL. The product loads an OpenSSL configuration file from an unsecured location. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-26767.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5481 | Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5481</link><description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26168.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5794 | Tenda AC5 setPptpUserList formSetPPTPUserList buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5794</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda AC5 15.03.06.47. Affected by this issue is the function formSetPPTPUserList of the file /goform/setPptpUserList. The manipulation of the argument list leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5795 | Tenda AC5 AdvSetLanip fromadvsetlanip buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5795</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda AC5 1.0/15.03.06.47. This affects the function fromadvsetlanip of the file /goform/AdvSetLanip. The manipulation of the argument lanMask leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5792 | TOTOLINK EX1200T HTTP POST Request formWlanRedirect buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5792</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK EX1200T 4.1.2cu.5232_B20210713. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boafrm/formWlanRedirect of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument redirect-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5793 | TOTOLINK EX1200T HTTP POST Request formPortFw buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5793</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK EX1200T 4.1.2cu.5232_B20210713. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formPortFw of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument service_type leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47950 | CoreDNS Vulnerable to DoQ Memory Exhaustion via Stream Amplification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47950</link><description>CoreDNS is a DNS server that chains plugins. In versions prior to 1.21.2, a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability exists in the CoreDNS DNS-over-QUIC (DoQ) server implementation. The server previously created a new goroutine for every incoming QUIC stream without imposing any limits on the number of concurrent streams or goroutines. A remote, unauthenticated attacker could open a large number of streams, leading to uncontrolled memory consumption and eventually causing an Out Of Memory (OOM) crash — especially in containerized or memory-constrained environments. The patch in version 1.21.2 introduces two key mitigation mechanisms: `max_streams`, which caps the number of concurrent QUIC streams per connection with a default value of `256`; and `worker_pool_size`, which Introduces a server-wide, bounded worker pool to process incoming streams with a default value of `1024`. This eliminates the 1:1 stream-to-goroutine model and ensures that CoreDNS remains resilient under high concurrency.  Some workarounds are available for those who are unable to upgrade. Disable QUIC support by removing or commenting out the `quic://` block in the Corefile, use container runtime resource limits to detect and isolate excessive memory usage, and/or monitor QUIC connection patterns and alert on anomalies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49011 | SpiceDB checks involving relations with caveats can result in no permission when permission is expected</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49011</link><description>SpiceDB is an open source database for storing and querying fine-grained authorization data. Prior to version 1.44.2, on schemas involving arrows with caveats on the arrow’ed relation, when the path to resolve a CheckPermission request involves the evaluation of multiple caveated branches, requests may return a negative response when a positive response is expected. Version 1.44.2 fixes the issue. As a workaround, do not use caveats in the schema over an arrow’ed relation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5789 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formPortFw buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5789</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. This affects an unknown part of the file /boafrm/formPortFw of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument service_type leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5790 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formIpQoS buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5790</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formIpQoS of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5788 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formReflashClientTbl buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5788</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formReflashClientTbl of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49599 | Huawei EG8141A5 devices through V5R019C00S100, EG8145V5 devices through V5R019C00S100, and EG8145V5-V2 devices through V5R021C00S184 allow t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49599</link><description>Huawei EG8141A5 devices through V5R019C00S100, EG8145V5 devices through V5R019C00S100, and EG8145V5-V2 devices through V5R021C00S184 allow the Epuser account to disable ONT firewall functionality, e.g., to remove the default blocking of the SSH and TELNET TCP ports, aka HWNO-56Q3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:48:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5786 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formDMZ buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5786</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formDMZ of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:48:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5787 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formWsc buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5787</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formWsc of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:48:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5784 | PHPGurukul Employee Record Management System myexp.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5784</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Employee Record Management System 1.3 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /myexp.php. The manipulation of the argument emp3ctc leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5785 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formWirelessTbl buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5785</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boafrm/formWirelessTbl of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13087 | QHora</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13087</link><description>A command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect QHora. If an attacker gains local network access who have also gained an administrator account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuRouter 2.4.6.028 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13088 | QHora</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13088</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability has been reported to affect QHora. If an attacker gains local network access, they can then exploit the vulnerability to compromise the security of the system.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuRouter 2.5.0.140 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50406 | License Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50406</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect License Center. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained user access to bypass security mechanisms or read application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
License Center 1.9.49 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56805 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56805</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained user access to modify memory or crash processes.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.4.3079 build 20250321 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.4.3079 build 20250321 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22481 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22481</link><description>A command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained user access to execute arbitrary commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.4.3079 build 20250321 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.4.3079 build 20250321 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22482 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22482</link><description>A use of externally-controlled format string vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained user access to obtain secret data or modify memory.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 4.5.0.6 ( 2025/03/20 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22484 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22484</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote  attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to prevent other systems, applications, or processes from accessing the same type of resource.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4847 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22486 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22486</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained user access to compromise the security of the system.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4791 and later
  and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22490 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22490</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote  attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4847 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29871 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29871</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a local  attacker gains an administrator account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to obtain secret data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4847 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29872 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29872</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote  attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to prevent other systems, applications, or processes from accessing the same type of resource.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4847 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29873 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29873</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote  attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4847 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29876 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29876</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote  attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4847 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29877 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29877</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote  attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4847 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29883 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29883</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained user access to compromise the security of the system.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4791 and later
  and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29884 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29884</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained user access to compromise the security of the system.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4791 and later
  and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29885 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29885</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained user access to compromise the security of the system.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4791 and later
  and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29892 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29892</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained user access to execute unauthorized code or commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 4.5.0.6 ( 2025/03/20 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30279 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30279</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote  attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to compromise the security of the system.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4847 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33031 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33031</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to compromise the security of the system.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4847 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33035 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33035</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote  attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to read the contents of unexpected files or system data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4847 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:59:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5747 | WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger MCU Command Parsing Misinterpretation of Input Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5747</link><description>WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger MCU Command Parsing Misinterpretation of Input Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installatons of WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger devices. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of command frames received by the MCU. When parsing frames, the process does not properly detect the start of a frame, which can lead to misinterpretation of input. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the device. Was ZDI-CAN-26501.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5748 | WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger LAN OTA Exposed Dangerous Method Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5748</link><description>WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger LAN OTA Exposed Dangerous Method Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the Tuya communications module software. The issue results from the exposure of a method allowing the upload of crafted software images to the module. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device. Was ZDI-CAN-26349.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5749 | WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger BLE Encryption Keys Uninitialized Variable Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5749</link><description>WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger BLE Encryption Keys Uninitialized Variable Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of cryptographic keys used in vendor-specific encrypted communications. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of a variable prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-26295.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5750 | WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger tuya_svc_devos_activate_result_parse Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5750</link><description>WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger tuya_svc_devos_activate_result_parse Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of the secKey, localKey, stdTimeZone and devId parameters. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device. Was ZDI-CAN-26294.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5751 | WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger Management Card Hard-coded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5751</link><description>WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger Management Card Hard-coded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of management cards. The issue results from the lack of personalization of management cards. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-26292.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5783 | PHPGurukul Employee Record Management System editmyexp.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5783</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Employee Record Management System 1.3. This affects an unknown part of the file /editmyexp.php. The manipulation of the argument emp3workduration leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5780 | code-projects Patient Record Management System view_dental.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5780</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /view_dental.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5782 | PHPGurukul Employee Record Management System resetpassword.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5782</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Employee Record Management System 1.3. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /resetpassword.php. The manipulation of the argument newpassword leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27531 | Apache InLong: An arbitrary file read vulnerability for JDBC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27531</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache InLong. 

This issue affects Apache InLong: from 1.13.0 before 2.1.0, 

this issue would allow an authenticated attacker to read arbitrary files by double writing the param.





Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.1.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41646 | RevPi Webstatus application is vulnerable to an authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41646</link><description>An unauthorized remote attacker can bypass the authentication of the affected software package by misusing an incorrect type conversion. This leads to full compromise of the device</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5779 | code-projects Patient Record Management System birthing.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5779</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /birthing.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no/comp_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:35:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5778 | 1000 Projects ABC Courier Management System adminSQL sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5778</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in 1000 Projects ABC Courier Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /adminSQL. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38001 | net_sched: hfsc: Address reentrant enqueue adding class to eltree twice</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38001</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net_sched: hfsc: Address reentrant enqueue adding class to eltree twice

Savino says:
    "We are writing to report that this recent patch
    (141d34391abbb315d68556b7c67ad97885407547) [1]
    can be bypassed, and a UAF can still occur when HFSC is utilized with
    NETEM.

    The patch only checks the cl-&gt;cl_nactive field to determine whether
    it is the first insertion or not [2], but this field is only
    incremented by init_vf [3].

    By using HFSC_RSC (which uses init_ed) [4], it is possible to bypass the
    check and insert the class twice in the eltree.
    Under normal conditions, this would lead to an infinite loop in
    hfsc_dequeue for the reasons we already explained in this report [5].

    However, if TBF is added as root qdisc and it is configured with a
    very low rate,
    it can be utilized to prevent packets from being dequeued.
    This behavior can be exploited to perform subsequent insertions in the
    HFSC eltree and cause a UAF."

To fix both the UAF and the infinite loop, with netem as an hfsc child,
check explicitly in hfsc_enqueue whether the class is already in the eltree
whenever the HFSC_RSC flag is set.

[1] https://web.git.kernel.org/pub/scm/linux/kernel/git/torvalds/linux.git/commit/?id=141d34391abbb315d68556b7c67ad97885407547
[2] https://elixir.bootlin.com/linux/v6.15-rc5/source/net/sched/sch_hfsc.c#L1572
[3] https://elixir.bootlin.com/linux/v6.15-rc5/source/net/sched/sch_hfsc.c#L677
[4] https://elixir.bootlin.com/linux/v6.15-rc5/source/net/sched/sch_hfsc.c#L1574
[5] https://lore.kernel.org/netdev/8DuRWwfqjoRDLDmBMlIfbrsZg9Gx50DHJc1ilxsEBNe2D6NMoigR_eIRIG0LOjMc3r10nUUZtArXx4oZBIdUfZQrwjcQhdinnMis_0G7VEk=@willsroot.io/T/#u</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38002 | io_uring/fdinfo: grab ctx-&amp;gt;uring_lock around io_uring_show_fdinfo()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38002</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

io_uring/fdinfo: grab ctx-&gt;uring_lock around io_uring_show_fdinfo()

Not everything requires locking in there, which is why the 'has_lock'
variable exists. But enough does that it's a bit unwieldy to manage.
Wrap the whole thing in a -&gt;uring_lock trylock, and just return
with no output if we fail to grab it. The existing trylock() will
already have greatly diminished utility/output for the failure case.

This fixes an issue with reading the SQE fields, if the ring is being
actively resized at the same time.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5806 | Jenkins Gatling Plugin 136.vb_9009b_3d33a_e serves Gatling reports in a manner that bypasses the Content-Security-Policy protection introduc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5806</link><description>Jenkins Gatling Plugin 136.vb_9009b_3d33a_e serves Gatling reports in a manner that bypasses the Content-Security-Policy protection introduced in Jenkins 1.641 and 1.625, resulting in a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exploitable by users able to change report content.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:50:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0620 | Samba: smbd doesn&amp;#x27;t pick up group membership changes when re-authenticating an expired smb session</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0620</link><description>A flaw was found in Samba. The smbd service daemon does not pick up group membership changes when re-authenticating an expired SMB session. This issue can expose file shares until clients disconnect and then connect again.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5791 | Users: `root` appended to group listings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5791</link><description>A flaw was found in the user's crate for Rust. This vulnerability allows privilege escalation via incorrect group listing when a user or process has fewer than exactly 1024 groups, leading to the erroneous inclusion of the root group in the access list.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25995 | WordPress AI Mortgage Calculator &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25995</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in choicehomemortgage AI Mortgage Calculator allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects AI Mortgage Calculator: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25997 | WordPress Sola Support Ticket &amp;lt;= 3.17 - Arbitrary Content Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25997</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in SolaPlugins Sola Support Ticket allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Sola Support Ticket: from n/a through 3.17.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26000 | WordPress Bang tinh vay &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26000</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in hanhdo205 Bang tinh vay allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Bang tinh vay: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26001 | WordPress Next Event Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26001</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Marchetti Design Next Event Calendar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Next Event Calendar: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26002 | WordPress 6Storage Rentals &amp;lt;= 2.19.5 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26002</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in 6Storage 6Storage Rentals allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects 6Storage Rentals: from n/a through 2.19.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26003 | WordPress WP Post Corrector &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26003</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in vipul Jariwala WP Post Corrector allows SQL Injection. This issue affects WP Post Corrector: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23969 | WordPress KI Live Video Conferences &amp;lt;= 5.5.15 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23969</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in whassan KI Live Video Conferences allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects KI Live Video Conferences: from n/a through 5.5.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23971 | WordPress KI Live Video Conferences &amp;lt;= 5.5.15 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23971</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in whassan KI Live Video Conferences allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects KI Live Video Conferences: from n/a through 5.5.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24762 | WordPress TicketBAI Facturas para WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.19 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24762</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in facturaone TicketBAI Facturas para WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects TicketBAI Facturas para WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24763 | WordPress bbPress API &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24763</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Pascal Casier bbPress API allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects bbPress API: from n/a through 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24772 | WordPress Pay with Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24772</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in cmsMinds Pay with Contact Form 7 allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Pay with Contact Form 7: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24776 | WordPress Responsive Flipbooks &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24776</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in codelobster Responsive Flipbooks allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Responsive Flipbooks: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24778 | WordPress No Spam At All &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24778</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in De paragon No Spam At All allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects No Spam At All: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26590 | WordPress Complete Google Seo Scan &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26590</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Nir Complete Google Seo Scan allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Complete Google Seo Scan: from n/a through 3.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26593 | WordPress FastBook &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26593</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in FasterThemes FastBook allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects FastBook: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27334 | WordPress Simple Google Static Map &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27334</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ángel C. Simple Google Static Map allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Simple Google Static Map: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27359 | WordPress WP Media File Type Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27359</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Seerox WP Media File Type Manager allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Media File Type Manager: from n/a through 2.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27360 | WordPress Quick Event Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27360</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP Corner Quick Event Calendar allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Quick Event Calendar: from n/a through 1.4.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28948 | WordPress Mediabay - WordPress Media Library Folders plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - CSRF to Reflected XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28948</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in codedraft Mediabay - WordPress Media Library Folders allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Mediabay - WordPress Media Library Folders: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28950 | WordPress Post Author &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28950</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in David Shabtai Post Author allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Post Author: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28952 | WordPress CubePoints &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28952</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jonathan Lau CubePoints allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects CubePoints: from n/a through 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28954 | WordPress Backwp plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - CSRF to Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28954</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wphobby Backwp allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Backwp: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28958 | WordPress Bg Orthodox Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 0.13.10 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28958</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Vadim Bogaiskov Bg Orthodox Calendar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Bg Orthodox Calendar: from n/a through 0.13.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28964 | WordPress Personal Favicon plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28964</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in mangup Personal Favicon allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Personal Favicon: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28966 | WordPress Recent Posts Slider Responsive plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28966</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in dilemma123 Recent Posts Slider Responsive allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Recent Posts Slider Responsive: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28974 | WordPress Free WP Mail SMTP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28974</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in mail250 Free WP Mail SMTP allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Free WP Mail SMTP: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28981 | WordPress WP Mail Options plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28981</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Soli WP Mail Options allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Mail Options: from n/a through 0.2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28984 | WordPress Subscription Renewal Reminders for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery to Notice Dismissal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28984</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in storepro Subscription Renewal Reminders for WooCommerce allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Subscription Renewal Reminders for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.3.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28985 | WordPress Elastic Email Subscribe Form &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28985</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Elastic Email Elastic Email Subscribe Form allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Elastic Email Subscribe Form: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28986 | WordPress Epicwin Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - CSRF to SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28986</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Webaholicson Epicwin Plugin allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Epicwin Plugin: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28989 | WordPress Read More Login &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28989</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in arildur Read More Login allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Read More Login: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28994 | WordPress Viral Loops WP Integration &amp;lt;= 3.8.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28994</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in viralloops Viral Loops WP Integration allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Viral Loops WP Integration: from n/a through 3.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28995 | WordPress Viral Loops WP Integration &amp;lt;= 3.8.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28995</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in viralloops Viral Loops WP Integration allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Viral Loops WP Integration: from n/a through 3.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28996 | WordPress GPP Slideshow &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28996</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Thad Allender GPP Slideshow allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects GPP Slideshow: from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28997 | WordPress WP AutoKeyword &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28997</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in EXEIdeas International WP AutoKeyword allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP AutoKeyword: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29003 | WordPress The Holiday Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.18.2.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29003</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in mva7 The Holiday Calendar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects The Holiday Calendar: from n/a through 1.18.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29005 | WordPress HR Management Lite &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29005</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in weblizar HR Management Lite allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects HR Management Lite: from n/a through 3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29006 | WordPress Direct Checkout for WooCommerce Lite &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29006</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in centangle Direct Checkout for WooCommerce Lite allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Direct Checkout for WooCommerce Lite: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29008 | WordPress SocialMark &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29008</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in ShawonPro SocialMark allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects SocialMark: from n/a through 2.0.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29010 | WordPress Behance Portfolio Manager &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29010</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in eleopard Behance Portfolio Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Behance Portfolio Manager: from n/a through 1.7.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29011 | WordPress YouTube Simple Gallery &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29011</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CHR Designer YouTube Simple Gallery allows Stored XSS. This issue affects YouTube Simple Gallery: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29013 | WordPress Custom Category/Post Type Post order &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29013</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in faaiq Custom Category/Post Type Post order allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Custom Category/Post Type Post order: from n/a through 1.5.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30624 | WordPress WordLift &amp;lt;= 3.54.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30624</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WordLift WordLift allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WordLift: from n/a through 3.54.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30625 | WordPress AppBanners &amp;lt;= 1.5.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30625</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Matt Pramschufer AppBanners allows Stored XSS. This issue affects AppBanners: from n/a through 1.5.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30627 | WordPress Elegant Visitor Counter &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30627</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in regolithsjk Elegant Visitor Counter allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Elegant Visitor Counter: from n/a through 3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30629 | WordPress Bitly URL Shortener &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30629</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Codehaveli Bitly URL Shortener allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Bitly URL Shortener: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30630 | WordPress Global Translator &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30630</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in pozzad Global Translator allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Global Translator: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30632 | WordPress Global Translator &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30632</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in pozzad Global Translator allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Global Translator: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30634 | WordPress WP Featured Content Slider &amp;lt;= 2.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30634</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in IWEBIX WP Featured Content Slider allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Featured Content Slider: from n/a through 2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30636 | WordPress Accessibility Suite &amp;lt;= 4.19 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30636</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ability, Inc Accessibility Suite allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Accessibility Suite: from n/a through 4.19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30637 | WordPress Booking Ultra Pro &amp;lt;= 1.1.20 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30637</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Deetronix Booking Ultra Pro allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Booking Ultra Pro: from n/a through 1.1.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30638 | WordPress Powie&amp;#x27;s Uptime Robot &amp;lt;= 0.9.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30638</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PowieT Powie's Uptime Robot allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Powie's Uptime Robot: from n/a through 0.9.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30927 | WordPress Wordapp &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30927</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Wordapp Team Wordapp allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Wordapp: from n/a through 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30928 | WordPress WP Biographia &amp;lt;= 4.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30928</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in vicchi WP Biographia allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Biographia: from n/a through 4.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30930 | WordPress ACF: Yandex Maps Field &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30930</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Unreal Themes ACF: Yandex Maps Field allows Stored XSS. This issue affects ACF: Yandex Maps Field: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30931 | WordPress «Подсказки» от DaData.ru &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30931</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Shamil Shafeev «Подсказки» от DaData.ru allows Stored XSS. This issue affects «Подсказки» от DaData.ru: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30932 | WordPress WP Compress for MainWP &amp;lt;= 6.30.32 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30932</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Compress WP Compress for MainWP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP Compress for MainWP: from n/a through 6.30.32.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30934 | WordPress 診断ジェネレータ作成プラグイン &amp;lt;= 1.4.16 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30934</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in OLIVESYSTEM 診断ジェネレータ作成プラグイン allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects 診断ジェネレータ作成プラグイン: from n/a through 1.4.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30935 | WordPress Contact Form &amp;lt;= 2.0.12 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30935</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NickDuncan Contact Form allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Contact Form: from n/a through 2.0.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30937 | WordPress Responsify WP &amp;lt;= 1.9.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30937</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in stefanledin Responsify WP allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Responsify WP: from n/a through 1.9.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30938 | WordPress Broadly for WordPress &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30938</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in broadly Broadly for WordPress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Broadly for WordPress: from n/a through 3.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30939 | WordPress IFrame Widget &amp;lt;= 4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30939</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Debashish IFrame Widget allows Stored XSS. This issue affects IFrame Widget: from n/a through 4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30940 | WordPress Melipayamak &amp;lt;= 2.2.12 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30940</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in melipayamak Melipayamak allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Melipayamak: from n/a through 2.2.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30941 | WordPress Pinterest Verify Meta Tag &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30941</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Marvie Pons Pinterest Verify Meta Tag allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Pinterest Verify Meta Tag: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30942 | WordPress  Post Custom Templates Lite &amp;lt;= 1.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30942</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in OTWthemes  Post Custom Templates Lite allows Stored XSS. This issue affects  Post Custom Templates Lite: from n/a through 1.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30945 | WordPress Taskbuilder &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30945</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in taskbuilder Taskbuilder allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Taskbuilder: from n/a through 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30946 | WordPress Custom Bulk/Quick Edit &amp;lt;= 1.6.10 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30946</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Michael Cannon Custom Bulk/Quick Edit allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Custom Bulk/Quick Edit: from n/a through 1.6.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30948 | WordPress Layouts for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.11 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30948</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Giraphix Creative Layouts for Elementor allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Layouts for Elementor: from n/a through 1.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30950 | WordPress All Currencies for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.4.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30950</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Wham All Currencies for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects All Currencies for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.4.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30951 | WordPress BlockStrap Page Builder - Bootstrap Blocks &amp;lt;= 0.1.36 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30951</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Stiofan BlockStrap Page Builder - Bootstrap Blocks allows Stored XSS. This issue affects BlockStrap Page Builder - Bootstrap Blocks: from n/a through 0.1.36.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30952 | WordPress Nexa Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30952</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wpdive Nexa Blocks allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Nexa Blocks: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30953 | WordPress WP Gravity Forms Salesforce &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Open Redirection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30953</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in CRM Perks WP Gravity Forms Salesforce allows Phishing. This issue affects WP Gravity Forms Salesforce: from n/a through 1.4.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30954 | WordPress WP Gravity Forms Constant Contact Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Open Redirection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30954</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in CRM Perks WP Gravity Forms Constant Contact Plugin allows Phishing. This issue affects WP Gravity Forms Constant Contact Plugin: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30956 | WordPress Booqable Rental &amp;lt;= 2.4.20 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30956</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Booqable Rental Software Booqable Rental allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Booqable Rental: from n/a through 2.4.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30957 | WordPress Activity Plus Reloaded for BuddyPress &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30957</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BuddyDev Activity Plus Reloaded for BuddyPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Activity Plus Reloaded for BuddyPress: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30958 | WordPress onOffice for WP-Websites &amp;lt;= 5.7 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30958</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in onOffice GmbH onOffice for WP-Websites allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects onOffice for WP-Websites: from n/a through 5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30968 | WordPress Advanced Post List &amp;lt;= 0.5.6.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30968</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in jokerbr313 Advanced Post List allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Advanced Post List: from n/a through 0.5.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30974 | WordPress Post Grid Master &amp;lt;= 3.4.13 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30974</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Akhtarujjaman Shuvo Post Grid Master allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Post Grid Master: from n/a through 3.4.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30976 | WordPress Nexa Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30976</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in wpdive Nexa Blocks allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects Nexa Blocks: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30977 | WordPress WP Live Chat + Chatbots Plugin for WordPress – Chaport &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30977</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Chaport Live Chat WP Live Chat + Chatbots Plugin for WordPress – Chaport allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Live Chat + Chatbots Plugin for WordPress – Chaport: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30978 | WordPress Slack Notifications by dorzki &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30978</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Dor Zuberi Slack Notifications by dorzki allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Slack Notifications by dorzki: from n/a through 2.0.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30980 | WordPress Simple Keyword to Link &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30980</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Alessandro Piconi Simple Keyword to Link allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Simple Keyword to Link: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30981 | WordPress WP-Recall plugin &amp;lt;= 16.26.14 - CSRF to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30981</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in tggfref WP-Recall allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects WP-Recall: from n/a through 16.26.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30986 | WordPress Elite Video Player &amp;lt;= 10.0.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30986</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in _CreativeMedia_ Elite Video Player allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Elite Video Player: from n/a through 10.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30989 | WordPress Libro de Reclamaciones y Quejas &amp;lt;= 0.9 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30989</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Renzo Tejada Libro de Reclamaciones y Quejas allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Libro de Reclamaciones y Quejas: from n/a through 0.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30990 | WordPress ThemeHunk &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30990</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThemeHunk ThemeHunk allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects ThemeHunk: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30991 | WordPress Premium Packages &amp;lt;= 6.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30991</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Shahjada Premium Packages allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Premium Packages: from n/a through 6.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30994 | WordPress CubeWP – All-in-One Dynamic Content Framework plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.23 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30994</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Emraan Cheema CubeWP – All-in-One Dynamic Content Framework allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects CubeWP – All-in-One Dynamic Content Framework: from n/a through 1.1.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30995 | WordPress Widgetize Pages Light plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30995</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in OTWthemes Widgetize Pages Light allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Widgetize Pages Light: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30997 | WordPress Car Repair Services &amp;lt;= 5.0 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30997</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in SmartDataSoft Car Repair Services allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects Car Repair Services: from n/a through 5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30999 | WordPress WP Shopify &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30999</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Fahad Mahmood WP Shopify allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects WP Shopify: from n/a through 1.5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38000 | sch_hfsc: Fix qlen accounting bug when using peek in hfsc_enqueue()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38000</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

sch_hfsc: Fix qlen accounting bug when using peek in hfsc_enqueue()

When enqueuing the first packet to an HFSC class, hfsc_enqueue() calls the
child qdisc's peek() operation before incrementing sch-&gt;q.qlen and
sch-&gt;qstats.backlog. If the child qdisc uses qdisc_peek_dequeued(), this may
trigger an immediate dequeue and potential packet drop. In such cases,
qdisc_tree_reduce_backlog() is called, but the HFSC qdisc's qlen and backlog
have not yet been updated, leading to inconsistent queue accounting. This
can leave an empty HFSC class in the active list, causing further
consequences like use-after-free.

This patch fixes the bug by moving the increment of sch-&gt;q.qlen and
sch-&gt;qstats.backlog before the call to the child qdisc's peek() operation.
This ensures that queue length and backlog are always accurate when packet
drops or dequeues are triggered during the peek.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49419 | WordPress Foxit eSign for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Other Vulnerability Type Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49419</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in esigngenie Foxit eSign for WordPress allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Foxit eSign for WordPress: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49421 | WordPress WP Text Expander &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49421</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Andrei Filonov WP Text Expander allows SQL Injection. This issue affects WP Text Expander: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49425 | WordPress Konami Easter Egg &amp;lt;= v0.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49425</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Adrian Hanft Konami Easter Egg allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Konami Easter Egg: from n/a through v0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49427 | WordPress Abbie Expander &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49427</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ryan Burnette Abbie Expander allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Abbie Expander: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49429 | WordPress Video Embeds &amp;lt;= 0.1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49429</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ryan Burnette Video Embeds allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Video Embeds: from n/a through 0.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49435 | WordPress Wp Easy Allopass &amp;lt;= 4.1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49435</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Hasina77 Wp Easy Allopass allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Wp Easy Allopass: from n/a through 4.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49439 | WordPress Atelier Create CV plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49439</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in mariusz88atelierweb Atelier Create CV allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Atelier Create CV: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49440 | WordPress WP Security Master &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49440</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Vuong Nguyen WP Security Master allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Security Master: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49441 | WordPress Interactive Regional Map of Florida &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49441</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Map Plugins Interactive Regional Map of Florida allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Interactive Regional Map of Florida: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49442 | WordPress Simple Nested Menu &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49442</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mostafa Shahiri Simple Nested Menu allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Simple Nested Menu: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49443 | WordPress Bacon Ipsum &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49443</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Chris McCoy Bacon Ipsum allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Bacon Ipsum: from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49445 | WordPress Interactive UK Regional Map plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49445</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP Map Plugins Interactive UK Regional Map allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Interactive UK Regional Map: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49446 | WordPress Admin Notes &amp;lt;=1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49446</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in minhlaobao Admin Notes allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Admin Notes: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49449 | WordPress Interactive Regional Map of Africa &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49449</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP Map Plugins Interactive Regional Map of Africa allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Interactive Regional Map of Africa: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49450 | WordPress SEPA Girocode &amp;lt;= 0.5.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49450</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in mhallmann SEPA Girocode allows Stored XSS. This issue affects SEPA Girocode: from n/a through 0.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49453 | WordPress BP Profile as Homepage plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49453</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jatinder Pal Singh BP Profile as Homepage allows Stored XSS. This issue affects BP Profile as Homepage: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5766 | code-projects Laundry System cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5766</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Laundry System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:35:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31000 | WordPress Payment QR WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31000</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Miguel Fuentes Payment QR WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Payment QR WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31025 | WordPress Image Hover Effects Block &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31025</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Blocksera Image Hover Effects Block allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Image Hover Effects Block: from n/a through 1.4.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49235 | WordPress RTMKit Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49235</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rometheme RTMKit Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects RTMKit Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49236 | WordPress Raychat &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49236</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in raychat Raychat allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Raychat: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49237 | WordPress POEditor plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.10 - CSRF to Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49237</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in POEditor POEditor allows Path Traversal. This issue affects POEditor: from n/a through 0.9.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49238 | WordPress Everest Backup &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49238</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in everestthemes Everest Backup allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Everest Backup: from n/a through 2.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49239 | WordPress Print Invoice &amp;amp; Delivery Notes for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.5.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49239</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in tychesoftwares Print Invoice &amp; Delivery Notes for WooCommerce allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Print Invoice &amp; Delivery Notes for WooCommerce: from n/a through 5.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49240 | WordPress DocsPress &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49240</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in nK DocsPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects DocsPress: from n/a through 2.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49241 | WordPress oik &amp;lt;= 4.15.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49241</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in bobbingwide oik allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects oik: from n/a through 4.15.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49242 | WordPress Bellows Accordion Menu &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49242</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sevenspark Bellows Accordion Menu allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Bellows Accordion Menu: from n/a through 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49243 | WordPress ShiftNav – Responsive Mobile Menu &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49243</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sevenspark ShiftNav – Responsive Mobile Menu allows Stored XSS. This issue affects ShiftNav – Responsive Mobile Menu: from n/a through 1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49244 | WordPress Shortcodes Ultimate &amp;lt;= 7.3.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49244</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Vova Shortcodes Ultimate allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Shortcodes Ultimate: from n/a through 7.3.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49246 | WordPress Testimonials Showcase &amp;lt;= 1.9.16 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49246</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in cmoreira Testimonials Showcase allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Testimonials Showcase: from n/a through 1.9.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49248 | WordPress Team Showcase &amp;lt; 25.05.13 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49248</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in cmoreira Team Showcase allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Team Showcase: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49250 | WordPress Team Showcase plugin &amp;lt; 25.05.13 - Arbitrary Shortcode Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49250</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in cmoreira Team Showcase allows Code Injection. This issue affects Team Showcase: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49262 | WordPress Sina Extension for Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.6.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49262</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in shaonsina Sina Extension for Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Sina Extension for Elementor: from n/a through 3.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49263 | WordPress WC Vendors Marketplace &amp;lt;= 2.5.6 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49263</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WCVendors WC Vendors Marketplace allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects WC Vendors Marketplace: from n/a through 2.5.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49268 | WordPress Verge3D &amp;lt;= 4.9.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49268</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Soft8Soft LLC Verge3D allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Verge3D: from n/a through 4.9.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49269 | WordPress Market Exporter &amp;lt;= 2.0.22 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49269</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Anton Vanyukov Market Exporter allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Market Exporter: from n/a through 2.0.22.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49270 | WordPress WP-CRM System &amp;lt;= 3.4.2 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49270</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mario Peshev WP-CRM System allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects WP-CRM System: from n/a through 3.4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49272 | WordPress Trinity Audio &amp;lt;= 5.20.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49272</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in sergiotrinity Trinity Audio allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Trinity Audio: from n/a through 5.20.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49273 | WordPress WP Tools &amp;lt;= 5.24 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49273</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Bill Minozzi WP Tools allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Tools: from n/a through 5.24.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49283 | WordPress Anti-spam, Spam protection, ReCaptcha for all forms and GDPR-compliant &amp;lt;= 4.1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49283</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Matthias Nordwig Anti-spam, Spam protection, ReCaptcha for all forms and GDPR-compliant allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Anti-spam, Spam protection, ReCaptcha for all forms and GDPR-compliant: from n/a through 4.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49284 | WordPress WP Maintenance Mode &amp;amp; Site Under Construction &amp;lt;= 4.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49284</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wp-buy WP Maintenance Mode &amp; Site Under Construction allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Maintenance Mode &amp; Site Under Construction: from n/a through 4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49285 | WordPress WP Cookie Notice for GDPR, CCPA &amp;amp; ePrivacy Consent &amp;lt;= 3.8.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49285</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP Legal Pages WP Cookie Notice for GDPR, CCPA &amp; ePrivacy Consent allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Cookie Notice for GDPR, CCPA &amp; ePrivacy Consent: from n/a through 3.8.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49286 | WordPress WP Table Builder &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49286</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP Table Builder WP Table Builder allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Table Builder: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49287 | WordPress Product Feed for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.2.8 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49287</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WebToffee Product Feed for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Product Feed for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49288 | WordPress Ultimate WP Mail &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49288</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Rustaurius Ultimate WP Mail allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Ultimate WP Mail: from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49289 | WordPress PDF for WPForms &amp;lt;= 5.5.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49289</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in add-ons.org PDF for WPForms allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects PDF for WPForms: from n/a through 5.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49291 | WordPress Calculated Fields Form &amp;lt;= 5.3.58 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49291</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in codepeople Calculated Fields Form allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Calculated Fields Form: from n/a through 5.3.58.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49292 | WordPress Profile Builder &amp;lt;= 3.13.8 - Content Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49292</link><description>Improper Validation of Specified Quantity in Input vulnerability in Cozmoslabs Profile Builder allows Phishing. This issue affects Profile Builder: from n/a through 3.13.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49293 | WordPress Crawlomatic Multisite Scraper Post Generator &amp;lt;= 2.6.8.2 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49293</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CodeRevolution Crawlomatic Multisite Scraper Post Generator allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Crawlomatic Multisite Scraper Post Generator: from n/a through 2.6.8.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49294 | WordPress Crawlomatic Multisite Scraper Post Generator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.8.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Log Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49294</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in CodeRevolution Crawlomatic Multisite Scraper Post Generator allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Crawlomatic Multisite Scraper Post Generator: from n/a through 2.6.8.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49298 | WordPress Event post &amp;lt;= 5.10.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49298</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bastien Ho Event post allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Event post: from n/a through 5.10.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49299 | WordPress WebHotelier &amp;lt;= 1.9.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49299</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPlugged.com WebHotelier allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WebHotelier: from n/a through 1.9.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49301 | WordPress Greenshift &amp;lt;= 11.5.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49301</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wpsoul Greenshift allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Greenshift: from n/a through 11.5.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49304 | WordPress Search with Typesense &amp;lt;= 2.0.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49304</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodeManas Search with Typesense allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Search with Typesense: from n/a through 2.0.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49305 | WordPress Product Catalog Simple &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49305</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in impleCode Product Catalog Simple allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Product Catalog Simple: from n/a through 1.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49306 | WordPress WP Social Widget &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49306</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in catchsquare WP Social Widget allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Social Widget: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49307 | WordPress WP Multilang &amp;lt;= 2.4.19 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49307</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Magazine3 WP Multilang allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects WP Multilang: from n/a through 2.4.19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49308 | WordPress WP Travel Engine &amp;lt;= 6.5.1 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49308</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in WP Travel Engine WP Travel Engine allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects WP Travel Engine: from n/a through 6.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49309 | WordPress HT Team Member &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49309</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HT Plugins HT Team Member allows Stored XSS. This issue affects HT Team Member: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49310 | WordPress Frontend Dashboard &amp;lt;= 2.2.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49310</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in M A Vinoth Kumar Frontend Dashboard allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Frontend Dashboard: from n/a through 2.2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49311 | WordPress The Events Calendar Countdown Addon &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49311</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CoolHappy The Events Calendar Countdown Addon allows Stored XSS. This issue affects The Events Calendar Countdown Addon: from n/a through 1.4.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49313 | WordPress BRW &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49313</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ovatheme BRW allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects BRW: from n/a through 1.8.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49314 | WordPress BRW &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49314</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ovatheme BRW allows Stored XSS. This issue affects BRW: from n/a through 1.8.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49315 | WordPress Persian Woocommerce SMS &amp;lt;= 7.0.10 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49315</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in PersianScript Persian Woocommerce SMS allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Persian Woocommerce SMS: from n/a through 7.0.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49317 | WordPress WP Page Loading &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49317</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in NTC WP Page Loading allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Page Loading: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49318 | WordPress WPtouch &amp;lt;= 4.3.60 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49318</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPtouch WPtouch allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WPtouch: from n/a through 4.3.60.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49320 | WordPress FraudLabs Pro for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.22.11 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49320</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in fraudlabspro FraudLabs Pro for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects FraudLabs Pro for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.22.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49322 | WordPress 404 Page by SeedProd &amp;lt; 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49322</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SeedProd 404 Page by SeedProd allows Stored XSS. This issue affects 404 Page by SeedProd: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49323 | WordPress Hydra Booking &amp;lt;= 1.1.10 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49323</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Themefic Hydra Booking allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Hydra Booking: from n/a through 1.1.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49324 | WordPress Job Board Manager &amp;lt;= 2.1.60 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49324</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in PickPlugins Job Board Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Job Board Manager: from n/a through 2.1.60.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49325 | WordPress Newspack Newsletters &amp;lt;= 3.13.0 - Open Redirection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49325</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Automattic Newspack Newsletters allows Phishing. This issue affects Newspack Newsletters: from n/a through 3.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49326 | WordPress GamiPress &amp;lt;= 7.4.5 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49326</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Ruben Garcia GamiPress allows SQL Injection. This issue affects GamiPress: from n/a through 7.4.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49327 | WordPress ShortLinks Pro &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49327</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Ruben Garcia ShortLinks Pro allows SQL Injection. This issue affects ShortLinks Pro: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49328 | WordPress Store Locator WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49328</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Agile Logix Store Locator WordPress allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Store Locator WordPress: from n/a through 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49329 | WordPress Store Locator WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49329</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Agile Logix Store Locator WordPress allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Store Locator WordPress: from n/a through 1.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49332 | WordPress WP Time Slots Booking Form &amp;lt;= 1.2.30 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49332</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in codepeople WP Time Slots Booking Form allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Time Slots Booking Form: from n/a through 1.2.30.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49333 | WordPress Simple Membership &amp;lt;= 4.6.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49333</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wp.insider Simple Membership allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Simple Membership: from n/a through 4.6.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5764 | code-projects Laundry System insert_laundry.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5764</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Laundry System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /data/insert_laundry.php. The manipulation of the argument Customer leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5765 | code-projects Laundry System edit_laundry.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5765</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Laundry System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /data/edit_laundry.php. The manipulation of the argument Customer leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49072 | WordPress Mr. Murphy &amp;lt; 1.2.12.1 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49072</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in AncoraThemes Mr. Murphy allows Object Injection.This issue affects Mr. Murphy: from n/a before 1.2.12.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49073 | WordPress Sweet Dessert &amp;lt; 1.1.13 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49073</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Axiomthemes Sweet Dessert allows Object Injection.This issue affects Sweet Dessert: from n/a before 1.1.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5762 | code-projects Patient Record Management System view_hematology.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5762</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file view_hematology.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5763 | Tenda CP3 apollo sub_F3C8C command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5763</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda CP3 11.10.00.2311090948 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_F3C8C of the file apollo. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41361 | Uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in IDF and ZLF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41361</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in IDF v0.10.0-0C03-03 and ZLF v0.10.0-0C03-04. The devices improperly handle TLS requests associated with PROCOME sockets, so TLS requests sent to those PROCOME ports could cause the device to reboot and result in a denial of service. To exploit this vulnerability, PROCOME ports must be configured and active, with communications encryption active.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41367 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in IDF and ZLF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41367</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in IDF v0.10.0-0C03-03 and ZLF v0.10.0-0C03-04. This vulnerability allows an attacker to store malicious JavaScript payload in software that will run in the victim's browser. Exploiting this vulnerability requires authenticating to the device and executing certain commands that can only be executed with permissions higher than the view permission.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39358 | WordPress WP Posts Carousel &amp;lt;= 1.3.12 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39358</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Teastudio.Pl WP Posts Carousel allows Object Injection.This issue affects WP Posts Carousel: from n/a through 1.3.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:55:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41362 | Code injection vulnerability in IDF and ZLF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41362</link><description>Code injection vulnerability in IDF v0.10.0-0C03-03 and ZLF v0.10.0-0C03-04. This vulnerability allows an attacker to store malicious payload in software that will run in the victim's browser. Exploiting this vulnerability requires authenticating to the device and executing certain commands that can be executed with view permission.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:55:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41363 | CORS vulnerability in IDF and ZLF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41363</link><description>In IDF v0.10.0-0C03-03 and ZLF v0.10.0-0C03-04, a configuration error has been detected in cross-origin resource sharing (CORS). Exploiting this vulnerability requires authenticating to the device and executing certain commands that can be executed with view permission.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:55:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41364 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in IDF and ZLF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41364</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in IDF v0.10.0-0C03-03 and ZLF v0.10.0-0C03-04. This vulnerability allows an attacker to store malicious JavaScript payload in software that will run in the victim's browser. Exploiting this vulnerability requires authenticating to the device and executing certain commands that can be executed with view permission.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:55:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41365 | Code injection vulnerability in IDF and ZLF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41365</link><description>Code injection vulnerability in IDF v0.10.0-0C03-03 and ZLF v0.10.0-0C03-04. This vulnerability allows an attacker to store malicious payload in software that will run in the victim's browser. Exploiting this vulnerability requires authenticating to the device and executing certain commands that can be executed only with permissions higher than the view permission.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41366 | CORS vulnerability in IDF and ZLF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41366</link><description>In IDF v0.10.0-0C03-03 and ZLF v0.10.0-0C03-04, a configuration error has been detected in cross-origin resource sharing (CORS). Exploiting this vulnerability requires authenticating to the device and executing certain commands that can only be executed with permissions higher than the view permission.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47584 | WordPress Photography theme &amp;lt;= 7.5.2 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47584</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ThemeGoods Photography.This issue affects Photography: from n/a through 7.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48329 | WordPress Real Time Validation for Gravity Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48329</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Daman Jeet Real Time Validation for Gravity Forms allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Real Time Validation for Gravity Forms: from n/a through 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41360 | Uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in IDF and ZLF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41360</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in IDF v0.10.0-0C03-03 and ZLF v0.10.0-0C03-04. The device is vulnerable to a packet flooding denial of service attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47586 | WordPress Motors - Events plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47586</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in StylemixThemes Motors - Events allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Motors - Events: from n/a through 1.4.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48328 | WordPress Real Time Validation for Gravity Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48328</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Daman Jeet Real Time Validation for Gravity Forms allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Real Time Validation for Gravity Forms: from n/a through 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48335 | WordPress Responsive Plus plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48335</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CyberChimps Responsive Plus allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Responsive Plus: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49074 | WordPress WidgetKit plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49074</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemesGrove WidgetKit allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WidgetKit: from n/a through 2.5.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49075 | WordPress Wishlist plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.43 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49075</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PickPlugins Wishlist allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Wishlist: from n/a through 1.0.43.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49076 | WordPress The Plus Addons for Elementor Page Builder Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49076</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in POSIMYTH Innovations The Plus Addons for Elementor Page Builder Lite allows Stored XSS.This issue affects The Plus Addons for Elementor Page Builder Lite: from n/a through 6.2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49067 | WordPress Nasa Core plugin &amp;lt; 6.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49067</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NasaTheme Nasa Core allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Nasa Core: from n/a before 6.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49068 | WordPress Ocean Extra plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49068</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in OceanWP Ocean Extra allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ocean Extra: from n/a through 2.4.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5761 | PHPGurukul BP Monitoring Management System edit-family-member.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5761</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul BP Monitoring Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /edit-family-member.php. The manipulation of the argument memberage leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48337 | WordPress QuickCab plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48337</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in QuickcabWP QuickCab.This issue affects QuickCab: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49077 | WordPress Dynamic Pricing and Discount Rules plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49077</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ThemeHigh Dynamic Pricing and Discount Rules allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Dynamic Pricing and Discount Rules: from n/a through 2.2.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5239 | Domain For Sale &amp;lt;= 3.0.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via class_name Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5239</link><description>The Domain For Sale plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘class_name’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5760 | Simple History &amp;lt;= 5.8.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Detective Mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5760</link><description>The Simple History plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to sensitive data exposure via Detective Mode due to improper sanitization within the append_debug_info_to_context() function in versions prior to 5.8.1. When Detective Mode is enabled, the plugin’s logger captures the entire contents of $_POST (and sometimes raw request bodies or $_GET) without redacting any password‐related keys. As a result, whenever a user submits a login form, whether via native wp_login or a third‐party login widget, their actual password is written in clear text into the logs. An authenticated attacker or any user whose actions generate a login event will have their password recorded; an administrator (or anyone with database read access) can then read those logs and retrieve every captured password.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5758 | SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System doctor.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5758</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /doctor.php. The manipulation of the argument doctorname leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5759 | PHPGurukul Local Services Search Engine Management System edit-person-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5759</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Local Services Search Engine Management System 2.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit-person-detail.php?editid=2. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5757 | code-projects Traffic Offense Reporting System save-reported.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5757</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Traffic Offense Reporting System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /save-reported.php. The manipulation of the argument offence_id/vehicle_no/driver_license/name/address/gender/officer_reporting/offence leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5756 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System EditCity.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5756</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Admin/EditCity.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48781 | Soar Cloud HRD Human Resource Management System - External Control of File Name or Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48781</link><description>An external control of file name or path vulnerability in the download file function of Soar Cloud HRD Human Resource Management System through version 7.3.2025.0408 allows remote attackers to obtain partial files by specifying arbitrary file paths.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48782 | Soar Cloud HRD Human Resource Management System - Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48782</link><description>An unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability in the upload file function of Soar Cloud HRD Human Resource Management System through version 7.3.2025.0408 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary system commands via a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48783 | Soar Cloud HRD Human Resource Management System - External Control of File Name or Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48783</link><description>An external control of file name or path vulnerability in the delete file function of Soar Cloud HRD Human Resource Management System through version 7.3.2025.0408 allows remote attackers to delete partial files by specifying arbitrary file paths.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48784 | Soar Cloud HRD Human Resource Management System - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48784</link><description>A missing authorization vulnerability in Soar Cloud HRD Human Resource Management System through version 7.3.2025.0408 allows remote attackers to modify system settings without prior authorization.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5755 | SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System email_config.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5755</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /email_config.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48780 | Soar Cloud HRD Human Resource Management System - Deserialization of Untrusted Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48780</link><description>A deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability in the download file function of Soar Cloud HRD Human Resource Management System through version 7.3.2025.0408 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary system commands via a crafted serialized object.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5192 | Soar Cloud HRD Human Resource Management System - Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5192</link><description>A missing authentication for critical function vulnerability in the client application of Soar Cloud HRD Human Resource Management System through version 7.3.2025.0408 allows remote attackers to bypass authentication and access application functions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5738 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formStats buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5738</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formStats of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5739 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formSaveConfig buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5739</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. This affects an unknown part of the file /boafrm/formSaveConfig of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5737 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formDosCfg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5737</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formDosCfg of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 08:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3322 | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements in OnlineSuite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3322</link><description>An improper neutralization of inputs used in expression
language allows remote code execution with the highest privileges on the
server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 08:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3365 | Relative Path Traversal in OnlineSuite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3365</link><description>A missing protection against path traversal allows to access
any file on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 08:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3321 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials in OnlineSuite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3321</link><description>A predefined administrative account is not documented and cannot
be deactivated. This account cannot be misused from the network, only by local
users on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 08:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5735 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formSetLg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5735</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boafrm/formSetLg of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 08:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5736 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formNtp buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5736</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formNtp of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 08:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5732 | code-projects Traffic Offense Reporting System cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5732</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in code-projects Traffic Offense Reporting System 1.0. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5734 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formWlanRedirect buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5734</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formWlanRedirect of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument redirect-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5728 | SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System manage_website.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5728</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /manage_website.php. The manipulation of the argument website_image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5729 | code-projects Health Center Patient Record Management System birthing_record.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5729</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Health Center Patient Record Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /birthing_record.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58114 | Resource allocation control failure vulnerability in the ArkUI framework
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect av...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58114</link><description>Resource allocation control failure vulnerability in the ArkUI framework
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2935 | Anti-Spam: Spam Protection | Block Spam Users, Comments, Forms &amp;lt;= 2024.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Multiple Administrative Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2935</link><description>The Anti-Spam: Spam Protection | Block Spam Users, Comments, Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2024.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation in the 'ss_option_maint.php' and 'ss_user_filter_list' files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete pending comments, and re-enable a previously blocked user via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48908 | Ability Auto Startup service vulnerability in the foundation process
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48908</link><description>Ability Auto Startup service vulnerability in the foundation process
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48909 | Bypass vulnerability in the device management channel
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48909</link><description>Bypass vulnerability in the device management channel
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48910 | Buffer overflow vulnerability in the DFile module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48910</link><description>Buffer overflow vulnerability in the DFile module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48911 | Vulnerability of improper permission assignment in the note sharing module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48911</link><description>Vulnerability of improper permission assignment in the note sharing module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4964 | WP Online Users Stats &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Editor+) SQL Injection via table_name Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4964</link><description>The WP Online Users Stats plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘table_name’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4966 | WP Online Users Stats &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via hk_dataset_results Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4966</link><description>The WP Online Users Stats plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing nonce validation within the hk_dataset_results() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5018 | Hive Support &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Missing Authorization via hs_update_ai_chat_settings and hive_lite_support_get_all_binbox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5018</link><description>The Hive Support plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data due to a missing capability check on the hs_update_ai_chat_settings() and hive_lite_support_get_all_binbox() functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read and overwrite the site’s OpenAI API key and inspection data or modify AI-chat prompts and behavior. This vulnerability is potentially a duplicate of CVE-2025-32208 or/and CVE-2025-32242.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5019 | Hive Support &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via hs_update_ai_chat_settings Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5019</link><description>The Hive Support | AI-Powered Help Desk, Live Chat &amp; AI Chat Bot Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the hs_update_ai_chat_settings() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reconfigure the plugin’s AI/chat settings (including API keys) and to potentially redirect notifications or leak data to attacker-controlled endpoints via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5486 | WP Email Debug 1.0 - 1.1.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via Password Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5486</link><description>The WP Email Debug plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the WPMDBUG_handle_settings() function in versions 1.0 to 1.1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable debugging and send all emails to an attacker controlled address and then trigger a password reset for an administrator to gain access to an administrator account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5533 | Knowledge Base &amp;lt;= 2.3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5533</link><description>The Knowledge Base plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'kbalert' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5534 | ESV Bible Shortcode for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5534</link><description>The ESV Bible Shortcode for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'esv' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5536 | Freemind Viewer &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5536</link><description>The Freemind Viewer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'freemind' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5538 | BNS Featured Category &amp;lt;= 2.8.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5538</link><description>The BNS Featured Category plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'bnsfc' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5541 | Runners Log &amp;lt;= 3.9.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5541</link><description>The Runners Log plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'runnerslog' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5563 | WP-Addpub &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5563</link><description>The WP-Addpub plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'wp-addpub' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.8 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5565 | Hide It &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5565</link><description>The Hide It plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'hideit' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5586 | WordPress Ajax Load More and Infinite Scroll &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5586</link><description>The WordPress Ajax Load More and Infinite Scroll plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5686 | Paged Gallery &amp;lt;= 0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5686</link><description>The Paged Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gallery' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5699 | Developer Formatter &amp;lt;= 2015.0.2.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom CSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5699</link><description>The Developer Formatter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Custom CSS in all versions up to, and including, 2015.0.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5703 | StageShow &amp;lt;= 10.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via anchor Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5703</link><description>The StageShow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘anchor’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 10.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48902 | Vulnerability of uncontrolled system resource applications in the setting module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48902</link><description>Vulnerability of uncontrolled system resource applications in the setting module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48903 | Permission bypass vulnerability in the media library module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48903</link><description>Permission bypass vulnerability in the media library module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48904 | Vulnerability that cards can call unauthorized APIs in the FRS process
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect avai...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48904</link><description>Vulnerability that cards can call unauthorized APIs in the FRS process
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48905 | Wasm exception capture vulnerability in the arkweb v8 module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause the failure to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48905</link><description>Wasm exception capture vulnerability in the arkweb v8 module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause the failure to capture specific Wasm exception types.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48906 | Authentication bypass vulnerability in the DSoftBus module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48906</link><description>Authentication bypass vulnerability in the DSoftBus module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48907 | Deserialization vulnerability in the IPC module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48907</link><description>Deserialization vulnerability in the IPC module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5727 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Announcement Page announcement cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5727</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /script/academic/announcement of the component Announcement Page. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2921 | Short URL &amp;lt;= 1.6.8 - Subscriber+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2921</link><description>The Short URL WordPress plugin through 1.6.8 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in SQL statement, leading to a SQL injection exploitable by users with relatively low privilege on the site, like subscribers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5726 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Division System Page division-system cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5726</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /script/academic/division-system of the component Division System Page. The manipulation of the argument Division leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5724 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Subjects Page subjects cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5724</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /script/academic/subjects of the component Subjects Page. The manipulation of the argument Subject leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 05:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5725 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Grading System Page grading-system cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5725</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /script/academic/grading-system of the component Grading System Page. The manipulation of the argument Remark leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 05:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1777 | BM Content Builder &amp;lt;= 3.16.2.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via ux_cb_page_options_save</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1777</link><description>The BM Content Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data to a missing capability check on the 'ux_cb_page_options_save' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.16.2.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 05:36:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1778 | Art Theme &amp;lt;= 3.12.2.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Theme Option Delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1778</link><description>The Art Theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the 'arttheme_theme_option_restore' AJAX function in all versions up to, and including, 3.12.2.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to delete the theme option.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 05:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5723 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Classes Page classes cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5723</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /script/academic/classes of the component Classes Page. The manipulation of the argument Class Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 05:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36513 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in surveillance cameras provided by i-PRO Co., Ltd.. If a user views a crafted page while lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36513</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in surveillance cameras provided by i-PRO Co., Ltd.. If a user views a crafted page while logged in to the affected product, unintended operations may be performed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 04:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5722 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Add Academic Term terms cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5722</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /script/academic/terms of the component Add Academic Term. The manipulation of the argument Academic Term leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 04:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5721 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Profile Setting Page update_profile cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5721</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /script/academic/core/update_profile of the component Profile Setting Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 04:15:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5716 | SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5716</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5719 | The wallet has an authentication bypass vulnerability that allows access to specific pages.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5719</link><description>The wallet has an authentication bypass vulnerability that allows access to specific pages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5733 | Modern Events Calendar &amp;lt;= 7.21.9 - Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5733</link><description>The Modern Events Calendar Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 7.21.9. This is due improper or insufficient validation of the id property when exporting calendars. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46941 | SystemUI component protection settings vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46941</link><description>SystemUI has an incorrect component protection setting, which allows access to specific information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5714 | SoluçõesCoop iSoluçõesWEB Profile Information Update up.upload.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5714</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SoluçõesCoop iSoluçõesWEB up to 20250516. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /sys/up.upload.php of the component Profile Information Update. The manipulation of the argument nomeArquivo leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5715 | Signal App Biometric Authentication missing critical step in authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5715</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Signal App 7.41.4 on Android. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Biometric Authentication Handler. The manipulation leads to missing critical step in authentication. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5712 | SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5712</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /appointment.php. The manipulation of the argument patient leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5713 | SoluçõesCoop iSoluçõesWEB Flow fluxos-dashboard cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5713</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SoluçõesCoop iSoluçõesWEB up to 20250519 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /fluxos-dashboard of the component Flow Handler. The manipulation of the argument Descrição da solicitação leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5711 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System InsertCity.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5711</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /Admin/InsertCity.php. The manipulation of the argument cmbState leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22330 | IBM Security Verify Governance information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22330</link><description>IBM Security Verify Governance 10.0.2 does not require that users should have strong passwords by default, which makes it easier for attackers to compromise user accounts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56342 | IBM Verify Identity Access Digital Credentials information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56342</link><description>IBM Verify Identity Access Digital Credentials 24.06 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56343 | IBM Verify Identity Access Digital Credentials denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56343</link><description>IBM Verify Identity Access Digital Credentials 24.06 could allow an authenticated user to crash the service with a specially crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 01:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5709 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System InsertCategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5709</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Admin/InsertCategory.php. The manipulation of the argument txtCategoryName leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 01:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5710 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System InsertState.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5710</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Admin/InsertState.php. The manipulation of the argument txtStateName leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 01:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5708 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System NewsReport.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5708</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /Admin/NewsReport.php. The manipulation of the argument txtFrom leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 01:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5707 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System registered-user-testing.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5707</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /registered-user-testing.php. The manipulation of the argument testtype leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 01:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5706 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System new-user-testing.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5706</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /new-user-testing.php. The manipulation of the argument state leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 01:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5705 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System Property.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5705</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /Admin/Property.php. The manipulation of the argument cmbCat leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 23:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5704 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System User.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5704</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Admin/User.php. The manipulation of the argument txtUserName leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 23:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49012 | Himmelblau&amp;#x27;s Name-Based Group Matching in `pam_allow_groups` Leads to Potential Security Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49012</link><description>Himmelblau is an interoperability suite for Microsoft Azure Entra ID and Intune. Himmelblau versions 0.9.0 through 0.9.14 and 1.00-alpha are vulnerable to a privilege escalation issue when Entra ID group-based access restrictions are configured using group display names instead of object IDs. Starting in version 0.9.0, Himmelblau introduced support for specifying group names in the `pam_allow_groups` configuration option. However, Microsoft Entra ID permits the creation of multiple groups with the same `displayName` via the Microsoft Graph API—even by non-admin users, depending on tenant settings. As a result, a user could create a personal group with the same name as a legitimate access group (e.g., `"Allow-Linux-Login"`), add themselves to it, and be granted authentication or `sudo` rights by Himmelblau. Because affected Himmelblau versions compare group names by either `displayName` or by the immutable `objectId`, this allows bypassing access control mechanisms intended to restrict login to members of official, centrally-managed groups. This issue is fixed in Himmelblau version **0.9.15** and later. In these versions, group name matching in `pam_allow_groups` has been deprecated and removed, and only group `objectId`s (GUIDs) may be specified for secure group-based filtering. To mitigate the issue without upgrading, replace all entries in `pam_allow_groups` with the objectId of the target Entra ID group(s) and/or audit your tenant for groups with duplicate display names using the Microsoft Graph API.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 22:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5698 | Brilliance Golden Link Secondary System logSelect.htm sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5698</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Brilliance Golden Link Secondary System up to 20250424. Affected is an unknown function of the file /sysframework/logSelect.htm. The manipulation of the argument nodename leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 22:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5696 | Brilliance Golden Link Secondary System rentChangeCheckInfoPage.htm sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5696</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Brilliance Golden Link Secondary System up to 20250424. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /storagework/rentChangeCheckInfoPage.htm. The manipulation of the argument clientname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 21:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5697 | Brilliance Golden Link Secondary System tcCustDeferPosiQuery.htm sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5697</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Brilliance Golden Link Secondary System up to 20250424. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /reprotframework/tcCustDeferPosiQuery.htm. The manipulation of the argument custTradeId leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 21:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5695 | FLIR AX8 Backend subscriptions.php subscribe_to_alarm command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5695</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in FLIR AX8 up to 1.46.16. This affects the function subscribe_to_spot/subscribe_to_delta/subscribe_to_alarm of the file /usr/www/application/models/subscriptions.php of the component Backend. The manipulation leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.55.16 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 21:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47966 | Power Automate Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47966</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 21:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48133 | WordPress Uncanny Automator &amp;lt;= 6.4.0.2 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48133</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Uncanny Automator allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Uncanny Automator: from n/a through 6.4.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 21:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5694 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System search-report-result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5694</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /search-report-result.php. The manipulation of the argument serachdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5685 | Tenda CH22 Natlimit formNatlimit stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5685</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda CH22 1.0.0.1. This affects the function formNatlimit of the file /goform/Natlimit. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5693 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System bwdates-report-result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5693</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /bwdates-report-result.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43026 | HP Support Assistant – Potential Escalation of Privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43026</link><description>A potential security vulnerability has been identified in the HP Support Assistant for versions prior to 9.44.18.0. The vulnerability could potentially allow a local attacker to escalate privileges via an arbitrary file write.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5680 | Shenzhen Dashi Tongzhou Information Technology AgileBPM Groovy Script SysScriptController.java executeScript deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5680</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Shenzhen Dashi Tongzhou Information Technology AgileBPM up to 2.5.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function executeScript of the file /src/main/java/com/dstz/sys/rest/controller/SysScriptController.java of the component Groovy Script Handler. The manipulation of the argument script leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5745 | The strncmp implementation optimized for the Power10 processor in the GNU C Library version 2.40 and later writes to vector registers v20 to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5745</link><description>The strncmp implementation optimized for the Power10 processor in the GNU C Library version 2.40 and later writes to vector registers v20 to v31 without saving contents from the caller (those registers are defined as non-volatile registers by the powerpc64le ABI), resulting in overwriting of its contents and potentially altering control flow of the caller, or leaking the input strings to the function to other parts of the program.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5677 | Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5677</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_application. The manipulation of the argument position_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5679 | Shenzhen Dashi Tongzhou Information Technology AgileBPM SysToolsController.java parseStrByFreeMarker deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5679</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Shenzhen Dashi Tongzhou Information Technology AgileBPM up to 2.5.0. Affected is the function parseStrByFreeMarker of the file /src/main/java/com/dstz/sys/rest/controller/SysToolsController.java. The manipulation of the argument str leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5674 | code-projects Patient Record Management System urinalysis_form.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5674</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file urinalysis_form.php. The manipulation of the argument urinalysis_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5675 | Campcodes Online Teacher Record Management System bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5675</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Teacher Record Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /trms/admin/bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5676 | Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5676</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=login. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5702 | The strcmp implementation optimized for the Power10 processor in the GNU C Library version 2.39 and later writes to vector registers v20 to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5702</link><description>The strcmp implementation optimized for the Power10 processor in the GNU C Library version 2.39 and later writes to vector registers v20 to v31 without saving contents from the caller (those registers are defined as non-volatile registers by the powerpc64le ABI), resulting in overwriting of its contents and potentially altering control flow of the caller, or leaking the input strings to the function to other parts of the program.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46257 | WordPress Element Pack Pro Plugin &amp;lt; 8.0.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46257</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in BdThemes Element Pack Pro allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Element Pack Pro: from n/a before 8.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46258 | WordPress Element Pack Pro Plugin &amp;lt; 8.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46258</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BdThemes Element Pack Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Element Pack Pro: from n/a before 8.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5671 | TOTOLINK N302R Plus HTTP POST Request formPortFw buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5671</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK N302R Plus up to 3.4.0-B20201028. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formPortFw of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument service_type leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5672 | TOTOLINK N302R Plus HTTP POST Request formFilter buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5672</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK N302R Plus up to 3.4.0-B20201028 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formFilter of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5670 | PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System manage-card.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5670</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/manage-card.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:10:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49009 | Para Inserts Sensitive Information into Log File for Facebook authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49009</link><description>Para is a multitenant backend server/framework for object persistence and retrieval. A vulnerability that exists in versions prior to 1.50.8 in `FacebookAuthFilter.java` results in a full request URL being logged during a failed request to a Facebook user profile. The log includes the user's access token in plain text. Since WARN-level logs are often retained in production and accessible to operators or log aggregation systems, this poses a risk of token exposure. Version 1.50.8 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48493 | Yii 2 Redis may expose AUTH paramters in logs in case of connection failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48493</link><description>The Yii 2 Redis extension provides the redis key-value store support for the Yii framework 2.0. On failing connection, the extension writes commands sequence to logs. Prior to version 2.0.20, AUTH parameters are written in plain text exposing username and password. That might be an issue if attacker has access to logs. Version 2.0.20 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5668 | PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System readenq.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5668</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/readenq.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5669 | PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System unreadenq.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5669</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/unreadenq.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5667 | FreeFloat FTP Server REIN Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5667</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component REIN Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5666 | FreeFloat FTP Server XMKD Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5666</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component XMKD Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 15:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5665 | FreeFloat FTP Server XCWD Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5665</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the component XCWD Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 15:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5664 | FreeFloat FTP Server RESTART Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5664</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component RESTART Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 14:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5663 | PHPGurukul Auto Taxi Stand Management System search-autoortaxi.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5663</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Auto Taxi Stand Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/search-autoortaxi.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 14:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47827 | In IGEL OS before 11, Secure Boot can be bypassed because the igel-flash-driver module improperly verifies a cryptographic signature. Ultima...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47827</link><description>In IGEL OS before 11, Secure Boot can be bypassed because the igel-flash-driver module improperly verifies a cryptographic signature. Ultimately, a crafted root filesystem can be mounted from an unverified SquashFS image.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 14:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0691 | Improper access control in permissions component in Devolutions Server 2025.1.10.0 and earlier allows an authenticated user to bypass the "E...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0691</link><description>Improper access control in permissions component in Devolutions Server 2025.1.10.0 and earlier allows an authenticated user to bypass the "Edit permission" permission by bypassing the client side validation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:56:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3768 | Improper access control in Tor network blocking feature in Devolutions Server 2025.1.10.0 and earlier allows an authenticated user to bypass...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3768</link><description>Improper access control in Tor network blocking feature in Devolutions Server 2025.1.10.0 and earlier allows an authenticated user to bypass the tor blocking feature when the Devolutions hosted endpoint is not reachable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5382 | Improper access control in users MFA feature in Devolutions Server 2025.1.7.0 and earlier allows a user with user management permission to r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5382</link><description>Improper access control in users MFA feature in Devolutions Server 2025.1.7.0 and earlier allows a user with user management permission to remove or change administrators MFA.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5661 | code-projects Traffic Offense Reporting System Setting save-settings.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5661</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in code-projects Traffic Offense Reporting System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /save-settings.php of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation of the argument site_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27445 | Extension - rsjoomla.com - A path traversal vulnerability RSFirewall component 2.9.7 - 3.1.5 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27445</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in RSFirewall component 2.9.7 - 3.1.5 for Joomla was discovered. This vulnerability allows authenticated users to read arbitrary files outside the Joomla root directory. The flaw is caused by insufficient sanitization of user-supplied input in file path parameters, allowing attackers to exploit directory traversal sequences (e.g., ../) to access sensitive files</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27753 | Extension - rsjoomla.com - A SQLi vulnerability RSMediaGallery component 1.7.4 - 2.1.6 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27753</link><description>A SQLi vulnerability in RSMediaGallery component 1.7.4 - 2.1.6 for Joomla was discovered. The vulnerability is due to the use of unescaped user-supplied parameters in SQL queries within the dashboard component. This allows an authenticated attacker to inject malicious SQL code through unsanitized input fields, which are used directly in SQL queries. Exploiting this flaw can lead to unauthorized database access, data leakage, or modification of records.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27754 | Extension - rsjoomla.com - A stored XSS vulnerability RSBlog! component 1.11.6 - 1.14.4 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27754</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability in RSBlog! component 1.11.6 - 1.14.4 for Joomla was discovered. The vulnerability allows authenticated users to inject malicious JavaScript into the plugin's resource. The injected payload is stored by the application and later executed when other users view the affected content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30084 | Extension - rsjoomla.com - A reflected XSS vulnerability RSMail! component 3.0.0 - 3.3.13 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30084</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability in RSMail! component 1.19.20 - 1.22.26 for Joomla was discovered. The issue occurs within the dashboard  component, where user-supplied input is not properly sanitized before being stored and rendered. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript code into text fields or other input points, which is subsequently executed in the browser of any user who clicks on the crafted text in the dashboard.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5659 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5659</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /user/profile.php. The manipulation of the argument pincode leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5660 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System register-complaint.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5660</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/register-complaint.php. The manipulation of the argument noc leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5658 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System updatecomplaint.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5658</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/updatecomplaint.php. The manipulation of the argument Status leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 12:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2011-10007 | File::Find::Rule through 0.34 for Perl is vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Execution when `grep()` encounters a crafted file name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2011-10007</link><description>File::Find::Rule through 0.34 for Perl is vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Execution when `grep()` encounters a crafted filename.

A file handle is opened with the 2 argument form of `open()` allowing an attacker controlled filename to provide the MODE parameter to `open()`, turning the filename into a command to be executed.

Example:

$ mkdir /tmp/poc; echo &gt; "/tmp/poc/|id"
$ perl -MFile::Find::Rule \
    -E 'File::Find::Rule-&gt;grep("foo")-&gt;in("/tmp/poc")'
uid=1000(user) gid=1000(user) groups=1000(user),100(users)</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 12:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5657 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System manage-users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5657</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/manage-users.php. The manipulation of the argument uid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 12:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5656 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System edit-category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5656</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit-category.php. The manipulation of the argument description leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5341 | Forminator &amp;lt;= 1.44.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via id and data-size Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5341</link><description>The Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp; Custom Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id' and 'data-size’ parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.44.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5701 | HyperComments &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Unauthenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5701</link><description>The HyperComments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the hc_request_handler function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5654 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System edit-state.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5654</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-state.php. The manipulation of the argument description leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5655 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System edit-subcategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5655</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit-subcategory.php. The manipulation of the argument subcategory leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5653 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System between-date-userreport.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5653</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/between-date-userreport.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4568 | SQL Injection in 2ClickPortal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4568</link><description>Improper neutralization of input provided by an unauthorized user into changes__reference_id parameter in URL allows for boolean-based Blind SQL Injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5651 | code-projects Traffic Offense Reporting System saveuser.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5651</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Traffic Offense Reporting System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file saveuser.php. The manipulation of the argument user_id/username/email/name/position leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5652 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System between-date-complaintreport.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5652</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/between-date-complaintreport.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:24:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5650 | 1000projects Online Notice Board register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5650</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in 1000projects Online Notice Board 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /register.php. The manipulation of the argument fname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 09:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5648 | Radare2 radiff2 pal.c r_cons_pal_init memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5648</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Radare2 5.9.9. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function r_cons_pal_init in the library /libr/cons/pal.c of the component radiff2. The manipulation of the argument -T leads to memory corruption. An attack has to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The name of the patch is 5705d99cc1f23f36f9a84aab26d1724010b97798. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The documentation explains that the parameter -T is experimental and "crashy". Further analysis has shown "the race is not a real problem unless you use asan". A new warning has been added.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 09:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5649 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Register Interface new_user access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5649</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/core/new_user of the component Register Interface. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 09:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5647 | Radare2 radiff2 cons.c r_cons_context_break_pop memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5647</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Radare2 5.9.9 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function r_cons_context_break_pop in the library /libr/cons/cons.c of the component radiff2. The manipulation of the argument -T leads to memory corruption. The attack needs to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The patch is named 5705d99cc1f23f36f9a84aab26d1724010b97798. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The documentation explains that the parameter -T is experimental and "crashy". Further analysis has shown "the race is not a real problem unless you use asan". A new warning has been added.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 08:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5646 | Radare2 radiff2 pal.c r_cons_rainbow_free memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5646</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Radare2 5.9.9 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function r_cons_rainbow_free in the library /libr/cons/pal.c of the component radiff2. The manipulation of the argument -T leads to memory corruption. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The patch is identified as 5705d99cc1f23f36f9a84aab26d1724010b97798. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The documentation explains that the parameter -T is experimental and "crashy". Further analysis has shown "the race is not a real problem unless you use asan". A new warning has been added.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 08:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5645 | Radare2 radiff2 pal.c r_cons_pal_init memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5645</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Radare2 5.9.9. This affects the function r_cons_pal_init in the library /libr/cons/pal.c of the component radiff2. The manipulation of the argument -T leads to memory corruption. Attacking locally is a requirement. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The identifier of the patch is 5705d99cc1f23f36f9a84aab26d1724010b97798. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The documentation explains that the parameter -T is experimental and "crashy". Further analysis has shown "the race is not a real problem unless you use asan". A new warning has been added.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 07:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5643 | Radare2 radiff2 cons.c cons_stack_load memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5643</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Radare2 5.9.9. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cons_stack_load in the library /libr/cons/cons.c of the component radiff2. The manipulation of the argument -T leads to memory corruption. An attack has to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The patch is named 5705d99cc1f23f36f9a84aab26d1724010b97798. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The documentation explains that the parameter -T is experimental and "crashy". Further analysis has shown "the race is not a real problem unless you use asan". A new warning has been added.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 07:19:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5644 | Radare2 radiff2 cons.c r_cons_flush use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5644</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Radare2 5.9.9. Affected by this issue is the function r_cons_flush in the library /libr/cons/cons.c of the component radiff2. The manipulation of the argument -T leads to use after free. Local access is required to approach this attack. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The name of the patch is 5705d99cc1f23f36f9a84aab26d1724010b97798. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The documentation explains that the parameter -T is experimental and "crashy". Further analysis has shown "the race is not a real problem unless you use asan". A new warning has been added.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 07:19:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5641 | Radare2 radiff2 cons.c r_cons_is_breaked memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5641</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Radare2 5.9.9. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function r_cons_is_breaked in the library /libr/cons/cons.c of the component radiff2. The manipulation of the argument -T leads to memory corruption. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The identifier of the patch is 5705d99cc1f23f36f9a84aab26d1724010b97798. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The documentation explains that the parameter -T is experimental and "crashy". Further analysis has shown "the race is not a real problem unless you use asan". An additional warning regarding threading support has been added.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 06:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5642 | Radare2 radiff2 pal.c r_cons_pal_init memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5642</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Radare2 5.9.9. Affected is the function r_cons_pal_init in the library /libr/cons/pal.c of the component radiff2. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack needs to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The patch is identified as 5705d99cc1f23f36f9a84aab26d1724010b97798. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The documentation explains that the parameter -T is experimental and "crashy". Further analysis has shown "the race is not a real problem unless you use asan". A new warning has been added.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 06:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5640 | PX4-Autopilot TRAJECTORY_REPRESENTATION_WAYPOINTS Message mavlink_receiver.cpp stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5640</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PX4-Autopilot 1.12.3. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function MavlinkReceiver::handle_message_trajectory_representation_waypoints of the file mavlink_receiver.cpp of the component TRAJECTORY_REPRESENTATION_WAYPOINTS Message Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 06:15:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3054 | WP User Frontend Pro &amp;lt;= 4.1.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3054</link><description>The WP User Frontend Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the upload_files() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. Please note that this requires the 'Private Message' module to be enabled and the Business version of the PRO software to be in use.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3055 | WP User Frontend Pro &amp;lt;= 4.1.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3055</link><description>The WP User Frontend Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the delete_avatar_ajax() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5639 | PHPGurukul Notice Board System forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5639</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Notice Board System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5683 | When loading a specifically crafted ICNS format image file in QImage then it will trigger a crash. This issue affects Qt from versions 6.3.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5683</link><description>When loading a specifically crafted ICNS format image file in QImage then it will trigger a crash. This issue affects Qt from versions 6.3.0 through 6.5.9, from 6.6.0 through 6.8.4, 6.9.0. This is fixed in 6.5.10, 6.8.5 and 6.9.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5638 | PHPGurukul Notice Board System admin-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5638</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Notice Board System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1793 | SQL Injection in run-llama/llama_index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1793</link><description>Multiple vector store integrations in run-llama/llama_index version v0.12.21 have SQL injection vulnerabilities. These vulnerabilities allow an attacker to read and write data using SQL, potentially leading to unauthorized access to data of other users depending on the usage of the llama-index library in a web application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5636 | PCMan FTP Server SET Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5636</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PCMan FTP Server 2.0.7. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component SET Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 04:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5637 | PCMan FTP Server SYSTEM Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5637</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PCMan FTP Server 2.0.7. Affected is an unknown function of the component SYSTEM Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 04:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5634 | PCMan FTP Server NOOP Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5634</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PCMan FTP Server 2.0.7. This affects an unknown part of the component NOOP Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 04:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5635 | PCMan FTP Server PLS Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5635</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PCMan FTP Server 2.0.7. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component PLS Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 04:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5633 | code-projects/anirbandutta9 Content Management System/News-Buzz users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5633</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects/anirbandutta9 Content Management System and News-Buzz 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/users.php. The manipulation of the argument delete leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 03:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5632 | code-projects/anirbandutta9 Content Management System/News-Buzz users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5632</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects/anirbandutta9 Content Management System and News-Buzz 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/users.php. The manipulation of the argument change_to_admin leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 03:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49466 | aerc before 93bec0d allows directory traversal in commands/msgview/open.go because of direct path concatenation of the name of an attachment...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49466</link><description>aerc before 93bec0d allows directory traversal in commands/msgview/open.go because of direct path concatenation of the name of an attachment part,</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 03:09:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5631 | code-projects/anirbandutta9 Content Management System/News-Buzz publicposts.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5631</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects/anirbandutta9 Content Management System and News-Buzz 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /publicposts.php. The manipulation of the argument post leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 03:09:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48432 | An issue was discovered in Django 5.2 before 5.2.2, 5.1 before 5.1.10, and 4.2 before 4.2.22. Internal HTTP response logging does not escape...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48432</link><description>An issue was discovered in Django 5.2 before 5.2.2, 5.1 before 5.1.10, and 4.2 before 4.2.22. Internal HTTP response logging does not escape request.path, which allows remote attackers to potentially manipulate log output via crafted URLs. This may lead to log injection or forgery when logs are viewed in terminals or processed by external systems.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 03:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5629 | Tenda AC10 HTTP SetPptpServerCfg formSetPPTPServer buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5629</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda AC10 up to 15.03.06.47. This affects the function formSetPPTPServer of the file /goform/SetPptpServerCfg of the component HTTP Handler. The manipulation of the argument startIp/endIp leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 03:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5630 | D-Link DIR-816 form2lansetup.cgi stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5630</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-816 1.10CNB05 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/form2lansetup.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 03:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5628 | SourceCodester Food Menu Manager Add Menu index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5628</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Food Menu Manager 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php of the component Add Menu Handler. The manipulation of the argument name/description leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 01:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5626 | Campcodes Online Teacher Record Management System edit-subjects-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5626</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Online Teacher Record Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit-subjects-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 01:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5627 | code-projects Patient Record Management System sputum_form.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5627</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /sputum_form.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 01:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49008 | Atheos Improper Input Validation Vulnerability Enables RCE in Common.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49008</link><description>Atheos is a self-hosted browser-based cloud integrated development environment. Prior to version 6.0.4, improper use of `escapeshellcmd()` in `/components/codegit/traits/execute.php` allows argument injection, leading to arbitrary command execution. Atheos administrators and users of vulnerable versions are at risk of data breaches or server compromise. Version 6.0.4 introduces a `Common::safe_execute` function that sanitizes all arguments using `escapeshellarg()` prior to execution and migrated all components potentially vulnerable to similar exploits to use this new templated execution system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 01:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5624 | D-Link DIR-816 QoSPortSetup stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5624</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-816 1.10CNB05. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function QoSPortSetup of the file /goform/QoSPortSetup. The manipulation of the argument port0_group/port0_remarker/ssid0_group/ssid0_remarker leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 01:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5625 | Campcodes Online Teacher Record Management System search-teacher.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5625</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Teacher Record Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /search-teacher.php. The manipulation of the argument searchteacher leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 01:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5622 | D-Link DIR-816 wirelessApcli_5g stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5622</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-816 1.10CNB05 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function wirelessApcli_5g of the file /goform/wirelessApcli_5g. The manipulation of the argument apcli_mode_5g/apcli_enc_5g/apcli_default_key_5g leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 01:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5623 | D-Link DIR-816 qosClassifier stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5623</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-816 1.10CNB05. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function qosClassifier of the file /goform/qosClassifier. The manipulation of the argument dip_address/sip_address leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 01:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>