<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:02:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-55462 | A CORS misconfiguration in Eramba Community and Enterprise Editions v3.26.0 allows an attacker-controlled Origin header to be reflected in t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55462</link><description>A CORS misconfiguration in Eramba Community and Enterprise Editions v3.26.0 allows an attacker-controlled Origin header to be reflected in the Access-Control-Allow-Origin response along with Access-Control-Allow-Credentials: true. This permits malicious third-party websites to perform authenticated cross-origin requests against the Eramba API, including endpoints like /system-api/login and /system-api/user/me. The response includes sensitive user session data (ID, name, email, access groups), which is accessible to the attacker's JavaScript. This flaw enables full session hijack and data exfiltration without user interaction. Eramba versions 3.23.3 and earlier were tested and appear unaffected. The vulnerability is present in default installations, requiring no custom configuration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:02:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13444 | OS Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability in Progress LoadMaster</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13444</link><description>OS Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability in API in Progress LoadMaster allows an authenticated attacker with “User Administration” permissions to execute arbitrary commands on the LoadMaster appliance by exploiting unsanitized input in the API input parameters</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13447 | OS Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability in Progress LoadMaster</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13447</link><description>OS Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability in API in Progress LoadMaster allows an authenticated attacker with “User Administration” permissions to execute arbitrary commands on the LoadMaster appliance by exploiting unsanitized input in the API input parameters</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11669 | Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11669</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine PAM360 versions before 8202; Password Manager Pro versions before 13221; Access Manager Plus versions prior to 4401 are vulnerable to an authorization issue in the initiate remote session functionality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11250 | Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11250</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADSelfService Plus versions before 6519 are vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to improper filter configurations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14507 | EventPrime - Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets &amp;lt;= 4.2.7.0 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14507</link><description>The EventPrime - Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.7.0 via the REST API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive booking data including user names, email addresses, ticket details, payment information, and order keys when the API is enabled by an administrator. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 4.2.7.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9427 | Admin reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9427</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Lemonsoft WordPress add on allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects WordPress add on: 2025.7.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0684 | CP Image Store with Slideshow &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Product Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0684</link><description>The CP Image Store with Slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.9 due to a logic error in the 'cpis_admin_init' function's permission check. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to import arbitrary products via XML, if the XML file has already been uploaded to the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0877 | Mitigation bypass in the DOM: Security component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0877</link><description>Mitigation bypass in the DOM: Security component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.32, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0878 | Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: CanvasWebGL component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0878</link><description>Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: CanvasWebGL component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0879 | Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0879</link><description>Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.32, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0880 | Sandbox escape due to integer overflow in the Graphics component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0880</link><description>Sandbox escape due to integer overflow in the Graphics component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.32, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0881 | Sandbox escape in the Messaging System component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0881</link><description>Sandbox escape in the Messaging System component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0882 | Use-after-free in the IPC component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0882</link><description>Use-after-free in the IPC component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.32, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0883 | Information disclosure in the Networking component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0883</link><description>Information disclosure in the Networking component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0884 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0884</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0885 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript: GC component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0885</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript: GC component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0886 | Incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0886</link><description>Incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.32, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0887 | Clickjacking issue, information disclosure in the PDF Viewer component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0887</link><description>Clickjacking issue, information disclosure in the PDF Viewer component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0888 | Information disclosure in the XML component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0888</link><description>Information disclosure in the XML component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0889 | Denial-of-service in the DOM: Service Workers component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0889</link><description>Denial-of-service in the DOM: Service Workers component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0890 | Spoofing issue in the DOM: Copy &amp;amp; Paste and Drag &amp;amp; Drop component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0890</link><description>Spoofing issue in the DOM: Copy &amp; Paste and Drag &amp; Drop component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0891 | Memory safety bugs fixed in Firefox ESR 140.7, Thunderbird ESR 140.7, Firefox 147 and Thunderbird 147</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0891</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox ESR 140.6, Thunderbird ESR 140.6, Firefox 146 and Thunderbird 146. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0892 | Memory safety bugs fixed in Firefox 147 and Thunderbird 147</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0892</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 146 and Thunderbird 146. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9435 | Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9435</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADManager Plus versions below 7230 are vulnerable to Path Traversal in the User Management module</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13774 | SQL injection leading to privilege escalation in Progress Flowmon ADS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13774</link><description>A vulnerability exists in Progress Flowmon ADS versions prior to 12.5.4 and 13.0.1 where an SQL injection vulnerability allows authenticated users to execute unintended SQL queries and commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59020 | TYPO3 CMS Allows Broken Access Control in Edit Document Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59020</link><description>By exploiting the defVals parameter, attackers could bypass field‑level access checks during record creation in the TYPO3 backend. This gave them the ability to insert arbitrary data into prohibited exclude fields of a database table for which the user already has write permission for a reduced set of fields. This issue affects TYPO3 CMS versions 10.0.0-10.4.54, 11.0.0-11.5.48, 12.0.0-12.4.40, 13.0.0-13.4.22 and 14.0.0-14.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59021 | TYPO3 CMS Allows Broken Access Control in Redirects Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59021</link><description>Backend users with access to the redirects module and write permission on the sys_redirect table were able to read, create, and modify any redirect record without restriction to the user’s own file-mounts or web-mounts. This allowed attackers to insert or alter redirects pointing to arbitrary URLs – facilitating phishing or other malicious redirect attacks. This issue affects TYPO3 CMS versions 10.0.0-10.4.54, 11.0.0-11.5.48, 12.0.0-12.4.40, 13.0.0-13.4.22 and 14.0.0-14.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59022 | TYPO3 CMS Allows Broken Access Control in Recycler Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59022</link><description>Backend users who had access to the recycler module could delete arbitrary data from any database table defined in the TCA - regardless of whether they had permission to that particular table. This allowed attackers to purge and destroy critical site data, effectively rendering the website unavailable. This issue affects TYPO3 CMS versions 10.0.0-10.4.54, 11.0.0-11.5.48, 12.0.0-12.4.40, 13.0.0-13.4.22 and 14.0.0-14.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0859 | TYPO3 CMS Allows Insecure Deserialization via Mailer File Spool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0859</link><description>TYPO3's mail‑file spool deserialization flaw lets local users with write access to the spool directory craft a malicious file that is deserialized during the mailer:spool:send command, enabling arbitrary PHP code execution on the web server. This issue affects TYPO3 CMS versions 10.0.0-10.4.54, 11.0.0-11.5.48, 12.0.0-12.4.40, 13.0.0-13.4.22 and 14.0.0-14.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14001 | WP Duplicate Page &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Post Duplication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14001</link><description>The WP Duplicate Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to missing capability checks on the 'duplicateBulkHandle' and 'duplicateBulkHandleHPOS' functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to duplicate arbitrary posts, pages, and WooCommerce HPOS orders even when their role is explicitly excluded from the plugin's "Allowed User Roles" setting, potentially exposing sensitive information and allowing duplicate fulfillment of WooCommerce orders.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40805 | Affected devices do not properly enforce user authentication on specific API endpoints. This could facilitate an unauthenticated remote atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40805</link><description>Affected devices do not properly enforce user authentication on specific API endpoints. This could facilitate an unauthenticated remote attacker to circumvent authentication and impersonate a legitimate user. Successful exploitation requires that the attacker has learned the identity of a legitimate user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40942 | A vulnerability has been identified in TeleControl Server Basic (All versions &lt; V3.1.2.4). Affected application contains a local privilege e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40942</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in TeleControl Server Basic (All versions &lt; V3.1.2.4). Affected application contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability that could allow an attacker to run arbitrary code with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40944 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC ET 200AL IM 157-1 PN (6ES7157-1AB00-0AB0) (All versions), SIMATIC ET 200MP IM 155-5 PN HF (6E...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40944</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC ET 200AL IM 157-1 PN (6ES7157-1AB00-0AB0) (All versions), SIMATIC ET 200MP IM 155-5 PN HF (6ES7155-5AA00-0AC0) (All versions &gt;= V4.2.0), SIMATIC ET 200SP IM 155-6 MF HF (6ES7155-6MU00-0CN0) (All versions), SIMATIC ET 200SP IM 155-6 PN HA (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V1.3), SIMATIC ET 200SP IM 155-6 PN R1 (6ES7155-6AU00-0HM0) (All versions &lt; V6.0.1), SIMATIC ET 200SP IM 155-6 PN/2 HF (6ES7155-6AU01-0CN0) (All versions &gt;= V4.2.0), SIMATIC ET 200SP IM 155-6 PN/3 HF (6ES7155-6AU30-0CN0) (All versions &lt; V4.2.2), SIMATIC PN/MF Coupler (6ES7158-3MU10-0XA0) (All versions), SIMATIC PN/PN Coupler (6ES7158-3AD10-0XA0) (All versions &lt; V6.0.0), SIPLUS ET 200MP IM 155-5 PN HF (6AG1155-5AA00-2AC0) (All versions &gt;= V4.2.0), SIPLUS ET 200MP IM 155-5 PN HF (6AG1155-5AA00-7AC0) (All versions &gt;= V4.2.0), SIPLUS ET 200MP IM 155-5 PN HF T1 RAIL (6AG2155-5AA00-1AC0) (All versions &gt;= V4.2.0), SIPLUS ET 200SP IM 155-6 PN HF (6AG1155-6AU01-2CN0) (All versions &gt;= V4.2.0), SIPLUS ET 200SP IM 155-6 PN HF (6AG1155-6AU01-7CN0) (All versions &gt;= V4.2.0), SIPLUS ET 200SP IM 155-6 PN HF T1 RAIL (6AG2155-6AU01-1CN0) (All versions &gt;= V4.2.0), SIPLUS ET 200SP IM 155-6 PN HF TX RAIL (6AG2155-6AU01-4CN0) (All versions &gt;= V4.2.0), SIPLUS NET PN/PN Coupler (6AG2158-3AD10-4XA0) (All versions &lt; V6.0.0). Affected devices do not properly handle S7 protocol session disconnect requests. When receiving a valid S7 protocol Disconnect Request (COTP DR TPDU) on TCP port 102, the devices enter an improper session state.

This could allow an attacker to cause the device to become unresponsive, leading to a denial-of-service condition that requires a power cycle to restore normal operation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41717 | Config-Upload Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41717</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can trick a high privileged user into uploading a malicious payload via the config-upload endpoint, leading to code injection as root. This results in a total loss of confidentiality, availability and integrity due to improper control of code generation ('Code Injection’).</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10915 | Dreamer Blog &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10915</link><description>The Dreamer Blog WordPress theme through 1.2 is vulnerable to arbitrary  installations due to a missing capability check.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:48:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14829 | e-xact-hosted-payment &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14829</link><description>The E-xact | Hosted Payment | WordPress plugin through 2.0 is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files on the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:48:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66176 | There is a Stack overflow Vulnerability in the device Search and Discovery feature of Hikvision Access Control Products. If exploited, an at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66176</link><description>There is a Stack overflow Vulnerability in the device Search and Discovery feature of Hikvision Access Control Products. If exploited, an attacker on the same local area network (LAN) could cause the device to malfunction by sending specially crafted packets to an unpatched device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66177 | There is a Stack overflow Vulnerability in the device Search and Discovery feature of Hikvision NVR/DVR/CVR/IPC models. If exploited, an att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66177</link><description>There is a Stack overflow Vulnerability in the device Search and Discovery feature of Hikvision NVR/DVR/CVR/IPC models. If exploited, an attacker on the same local area network (LAN) could cause the device to malfunction by sending specially crafted packets to an unpatched device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0491 | Code Injection vulnerability in SAP Landscape Transformation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0491</link><description>SAP Landscape Transformation allows an attacker with admin privileges to exploit a vulnerability in the function module exposed via RFC. This flaw enables the injection of arbitrary ABAP code/OS commands into the system, bypassing essential authorization checks. This vulnerability effectively functions as a backdoor, creating the risk of full system compromise, undermining the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0492 | Privilege escalation vulnerability in SAP HANA database</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0492</link><description>SAP HANA database is vulnerable to privilege escalation allowing an attacker with valid credentials of any user to switch to another user potentially gaining administrative access. This exploit could result in a total compromise of the system�s confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0493 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SAP Fiori App (Intercompany Balance Reconciliation)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0493</link><description>Due to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SAP Fiori App Intercompany Balance Reconciliation an attacker could execute state?changing actions using an inappropriate request type, this deviation from expected request semantics may allow an attacker to trigger unintended actions on behalf of an authenticated user causing low impact on integrity of the system. This has no impact on confidentiality and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0494 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP Fiori App (Intercompany Balance Reconciliation)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0494</link><description>Under certain conditions SAP Fiori App Intercompany Balance Reconciliation application allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted. This has low impact on confidentiality of the application, integrity and availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0495 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP Fiori App (Intercompany Balance Reconciliation)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0495</link><description>SAP Fiori App Intercompany Balance Reconciliation allows an attacker with high privileges  to send uploaded files to arbitrary emails which could enable effective phishing campaigns. This has low impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0496 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP Fiori App (Intercompany Balance Reconciliation)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0496</link><description>SAP Fiori App Intercompany Balance Reconciliation allows an attacker with high privileges  to upload any file (including script files) without proper file format validation. This has low impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0497 | Missing Authorization check in Business Server Pages Application (Product Designer Web UI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0497</link><description>SAP Product Designer Web UI of Business Server Pages allows authenticated non-administrative users to access non-sensitive information. This results in a low impact on confidentiality, with no impact on integrity or availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0498 | Code Injection vulnerability in SAP S/4HANA (Private Cloud and On-Premise)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0498</link><description>SAP S/4HANA (Private Cloud and On-Premise) allows an attacker with admin privileges to exploit a vulnerability in the function module exposed via RFC. This flaw enables the injection of arbitrary ABAP code/OS commands into the system, bypassing essential authorization checks. This vulnerability effectively functions as a backdoor, creating the risk of full system compromise, undermining the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0499 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Enterprise Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0499</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Enterprise Portal allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject malicious scripts into a URL parameter. The scripts are reflected in the server response and executed in a user's browser when the crafted URL is visited, leading to theft of session information, manipulation of portal content, or user redirection, resulting in a low impact on the application's confidentiality and integrity, with no impact on availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0500 | Remote code execution in SAP Wily Introscope Enterprise Manager (WorkStation)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0500</link><description>Due to the usage of vulnerable third party component in SAP Wily Introscope Enterprise Manager (WorkStation), an unauthenticated attacker could create a malicious JNLP (Java Network Launch Protocol) file accessible by a public facing URL. When a victim clicks on the URL the accessed Wily Introscope Server could execute OS commands on the victim's machine. This could completely compromising confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0501 | SQL Injection Vulnerability in SAP S/4HANA Private Cloud and On-Premise (Financials � General Ledger)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0501</link><description>Due to insufficient input validation in SAP S/4HANA Private Cloud and On-Premise (Financials General Ledger), an authenticated user could execute crafted SQL queries to read, modify, and delete backend database data. This leads to a high impact on the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0503 | Missing Authorization check in in SAP ERP Central Component and SAP S/4HANA (SAP EHS Management)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0503</link><description>Due to missing authorization check in the SAP ERP Central Component (SAP ECC) and SAP S/4HANA (SAP EHS Management), an attacker could extract hardcoded clear-text credentials and bypass the password authentication check by manipulating user parameters. Upon successful exploitation, the attacker can access, modify or delete certain change pointer information within EHS objects in the application which might further affect the subsequent systems. This vulnerability leads to a low impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application with no affect on the availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0504 | Insufficient Input Handling in JNDI Operations of SAP Identity Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0504</link><description>Due to insufficient input handling, the SAP Identity Management REST interface allows an authenticated administrator to submit specially crafted malicious REST requests that are processed by JNDI operations without adequate input neutralization. This may lead to limited disclosure or modification of data, resulting in low impact on confidentiality and integrity, with no impact on application availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0506 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0506</link><description>Due to a Missing Authorization Check vulnerability in Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform, an authenticated attacker could misuse an RFC function to execute form routines (FORMs) in the ABAP system. Successful exploitation could allow the attacker to write or modify data accessible via FORMs and invoke system functionality exposed via FORMs, resulting in a high impact on integrity and availability, while confidentiality remains unaffected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0507 | OS Command Injection vulnerability in SAP Application Server for ABAP and SAP NetWeaver RFCSDK</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0507</link><description>Due to an OS Command Injection vulnerability in SAP Application Server for ABAP and SAP NetWeaver RFCSDK, an authenticated attacker with administrative access and adjacent network access could upload specially crafted content to the server. If processed by the application, this content enables execution of arbitrary operating system commands. Successful exploitation could lead to full compromise of the system�s confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0510 | Obsolete Encryption Algorithm Used in NW AS Java UME User Mapping</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0510</link><description>The User Management Engine (UME) in NetWeaver Application Server for Java (NW AS Java) utilizes an obsolete cryptographic algorithm for encrypting User Mapping data. This weakness could allow an attacker with high-privileged access to exploit the vulnerability under specific conditions potentially leading to partial disclosure of sensitive information.This has low impact on confidentiality with no impact on integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0511 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP Fiori App (Intercompany Balance Reconciliation)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0511</link><description>SAP Fiori App Intercompany Balance Reconciliation does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. This has high impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application ,availability is not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0513 | Open Redirect Vulnerability in SAP Supplier Relationship Management (SICF Handler in SRM Catalog)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0513</link><description>Due to an Open Redirect Vulnerability in SAP Supplier Relationship Management (SICF Handler in SRM Catalog), an unauthenticated attacker could craft a malicious URL that, if accessed by a victim, redirects them to an attacker-controlled site.This causes low impact on integrity of the application. Confidentiality and availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0514 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP Business Connector</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0514</link><description>Due to a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP Business Connector, an unauthenticated attacker could craft a malicious link. When an unsuspecting user clicks this link, the user may be redirected to a site controlled by the attacker. Successful exploitation could allow the attacker to access or modify information related to the webclient, impacting confidentiality and integrity, with no effect on availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-14021 | LlamaIndex &amp;lt;= 0.11.6 BGEM3Index Unsafe Deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-14021</link><description>LlamaIndex (run-llama/llama_index) versions up to and including 0.11.6 contain an unsafe deserialization vulnerability in BGEM3Index.load_from_disk() in llama_index/indices/managed/bge_m3/base.py. The function uses pickle.load() to deserialize multi_embed_store.pkl from a user-supplied persist_dir without validation. An attacker who can provide a crafted persist directory containing a malicious pickle file can trigger arbitrary code execution when the victim loads the index from disk.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58339 | LlamaIndex &amp;lt;= 0.12.2 VannaQueryEngine SQL Execution Allows Resource Exhaustion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58339</link><description>LlamaIndex (run-llama/llama_index) versions up to and including 0.12.2 contain an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in the VannaPack VannaQueryEngine implementation. The custom_query() logic generates SQL statements from a user-supplied prompt and executes them via vn.run_sql() without enforcing query execution limits In downstream deployments where untrusted users can supply prompts, an attacker can trigger expensive or unbounded SQL operations that exhaust CPU or memory resources, resulting in a denial-of-service condition. The vulnerable execution path occurs in llama_index/packs/vanna/base.py within custom_query().</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58340 | LangChain &amp;lt;= 0.3.1 MRKLOutputParser ReDoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58340</link><description>LangChain versions up to and including 0.3.1 contain a regular expression denial-of-service (ReDoS) vulnerability in the MRKLOutputParser.parse() method (libs/langchain/langchain/agents/mrkl/output_parser.py). The parser applies a backtracking-prone regular expression when extracting tool actions from model output. An attacker who can supply or influence the parsed text (for example via prompt injection in downstream applications that pass LLM output directly into MRKLOutputParser.parse()) can trigger excessive CPU consumption by providing a crafted payload, causing significant parsing delays and a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15514 | Ollama Multi-Modal Model Image Processing NULL Pointer Dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15514</link><description>Ollama 0.11.5-rc0 through current version 0.13.5 contain a null pointer dereference vulnerability in the multi-modal model image processing functionality. When processing base64-encoded image data via the /api/chat endpoint, the application fails to validate that the decoded data represents valid media before passing it to the mtmd_helper_bitmap_init_from_buf function. This function can return NULL for malformed input, but the code does not check this return value before dereferencing the pointer in subsequent operations. A remote attacker can exploit this by sending specially crafted base64 image data that decodes to invalid media, causing a segmentation fault and crashing the runner process. This results in a denial of service condition where the model becomes unavailable to all users until the service is restarted.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22212 | TinyOS &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 Stack-Based Buffer Overflow in mcp2200gpio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22212</link><description>TinyOS versions up to and including 2.1.2 contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the mcp2200gpio utility. The vulnerability is caused by unsafe use of strcpy() and strcat() functions when constructing device paths during automatic device discovery. A local attacker can exploit this by creating specially crafted filenames under /dev/usb/, leading to stack memory corruption and application crashes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22213 | RIOT OS &amp;lt;= 2026.01-devel-317 Stack-Based Buffer Overflow in tapslip6 Utility</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22213</link><description>RIOT OS versions up to and including 2026.01-devel-317 contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the tapslip6 utility. The vulnerability is caused by unsafe string concatenation in the devopen() function, which constructs a device path using unbounded user-controlled input. The utility uses strcpy() and strcat() to concatenate the fixed prefix '/dev/' with a user-supplied device name provided via the -s command-line option without bounds checking. This allows an attacker to supply an excessively long device name and overflow a fixed-size stack buffer, leading to process crashes and memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22214 | RIOT OS &amp;lt;= 2026.01-devel-317 Stack-Based Buffer Overflow in ethos Serial Frame Parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22214</link><description>RIOT OS versions up to and including 2026.01-devel-317 contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the ethos utility due to missing bounds checking when processing incoming serial frame data. The vulnerability occurs in the _handle_char() function, where incoming frame bytes are appended to a fixed-size stack buffer without verifying that the current write index remains within bounds. An attacker capable of sending crafted serial or TCP-framed input can cause the current write index to exceed the buffer size, resulting in a write past the end of the stack buffer. This condition leads to memory corruption and application crash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22695 | LIBPNG has a heap buffer over-read in png_image_read_direct_scaled (regression from CVE-2025-65018 fix)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22695</link><description>LIBPNG is a reference library for use in applications that read, create, and manipulate PNG (Portable Network Graphics) raster image files. From 1.6.51 to 1.6.53, there is a heap buffer over-read in the libpng simplified API function png_image_finish_read when processing interlaced 16-bit PNGs with 8-bit output format and non-minimal row stride. This is a regression introduced by the fix for CVE-2025-65018. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.6.54.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22801 | LIBPNG has an integer truncation causing heap buffer over-read in png_image_write_*</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22801</link><description>LIBPNG is a reference library for use in applications that read, create, and manipulate PNG (Portable Network Graphics) raster image files. From 1.6.26 to 1.6.53, there is an integer truncation in the libpng simplified write API functions png_write_image_16bit and png_write_image_8bit causes heap buffer over-read when the caller provides a negative row stride (for bottom-up image layouts) or a stride exceeding 65535 bytes. The bug was introduced in libpng 1.6.26 (October 2016) by casts added to silence compiler warnings on 16-bit systems. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.6.54.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22812 | OpenCode&amp;#x27;s Unauthenticated HTTP Server Allows Arbitrary Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22812</link><description>OpenCode is an open source AI coding agent. Prior to 1.0.216, OpenCode automatically starts an unauthenticated HTTP server that allows any local process (or any website via permissive CORS) to execute arbitrary shell commands with the user's privileges. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.0.216.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22813 | Malicious website can execute commands on the local system through XSS in the OpenCode web UI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22813</link><description>OpenCode is an open source AI coding agent. The markdown renderer used for LLM responses will insert arbitrary HTML into the DOM. There is no sanitization with DOMPurify or even a CSP on the web interface to prevent JavaScript execution via HTML injection. This means controlling the LLM response for a chat session gets JavaScript execution on the http://localhost:4096 origin. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.1.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22805 | Metabase channel test endpoint can reach internal local addresses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22805</link><description>Metabase is an open-source data analytics platform. Prior to 55.13, 56.3, and 57.1, self-hosted Metabase instances that allow users to create subscriptions could be potentially impacted if their Metabase is colocated with other unsecured resources. This vulnerability is fixed in 55.13, 56.3, and 57.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22800 | PILOS affected by a CSRF via GET request allows unintentional termination of all active video conferences</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22800</link><description>PILOS (Platform for Interactive Live-Online Seminars) is a frontend for BigBlueButton. Prior to 4.10.0, Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in an administrative API endpoint responsible for terminating all active video conferences on a single server. The affected endpoint performs a destructive action but is exposed via an HTTP GET request. Although proper authorization checks are enforced and the endpoint cannot be triggered cross-site, the use of GET allows the action to be implicitly invoked through same-site content (e.g. embedded resources rendered within the application). As a result, an authenticated administrator who views crafted content within the application may unknowingly trigger the endpoint, causing all active video conferences on the server to be terminated without explicit intent or confirmation. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.10.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22804 | Termix has a Stored XSS in File Manager leading to Local File Inclusion (LFI) in Electron and Session Hijacking in Browser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22804</link><description>Termix is a web-based server management platform with SSH terminal, tunneling, and file editing capabilities. From 1.7.0 to 1.9.0, Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Termix File Manager component. The application fails to sanitize SVG file content before rendering it. This allows an attacker who has compromised a managed SSH server to plant a malicious file, which, when previewed by the Termix user, executes arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the application. The vulnerability is located in src/ui/desktop/apps/file-manager/components/FileViewer.tsx. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.10.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22798 | hermes&amp;#x27;s raw options logging may disclose secrets passed in via subcommand options argument</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22798</link><description>hermes is an implementation of the HERMES workflow to automatize software publication with rich metadata. From 0.8.1 to before 0.9.1, hermes subcommands take arbitrary options under the -O argument. These have been logged in raw form. If users provide sensitive data such as API tokens (e.g., via hermes deposit -O invenio_rdm.auth_token SECRET), these are written to the log file in plain text, making them available to whoever can access the log file. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.9.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22799 | emlog Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22799</link><description>Emlog is an open source website building system. emlog v2.6.1 and earlier exposes a REST API endpoint (/index.php?rest-api=upload) for media file uploads. The endpoint fails to implement proper validation of file types, extensions, and content, allowing authenticated attackers (with a valid API key or admin session cookie) to upload arbitrary files (including malicious PHP scripts) to the server. An attacker can obtain the API key either by gaining administrator access to enable the REST API setting, or via information disclosure vulnerabilities in the application. Once uploaded, the malicious PHP file can be executed to gain remote code execution (RCE) on the target server, leading to full server compromise.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22794 | Account Takeover Vulnerability in Appsmith</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22794</link><description>Appsmith is a platform to build admin panels, internal tools, and dashboards. Prior to 1.93, the server uses the Origin value from the request headers as the email link baseUrl without validation. If an attacker controls the Origin, password reset / email verification links in emails can be generated pointing to the attacker’s domain, causing authentication tokens to be exposed and potentially leading to account takeover. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.93.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22789 | WebErpMesv2 has a File Upload Validation Bypass Leading to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22789</link><description>WebErpMesv2 is a Resource Management and Manufacturing execution system Web for industry. Prior to 1.19, WebErpMesv2 contains a file upload validation bypass vulnerability in multiple controllers that allows authenticated users to upload arbitrary files, including PHP scripts, leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE). This vulnerability is identical in nature to CVE-2025-52130 but exists in different code locations that were not addressed by the original fix. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.19.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29329 | Buffer Overflow in the ippprint (Internet Printing Protocol) service in Sagemcom F@st 3686 MAGYAR_4.121.0 allows remote attacker to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29329</link><description>Buffer Overflow in the ippprint (Internet Printing Protocol) service in Sagemcom F@st 3686 MAGYAR_4.121.0 allows remote attacker to execute arbitrary code by sending a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22788 | WebErpMesv2 allows unauthenticated API Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22788</link><description>WebErpMesv2 is a Resource Management and Manufacturing execution system Web for industry. Prior to 1.19, the WebErpMesV2 application exposes multiple sensitive API endpoints without authentication middleware. An unauthenticated remote attacker can read business-critical data including companies, quotes, orders, tasks, and whiteboards. Limited write access allows creation of company records and full manipulation of collaboration whiteboards. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.19.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12420 | Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation in ServiceNow AI Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12420</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the ServiceNow AI Platform that could enable an unauthenticated user to impersonate another user and perform the operations that the impersonated user is entitled to perform.

ServiceNow has addressed this vulnerability by deploying a relevant security update to  hosted instances in October 2025. Security updates have also been provided to ServiceNow self-hosted customers, partners, and hosted customers with unique configurations. Additionally, the vulnerability is addressed in the listed Store App versions. We recommend that customers promptly apply an appropriate security update or upgrade if they have not already done so.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67146 | Multiple SQL Injection vulnerabilities exist in AbhishekMali21 GYM-MANAGEMENT-SYSTEM 1.0 via the 'name' parameter in (1) member_search.php, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67146</link><description>Multiple SQL Injection vulnerabilities exist in AbhishekMali21 GYM-MANAGEMENT-SYSTEM 1.0 via the 'name' parameter in (1) member_search.php, (2) trainer_search.php, and (3) gym_search.php, and via the 'id' parameter in (4) payment_search.php. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit these issues to inject malicious SQL commands, leading to unauthorized data extraction, authentication bypass, or modification of database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:29:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22786 | The arbitrary file upload vulnerability caused by path traversal is on github.com/flipped-aurora/gin-vue-admin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22786</link><description>Gin-vue-admin is a backstage management system based on vue and gin. Gin-vue-admin &lt;= v2.8.7 has a path traversal vulnerability in the breakpoint resume upload functionality. Attacker can upload any files on any directory. In the breakpoint_continue.go file, the MakeFile function accepts a fileName parameter through the /fileUploadAndDownload/breakpointContinueFinish API endpoint and directly concatenates it with the base directory path (./fileDir/) using os.OpenFile() without any validation for directory traversal sequences (e.g., ../). An attacker with file upload privileges could exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67147 | Multiple SQL Injection vulnerabilities exist in amansuryawanshi Gym-Management-System-PHP 1.0 via the 'name', 'email', and 'comment' paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67147</link><description>Multiple SQL Injection vulnerabilities exist in amansuryawanshi Gym-Management-System-PHP 1.0 via the 'name', 'email', and 'comment' parameters in (1) submit_contact.php, the 'username' and 'pass_key' parameters in (2) secure_login.php, and the 'login_id', 'pwfield', and 'login_key' parameters in (3) change_s_pwd.php. An unauthenticated or authenticated attacker can exploit these issues to bypass authentication, execute arbitrary SQL commands, modify database records, delete data, or escalate privileges to administrator level.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22772 | Fulcio vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via MetaIssuer Regex Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22772</link><description>Fulcio is a certificate authority for issuing code signing certificates for an OpenID Connect (OIDC) identity. Prior to 1.8.5, Fulcio's metaRegex() function uses unanchored regex, allowing attackers to bypass MetaIssuer URL validation and trigger SSRF to arbitrary internal services. Since the SSRF only can trigger GET requests, the request cannot mutate state. The response from the GET request is not returned to the caller so data exfiltration is not possible. A malicious actor could attempt to probe an internal network through Blind SSRF. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:29:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-41074 | A CSRF issue in index.php in QloApps hotel eCommerce 1.5.1 allows an attacker to change the admin's email address via a crafted HTML documen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41074</link><description>A CSRF issue in index.php in QloApps hotel eCommerce 1.5.1 allows an attacker to change the admin's email address via a crafted HTML document.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36331 | Incorrect access control in the /member/orderList API of xmall v1.1 allows attackers to arbitrarily access other users' order details via ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36331</link><description>Incorrect access control in the /member/orderList API of xmall v1.1 allows attackers to arbitrarily access other users' order details via manipulation of the query parameter userId.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51567 | A SQL Injection was found in the /exam/user/profile.php page of kashipara Online Exam System V1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51567</link><description>A SQL Injection was found in the /exam/user/profile.php page of kashipara Online Exam System V1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL command to get unauthorized database access via the rname, rcollage, rnumber, rgender and rpassword parameters in a POST HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66802 | Sourcecodester Covid-19 Contact Tracing System 1.0 is vulnerable to RCE (Remote Code Execution). The application receives a reverse shell (p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66802</link><description>Sourcecodester Covid-19 Contact Tracing System 1.0 is vulnerable to RCE (Remote Code Execution). The application receives a reverse shell (php) into imagem of the user enabling RCE.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22200 | osTicket &amp;lt;= 1.18.2 PDF Export Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22200</link><description>Enhancesoft osTicket versions up to and including 1.18.2 contain an arbitrary file read vulnerability in the ticket PDF export functionality. A remote attacker can submit a ticket containing crafted rich-text HTML that includes PHP filter expressions which are insufficiently sanitized before being processed by the mPDF PDF generator during export. When the attacker exports the ticket to PDF, the generated PDF can embed the contents of attacker-selected files from the server filesystem as bitmap images, allowing disclosure of sensitive local files in the context of the osTicket application user. This issue is exploitable in default configurations where guests may create tickets and access ticket status, or where self-registration is enabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22784 | Lychee cross-album password propagation on Album unlocking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22784</link><description>Lychee is a free, open-source photo-management tool. Prior to 7.1.0, an authorization vulnerability exists in Lychee's album password unlock functionality that allows users to gain possibly unauthorized access to other users' password-protected albums. When a user unlocks a password-protected public album, the system automatically unlocks ALL other public albums that share the same password, resulting in a complete authorization bypass. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22785 | orval MCP client is vulnerable to a code injection attack.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22785</link><description>orval generates type-safe JS clients (TypeScript) from any valid OpenAPI v3 or Swagger v2 specification. Prior to 7.18.0, the MCP server generation logic relies on string manipulation that incorporates the summary field from the OpenAPI specification without proper validation or escaping. This allows an attacker to "break out" of the string literal and inject arbitrary code. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.18.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22776 | cpp-httplib vulnerable to a denial of service (DOS) using a zip bomb</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22776</link><description>cpp-httplib is a C++11 single-file header-only cross platform HTTP/HTTPS library. Prior to version 0.30.1, a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability exists in cpp-httplib due to the unsafe handling of compressed HTTP request bodies (Content-Encoding: gzip, br, etc.). The library validates the payload_max_length against the compressed data size received from the network, but does not limit the size of the decompressed data stored in memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22781 | TinyWeb CGI Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22781</link><description>TinyWeb is a web server (HTTP, HTTPS) written in Delphi for Win32. TinyWeb HTTP Server before version 1.98 is vulnerable to OS command injection via CGI ISINDEX-style query parameters. The query parameters are passed as command-line arguments to the CGI executable via Windows CreateProcess(). An unauthenticated remote attacker can execute arbitrary commands on the server by injecting Windows shell metacharacters into HTTP requests. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.98.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:46:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22783 | Iris Allows Arbitrary File Deletion via Mass Assignment in Datastore File Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22783</link><description>Iris is a web collaborative platform that helps incident responders share technical details during investigations. Prior to 2.4.24, the DFIR-IRIS datastore file management system has a vulnerability where mass assignment of the file_local_name field combined with path trust in the delete operation enables authenticated users to delete arbitrary filesystem paths. The vulnerability manifests through a three-step attack chain: authenticated users upload a file to the datastore, update the file's file_local_name field to point to an arbitrary filesystem path through mass assignment, then trigger the delete operation which removes the target file without path validation. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.4.24.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:46:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22252 | LibreChat MCP Stdio Remote Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22252</link><description>LibreChat is a ChatGPT clone with additional features. Prior to v0.8.2-rc2, LibreChat's MCP stdio transport accepts arbitrary commands without validation, allowing any authenticated user to execute shell commands as root inside the container through a single API request. This vulnerability is fixed in v0.8.2-rc2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:46:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22771 | Envoy Extension Policy lua scripts injection causes arbitrary command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22771</link><description>Envoy Gateway is an open source project for managing Envoy Proxy as a standalone or Kubernetes-based application gateway. Prior to 1.5.7 and 1.6.2, EnvoyExtensionPolicy Lua scripts executed by Envoy proxy can be used to leak the proxy's credentials. These credentials can then be used to communicate with the control plane and gain access to all secrets that are used by Envoy proxy, e.g. TLS private keys and credentials used for downstream and upstream communication. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.7 and 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:46:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22251 | wlc may leak API keys due to an insecure API key configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22251</link><description>wlc is a Weblate command-line client using Weblate's REST API. Prior to 1.17.0, wlc supported providing unscoped API keys in the setting. This practice was discouraged for years, but the code was never removed. This might cause the API key to be leaked to different servers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22033 | Label Studio vulnerable to full account takeover by chaining Stored XSS + IDOR in User Profile via custom_hotkeys field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22033</link><description>Label Studio is a multi-type data labeling and annotation tool. In 1.22.0 and earlier, a persistent stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the custom_hotkeys functionality of the application. An authenticated attacker (or one who can trick a user/administrator into updating their custom_hotkeys) can inject JavaScript code that executes in other users’ browsers when those users load any page using the templates/base.html template. Because the application exposes an API token endpoint (/api/current-user/token) to the browser and lacks robust CSRF protection on some API endpoints, the injected script may fetch the victim’s API token or call token reset endpoints — enabling full account takeover and unauthorized API access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22250 | wlc can skip SSL verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22250</link><description>wlc is a Weblate command-line client using Weblate's REST API. Prior to 1.17.0, the SSL verification would be skipped for some crafted URLs. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.17.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68471 | Avahi has a reachable assertion in lookup_start</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68471</link><description>Avahi is a system which facilitates service discovery on a local network via the mDNS/DNS-SD protocol suite. In 0.9-rc2 and earlier, avahi-daemon can be crashed by sending 2 unsolicited announcements with CNAME resource records 2 seconds apart.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68276 | Avahi has a reachable assertion in avahi_wide_area_scan_cache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68276</link><description>Avahi is a system which facilitates service discovery on a local network via the mDNS/DNS-SD protocol suite. In 0.9-rc2 and earlier, an unprivileged local users can crash avahi-daemon (with wide-area disabled) by creating record browsers with the AVAHI_LOOKUP_USE_WIDE_AREA flag set via D-Bus. This can be done by either calling
the RecordBrowserNew method directly or creating hostname/address/service resolvers/browsers that create those browsers internally themselves.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68468 | Avahi has a reachable assertion in lookup_multicast_callback</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68468</link><description>Avahi is a system which facilitates service discovery on a local network via the mDNS/DNS-SD protocol suite. In 0.9-rc2 and earlier, avahi-daemon can be crashed by sending unsolicited announcements containing CNAME resource records pointing it to resource records with short TTLs. As soon as they expire avahi-daemon crashes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68657 | espressif/usb_host_hid Double-Free Race Condition in USB Host HID Device Close Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68657</link><description>Espressif ESP-IDF USB Host HID (Human Interface Device) Driver allows access to HID devices. Prior to 1.1.0, calls to hid_host_device_close() can free the same usb_transfer_t twice. The USB event callback and user code share the hid_iface_t state without locking, so both can tear down a READY interface simultaneously, corrupting heap metadata inside the ESP USB host stack. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68656 | Espressif ESP-IDF USB Host HID (Human Interface Device) Driver Descriptor Use-After-Free Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68656</link><description>Espressif ESP-IDF USB Host HID (Human Interface Device) Driver allows access to HID devices. Prior to 1.1.0, usb_class_request_get_descriptor() frees and reallocates hid_device-&gt;ctrl_xfer when an oversized descriptor is requested but continues to use the stale local pointer, leading to an immediate use-after-free when processing attacker-controlled Report Descriptor lengths. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22050 | ONTAP versions 9.16.1 prior to 9.16.1P9 and 9.17.1 prior to 9.17.1P2 with snapshot locking enabled are susceptible to a vulnerability which ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22050</link><description>ONTAP versions 9.16.1 prior to 9.16.1P9 and 9.17.1 prior to 9.17.1P2 with snapshot locking enabled are susceptible to a vulnerability which could allow a privileged remote attacker to set the snapshot expiry time to none.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63314 | A static password reset token in the password reset function of DDSN Interactive Acora CMS v10.7.1 allows attackers to arbitrarily reset the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63314</link><description>A static password reset token in the password reset function of DDSN Interactive Acora CMS v10.7.1 allows attackers to arbitrarily reset the user password and execute a full account takeover via a replay attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68622 | Espressif ESP-IDF USB Host UVC Class Driver has a stack buffer overflow in UVC descriptor printing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68622</link><description>Espressif ESP-IDF USB Host UVC Class Driver allows video streaming from USB cameras. Prior to 2.4.0, a vulnerability in the esp-usb UVC host implementation allows a malicious USB Video Class (UVC) device to trigger a stack buffer overflow during configuration-descriptor parsing. When UVC configuration-descriptor printing is enabled, the host prints detailed descriptor information provided by the connected USB device. A specially crafted UVC descriptor may advertise an excessively large length. Because this value is not validated before being copied into a fixed-size stack buffer, an attacker can overflow the buffer and corrupt memory. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68472 | MindsDB has improper sanitation of filepath that leads to information disclosure and DOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68472</link><description>MindsDB is a platform for building artificial intelligence from enterprise data. Prior to version 25.11.1, an unauthenticated path traversal in the file upload API lets any caller read arbitrary files from the server filesystem and move them into MindsDB’s storage, exposing sensitive data. The PUT handler in file.py directly joins user-controlled data into a filesystem path when the request body is JSON and source_type is not "url". Only multipart uploads and URL-sourced uploads receive sanitization; JSON uploads lack any call to clear_filename or equivalent checks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66689 | A path traversal vulnerability exists in Zen MCP Server before 9.8.2 that allows authenticated attackers to read arbitrary files on the syst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66689</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in Zen MCP Server before 9.8.2 that allows authenticated attackers to read arbitrary files on the system. The vulnerability is caused by flawed logic in the is_dangerous_path() validation function that uses exact string matching against a blacklist of system directories. Attackers can bypass these restrictions by accessing subdirectories of blacklisted paths.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46068 | An issue in Automai Director v.25.2.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the update mechanism</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46068</link><description>An issue in Automai Director v.25.2.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the update mechanism</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46070 | An issue in Automai BotManager v.25.2.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the BotManager.exe component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46070</link><description>An issue in Automai BotManager v.25.2.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the BotManager.exe component</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46066 | An issue in Automai Director v.25.2.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46066</link><description>An issue in Automai Director v.25.2.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46067 | An issue in Automai Director v.25.2.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via a crafted js file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46067</link><description>An issue in Automai Director v.25.2.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via a crafted js file</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66939 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in 66biolinks by AltumCode v.61.0.1 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted favicon fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66939</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in 66biolinks by AltumCode v.61.0.1 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted favicon file</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71063 | Errands before 46.2.10 does not verify TLS certificates for CalDAV servers.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71063</link><description>Errands before 46.2.10 does not verify TLS certificates for CalDAV servers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67813 | Quest KACE Desktop Authority through 11.3.1 has Insecure Permissions on the Named Pipes used for inter-process communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67813</link><description>Quest KACE Desktop Authority through 11.3.1 has Insecure Permissions on the Named Pipes used for inter-process communication</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41077 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Viafirma products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41077</link><description>IDOR vulnerability has been found in Viafirma Inbox v4.5.13 that allows any authenticated user without privileges in the application to list all users, access and modify their data. This allows the user's email addresses to be modified and, subsequently, using the password recovery functionality to access the application by impersonating any user, including those with administrative permissions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41078 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Viafirma products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41078</link><description>Weaknesses in the authorization mechanisms of Viafirma Documents v3.7.129 allow an authenticated user without privileges to list and access other user data, use user creation, modification, and deletion features, and escalate privileges by impersonating other users of the application in the generation and signing of documents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65552 | D3D Wi-Fi Home Security System ZX-G12 v2.1.1 is vulnerable to RF replay attacks on the 433 MHz sensor communication channel. The system does...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65552</link><description>D3D Wi-Fi Home Security System ZX-G12 v2.1.1 is vulnerable to RF replay attacks on the 433 MHz sensor communication channel. The system does not implement rolling codes, message authentication, or anti-replay protection, allowing an attacker within RF range to record valid alarm/control frames and replay them to trigger false alarms.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65553 | D3D Wi-Fi Home Security System ZX-G12 v2.1.17 is susceptible to RF jamming on the 433 MHz alarm sensor channel. An attacker within RF range ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65553</link><description>D3D Wi-Fi Home Security System ZX-G12 v2.1.17 is susceptible to RF jamming on the 433 MHz alarm sensor channel. An attacker within RF range can transmit continuous interference to block sensor transmissions, resulting in missed alarms and loss of security monitoring. The device lacks jamming detection or mitigations, creating a denial-of-service condition that may lead to undetected intrusions or failure to trigger safety alerts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41005 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Imaster products Open configuration options</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41005</link><description>Imaster's MEMS Events CRM contains an SQL injection vulnerability in‘keyword’ parameter in ‘/memsdemo/exchange_offers.php’.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:48:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41006 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Imaster products Open configuration options</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41006</link><description>Imaster's MEMS Events CRM contains an SQL injection vulnerability in ‘phone’ parameter in ‘/memsdemo/login.php’.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41004 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Imaster products Open configuration options</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41004</link><description>Imaster's Patient Records Management System is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the endpoint ‘/projects/hospital/admin/complaints.php’ through the ‘id’ parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:16:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41003 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Imaster products Open configuration options</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41003</link><description>Imaster's Patient Record Management System contains a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the endpoint ‘/projects/hospital/admin/edit_patient.php’. By injecting a malicious script into the ‘firstname’ parameter, the JavaScript code is stored and executed every time a user accesses the patient list, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in a victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40975 | Multiple vulnerabilities in WorkDo products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40975</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WorkDo's HRMGo, consisting of a lack of proper validation of user input by sending a POST request to ‘/hrmgo/ticket/changereply’, using the ‘description’ parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40976 | Multiple vulnerabilities in WorkDo products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40976</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WorkDo's TicketGo, consisting of a lack of proper validation of user input by sending a POST request to ‘/ticketgo-saas/home’, using the ‘description’ parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40977 | Multiple vulnerabilities in WorkDo products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40977</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WorkDo's eCommerceGo SaaS, consisting of a lack of proper validation of user input by sending a POST request to ‘/store-ticket’, using the ‘subject’ and ‘description’ parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40978 | Multiple vulnerabilities in WorkDo products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40978</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WorkDo's eCommerceGo SaaS, consisting of a stored XSS due to a lack of proper validation of user input by sending a POST request to ‘/ticket/x/conversion’, using the ‘reply_description’ parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14279 | DNS Rebinding Vulnerability in mlflow/mlflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14279</link><description>MLFlow versions up to and including 3.4.0 are vulnerable to DNS rebinding attacks due to a lack of Origin header validation in the MLFlow REST server. This vulnerability allows malicious websites to bypass Same-Origin Policy protections and execute unauthorized calls against REST endpoints. An attacker can query, update, and delete experiments via the affected endpoints, leading to potential data exfiltration, destruction, or manipulation. The issue is resolved in version 3.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 08:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0855 | Merit LILIN｜IP Camera - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0855</link><description>Certain IP Camera models developed by Merit LILIN has a OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary OS commands and execute them on the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 07:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14579 | Quiz Maker &amp;lt; 6.7.0.89 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14579</link><description>The Quiz Maker WordPress plugin before 6.7.0.89 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0854 | Merit LILIN｜NVR - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0854</link><description>Certain DVR/NVR models developed by Merit LILIN has a OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary OS commands and execute them on the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69274 | Spectrum broken authorization scheme</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69274</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 24.3.10 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 05:06:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69275 | Spectrum outdated java library in class-path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69275</link><description>Dependency on Vulnerable Third-Party Component vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 24.3.9 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 05:06:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69276 | Spectrum insecure deserialiation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69276</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows Object Injection.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 24.3.13 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 05:06:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69270 | Spectrum session token in URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69270</link><description>Information Exposure Through Query Strings in GET Request vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows Session Hijacking.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 24.3.8 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 05:06:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69271 | Spectrum basic authentication in use</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69271</link><description>Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows Sniffing Attacks.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 24.3.13 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 05:06:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69272 | Spectrum password returned in clear</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69272</link><description>Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows Sniffing Attacks.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 21.2.1 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 05:06:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69273 | Spectrum broken authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69273</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 24.3.10 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 05:06:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69267 | Spectrum directory path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69267</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (Path Traversal) vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows Path Traversal.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 24.3.8 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69268 | Spectrum reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69268</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 24.3.8 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69269 | Spectrum command injection in NCM service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69269</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 23.3.6 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0853 | A-Plus Video Technologies｜NVR - Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0853</link><description>Certain NVR models developed by A-Plus Video Technologies has a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to access the debug page and obtain device status information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52694 | Execution of arbitrary SQL commands</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52694</link><description>Successful exploitation of the SQL injection vulnerability could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands on the vulnerable service when it is exposed to the Internet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0852 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminUpdateUser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0852</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminUpdateUser.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:24:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0851 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminAddUser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0851</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminAddUser.php. The manipulation of the argument txtusername leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 23:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0850 | code-projects Intern Membership Management System delete_activity.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0850</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Intern Membership Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/delete_activity.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument activity_id can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 23:19:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68493 | Apache Struts, Apache Struts: XXE vulnerability in outdated XWork component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68493</link><description>Missing XML Validation vulnerability in Apache Struts, Apache Struts.

This issue affects Apache Struts: from 2.0.0 before 2.2.1; Apache Struts: from 2.2.1 through 6.1.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 6.1.1, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 13:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15506 | AcademySoftwareFoundation OpenColorIO FileRules.cpp ConvertToRegularExpression out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15506</link><description>A vulnerability was found in AcademySoftwareFoundation OpenColorIO up to 2.5.0. This issue affects the function ConvertToRegularExpression of the file src/OpenColorIO/FileRules.cpp. Performing a manipulation results in out-of-bounds read. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The patch is named ebdbb75123c9d5f4643e041314e2bc988a13f20d. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch. The fix was added to the 2.5.1 milestone.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0843 | jiujiujia/victor123/wxw850227 jjjfood/jjjshop_food index sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0843</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in jiujiujia/victor123/wxw850227 jjjfood and jjjshop_food up to 20260103. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php/api/product.category/index. Such manipulation of the argument latitude leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is distributed under multiple different names. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:11:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0842 | Flycatcher Toys smART Sketcher Bluetooth Low Energy missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0842</link><description>A flaw has been found in Flycatcher Toys smART Sketcher up to 2.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Bluetooth Low Energy Interface. This manipulation causes missing authentication. The attack can only be done within the local network. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 08:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0841 | UTT 进取 520W formPictureUrl strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0841</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. Affected by this issue is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formPictureUrl. The manipulation of the argument importpictureurl results in buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 07:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0840 | UTT 进取 520W formConfigNoticeConfig strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0840</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. Affected by this vulnerability is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formConfigNoticeConfig. The manipulation of the argument timestart leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0839 | UTT 进取 520W APSecurity strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0839</link><description>A weakness has been identified in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. Affected is the function strcpy of the file /goform/APSecurity. Executing a manipulation of the argument wepkey1 can lead to buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0838 | UTT 进取 520W ConfigWirelessBase strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0838</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. This impacts the function strcpy of the file /goform/ConfigWirelessBase. Performing a manipulation of the argument ssid results in buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 05:50:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0837 | UTT 进取 520W formFireWall strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0837</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. This affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/formFireWall. Such manipulation of the argument GroupName leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 05:31:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0836 | UTT 进取 520W formConfigFastDirectionW strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0836</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. The impacted element is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formConfigFastDirectionW. This manipulation of the argument ssid causes buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15505 | Luxul XWR-600 Web Administration cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15505</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Luxul XWR-600 up to 4.0.1. The affected element is an unknown function of the component Web Administration Interface. The manipulation of the argument Guest Network/Wireless Profile SSID results in cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond with a technical statement.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>