<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:29:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-12641 | Chunghwa Telecom TenderDocTransfer - Reflected Cross-site Scripting to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12641</link><description>TenderDocTransfer from Chunghwa Telecom has a Reflected Cross-site scripting vulnerability. The application sets up a simple local web server and provides APIs for communication with the target website. Due to the lack of CSRF protection for the APIs, unauthenticated remote attackers could use specific APIs through phishing to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the user’s browser. Since the web server set by the application supports Node.Js features, attackers can further leverage this to run OS commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56084 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint UniversalNormalizer before 5.7.0. Authenticated users can inject payloads while creating Universal Norma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56084</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint UniversalNormalizer before 5.7.0. Authenticated users can inject payloads while creating Universal Normalizer. These are executed, leading to Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56085 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.5.0. Authenticated users can inject payloads while creating Search Template Dashboard. These ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56085</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.5.0. Authenticated users can inject payloads while creating Search Template Dashboard. These are executed, leading to Server-Side Template Injection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56086 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.5.0. Authenticated users can inject payloads in Report Templates. These are executed when the b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56086</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.5.0. Authenticated users can inject payloads in Report Templates. These are executed when the backup process is initiated, leading to Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56087 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.5.0. Authenticated users can inject payloads while querying Search Template Dashboard. These ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56087</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.5.0. Authenticated users can inject payloads while querying Search Template Dashboard. These are executed, leading to Server-Side Template Injection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56112 | CyberPanel (aka Cyber Panel) before f0cf648 allows XSS via token or username to plogical/phpmyadminsignin.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56112</link><description>CyberPanel (aka Cyber Panel) before f0cf648 allows XSS via token or username to plogical/phpmyadminsignin.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11841 | Tithe.ly Giving Button &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Contributor+ Stored XSS via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11841</link><description>The Tithe.ly Giving Button WordPress plugin through 1.1 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5333 | The Events Calendar &amp;lt; 6.8.2.1 - Unauthenticated Password Protected Event Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5333</link><description>The Events Calendar WordPress plugin before 6.8.2.1 is missing access checks in the REST API, allowing for unauthenticated users to access information about password protected events.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8116 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8116</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.9 before 17.4.6, 17.5 before 17.5.4, and 17.6 before 17.6.2. By using a specific GraphQL query, under specific conditions an unauthorized user can retrieve branch names.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 04:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8650 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8650</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 15.0 prior to 17.4.6, 17.5 prior to 17.5.4, and 17.6 prior to 17.6.2 that allowed non-member users to view unresolved threads marked as internal notes in public projects merge requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 04:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53376 | CyberPanel before 2.3.8 allows remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary commands via shell metacharacters in the phpSelection field t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53376</link><description>CyberPanel before 2.3.8 allows remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary commands via shell metacharacters in the phpSelection field to the websites/submitWebsiteCreation URI.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 03:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56083 | Cognition Devin before 2024-12-12 provides write access to code by an attacker who discovers the https://vscode-randomly_generated_string.de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56083</link><description>Cognition Devin before 2024-12-12 provides write access to code by an attacker who discovers the https://vscode-randomly_generated_string.devinapps.com URL (aka the VSCode live share URL) for a specific "Use Devin's Machine" session. For example, this URL may be discovered if a customer posts a screenshot of a Devin session to social media, or publicly streams their Devin session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 02:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8798 | Bluetooth: classic: avdtp: missing buffer length check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8798</link><description>No proper validation of the length of user input in olcp_ind_handler in zephyr/subsys/bluetooth/services/ots/ots_client.c.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 23:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11858 | Radare2: command injection via pebble application files in radare2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11858</link><description>A flaw was found in Radare2, which contains a command injection vulnerability caused by insufficient input validation when handling Pebble Application files. Maliciously crafted inputs can inject shell commands during command parsing, leading to unintended behavior during file processing​</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 14:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7701 | Misuse of SHA256 to create an encryption key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7701</link><description>Use of Password Hash With Insufficient Computational Effort vulnerability in percona percona-toolkit allows Encryption Brute Forcing.This issue affects percona-toolkit: 3.6.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 11:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56082 | ChatBar.tsx in Lumos before 1.0.17 parses raw HTML in Markdown because the markdown-to-jsx package is used without disableParsingRawHTML set...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56082</link><description>ChatBar.tsx in Lumos before 1.0.17 parses raw HTML in Markdown because the markdown-to-jsx package is used without disableParsingRawHTML set to true.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 04:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55969 | DocIO in Syncfusion Essential Studio for ASP.NET MVC before 27.1.55 throws XMLException during the resaving of a DOCX document with an exter...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55969</link><description>DocIO in Syncfusion Essential Studio for ASP.NET MVC before 27.1.55 throws XMLException during the resaving of a DOCX document with an external reference XML, aka I640714.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 03:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56074 | gitingest before 9996a06 mishandles symbolic links that point outside of the base directory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56074</link><description>gitingest before 9996a06 mishandles symbolic links that point outside of the base directory.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 03:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55970 | File Manager in Syncfusion Essential Studio for ASP.NET MVC before 27.1.55 has a traversal issue that is related to the request parameter, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55970</link><description>File Manager in Syncfusion Essential Studio for ASP.NET MVC before 27.1.55 has a traversal issue that is related to the request parameter, aka I644734.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 03:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56072 | An issue was discovered in FastNetMon Community Edition through 1.2.7. The sFlow v5 plugin allows remote attackers to cause a denial of serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56072</link><description>An issue was discovered in FastNetMon Community Edition through 1.2.7. The sFlow v5 plugin allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (application crash) via a crafted packet that specifies many sFlow samples.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 03:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56073 | An issue was discovered in FastNetMon Community Edition through 1.2.7. Zero-length templates for Netflow v9 allow remote attackers to cause ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56073</link><description>An issue was discovered in FastNetMon Community Edition through 1.2.7. Zero-length templates for Netflow v9 allow remote attackers to cause a denial of service (divide-by-zero error and application crash).</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 03:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31891 | IBM Storage Scale privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31891</link><description>IBM Storage Scale GUI 5.1.9.0 through 5.1.9.6 and 5.2.0.0 through 5.2.1.1 

contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with command line access to the 'scalemgmt' user can elevate privileges to gain root access to the host operating system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 13:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31892 | IBM Storage Scale SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31892</link><description>IBM Storage Scale GUI 5.1.9.0 through 5.1.9.6 and 5.2.0.0 through 5.2.1.1 could allow a user to perform unauthorized actions after intercepting and modifying a csv file due to improper neutralization of formula elements.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 13:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11720 | Frontend Admin by DynamiApps &amp;lt;= 3.24.5 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11720</link><description>The Frontend Admin by DynamiApps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via submission forms in all versions up to, and including, 3.24.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the new Taxonomy form. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This is only exploitable when lower-level users have been granted access to submit specific forms, which is disabled by default.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 08:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11721 | Frontend Admin by DynamiApps &amp;lt;= 3.24.5 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11721</link><description>The Frontend Admin by DynamiApps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 3.24.5. This is due to insufficient controls on the user role select field when utilizing the 'Role' field in a form. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create new administrative user accounts, even when the administrative user role has not been provided as an option to the user, granted that unauthenticated users have been provided access to the form.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 08:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11710 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11710</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'fieldfor', 'visibleParent' and 'id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11711 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11711</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'resumeid' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11712 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Resume Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11712</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the getResumeFileDownloadById() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download other users resumes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11713 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection via wpjobportal_deactivate()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11713</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'page_id' parameter of the wpjobportal_deactivate() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11714 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection via getFieldsForVisibleCombobox()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11714</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'ff' parameter of the getFieldsForVisibleCombobox() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11715 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Missing Authorization to Limited Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11715</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the assignUserRole() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to elevate their privileges to that of an employer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12446 | Post to Pdf &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12446</link><description>The Post to Pdf plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gmptp_single_post' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12628 | bodi0’s Easy Cache &amp;lt;= 0.8 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12628</link><description>The bodi0`s Easy cache plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'cache-folder' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10646 | Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp;amp; Drop WP Form Builder &amp;lt;= 5.2.6 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Form Subject</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10646</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the form's subject parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10690 | Shortcodes for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10690</link><description>The Shortcodes for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 via the 'SHORTCODE_ELEMENTOR' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private and draft posts created with Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11752 | Eveeno &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11752</link><description>The Eveeno plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'eveeno' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12422 | Import Eventbrite Events &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12422</link><description>The Import Eventbrite Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12459 | Ganohrs Toggle Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12459</link><description>The Ganohrs Toggle Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'toggle' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12474 | GeoDataSource Country Region DropDown &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12474</link><description>The GeoDataSource Country Region DropDown plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gds-country-dropdown' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12501 | Simple Locator &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12501</link><description>The Simple Locator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11095 | Visualmodo Elements &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11095</link><description>The Visualmodo Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via REST API SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11462 | Filestack Official &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11462</link><description>The Filestack Official plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'fstab' and 'filestack_options' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11751 | TCBD Popover &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11751</link><description>The TCBD Popover plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tcbd-popover-image ' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11755 | IMS Countdown &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11755</link><description>The IMS Countdown plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown post settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11759 | Bukza &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11759</link><description>The Bukza plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'bukza' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11763 | Plezi &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11763</link><description>The Plezi plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'plezi' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11770 | Post Carousel &amp;amp; Slider &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11770</link><description>The Post Carousel &amp; Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'post-cs' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11855 | Koalendar – Events &amp;amp; Appointments Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via height Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11855</link><description>The Koalendar – Events &amp; Appointments Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘height’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11865 | Tabs Maker &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11865</link><description>The Tabs Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on tab descriptions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11867 | Companion Portfolio – Responsive Portfolio Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11867</link><description>The Companion Portfolio – Responsive Portfolio Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'companion-portfolio' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11869 | Buk for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11869</link><description>The Buk for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'buk' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11873 | glomex oEmbed &amp;lt;= 0.9.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11873</link><description>The glomex oEmbed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'glomex_integration' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11876 | Kredeum NFTs, the easiest way to sell your NFTs directly on your WordPress site &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11876</link><description>The Kredeum NFTs, the easiest way to sell your NFTs directly on your WordPress site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'kredeum_opensky' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11877 | Cricket Live Score &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11877</link><description>The Cricket Live Score plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'cricket_score' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11879 | Stripe Donation &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11879</link><description>The Stripe Donation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'stripe_donation' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11883 | Connatix Video Embed &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11883</link><description>The Connatix Video Embed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'cnx_script_code' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11884 | Wp photo text slider 50 &amp;lt;= 8.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11884</link><description>The Wp photo text slider 50 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wp-photo-slider' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 8.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11888 | IDer Login for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11888</link><description>The IDer Login for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ider_login_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11889 | My IDX Home Search &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11889</link><description>The My IDX Home Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'homeasap-idx-search' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11894 | The Permalinker &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11894</link><description>The The Permalinker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'permalink' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12411 | WP Ad Guru – Banner ad, Responsive popup, Popup maker, Ad rotator &amp;amp; More &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12411</link><description>The WP Ad Guru – Banner ad, Responsive popup, Popup maker, Ad rotator &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12447 | Get Post Content Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.4 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Disclosure via post_content Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12447</link><description>The Get Post Content Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 0.4 via the 'post-content' shortcode due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the content of password-protected, private, draft, and pending posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12448 | Posts and Products Views for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12448</link><description>The Posts and Products Views for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'papvfwc_views' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12458 | Smart PopUp Blaster &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12458</link><description>The Smart PopUp Blaster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'spb-button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12502 | My IDX Home Search &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12502</link><description>The My IDX Home Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'homeasap-idx-landing' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12517 | WooCommerce Cart Count Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12517</link><description>The WooCommerce Cart Count Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'cart_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12523 | States Map US &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12523</link><description>The States Map US plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'states_map' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12555 | SIP Calculator &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12555</link><description>The SIP Calculator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12578 | Tickera – WordPress Event Ticketing &amp;lt;= 3.5.4.8 - Unauthenticated Customer Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12578</link><description>The Tickera – WordPress Event Ticketing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.4.8 via the 'tickera_tickets_info' endpoint. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from bookings like full names, email addresses, check-in/out timestamps and more.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9698 | Crafthemes Demo Import &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Upload in process_uploaded_files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9698</link><description>The Crafthemes Demo Import plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'process_uploaded_files' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29476 | In Menlo On-Premise Appliance before 2.88, web policy may not be consistently applied properly to intentionally malformed client requests. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29476</link><description>In Menlo On-Premise Appliance before 2.88, web policy may not be consistently applied properly to intentionally malformed client requests. This is fixed in 2.88.2+, 2.89.1+, and 2.90.1+.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 02:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>