<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:20:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-15197 | code-projects/anirbandutta9 Content Management System/News-Buzz editposts.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15197</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects/anirbandutta9 Content Management System and News-Buzz 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/editposts.php. Performing manipulation of the argument image results in unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66869 | Buffer overflow vulnerability in function strcat in asan_interceptors.cpp in libming 0.4.8.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66869</link><description>Buffer overflow vulnerability in function strcat in asan_interceptors.cpp in libming 0.4.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66862 | A buffer overflow vulnerability in function gnu_special in file cplus-dem.c in BinUtils 2.26 allows attackers to cause a denial of service v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66862</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in function gnu_special in file cplus-dem.c in BinUtils 2.26 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted PE file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66864 | An issue was discovered in function d_print_comp_inner in file cp-demangle.c in BinUtils 2.26 allows attackers to cause a denial of service ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66864</link><description>An issue was discovered in function d_print_comp_inner in file cp-demangle.c in BinUtils 2.26 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted PE file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66866 | An issue was discovered in function d_abi_tags in file cp-demangle.c in BinUtils 2.26 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66866</link><description>An issue was discovered in function d_abi_tags in file cp-demangle.c in BinUtils 2.26 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted PE file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15196 | code-projects Assessment Management login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15196</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Assessment Management 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file login.php. Such manipulation of the argument userid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66861 | An issue was discovered in function d_unqualified_name in file cp-demangle.c in BinUtils 2.26 allowing attackers to cause a denial of servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66861</link><description>An issue was discovered in function d_unqualified_name in file cp-demangle.c in BinUtils 2.26 allowing attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted PE file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66863 | An issue was discovered in function d_discriminator in file cp-demangle.c in BinUtils 2.26 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66863</link><description>An issue was discovered in function d_discriminator in file cp-demangle.c in BinUtils 2.26 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted PE file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66865 | An issue was discovered in function d_print_comp_inner in file cp-demangle.c in BinUtils 2.26 allows attackers to cause a denial of service ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66865</link><description>An issue was discovered in function d_print_comp_inner in file cp-demangle.c in BinUtils 2.26 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted PE file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53627 | Meshtastic firmware allows forged DMs with no PKC to show up as encrypted</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53627</link><description>Meshtastic is an open source mesh networking solution. The Meshtastic firmware (starting from version 2.5) introduces asymmetric encryption (PKI) for direct messages, but when the `pki_encrypted` flag is missing, the firmware silently falls back to legacy AES-256-CTR channel encryption. This was an intentional decision to maintain backwards compatibility. However, the end-user applications, like Web app, iOS/Android app, and applications built on top of Meshtastic using the SDK, did not have a way to differentiate between end-to-end encrypted DMs and the legacy DMs. This creates a downgrade attack path where adversaries who know a shared channel key can craft and inject spoofed direct messages that are displayed as if they were PKC encrypted. Users are not given any feedback of whether a direct message was decrypted with PKI or with legacy symmetric encryption, undermining the expected security guarantees of the PKI rollout. Version 2.7.15 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68868 | WordPress Wp Text Slider Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68868</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Codeaffairs Wp Text Slider Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Wp Text Slider Widget: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68870 | WordPress CookieHint WP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68870</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in reDim GmbH CookieHint WP allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects CookieHint WP: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15195 | code-projects Assessment Management add-module.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15195</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Assessment Management 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/add-module.php. This manipulation of the argument linked[] causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56333 | An issue in Fossorial fosrl/pangolin v.1.6.2 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the 2FA component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56333</link><description>An issue in Fossorial fosrl/pangolin v.1.6.2 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the 2FA component</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68876 | WordPress Invelity SPS connect plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68876</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in INVELITY Invelity SPS connect allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Invelity SPS connect: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68877 | WordPress CedCommerce Integration for Good Market plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68877</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in CedCommerce CedCommerce Integration for Good Market allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects CedCommerce Integration for Good Market: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:13:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68878 | WordPress Advanced Custom CSS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68878</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Prasadkirpekar Advanced Custom CSS allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Advanced Custom CSS: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:13:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68879 | WordPress Content Grid Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68879</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Councilsoft Content Grid Slider allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Content Grid Slider: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69211 | Nest has a Fastify URL Encoding Middleware Bypass (TOCTOU)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69211</link><description>Nest is a framework for building scalable Node.js server-side applications. Versions prior to 11.1.11 have a Fastify URL encoding middleware bypass. A NestJS application is vulnerable if it uses `@nestjs/platform-fastify`; relies on `NestMiddleware` (via `MiddlewareConsumer`) for security checks (authentication, authorization, etc.), or through `app.use()`; and applies middleware to specific routes using string paths or controllers (e.g., `.forRoutes('admin')`). Exploitation can result in unauthenticated users accessing protected routes, restricted administrative endpoints becoming accessible to lower-privileged users, and/or middleware performing sanitization or validation being skipped. This issue is patched in `@nestjs/platform-fastify@11.1.11`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68893 | WordPress WordPress Image shrinker plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68893</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in HETWORKS WordPress Image shrinker allows Server Side Request Forgery.This issue affects WordPress Image shrinker: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:13:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68897 | WordPress IF AS Shortcode plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68897</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Mohammad I. Okfie IF AS Shortcode allows Code Injection.This issue affects IF AS Shortcode: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:13:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69206 | Hemmelig has SSRF Filter bypass in Secret Request functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69206</link><description>Hemmelig is a messing app with with client-side encryption and self-destructing messages. Prior to version 7.3.3, a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) filter bypass vulnerability exists in the webhook URL validation of the Secret Requests feature. The application attempts to block internal/private IP addresses but can be bypassed using DNS rebinding or open redirect services. This allows an authenticated user to make the server initiate HTTP requests to internal network resources. Version 7.3.3 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:13:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69201 | Tugtainer has RCE in Agent Command Execution Api</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69201</link><description>Tugtainer is a self-hosted app for automating updates of docker containers. In versions prior to 1.15.1, arbitary arguments can be injected in tugtainer-agent `POST api/command/run`. Version 1.15.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15194 | D-Link DIR-600 HTTP Header hedwig.cgi stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15194</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-600 up to 2.15WWb02. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file hedwig.cgi of the component HTTP Header Handler. The manipulation of the argument Cookie results in stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:38:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69200 | phpMyFAQ has unauthenticated config backup download via /api/setup/backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69200</link><description>phpMyFAQ is an open source FAQ web application. In versions prior to 4.0.16, an unauthenticated remote attacker can trigger generation of a configuration backup ZIP via `POST /api/setup/backup` and then download the generated ZIP from a web-accessible location. The ZIP contains sensitive configuration files (e.g., `database.php` with database credentials), leading to high-impact information disclosure and potential follow-on compromise. Version 4.0.16 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:38:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68951 | phpMyFAQ has stored XSS in admin &amp;quot;List of users&amp;quot; via display_name HTML entity decoding (html_entity_decode) + Twig |raw</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68951</link><description>phpMyFAQ is an open source FAQ web application. Versions 4.0.14 and 4.0.15 have a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability that allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in an administrator’s browser by registering a user whose display name contains HTML entities. When an administrator views the admin user list, the payload is decoded server-side and rendered without escaping, resulting in script execution in the admin context. Version 4.0.16 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:38:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15193 | D-Link DWR-M920 formParentControl sub_423848 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15193</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DWR-M920 up to 1.1.50. This affects the function sub_423848 of the file /boafrm/formParentControl. Performing manipulation of the argument submit-url results in buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68928 | Frappe CRM vulnerable to authenticated XSS via website field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68928</link><description>Frappe CRM is an open-source customer relationship management tool. Prior to version 1.56.2, authenticated users could set crafted URLs in a website field, which were not sanitized, causing cross-site scripting. Version 1.56.2 fixes the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68929 | Frappe may be vulnerable remote code execution due to server-side template injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68929</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. Prior to versions 14.99.6 and 15.88.1, an authenticated user with specific permissions could be tricked into accessing a specially crafted link. This could lead to a malicious template being executed on the server, resulting in remote code execution. Versions 14.99.6 and 15.88.1 fix the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60458 | UxPlay 1.72 contains a double free vulnerability in its RTSP request handling. A specially crafted RTSP TEARDOWN request can trigger multipl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60458</link><description>UxPlay 1.72 contains a double free vulnerability in its RTSP request handling. A specially crafted RTSP TEARDOWN request can trigger multiple calls to free() on the same memory address, potentially causing a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65442 | DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in 201206030 novel V3.5.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code or...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65442</link><description>DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in 201206030 novel V3.5.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code or disclose sensitive information (e.g., user session cookies) via a crafted "wvstest" parameter in the URL or malicious script injection into window.localStorage. The vulnerability arises from insufficient validation and encoding of user-controllable data in the book comment module: unfiltered user input is stored in the backend database (book_comment table, commentContent field) and returned via API, then rendered directly into the page DOM via Vue 3's v-html directive without sanitization. Even if modern browsers' built-in XSS filters block pop-up alerts, attackers can use concealed payloads to bypass interception and achieve actual harm.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65570 | A type confusion in jsish 2.0 allows incorrect control flow during execution of the OP_NEXT opcode. When an “instanceof” expression uses an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65570</link><description>A type confusion in jsish 2.0 allows incorrect control flow during execution of the OP_NEXT opcode. When an “instanceof” expression uses an array element access as the left-hand operand inside a for-in loop, the instructions implementation leaves an additional array reference on the stack rather than consuming it during OP_INSTANCEOF. As a result, OP_NEXT interprets the array as an iterator object and reads the iterCmd function pointer from an invalid structure, potentially causing a crash or enabling code execution depending on heap layout.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15192 | D-Link DWR-M920 formLtefotaUpgradeQuectel sub_415328 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15192</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DWR-M920 up to 1.1.50. The impacted element is the function sub_415328 of the file /boafrm/formLtefotaUpgradeQuectel. Such manipulation of the argument fota_url leads to command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57462 | Reflected Cross site scripting (xss) in machsol machpanel 8.0.32 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted PDF...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57462</link><description>Reflected Cross site scripting (xss) in machsol machpanel 8.0.32 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted PDF file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15191 | D-Link DWR-M920 formLtefotaUpgradeFibocom sub_4155B4 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15191</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DWR-M920 up to 1.1.50. The affected element is the function sub_4155B4 of the file /boafrm/formLtefotaUpgradeFibocom. This manipulation of the argument fota_url causes command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57460 | File upload vulnerability in machsol machpanel 8.0.32 allows attacker to gain a webshell.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57460</link><description>File upload vulnerability in machsol machpanel 8.0.32 allows attacker to gain a webshell.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15190 | D-Link DWR-M920 formFilter sub_42261C stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15190</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in D-Link DWR-M920 up to 1.1.50. Impacted is the function sub_42261C of the file /boafrm/formFilter. The manipulation of the argument ip6addr results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15189 | D-Link DWR-M920 formDefRoute sub_464794 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15189</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DWR-M920 up to 1.1.50. This issue affects the function sub_464794 of the file /boafrm/formDefRoute. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15188 | Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System search-invoices.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15188</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/search-invoices.php. Executing manipulation of the argument searchdata can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15187 | GreenCMS File DataController.class.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15187</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GreenCMS up to 2.3. This affects an unknown part of the file /DataController.class.php of the component File Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument sqlFiles/zipFiles results in path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15186 | code-projects Refugee Food Management System addusers.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15186</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Refugee Food Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /home/addusers.php. Such manipulation of the argument a leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15185 | code-projects Refugee Food Management System refugeesreport.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15185</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Refugee Food Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /home/refugeesreport.php. This manipulation of the argument a causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15184 | code-projects Refugee Food Management System refugeesreport2.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15184</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Refugee Food Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /home/refugeesreport2.php. The manipulation of the argument a results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15183 | code-projects Refugee Food Management System viewtakenfd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15183</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Refugee Food Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /home/viewtakenfd.php. The manipulation of the argument tfid leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15182 | code-projects Refugee Food Management System served.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15182</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Refugee Food Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /home/served.php. Executing manipulation of the argument refNo can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15181 | code-projects Refugee Food Management System pagenateRefugeesList.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15181</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Refugee Food Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /home/pagenateRefugeesList.php. Performing manipulation of the argument rfid results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15180 | Tenda WH450 HTTP Request webExcptypemanFilte stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15180</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /goform/webExcptypemanFilte of the component HTTP Request Handler. Such manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15179 | Tenda WH450 qossetting stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15179</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /goform/qossetting. This manipulation of the argument page causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15178 | Tenda WH450 HTTP Request VirtualSer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15178</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/VirtualSer of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument page results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15228 | WELLTEND TECHNOLOGY｜ BPMFlowWebkit - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15228</link><description>BPMFlowWebkit developed by WELLTEND TECHNOLOGY has a Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to upload and execute web shell backdoors, thereby enabling arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15227 | WELLTEND TECHNOLOGY｜ BPMFlowWebkit - Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15227</link><description>BPMFlowWebkit developed by WELLTEND TECHNOLOGY has a Arbitrary File Read vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit Absolute Path Traversal to download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15177 | Tenda WH450 HTTP Request SetIpBind stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15177</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/SetIpBind of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15226 | Sunnet｜WMPro - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15226</link><description>WMPro developed by Sunnet has a Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to upload and execute web shell backdoors, thereby enabling arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:02:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15176 | Open5GS PFCP Session Establishment Request rule-match.c ogs_pfcp_pdr_rule_find_by_packet assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15176</link><description>A flaw has been found in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. This affects the function decode_ipv6_header/ogs_pfcp_pdr_rule_find_by_packet of the file lib/pfcp/rule-match.c of the component PFCP Session Establishment Request Handler. Executing manipulation can lead to reachable assertion. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. This patch is called b72d8349980076e2c033c8324f07747a86eea4f8. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15225 | Sunnet｜WMPro - Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15225</link><description>WMPro developed by Sunnet has an Arbitrary File Read vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit Relative Path Traversal to read arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13417 | Plugin Organizer &amp;lt; 10.2.4 - Subscriber+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13417</link><description>The Plugin Organizer WordPress plugin before 10.2.4 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing subscribers to perform SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13958 | YaMaps &amp;lt; 0.6.40 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13958</link><description>The YaMaps for WordPress Plugin WordPress plugin before 0.6.40 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15175 | SohuTV CacheCloud AppController.java appCommandAnalysis cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15175</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SohuTV CacheCloud up to 3.2.0. Affected by this issue is the function doAppList/appCommandAnalysis of the file src/main/java/com/sohu/cache/web/controller/AppController.java. Performing manipulation results in cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15174 | SohuTV CacheCloud AppManageController.java doAppAuditList cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15174</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SohuTV CacheCloud up to 3.2.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function doAppAuditList of the file src/main/java/com/sohu/cache/web/controller/AppManageController.java. Such manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15068 | Account Takeover in Gmission Web FAX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15068</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Gmission Web Fax allows Privilege Abuse, Session Credential Falsification through Manipulation.This issue affects Web Fax: from 3.0 before 4.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15069 | Privilege Escalation in Gmission Web FAX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15069</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Gmission Web Fax allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Web Fax: from 3.0 before 4.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15070 | Data Exposure in Gmission Web FAX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15070</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor, Missing Authorization vulnerability in Gmission Web Fax allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects Web Fax: from 3.0 before 4.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15173 | SohuTV CacheCloud InstanceController.java advancedAnalysis cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15173</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SohuTV CacheCloud up to 3.2.0. Affected is the function advancedAnalysis of the file src/main/java/com/sohu/cache/web/controller/InstanceController.java. This manipulation causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:05:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15172 | SohuTV CacheCloud RedisConfigTemplateController.java preview cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15172</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in SohuTV CacheCloud up to 3.2.0. This impacts the function preview of the file src/main/java/com/sohu/cache/web/controller/RedisConfigTemplateController.java. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:05:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15171 | SohuTV CacheCloud ServerController.java index cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15171</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SohuTV CacheCloud up to 3.2.0. This affects the function index of the file src/main/java/com/sohu/cache/web/controller/ServerController.java. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15170 | Advaya Softech GEMS ERP Portal Error Message home.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15170</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Advaya Softech GEMS ERP Portal up to 2.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /home.jsp?isError=true of the component Error Message Handler. The manipulation of the argument Message leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15169 | BiggiDroid Simple PHP CMS editsite.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15169</link><description>A weakness has been identified in BiggiDroid Simple PHP CMS 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/editsite.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15167 | itsourcecode Online Cake Ordering System detailtransac.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15167</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Online Cake Ordering System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /detailtransac.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15168 | itsourcecode Student Management System statistical.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15168</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Student Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /statistical.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52691 | Upload Arbitrary Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52691</link><description>Successful exploitation of the vulnerability could allow an unauthenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files to any location on the mail server, potentially enabling remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15166 | itsourcecode Online Cake Ordering System updatesupplier.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15166</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Cake Ordering System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /updatesupplier.php?action=edit. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15066 | Arbitrary File Download through Path Traversal in Innorix WP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15066</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal'), Missing Authorization vulnerability in Innorix WP allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Innorix WP from All versions If the "exam" directory exists under the directory where the product is installed (ex: innorix/exam)</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15067 | File Upload in Innorix WP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15067</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Innorix Innorix WP allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Innorix WP from All versions If the "exam" directory exists under the directory where the product is installed (ex: innorix/exam)</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 01:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15165 | itsourcecode Online Cake Ordering System updatecustomer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15165</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Online Cake Ordering System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /updatecustomer.php?action=edit. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 01:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15065 | Data Exposure in Kings Information &amp;amp; Network KESS Enterprise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15065</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor, Missing Encryption of Sensitive Data, Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties vulnerability in Kings Information &amp; Network Co. KESS Enterprise on Windows allows Privilege Escalation, Modify Existing Service, Modify Shared File.This issue affects KESS Enterprise: before *.25.9.19.Exe.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 01:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15163 | Tenda WH450 SafeEmailFilter stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15163</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /goform/SafeEmailFilter. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 01:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15164 | Tenda WH450 SafeMacFilter stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15164</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. This affects an unknown part of the file /goform/SafeMacFilter. The manipulation of the argument page results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 01:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15162 | Tenda WH450 RouteStatic stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15162</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /goform/RouteStatic. Executing manipulation of the argument page can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 23:36:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15161 | Tenda WH450 PPTPUserSetting stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15161</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. Affected is an unknown function of the file /goform/PPTPUserSetting. Performing manipulation of the argument delno results in stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 23:20:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15160 | Tenda WH450 PPTPServer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15160</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/PPTPServer. Such manipulation of the argument ip1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 22:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15156 | omec-project UPF PFCP Session Establishment Request messages_session.go handleSessionEstablishmentRequest null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15156</link><description>A flaw has been found in omec-project UPF up to 2.1.3-dev. This affects the function handleSessionEstablishmentRequest of the file /pfcpiface/pfcpiface/messages_session.go of the component PFCP Session Establishment Request Handler. This manipulation causes null pointer dereference. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 22:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15155 | floooh sokol sokol_gfx.h _sg_pipeline_desc_defaults stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15155</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in floooh sokol up to 16cbcc864012898793cd2bc57f802499a264ea40. The impacted element is the function _sg_pipeline_desc_defaults in the library sokol_gfx.h. The manipulation results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack requires a local approach. The exploit is now public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The patch is identified as 5d11344150973f15e16d3ec4ee7550a73fb995e0. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 21:44:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15154 | PbootCMS Header handle.php get_user_ip less trusted source</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15154</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in PbootCMS up to 3.2.12. The affected element is the function get_user_ip of the file core/function/handle.php of the component Header Handler. The manipulation of the argument X-Forwarded-For leads to use of less trusted source. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 21:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15153 | PbootCMS SQLite Database pbootcms.db file access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15153</link><description>A weakness has been identified in PbootCMS up to 3.2.12. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /data/pbootcms.db of the component SQLite Database. Executing manipulation can lead to files or directories accessible. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. Modifying the configuration settings is advised.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 20:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15152 | h-moses moga-mall PmsProductController.java addProduct unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15152</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in h-moses moga-mall up to 392d631a5ef15962a9bddeeb9f1269b9085473fa. This vulnerability affects the function addProduct of the file src/main/java/com/ms/product/controller/PmsProductController.java. Such manipulation of the argument objectName leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. This product utilizes a rolling release system for continuous delivery, and as such, version information for affected or updated releases is not disclosed.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 20:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15151 | TaleLin Lin-CMS Tests Folder config.py password in configuration file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15151</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in TaleLin Lin-CMS up to 0.6.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /tests/config.py of the component Tests Folder. This manipulation of the argument username/password causes password in configuration file. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. It is indicated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15150 | PX4 PX4-Autopilot mavlink_log_handler.cpp log_entry_from_id stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15150</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PX4 PX4-Autopilot up to 1.16.0. Affected by this issue is the function MavlinkLogHandler::state_listing/MavlinkLogHandler::log_entry_from_id of the file src/modules/mavlink/mavlink_log_handler.cpp. The manipulation results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is only possible with local access. The patch is identified as 338595edd1d235efd885fd5e9f45e7f9dcf4013d. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15149 | rawchen ecms Add New Product updateProductServlet.java updateProductServlet cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15149</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in rawchen ecms up to b59d7feaa9094234e8aa6c8c6b290621ca575ded. Affected by this vulnerability is the function updateProductServlet of the file src/servlet/product/updateProductServlet.java of the component Add New Product Page. The manipulation of the argument productName leads to cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 18:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15148 | CmsEasy Backend Template Management template_admin.php savetemp_action code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15148</link><description>A flaw has been found in CmsEasy up to 7.7.7. Affected is the function savetemp_action in the library /lib/admin/template_admin.php of the component Backend Template Management Page. Executing manipulation of the argument content/tempdata can lead to code injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 18:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15146 | SohuTV CacheCloud UserManageController.java doUserList cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15146</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SohuTV CacheCloud up to 3.2.0. This impacts the function doUserList of the file src/main/java/com/sohu/cache/web/controller/UserManageController.java. Performing manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 17:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15145 | SohuTV CacheCloud TotalManageController.java doTotalList cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15145</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SohuTV CacheCloud up to 3.2.0. This affects the function doTotalList of the file src/main/java/com/sohu/cache/web/controller/TotalManageController.java. Such manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 17:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15144 | dayrui XunRuiCMS JSONP Callback Init.php dr_exit_msg cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15144</link><description>A weakness has been identified in dayrui XunRuiCMS up to 4.7.1. The impacted element is the function dr_show_error/dr_exit_msg of the file /dayrui/Fcms/Init.php of the component JSONP Callback Handler. This manipulation of the argument callback causes cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68973 | In GnuPG through 2.4.8, armor_filter in g10/armor.c has two increments of an index variable where one is intended, leading to an out-of-boun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68973</link><description>In GnuPG through 2.4.8, armor_filter in g10/armor.c has two increments of an index variable where one is intended, leading to an out-of-bounds write for crafted input.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15143 | EyouCMS Backend Template Management FilemanagerLogic.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15143</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in EyouCMS up to 1.7.6. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /application/admin/logic/FilemanagerLogic.php of the component Backend Template Management. The manipulation of the argument content results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15142 | 9786 phpok3w show.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15142</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in 9786 phpok3w up to 901d96a06809fb28b17f3a4362c59e70411c933c. Impacted is an unknown function of the file show.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15141 | Halo Configuration actuator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15141</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Halo up to 2.21.10. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /actuator of the component Configuration Handler. Executing manipulation can lead to information disclosure. The attack may be performed from remote. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15140 | saiftheboss7 onlinemcqexam quesadd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15140</link><description>A vulnerability was found in saiftheboss7 onlinemcqexam up to 0e56806132971e49721db3ef01868098c7b42ada. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/quesadd.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ans1/ans2 results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15139 | TRENDnet TEW-822DRE formWsc sub_43ACF4  command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15139</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TRENDnet TEW-822DRE 1.00B21/1.01B06. This affects the function sub_43ACF4  of the file /boafrm/formWsc. Such manipulation of the argument peerPin leads to command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:12:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15138 | prasathmani TinyFileManager tinyfilemanager.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15138</link><description>A flaw has been found in prasathmani TinyFileManager up to 2.6. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file tinyfilemanager.php. This manipulation of the argument fullpath causes path traversal. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 13:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15137 | TRENDnet TEW-800MB NTPSyncWithHost.cgi sub_F934  command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15137</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in TRENDnet TEW-800MB 1.0.1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_F934  of the file NTPSyncWithHost.cgi. The manipulation results in command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 13:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15136 | TRENDnet TEW-800MB Management wizardset do_setWizard_asp command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15136</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in TRENDnet TEW-800MB 1.0.1.0. Affected is the function do_setWizard_asp of the file /goform/wizardset of the component Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument WizardConfigured leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15135 | joey-zhou xiaozhi-esp32-server-java Cookie AuthenticationInterceptor.java tryAuthenticateWithCookies improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15135</link><description>A weakness has been identified in joey-zhou xiaozhi-esp32-server-java up to 3.0.0. This impacts the function tryAuthenticateWithCookies of the file AuthenticationInterceptor.java of the component Cookie Handler. Executing manipulation can lead to improper authentication. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. Upgrading to version 4.0.0 will fix this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15134 | yourmaileyes MOOC Submission MainController.java subreview cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15134</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in yourmaileyes MOOC up to 1.17. This affects the function subreview of the file mooc/controller/MainController.java of the component Submission Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument review results in cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 11:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15133 | ZSPACE Z4Pro+ HTTP POST Request close zfilev2_api_CloseSafe command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15133</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in ZSPACE Z4Pro+ 1.0.0440024. The impacted element is the function zfilev2_api_CloseSafe of the file /v2/file/safe/close of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. Such manipulation leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 11:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15132 | ZSPACE Z4Pro+ HTTP POST Request open zfilev2_api_open command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15132</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in ZSPACE Z4Pro+ 1.0.0440024. The affected element is the function zfilev2_api_open of the file /v2/file/safe/open of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. This manipulation causes command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15131 | ZSPACE Z4Pro+ HTTP POST Request status zfilev2_api_SafeStatus command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15131</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZSPACE Z4Pro+ 1.0.0440024. Impacted is the function zfilev2_api_SafeStatus of the file /v2/file/safe/status of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation results in command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15130 | shanyu SyCms Administrative Panel FileManageController.class.php addPost code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15130</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in shanyu SyCms up to a242ef2d194e8bb249dc175e7c49f2c1673ec921. This issue affects the function addPost of the file Application/Admin/Controller/FileManageController.class.php of the component Administrative Panel. The manipulation leads to code injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15129 | ChenJinchuang Lin-CMS-TP5 File Upload LocalUploader.php upload code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15129</link><description>A flaw has been found in ChenJinchuang Lin-CMS-TP5 up to 0.3.3. This vulnerability affects the function Upload of the file application/lib/file/LocalUploader.php of the component File Upload Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument File can lead to code injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15128 | ZKTeco BioTime Endpoint safe_setting credentials storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15128</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in ZKTeco BioTime up to 9.0.3/9.0.4/9.5.2. This affects an unknown part of the file /base/safe_setting/ of the component Endpoint. Performing manipulation of the argument backup_encryption_password_decrypt/export_encryption_password_decrypt results in unprotected storage of credentials. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15127 | FantasticLBP Hotels_Server Room.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15127</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in FantasticLBP Hotels_Server up to 67b44df162fab26df209bd5d5d542875fcbec1d0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /controller/api/Room.php. Such manipulation of the argument hotelId leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product operates on a rolling release basis, ensuring continuous delivery. Consequently, there are no version details for either affected or updated releases. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15126 | JeecgBoot getPositionUserList improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15126</link><description>A weakness has been identified in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getPositionUserList of the file /sys/position/getPositionUserList. This manipulation of the argument positionId causes improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 07:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15125 | JeecgBoot queryDepartPermission improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15125</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. Affected is the function queryDepartPermission of the file /sys/permission/queryDepartPermission. The manipulation of the argument departId results in improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 07:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15124 | JeecgBoot list getParameterMap improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15124</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. This impacts the function getParameterMap of the file /sys/sysDepartPermission/list. The manipulation of the argument departId leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is said to be difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15123 | JeecgBoot datarule improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15123</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /sys/sysDepartPermission/datarule/. Executing manipulation can lead to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The attack requires a high level of complexity. The exploitability is reported as difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15122 | JeecgBoot datarule loadDatarule improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15122</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. The impacted element is the function loadDatarule of the file /sys/sysDepartRole/datarule/. Performing manipulation of the argument departId/roleId results in improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 05:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15121 | JeecgBoot getDeptRoleByUserId information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15121</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. The affected element is the function getDeptRoleByUserId of the file /sys/sysDepartRole/getDeptRoleByUserId. Such manipulation of the argument departId leads to information disclosure. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 04:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15120 | JeecgBoot getDeptRoleList improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15120</link><description>A flaw has been found in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. Impacted is the function getDeptRoleList of the file /sys/sysDepartRole/getDeptRoleList. This manipulation of the argument departId causes improper authorization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. A high degree of complexity is needed for the attack. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 04:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15119 | JeecgBoot list queryPageList improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15119</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. This issue affects the function queryPageList of the file /sys/sysDepartRole/list. The manipulation of the argument deptId results in improper authorization. The attack can be executed remotely. A high complexity level is associated with this attack. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 04:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15118 | macrozheng mall Member Endpoint update improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15118</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in macrozheng mall up to 1.0.3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /member/address/update/ of the component Member Endpoint. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 04:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15116 | OpenCart Single-Use Coupon race condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15116</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in OpenCart up to 4.1.0.3. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Single-Use Coupon Handler. Performing manipulation results in race condition. The attack may be initiated remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 03:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15117 | Dromara Sa-Token SaJdkSerializer.java ObjectInputStream.readObject deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15117</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Dromara Sa-Token up to 1.44.0. This affects the function ObjectInputStream.readObject of the file SaJdkSerializer.java. Executing manipulation can lead to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. It is indicated that the exploitability is difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 03:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68972 | In GnuPG through 2.4.8, if a signed message has \f at the end of a plaintext line, an adversary can construct a modified message that places...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68972</link><description>In GnuPG through 2.4.8, if a signed message has \f at the end of a plaintext line, an adversary can construct a modified message that places additional text after the signed material, such that signature verification of the modified message succeeds (although an "invalid armor" message is printed during verification). This is related to use of \f as a marker to denote truncation of a long plaintext line.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 23:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15110 | jackq XCMS Backend ProductImageController.class.php upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15110</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in jackq XCMS up to 3fab5342cc509945a7ce1b8ec39d19f701b89261. Affected is the function Upload of the file Admin/Home/Controller/ProductImageController.class.php of the component Backend. Such manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 20:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14177 | Information Leak of Memory in getimagesize</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14177</link><description>In PHP versions:8.1.* before 8.1.34, 8.2.* before 8.2.30, 8.3.* before 8.3.29, 8.4.* before 8.4.16, 8.5.* before 8.5.1, the getimagesize() function may leak uninitialized heap memory into the APPn segments (e.g., APP1) when reading images in multi-chunk mode (such as via php://filter). This occurs due to a bug in php_read_stream_all_chunks() that overwrites the buffer without advancing the pointer, leaving tail bytes uninitialized. This may lead to information disclosure of sensitive heap data and affect the confidentiality of the target server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14178 | Heap buffer overflow in array_merge()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14178</link><description>In PHP versions:8.1.* before 8.1.34, 8.2.* before 8.2.30, 8.3.* before 8.3.29, 8.4.* before 8.4.16, 8.5.* before 8.5.1, a heap buffer overflow occurs in array_merge() when the total element count of packed arrays exceeds 32-bit limits or HT_MAX_SIZE, due to an integer overflow in the precomputation of element counts using zend_hash_num_elements(). This may lead to memory corruption or crashes and affect the integrity and availability of the target server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14180 | NULL Pointer Dereference in PDO quoting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14180</link><description>In PHP versions 8.1.* before 8.1.34, 8.2.* before 8.2.30, 8.3.* before 8.3.29, 8.4.* before 8.4.16, 8.5.* before 8.5.1 when using the PDO PostgreSQL driver with PDO::ATTR_EMULATE_PREPARES enabled, an invalid character sequence (such as \x99) in a prepared statement parameter may cause the quoting function PQescapeStringConn to return NULL, leading to a null pointer dereference in pdo_parse_params() function. This may lead to crashes (segmentation fault) and affect the availability of the target server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15109 | jackq XCMS upload.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15109</link><description>A flaw has been found in jackq XCMS up to 3fab5342cc509945a7ce1b8ec39d19f701b89261. This impacts an unknown function of the file Public/javascripts/admin/plupload-2.1.2/examples/upload.php. This manipulation causes unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15108 | PandaXGO PandaX JWT Secret config.yml hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15108</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in PandaXGO PandaX up to fb8ff40f7ce5dfebdf66306c6d85625061faf7e5. This affects an unknown function of the file config.yml of the component JWT Secret Handler. The manipulation of the argument key results in use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The attack may be performed from remote. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is reported as difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. This product utilizes a rolling release system for continuous delivery, and as such, version information for affected or updated releases is not disclosed. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54322 | Xspeeder SXZOS through 2025-12-26 allows root remote code execution via base64-encoded Python code in the chkid parameter to vLogin.py. The ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54322</link><description>Xspeeder SXZOS through 2025-12-26 allows root remote code execution via base64-encoded Python code in the chkid parameter to vLogin.py. The title and oIP parameters are also used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 13:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15107 | actiontech sqle JWT Secret jwt.go hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15107</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in actiontech sqle up to 4.2511.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file sqle/utils/jwt.go of the component JWT Secret Handler. The manipulation of the argument JWTSecretKey leads to use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report and is planning to fix this flaw in an upcoming release.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 13:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15106 | getmaxun Authentication Endpoint auth.ts router.get improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15106</link><description>A weakness has been identified in getmaxun maxun up to 0.0.28. The affected element is the function router.get of the file server/src/routes/auth.ts of the component Authentication Endpoint. Executing manipulation can lead to improper authorization. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 10:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15105 | getmaxun auth.ts hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15105</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in getmaxun maxun up to 0.0.28. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /getmaxun/maxun/blob/develop/server/src/routes/auth.ts. Performing manipulation of the argument api_key results in use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:23:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59946 | NanoMQ has a Use After Free vulnerability via sub info list</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59946</link><description>NanoMQ MQTT Broker (NanoMQ) is an Edge Messaging Platform. Prior to version 0.24.2, there is a classical data racing issue about sub info list which could result in heap use after free crash. This issue has been patched in version 0.24.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68927 | Improper Neutralization of  HTML Tags in a Web Page in libredesk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68927</link><description>Libredesk is a self-hosted customer support desk. Prior to version 0.8.6-beta, LibreDesk is vulnerable to stored HTML injection in the contact notes feature. When adding notes via POST /api/v1/contacts/{id}/notes, the backend automatically wraps user input in &lt;p&gt; tags. However, by intercepting the request and removing the &lt;p&gt; tag, an attacker can inject arbitrary HTML elements such as forms and images, which are then stored and rendered without proper sanitization. This can lead to phishing, CSRF-style forced actions, and UI redress attacks. This issue has been patched in version 0.8.6-beta.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68948 | SiYuan: Information Disclosure and Authentication Bypass via Hardcoded Session Secret</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68948</link><description>SiYuan is self-hosted, open source personal knowledge management software. In versions 3.5.1 and prior, the SiYuan Note application utilizes a hardcoded cryptographic secret for its session store. This unsafe practice renders the session encryption ineffective. Since the sensitive AccessAuthCode is stored within the session cookie, an attacker who intercepts or obtains a user's encrypted session cookie (e.g., via session hijacking) can locally decrypt it using the public key. Once decrypted, the attacker can retrieve the AccessAuthCode in plain text and use it to authenticate or take over the session.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68952 | 1-click Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in Eigent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68952</link><description>Eigent is a multi-agent Workforce. In version 0.0.60, a 1-click Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability has been identified in Eigent. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the victim's machine or server through a specific interaction (1-click). This issue has been patched in version 0.0.61.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68473 | ESF-IDF Has Out-of-Bounds Read in ESP32 Bluetooth SDP Result Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68473</link><description>ESF-IDF is the Espressif Internet of Things (IOT) Development Framework. In versions 5.5.1, 5.4.3, 5.3.4, 5.2.6, 5.1.6, and earlier, in the ESP-IDF Bluetooth host stack (BlueDroid), the function bta_dm_sdp_result() used a fixed-size array uuid_list[32][MAX_UUID_SIZE] to store discovered service UUIDs during the SDP (Service Discovery Protocol) process. On modern Bluetooth devices, it is possible for the number of available services to exceed this fixed limit (32). In such cases, if more than 32 services are discovered, subsequent writes to uuid_list could exceed the bounds of the array, resulting in a potential out-of-bounds write condition.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:21:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68474 | ESF-IDF Has Out-of-Bounds Write in ESP32 Bluetooth AVRCP Vendor Command Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68474</link><description>ESF-IDF is the Espressif Internet of Things (IOT) Development Framework. In versions 5.5.1, 5.4.3, 5.3.4, 5.2.6, 5.1.6, and earlier, in the avrc_vendor_msg() function of the ESP-IDF BlueDroid AVRCP stack, the allocated buffer size was validated using AVRC_MIN_CMD_LEN (20 bytes). However, the actual fixed header data written before the vendor payload exceeds this value. This totals 29 bytes written before p_msg-&gt;p_vendor_data is copied. Using the old AVRC_MIN_CMD_LEN could allow an out-of-bounds write if vendor_len approaches the buffer limit. For commands where vendor_len is large, the original buffer allocation may be insufficient, causing writes beyond the allocated memory. This can lead to memory corruption, crashes, or other undefined behavior. The overflow could be larger when assertions are disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:21:48 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>