<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 01:37:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-28122 |  JWX vulnerable to a denial of service attack using compressed JWE message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28122</link><description>JWX is Go module implementing various JWx (JWA/JWE/JWK/JWS/JWT, otherwise known as JOSE) technologies. This vulnerability allows an attacker with a trusted public key to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS) condition by crafting a malicious JSON Web Encryption (JWE) token with an exceptionally high compression ratio. This issue has been patched in versions 1.2.29 and 2.0.21.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 01:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28176 | jose vulnerable to resource exhaustion via specifically crafted JWE with compressed plaintext</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28176</link><description>jose is JavaScript module for JSON Object Signing and Encryption, providing support for JSON Web Tokens (JWT), JSON Web Signature (JWS), JSON Web Encryption (JWE), JSON Web Key (JWK), JSON Web Key Set (JWKS), and more. A vulnerability has 
 been identified in the JSON Web Encryption (JWE) decryption interfaces, specifically related to the support for decompressing plaintext after its decryption. Under certain conditions it is possible to have the user's environment consume unreasonable amount of CPU time or memory during JWE Decryption operations. This issue has been patched in versions 2.0.7 and 4.15.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 01:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28180 | Go JOSE vulnerable to Improper Handling of Highly Compressed Data (Data Amplification)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28180</link><description>Package jose aims to provide an implementation of the Javascript Object Signing and Encryption set of standards. An attacker could send a JWE containing compressed data that used large amounts of memory and CPU when decompressed by Decrypt or DecryptMulti. Those functions now return an error if the decompressed data would exceed 250kB or 10x the compressed size (whichever is larger). This vulnerability has been patched in versions 4.0.1, 3.0.3 and 2.6.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 01:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28184 | WeasyPrint allows the attachment of arbitrary files and URLs to a PDF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28184</link><description>WeasyPrint helps web developers to create PDF documents. Since version 61.0, there's a vulnerability which allows attaching content of arbitrary files and URLs to a generated PDF document, even if `url_fetcher` is configured to prevent access to files and URLs. This vulnerability has been patched in version 61.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 01:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28753 | RaspAP (aka raspap-webgui) through 3.0.9 allows remote attackers to read the /etc/passwd file via a crafted request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28753</link><description>RaspAP (aka raspap-webgui) through 3.0.9 allows remote attackers to read the /etc/passwd file via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 23:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28754 | RaspAP (aka raspap-webgui) through 3.0.9 allows remote attackers to cause a persistent denial of service (bricking) via a crafted request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28754</link><description>RaspAP (aka raspap-webgui) through 3.0.9 allows remote attackers to cause a persistent denial of service (bricking) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 23:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28123 | Wasmi Out-of-bounds Write for host to Wasm calls with more than 128 Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28123</link><description>Wasmi is an efficient and lightweight WebAssembly interpreter with a focus on constrained and embedded systems. In the WASMI Interpreter, an Out-of-bounds Buffer Write will arise if the host calls or resumes a Wasm function with more parameters than the default limit (128), as it will surpass the stack value. This doesn’t affect calls from Wasm to Wasm, only from host to Wasm. This vulnerability was patched in version 0.31.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 21:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32264 | CWE-1385 vulnerability in OpenText Documentum D2 affecting versions16.5.1 to CE 23.2. The vulnerability could allow upload arbitrary code an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32264</link><description>CWE-1385 vulnerability in OpenText Documentum D2 affecting versions16.5.1 to CE 23.2. The vulnerability could allow upload arbitrary code and execute it on the client's computer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 20:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2338 | SQL Injection in PostgreSQL Anonymizer 1.2 allows table owner to gain superuser privileges via masking rule</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2338</link><description>PostgreSQL Anonymizer v1.2 contains a SQL injection vulnerability that allows a user who owns a table to elevate to superuser when dynamic masking is enabled. PostgreSQL Anonymizer enables users to set security labels on tables to mask specified columns. There is a flaw that allows complex expressions to be provided as a value. This expression is then later used as it to create the masked views leading to SQL Injection. If dynamic masking is enabled, this will lead to privilege escalation to superuser after the label is created. Users that don't own a table, especially masked users cannot exploit this vulnerability. The problem is resolved in v1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 20:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2339 | Improper Input Validation in PostgreSQL Anonymizer 1.2 allows table owner to gain superuser privileges via masking rule</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2339</link><description>PostgreSQL Anonymizer v1.2 contains a vulnerability  that allows a user who owns a table to elevate to superuser. A user can define a masking function for a column and place malicious code in that function. When a privileged user applies the masking rules using the static masking or the anonymous dump method, the malicious code is executed and can grant escalated privileges to the malicious user. PostgreSQL Anonymizer v1.2 does provide a protection against this risk with the restrict_to_trusted_schemas option, but that protection is incomplete. Users that don't own a table, especially masked users cannot exploit this vulnerability. The problem is resolved in v1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 20:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43855 | IBM SPSS Statistics denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43855</link><description>IBM SPSS Statistics 26.0, 27.0.1, and 28.0 could allow a local user to create multiple files that could exhaust the file handles capacity and cause a denial of service.  IBM X-Force ID:  230235.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21899 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21899</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to compromise the security of the system via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21900 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21900</link><description>An injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21901 | myQNAPcloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21901</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been reported to affect myQNAPcloud. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
myQNAPcloud 1.0.52 ( 2023/11/24 ) and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32969 | Network &amp;amp; Virtual Switch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32969</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect Network &amp; Virtual Switch. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34980 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34980</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47221 | Photo Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47221</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect Photo Station. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to read the contents of unexpected files and expose sensitive data via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Photo Station 6.4.2 ( 2023/12/15 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2319 | Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in Django MarkdownX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2319</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Django MarkdownX project, affecting version 4.0.2. An attacker could store a specially crafted JavaScript payload in the upload functionality due to lack of proper sanitisation of JavaScript elements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 13:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2318 | ZKTeco ZKBio Media Service Port 9999 download path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2318</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZKTeco ZKBio Media 2.0.0_x64_2024-01-29-1028. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pro/common/download of the component Service Port 9999. The manipulation of the argument fileName with the input ../../../../zkbio_media.sql leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256272. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 13:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2317 | Bdtask Hospital AutoManager Prescription Page improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2317</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Bdtask Hospital AutoManager up to 20240227 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /prescription/prescription/delete/ of the component Prescription Page. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256271. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 12:14:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2316 | Bdtask Hospital AutoManager Update Bill Page cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2316</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Bdtask Hospital AutoManager up to 20240227 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /billing/bill/edit/ of the component Update Bill Page. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256270 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 11:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1851 | The affiliate-toolkit – WordPress Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability che...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1851</link><description>The affiliate-toolkit – WordPress Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the atkp_create_list() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to to perform unauthorized actions such as creating product lists.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 07:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2298 | The affiliate-toolkit – WordPress Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability che...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2298</link><description>The affiliate-toolkit – WordPress Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the atkp_import_product() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to to perform unauthorized actions such as creating importing products.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 07:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27612 | Numbas editor before 7.3 mishandles editing of themes and extensions.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27612</link><description>Numbas editor before 7.3 mishandles editing of themes and extensions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 05:56:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27613 | Numbas editor before 7.3 mishandles reading of themes and extensions.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27613</link><description>Numbas editor before 7.3 mishandles reading of themes and extensions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 05:56:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1987 | The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1987</link><description>The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.9.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 05:36:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2285 | boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System member_edit.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2285</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /member/member_edit.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256052. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 03:07:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2284 | boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System Chat Book chat.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2284</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /member/chat.php of the component Chat Book. The manipulation of the argument msg leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256051. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-6268 | RAD SecFlow-2 devices with Hardware 0202, Firmware 4.1.01.63, and U-Boot 2010.12 allow URIs beginning with /.. for Directory Traversal, as d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6268</link><description>RAD SecFlow-2 devices with Hardware 0202, Firmware 4.1.01.63, and U-Boot 2010.12 allow URIs beginning with /.. for Directory Traversal, as demonstrated by reading /etc/shadow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26309 | Archer Platform 6.x before 6.14 P2 HF2 (6.14.0.2.2) contains a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26309</link><description>Archer Platform 6.x before 6.14 P2 HF2 (6.14.0.2.2) contains a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker could potentially obtain access to sensitive information via an internal URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26313 | Archer Platform 6.x before 6.14 P2 HF2 (6.14.0.2.2) contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. A remote authenticated malic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26313</link><description>Archer Platform 6.x before 6.14 P2 HF2 (6.14.0.2.2) contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially exploit this to store malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a trusted application data store. When victim users access the data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable application. 6.13.P3 HF1 (6.13.0.3.1) is also a fixed release.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2283 | boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System view.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2283</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /member/view.php. The manipulation of the argument date leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256050 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25845 | In the module "CD Custom Fields 4 Orders" (cdcustomfields4orders) &lt;= 1.0.0 from Cleanpresta.com for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL inje...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25845</link><description>In the module "CD Custom Fields 4 Orders" (cdcustomfields4orders) &lt;= 1.0.0 from Cleanpresta.com for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection in affected versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25848 | In the module "Ever Ultimate SEO" (everpsseo) &lt;= 8.1.2 from Team Ever for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection in affected versions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25848</link><description>In the module "Ever Ultimate SEO" (everpsseo) &lt;= 8.1.2 from Team Ever for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection in affected versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25849 | In the module "Make an offer" (makeanoffer) &lt;= 1.7.1 from PrestaToolKit for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection via MakeOffers::ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25849</link><description>In the module "Make an offer" (makeanoffer) &lt;= 1.7.1 from PrestaToolKit for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection via MakeOffers::checkUserExistingOffer()` and `MakeOffers::addUserOffer()` .</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28826 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, macOS Monter...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28826</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0258 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0258</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchOS 10.4. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code out of its sandbox or with certain elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23201 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, macOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23201</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, macOS Sonoma 14.3. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23205 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23205</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23216 | A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23216</link><description>A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to overwrite arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23220 | The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An app may be able ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23220</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An app may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23226 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, wat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23226</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, tvOS 17.4. Processing web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23227 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23227</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to read sensitive location information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23230 | This issue was addressed with improved file handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23230</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved file handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23231 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonom...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23231</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23232 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to cap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23232</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to capture a user's screen.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23233 | This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. Entitlements and privacy permissions granted to thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23233</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. Entitlements and privacy permissions granted to this app may be used by a malicious app.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23234 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23234</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23235 | A race condition was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23235</link><description>A race condition was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, tvOS 17.4. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23238 | An access issue was addressed with improved access restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to edit NVRAM ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23238</link><description>An access issue was addressed with improved access restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to edit NVRAM variables.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23239 | A race condition was addressed with improved state handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23239</link><description>A race condition was addressed with improved state handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchOS 10.4. An app may be able to leak sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23240 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. Shake-to-undo may allow a deleted photo to be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23240</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. Shake-to-undo may allow a deleted photo to be re-surfaced without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23241 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4. A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23241</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to leak sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23242 | A privacy issue was addressed by not logging contents of text fields. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23242</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed by not logging contents of text fields. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An app may be able to view Mail data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23244 | A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4. An app from a stand...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23244</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4. An app from a standard user account may be able to escalate privilege after admin user login.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23245 | This issue was addressed by adding an additional prompt for user consent. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23245</link><description>This issue was addressed by adding an additional prompt for user consent. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. Third-party shortcuts may use a legacy action from Automator to send events to apps without user consent.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23246 | This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23246</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, tvOS 17.4. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23247 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23247</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. Processing a file may lead to unexpected app termination or arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23248 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing a file may lead to a denial-of-s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23248</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing a file may lead to a denial-of-service or potentially disclose memory contents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23249 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing a file may lead to a denial-of-s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23249</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing a file may lead to a denial-of-service or potentially disclose memory contents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23250 | An access issue was addressed with improved access restrictions. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23250</link><description>An access issue was addressed with improved access restrictions. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchOS 10.4. An app may be able to access Bluetooth-connected microphones without user permission.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23252 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4. Proc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23252</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing web content may lead to a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23253 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to access a use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23253</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to access a user's Photos Library.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23254 | The issue was addressed with improved UI handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23254</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved UI handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, Safari 17.4. A malicious website may exfiltrate audio data cross-origin.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23255 | An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. Ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23255</link><description>An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. Photos in the Hidden Photos Album may be viewed without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23257 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23257</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6. Processing an image may result in disclosure of process memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23258 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.1, macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing an im...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23258</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.1, macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing an image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23259 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23259</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing web content may lead to a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23260 | This issue was addressed by removing additional entitlements. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to access user-se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23260</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing additional entitlements. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23262 | This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, iOS 16.7.6 and i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23262</link><description>This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6. An app may be able to spoof system notifications and UI.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23263 | A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23263</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, Safari 17.4. Processing maliciously crafted web content may prevent Content Security Policy from being enforced.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23264 | A validation issue was addressed with improved input sanitization. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23264</link><description>A validation issue was addressed with improved input sanitization. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, tvOS 17.4. An application may be able to read restricted memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23265 | A memory corruption vulnerability was addressed with improved locking. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23265</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability was addressed with improved locking. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, tvOS 17.4. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or write kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23266 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23266</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23267 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23267</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to bypass certain Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23268 | An injection issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Vent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23268</link><description>An injection issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to elevate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23269 | A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23269</link><description>A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23270 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23270</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, tvOS 17.4. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23272 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. A u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23272</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. A user may gain access to protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23273 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23273</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4. Private Browsing tabs may be accessed without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23274 | An injection issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Vent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23274</link><description>An injection issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to elevate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23275 | A race condition was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23275</link><description>A race condition was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23276 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23276</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to elevate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23277 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An attacker in a privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23277</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An attacker in a privileged network position may be able to inject keystrokes by spoofing a keyboard.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23278 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23278</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, tvOS 17.4. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23279 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23279</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:03:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23280 | An injection issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in Safari 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23280</link><description>An injection issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in Safari 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, tvOS 17.4. A maliciously crafted webpage may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23281 | This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to access sensitive us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23281</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23283 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, mac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23283</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23284 | A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23284</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, Safari 17.4. Processing maliciously crafted web content may prevent Content Security Policy from being enforced.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23285 | This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to create symlinks...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23285</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to create symlinks to protected regions of the disk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23286 | A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, mac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23286</link><description>A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Sonoma 14.4, visionOS 1.1, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4, iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, tvOS 17.4. Processing an image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23287 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23287</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23288 | This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, wat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23288</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchOS 10.4. An app may be able to elevate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23289 | A lock screen issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23289</link><description>A lock screen issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.6 and iPadOS 16.7.6, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchOS 10.4. A person with physical access to a device may be able to use Siri to access private calendar information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23290 | A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23290</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchOS 10.4. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23291 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23291</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchOS 10.4. A malicious app may be able to observe user data in log entries related to accessibility notifications.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23292 | This issue was addressed with improved data protection. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An app may be ab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23292</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved data protection. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. An app may be able to access information about a user's contacts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23293 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23293</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma 14.4, watchOS 10.4. An attacker with physical access may be able to use Siri to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23294 | This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing malicious input may lead to c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23294</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. Processing malicious input may lead to code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23295 | A permissions issue was addressed to help ensure Personas are always protected This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.1. An unauthenticated user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23295</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed to help ensure Personas are always protected This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.1. An unauthenticated user may be able to use an unprotected Persona.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23297 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4. A malicious applicat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23297</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.4, iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, watchOS 10.4. A malicious application may be able to access private information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2282 | boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System Login Page index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2282</link><description>A vulnerability was found in boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /index.php of the component Login Page. The manipulation of the argument useremail leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256049 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:04:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2277 | Bdtask G-Prescription Gynaecology &amp;amp; OBS Consultation Software Password Reset change_password_save cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2277</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Bdtask G-Prescription Gynaecology &amp; OBS Consultation Software 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Setting/change_password_save of the component Password Reset Handler. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256046 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 01:31:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2281 | boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System Setting index.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2281</link><description>A vulnerability was found in boyiddha Automated-Mess-Management-System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/index.php of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256048. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 01:31:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2276 | Bdtask G-Prescription Gynaecology &amp;amp; OBS Consultation Software Edit Venue Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2276</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Bdtask G-Prescription Gynaecology &amp; OBS Consultation Software 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Venue_controller/edit_venue/ of the component Edit Venue Page. The manipulation of the argument Venue map leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256045 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 01:31:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2274 | Bdtask G-Prescription Gynaecology &amp;amp; OBS Consultation Software Prescription Dashboard Index cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2274</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Bdtask G-Prescription Gynaecology &amp; OBS Consultation Software 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Home/Index of the component Prescription Dashboard. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256043. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2275 | Bdtask G-Prescription Gynaecology &amp;amp; OBS Consultation Software OBS Patient/Gynee Prescription cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2275</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Bdtask G-Prescription Gynaecology &amp; OBS Consultation Software 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component OBS Patient/Gynee Prescription. The manipulation of the argument Patient Title/Full Name/Address/Cheif Complain/LMP/Menstrual Edd/OBS P/OBS Alc/Medicine Name/Medicine Type/Ml/Dose/Days/Comments/Template Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256044. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2271 | keerti1924 Online-Book-Store-Website HTTP POST Request shop.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2271</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in keerti1924 Online-Book-Store-Website 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /shop.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument product_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256041 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 23:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2272 | keerti1924 Online-Book-Store-Website HTTP POST Request home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2272</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in keerti1924 Online-Book-Store-Website 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /home.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument product_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256042 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 23:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25327 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Justice Systems FullCourt Enterprise v.8.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25327</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Justice Systems FullCourt Enterprise v.8.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the formatCaseNumber parameter of the Citation search function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 23:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25729 | Arris SBG6580 devices have predictable default WPA2 security passwords that could lead to unauthorized remote access. (They use the first 6 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25729</link><description>Arris SBG6580 devices have predictable default WPA2 security passwords that could lead to unauthorized remote access. (They use the first 6 characters of the SSID and the last 6 characters of the BSSID, decrementing the last octet.)</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 23:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2269 | keerti1924 Online-Book-Store-Website search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2269</link><description>A vulnerability was found in keerti1924 Online-Book-Store-Website 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /search.php. The manipulation of the argument search leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256039. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 23:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2270 | keerti1924 Online-Book-Store-Website signup.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2270</link><description>A vulnerability was found in keerti1924 Online-Book-Store-Website 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /signup.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256040. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 23:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2268 | keerti1924 Online-Book-Store-Website unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2268</link><description>A vulnerability was found in keerti1924 Online-Book-Store-Website 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /product_update.php?update=1. The manipulation of the argument update_image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256038 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 22:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2267 | keerti1924 Online-Book-Store-Website shop.php logic error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2267</link><description>A vulnerability was found in keerti1924 Online-Book-Store-Website 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /shop.php. The manipulation of the argument product_price leads to business logic errors. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256037 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 22:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2265 | keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System login.sql inclusion of sensitive information in source code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2265</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file login.sql. The manipulation leads to inclusion of sensitive information in source code. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256035. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 21:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2266 | keerti1924 Secret-Coder-PHP-Project Login Page login.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2266</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in keerti1924 Secret-Coder-PHP-Project 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /login.php of the component Login Page. The manipulation of the argument emailcookie/passwordcookie leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256036. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 21:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27707 | Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in hcengineering Huly Platform v.0.6.202 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via upload ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27707</link><description>Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in hcengineering Huly Platform v.0.6.202 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via upload of crafted SVG file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 21:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2264 | keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2264</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256034 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 21:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26492 | An issue in Online Diagnostic Lab Management System 1.0 allows a remote attacker to gain control of a 'Staff' user account via a crafted POS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26492</link><description>An issue in Online Diagnostic Lab Management System 1.0 allows a remote attacker to gain control of a 'Staff' user account via a crafted POST request using the id, email, password, and cpass parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 21:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28115 | Privilege Escalation in FreeRTOS Kernel ARMv7-M MPU ports and ARMv8-M ports with MPU support enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28115</link><description>FreeRTOS is a real-time operating system for microcontrollers. FreeRTOS Kernel versions through 10.6.1 do not sufficiently protect against local privilege escalation via Return Oriented Programming techniques should a vulnerability exist that allows code injection and execution. These issues affect ARMv7-M MPU ports, and ARMv8-M ports with Memory Protected Unit (MPU) support enabled (i.e. `configENABLE_MPU` set to 1). These issues are fixed in version 10.6.2 with a new MPU wrapper.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 21:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24035 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Setor Informatica SIL 3.1 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the hmessage parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24035</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Setor Informatica SIL 3.1 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the hmessage parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2044 | Unsafe Deserialisation and Remote Code Execution by an Authenticated user in pgAdmin 4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2044</link><description>pgAdmin 4 uses a file-based session management approach. The session files are saved on disk as pickle objects. When a user performs a request, the value of the session cookie 'pga4_session' is used to retrieve the file, then its content is deserialised, and finally its signature verified.
The cookie value is split in 2 parts at the first '!' character. The first part is the session ID (sid), while the second is the session digest.
 The vulnerability lies in versions of pgAdmin prior to 8.4 where a method loads session files by concatenating the sessions folder - located inside the pgAdmin 4 DATA_DIR - with the session ID. Precisely, the two values are concatenated using the ['os.path.join'] function. It does not set a trusted base-path which should not be escaped</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46169 | IBM DS8900F file manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46169</link><description>IBM DS8900F HMC 89.21.19.0, 89.21.31.0, 89.30.68.0, 89.32.40.0, and 89.33.48.0 could allow an authenticated user to arbitrarily delete a file.  IBM X-Force ID:  269406.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46172 | IBM DS8900F security bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46172</link><description>IBM DS8900F HMC 89.21.19.0, 89.21.31.0, 89.30.68.0, 89.32.40.0, and 89.33.48.0 could allow a remote attacker to bypass authentication restrictions for authorized user.   IBM X-Force ID:  269409.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46170 | IBM DS8900F information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46170</link><description>IBM DS8900F HMC 89.21.19.0, 89.21.31.0, 89.30.68.0, 89.32.40.0, and 89.33.48.0 could allow an authenticated user to arbitrarily read files after enumerating file names. IBM X-Force ID: 269407.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1802 | The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor pl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1802</link><description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Wistia embed block in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the user supplied url. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1986 | The Booster Elite for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the wc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1986</link><description>The Booster Elite for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the wc_add_new_product() function in all versions up to, and including, 7.1.7. This makes it possible for customer-level attackers, and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. This is only exploitable when the user product upload functionality is enabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46171 | IBM DS8900F information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46171</link><description>IBM DS8900F HMC 89.21.19.0, 89.21.31.0, 89.30.68.0, 89.32.40.0, and 89.33.48.0 could allow an authenticated user to view sensitive log information after enumerating filenames.  IBM X-Force ID:  269408.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26167 | Microsoft Edge for Android Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26167</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1725 | Kubevirt-csi: pv allows access to hcp&amp;#x27;s root node</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1725</link><description>A flaw was found in the kubevirt-csi component of OpenShift Virtualization's Hosted Control Plane (HCP). This issue could allow an authenticated attacker to gain access to the root HCP worker node's volume by creating a custom Persistent Volume that matches the name of a worker node.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:11:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0203 | The Digits plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 8.4.1. This is due to missing ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0203</link><description>The Digits plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 8.4.1. This is due to missing nonce validation in the 'digits_save_settings' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the default role of registered users to elevate user privileges via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 19:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2127 | The Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via custom att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2127</link><description>The Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via custom attributes in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 19:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2128 | The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor pl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2128</link><description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's embed widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 19:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1773 | The PDF Invoices and Packing Slips For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and inc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1773</link><description>The PDF Invoices and Packing Slips For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7 via deserialization of untrusted input via the order_id parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 18:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1442 | User with permissions to create a data source can CRUD all data sources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1442</link><description>A user with the permissions to create a data source can use Grafana API to create a data source with UID set to *.
Doing this will grant the user access to read, query, edit and delete all data sources within the organization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 17:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22752 | Insecure permissions issue in EaseUS MobiMover 6.0.5 Build 21620 allows attackers to gain escalated privileges via use of crafted executable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22752</link><description>Insecure permissions issue in EaseUS MobiMover 6.0.5 Build 21620 allows attackers to gain escalated privileges via use of crafted executable launched from the application installation directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 17:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27733 | File Upload vulnerability in Byzro Network Smart s42 Management Platform v.S42 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27733</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in Byzro Network Smart s42 Management Platform v.S42 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the useratte/userattestation.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 17:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1351 | MongoDB Server may allow successful untrusted connection </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1351</link><description>Under certain configurations of --tlsCAFile and tls.CAFile, MongoDB Server may skip peer certificate validation which may result in untrusted connections to succeed. This may effectively reduce the security guarantees provided by TLS and open connections  that should have been closed due to failing certificate validation. This issue affects MongoDB Server v7.0 versions prior to and including 7.0.5, MongoDB Server v6.0 versions prior to and including 6.0.13, MongoDB Server v5.0 versions prior to and including 5.0.24 and MongoDB Server v4.4 versions prior to and including 4.4.28.

Required Configuration : A server process will allow incoming connections to skip peer certificate validation if the server process was started with TLS enabled (net.tls.mode set to allowTLS, preferTLS, or requireTLS) and without a net.tls.CAFile configured.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 16:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48725 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the JSON Parsing getblockschedule() functionality of Netgear RAX30 1.0.11.96 and 1.0.7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48725</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the JSON Parsing getblockschedule() functionality of Netgear RAX30 1.0.11.96 and 1.0.7.78. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to code execution. An attacker can make an authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42509 | JFrog Artifactory Sensitive Data Leakage in Repository configuration process</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42509</link><description>JFrog Artifactory later than version 7.17.4 but prior to version 7.77.0 is vulnerable to an issue whereby a sequence of improperly handled exceptions in repository configuration initialization steps may lead to exposure of sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 14:10:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42661 | JFrog Artifactory Improper input validation leads to arbitrary file write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42661</link><description>JFrog Artifactory prior to version 7.76.2 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Write of untrusted data, which may lead to DoS or Remote Code Execution when a specially crafted series of requests is sent by an authenticated user. This is due to insufficient validation of artifacts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 14:10:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47691 | WordPress Podlove Web Player Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7.3 is vulnerable to Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47691</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Podlove Podlove Web Player.This issue affects Podlove Web Player: from n/a through 5.7.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 13:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2241 | Improper access control in the user interface in Devolutions Workspace 2024.1.0 and earlier allows an authenticated user to perform unintend...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2241</link><description>Improper access control in the user interface in Devolutions Workspace 2024.1.0 and earlier allows an authenticated user to perform unintended actions via specific permissions</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 13:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2245 | Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in moziloCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2245</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in moziloCMS version 2.0. By sending a POST request to the '/install.php' endpoint, a JavaScript payload could be executed in the 'username' parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 13:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0818 | Arbitrary File Overwrite Via Path Traversal in paddlepaddle/paddle before 2.6</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0818</link><description>Arbitrary File Overwrite Via Path Traversal in paddlepaddle/paddle before 2.6</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:55:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28228 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.1.25893 creation comments on behalf of an arbitrary user in HelpDesk was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28228</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.1.25893 creation comments on behalf of an arbitrary user in HelpDesk was possible</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 11:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28229 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.1.25893 user without appropriate permissions could restore issues and articles</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28229</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.1.25893 user without appropriate permissions could restore issues and articles</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 11:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28230 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.1.25893 attaching/detaching workflow to a project was possible without project admin permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28230</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.1.25893 attaching/detaching workflow to a project was possible without project admin permissions</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 11:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1169 | The Post Form – Registration Form – Profile Form for User Profiles – Frontend Content Forms for User Submissions (UGC) plugin for WordPress ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1169</link><description>The Post Form – Registration Form – Profile Form for User Profiles – Frontend Content Forms for User Submissions (UGC) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized media upload due to a missing capability check on the buddyforms_upload_handle_dropped_media function in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload media files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 11:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1170 | The Post Form – Registration Form – Profile Form for User Profiles – Frontend Content Forms for User Submissions (UGC) plugin for WordPress ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1170</link><description>The Post Form – Registration Form – Profile Form for User Profiles – Frontend Content Forms for User Submissions (UGC) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized media file deletion due to a missing capability check on the handle_deleted_media function in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary media files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 11:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22256 | VMware Cloud Director contains a partial information disclosure vulnerability. A malicious actor can potentially gather information about or...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22256</link><description>VMware Cloud Director contains a partial information disclosure vulnerability. A malicious actor can potentially gather information about organization names based on the behavior of the instance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 10:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1534 | The Booster for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1534</link><description>The Booster for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 7.1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 09:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1931 | Denial of service when trimming EDE text on positive replies</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1931</link><description>NLnet Labs Unbound version 1.18.0 up to and including version 1.19.1 contain a vulnerability that can cause denial of service by a certain code path that can lead to an infinite loop. Unbound 1.18.0 introduced a feature that removes EDE records from responses with size higher than the client's advertised buffer size. Before removing all the EDE records however, it would try to see if trimming the extra text fields on those records would result in an acceptable size while still retaining the EDE codes. Due to an unchecked condition, the code that trims the text of the EDE records could loop indefinitely. This happens when Unbound would reply with attached EDE information on a positive reply and the client's buffer size is smaller than the needed space to include EDE records. The vulnerability can only be triggered when the 'ede: yes' option is used; non default configuration. From version 1.19.2 on, the code is fixed to avoid looping indefinitely.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 09:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41503 | Student Enrollment In PHP v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the Login function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41503</link><description>Student Enrollment In PHP v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the Login function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 09:10:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41014 | code-projects.org Online Job Portal 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the Username parameter for "Employer."</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41014</link><description>code-projects.org Online Job Portal 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the Username parameter for "Employer."</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 08:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41015 | code-projects.org Online Job Portal 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /Employer/DeleteJob.php?JobId=1.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41015</link><description>code-projects.org Online Job Portal 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /Employer/DeleteJob.php?JobId=1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 08:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46499 | Hospital Management System 1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the pat_number parameter at his_admin_view_single...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46499</link><description>Hospital Management System 1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the pat_number parameter at his_admin_view_single_patient.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 08:51:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33676 | Sourcecodester Lost and Found Information System's Version 1.0 is vulnerable to unauthenticated SQL Injection at "?page=items/view&amp;id=*" whi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33676</link><description>Sourcecodester Lost and Found Information System's Version 1.0 is vulnerable to unauthenticated SQL Injection at "?page=items/view&amp;id=*" which can be escalated to the remote command execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 08:51:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46498 | Hospital Management System 1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the doc_number parameter at his_admin_view_single...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46498</link><description>Hospital Management System 1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the doc_number parameter at his_admin_view_single_employee.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 08:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46497 | Hospital Management System 1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the pat_number parameter at his_doc_view_single_p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46497</link><description>Hospital Management System 1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the pat_number parameter at his_doc_view_single_patien.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 08:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1382 | The Restaurant Reservations plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.9 via the nd_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1382</link><description>The Restaurant Reservations plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.9 via the nd_rst_layout attribute of the nd_rst_search shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary PHP files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where an uploaded PHP file may not be directly accessible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 08:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2136 | The WPKoi Templates for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Advanced Heading widget in all v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2136</link><description>The WPKoi Templates for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Advanced Heading widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 08:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42662 | JFrog Artifactory Improper SSO Mechanism may lead to Exposure of Access Tokens</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42662</link><description>JFrog Artifactory versions 7.59 and above, but below 7.59.18, 7.63.18, 7.68.19, 7.71.8 are vulnerable to an issue whereby user interaction with specially crafted URLs could lead to exposure of user access tokens due to improper handling of the CLI / IDE browser based SSO integration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 08:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0917 | remote code execution in paddlepaddle/paddle 2.6.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0917</link><description>remote code execution in paddlepaddle/paddle 2.6.0</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 08:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46091 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the feedback form of Online Flight Booking Management System v1.0 allows attackers to execute ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46091</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the feedback form of Online Flight Booking Management System v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the airline parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 08:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1419 | The The Plus Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘_id’ attribute of the Header Me...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1419</link><description>The The Plus Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘_id’ attribute of the Header Meta Content widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 07:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1506 | The Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'title_tags' attribute of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1506</link><description>The Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'title_tags' attribute of the Fiestar widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.13.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 07:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28222 | In Veritas NetBackup before 8.1.2 and NetBackup Appliance before 3.1.2, the BPCD process inadequately validates the file path, allowing an u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28222</link><description>In Veritas NetBackup before 8.1.2 and NetBackup Appliance before 3.1.2, the BPCD process inadequately validates the file path, allowing an unauthenticated attacker to upload and execute a custom file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 07:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1366 | The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘archive_title_tag’ attribute of th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1366</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘archive_title_tag’ attribute of the Archive Title widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 05:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1377 | The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘author_meta_tag’ attribute of the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1377</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘author_meta_tag’ attribute of the Author Meta widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 05:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1500 | The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Logo Widget in all versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1500</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Logo Widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.91 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied URLs. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 05:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1720 | The User Registration – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile WordPress Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1720</link><description>The User Registration – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile WordPress Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Display Name' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This vulnerability requires social engineering to successfully exploit, and the impact would be very limited due to the attacker requiring a user to login as the user with the injected payload for execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 05:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51395 | Z-Wave S0 Decryption Vulnerability in End Devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51395</link><description>The vulnerability described by CVE-2023-0972 has been additionally discovered in Silicon Labs Z-Wave end devices. This vulnerability may allow an unauthenticated attacker within Z-Wave range to overflow a stack buffer, leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 04:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28211 | nGrinder before 3.5.9 allows connection to malicious JMX/RMI server by default, which could be the cause of executing arbitrary code via RMI...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28211</link><description>nGrinder before 3.5.9 allows connection to malicious JMX/RMI server by default, which could be the cause of executing arbitrary code via RMI registry by remote attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 04:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28212 | nGrinder before 3.5.9 uses old version of SnakeYAML, which could allow remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via unsafe deserialization.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28212</link><description>nGrinder before 3.5.9 uses old version of SnakeYAML, which could allow remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via unsafe deserialization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 04:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28213 | nGrinder before 3.5.9 allows to accept serialized Java objects from unauthenticated users, which could allow remote attacker to execute arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28213</link><description>nGrinder before 3.5.9 allows to accept serialized Java objects from unauthenticated users, which could allow remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via unsafe Java objects deserialization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 04:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28214 | nGrinder before 3.5.9 allows to set delay without limitation, which could be the cause of Denial of Service by remote attacker.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28214</link><description>nGrinder before 3.5.9 allows to set delay without limitation, which could be the cause of Denial of Service by remote attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 04:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28215 | nGrinder before 3.5.9 allows an attacker to create or update webhook configuration due to lack of access control, which could be the cause o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28215</link><description>nGrinder before 3.5.9 allows an attacker to create or update webhook configuration due to lack of access control, which could be the cause of information disclosure and limited Server-Side Request Forgery.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 04:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28216 | nGrinder before 3.5.9 allows an attacker to obtain the results of webhook requests due to lack of access control, which could be the cause o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28216</link><description>nGrinder before 3.5.9 allows an attacker to obtain the results of webhook requests due to lack of access control, which could be the cause of information disclosure and limited Server-Side Request Forgery.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 04:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1761 | The WP Chat App plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widget/block in all versions up to, and i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1761</link><description>The WP Chat App plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widget/block in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as 'buttonColor' and 'phoneNumber'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 04:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28095 | Stored Cross-site Scripting in News functionality in Schoolbox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28095</link><description>News functionality in Schoolbox application before
 version 23.1.3 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting allowing 
authenticated attacker to perform security actions in the context of the
 affected users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 03:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28096 | Stored Cross-site Scripting in Class functionality in Schoolbox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28096</link><description>Class functionality in Schoolbox application 
before version 23.1.3 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting 
allowing authenticated attacker to perform security actions in the 
context of the affected users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 03:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28097 | Stored Cross-site Scripting in Calendar functionality in Schoolbox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28097</link><description>Calendar functionality in Schoolbox application 
before version 23.1.3 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting 
allowing authenticated attacker to perform security actions in the 
context of the affected users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 03:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0815 | Command injection in paddle.utils.download._wget_download (bypass filter) in paddlepaddle/paddle 2.6.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0815</link><description>Command injection in paddle.utils.download._wget_download (bypass filter) in paddlepaddle/paddle 2.6.0</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 03:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28094 | Blind SQL Injection in Chat functionality in Schoolbox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28094</link><description>Chat functionality in Schoolbox application before
 version 23.1.3 is vulnerable to blind SQL Injection enabling the 
authenticated attackers to read, modify, and delete database records.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 03:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1460 | MSI Afterburner v4.6.5.16370 - Kernel Memory Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1460</link><description>MSI Afterburner v4.6.5.16370 is vulnerable to a Kernel Memory Leak vulnerability by triggering the 0x80002040 IOCTL code of the RTCore64.sys driver. The handle to the driver can only be obtained from a high integrity process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1443 | MSI Afterburner v4.6.5.16370 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1443</link><description>MSI Afterburner v4.6.5.16370 is vulnerable to a Denial of Service vulnerability by triggering the 0x80002000 IOCTL code of the RTCore64.sys driver. The handle to the driver can only be obtained from a high integrity process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 02:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46089 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the add-airline form of Online Flight Booking Management System v1.0 allows attackers to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46089</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the add-airline form of Online Flight Booking Management System v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the airline parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 01:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0817 | Command injection in IrGraph.draw in paddlepaddle/paddle 2.6.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0817</link><description>Command injection in IrGraph.draw in paddlepaddle/paddle 2.6.0</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 01:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24389 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in XunRuiCMS up to v4.6.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24389</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in XunRuiCMS up to v4.6.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Add Column Name parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 01:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49986 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /admin/parent of School Fees Management System 1.0 allow attackers to execute ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49986</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /admin/parent of School Fees Management System 1.0 allow attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the name parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 01:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49987 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /management/term of School Fees Management System v1.0 allows attackers to execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49987</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /management/term of School Fees Management System v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the tname parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 01:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49988 | Hotel Booking Management v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the npss parameter at rooms.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49988</link><description>Hotel Booking Management v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the npss parameter at rooms.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 01:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49989 | Hotel Booking Management v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at update.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49989</link><description>Hotel Booking Management v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at update.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 01:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51281 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Customer Support System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script fir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51281</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Customer Support System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script firstname, "lastname", "middlename", "contact" and address parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 01:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51786 | An issue was discovered in Lustre versions 2.13.x, 2.14.x, and 2.15.x before 2.15.4, allows attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sens...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51786</link><description>An issue was discovered in Lustre versions 2.13.x, 2.14.x, and 2.15.x before 2.15.4, allows attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via Incorrect Access Control.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 01:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0199 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0199</link><description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 11.3 prior to 16.7.7, 16.7.6 prior to 16.8.4, and 16.8.3 prior to 16.9.2. An attacker could bypass CODEOWNERS by utilizing a crafted payload in an old feature branch to perform malicious actions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 01:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1299 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1299</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 16.8 prior to 16.8.4 and 16.9 prior to 16.9.2. It was possible for a user with custom role of `manage_group_access_tokens` to rotate group access tokens with owner privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 01:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24375 | SQL injection vulnerability in Jfinalcms v.5.0.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via /admin/admin name parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24375</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Jfinalcms v.5.0.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via /admin/admin name parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 01:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26566 | An issue in Cute Http File Server v.3.1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the password verification component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26566</link><description>An issue in Cute Http File Server v.3.1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the password verification component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 01:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22857 | zlog 1.2.16 has a heap-based buffer overflow in struct zlog_rule_s while creating a new rule that is already defined in the provided configu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22857</link><description>zlog 1.2.16 has a heap-based buffer overflow in struct zlog_rule_s while creating a new rule that is already defined in the provided configuration file. A regular user can achieve arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 01:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47415 | Cypress Solutions CTM-200 v2.7.1.5600 and below was discovered to contain an OS command injection vulnerability via the cli_text parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47415</link><description>Cypress Solutions CTM-200 v2.7.1.5600 and below was discovered to contain an OS command injection vulnerability via the cli_text parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>