<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:44:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2017-13323 | In String16 of String16.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13323</link><description>In String16 of String16.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege in an unprivileged process with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-13320 | In impeg2d_bit_stream_flush() of libmpeg2dec there is a possible OOB read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to Remote DoS with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13320</link><description>In impeg2d_bit_stream_flush() of libmpeg2dec there is a possible OOB read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to Remote DoS with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-13321 | In SensorService::isDataInjectionEnabled of frameworks/native/services/sensorservice/SensorService.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13321</link><description>In SensorService::isDataInjectionEnabled of frameworks/native/services/sensorservice/SensorService.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53260 | Course Roster vulnerable to CSV Injection in Autolab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53260</link><description>Autolab is a course management service that enables auto-graded programming assignments. A user can modify their first and or last name to include a valid excel / spreadsheet formula. When an instructor downloads their course's roster and opens, this name will then be evaluated as a formula. This could lead to leakage of information of students in the course roster by sending the data to a remote endpoint. This issue has been patched in the source code repository and the fix is expected to be released in the next version. Users are advised to manually patch their systems or to wait for the next release. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:37:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53858 | Recursive repository cloning can leak authentication tokens to non-GitHub submodule hosts in the gh cli</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53858</link><description>The gh cli is GitHub’s official command line tool. A security vulnerability has been identified in the GitHub CLI that could leak authentication tokens when cloning repositories containing `git` submodules hosted outside of GitHub.com and ghe.com. This vulnerability stems from several `gh` commands used to clone a repository with submodules from a non-GitHub host including `gh repo clone`, `gh repo fork`, and `gh pr checkout`. These GitHub CLI commands invoke git with instructions to retrieve authentication tokens using the `credential.helper` configuration variable for any host encountered. Prior to version `2.63.0`, hosts other than GitHub.com and ghe.com are treated as GitHub Enterprise Server hosts and have tokens sourced from the following environment variables before falling back to host-specific tokens stored within system-specific secured storage: 1. `GITHUB_ENTERPRISE_TOKEN`, 2. `GH_ENTERPRISE_TOKEN` and 3. `GITHUB_TOKEN` when the `CODESPACES` environment variable is set. The result being `git` sending authentication tokens when cloning submodules. In version `2.63.0`, these GitHub CLI commands will limit the hosts for which `gh` acts as a credential helper to source authentication tokens. Additionally, `GITHUB_TOKEN` will only be used for GitHub.com and ghe.com. Users are advised to upgrade. Additionally users are advised to revoke authentication tokens used with the GitHub CLI and to review their personal security log and any relevant audit logs for actions associated with their account or enterprise</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:37:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53859 | go-gh `auth.TokenForHost` violates GitHub host security boundary within a codespace</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53859</link><description>go-gh is a Go module for interacting with the `gh` utility and the GitHub API from the command line. A security vulnerability has been identified in `go-gh` that could leak authentication tokens intended for GitHub hosts to non-GitHub hosts when within a codespace. `go-gh` sources authentication tokens from different environment variables depending on the host involved: 1. `GITHUB_TOKEN`, `GH_TOKEN` for GitHub.com and ghe.com and 2. `GITHUB_ENTERPRISE_TOKEN`, `GH_ENTERPRISE_TOKEN` for GitHub Enterprise Server. Prior to version `2.11.1`, `auth.TokenForHost` could source a token from the `GITHUB_TOKEN` environment variable for a host other than GitHub.com or ghe.com when within a codespace. In version `2.11.1`, `auth.TokenForHost` will only source a token from the `GITHUB_TOKEN` environment variable for GitHub.com or ghe.com hosts. Successful exploitation could send authentication token to an unintended host. This issue has been addressed in version 2.11.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. Users are also advised to regenerate authentication tokens and to review their personal security log and any relevant audit logs for actions associated with their account or enterprise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53860 | Potential Abuse for Sending Arbitrary Emails in sp-php-email-handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53860</link><description>sp-php-email-handler is a PHP package for handling contact form submissions. Messages sent using this script are vulnerable to abuse, as the script allows anybody to specify arbitrary email recipients and include user-provided content in confirmation emails. This could enable malicious actors to use your server to send spam, phishing emails, or other malicious content, potentially damaging your domain's reputation and leading to blacklisting by email providers. Patched in version 1.0.0 by removing user-provided content from confirmation emails. All pre-release versions (alpha and beta) are vulnerable to this issue and should not be used. There are no workarounds for this issue. Users must upgrade to version 1.0.0 to mitigate the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-13319 | In pvmp3_get_main_data_size of pvmp3_get_main_data_size.cpp, there is a possible buffer overread due to a missing bounds check. This could l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13319</link><description>In pvmp3_get_main_data_size of pvmp3_get_main_data_size.cpp, there is a possible buffer overread due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure of global static variables with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 20:11:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-13316 | In checkPermissions of RecognitionService.java, there is a possible permissions bypass due to a missing permission check. This could lead to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13316</link><description>In checkPermissions of RecognitionService.java, there is a possible permissions bypass due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 19:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29001 | Uncontrolled recursion due to insufficient validation of the IPv6 source routing header in Contiki-NG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29001</link><description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for IoT devices. The Contiki-NG operating system processes source routing headers (SRH) in its two alternative RPL protocol implementations. The IPv6 implementation uses the results of this processing to determine whether an incoming packet should be forwarded to another host. Because of missing validation of the resulting next-hop address, an uncontrolled recursion may occur in the tcpip_ipv6_output function in the os/net/ipv6/tcpip.c module when receiving a packet with a next-hop address that is a local address. Attackers that have the possibility to send IPv6 packets to the Contiki-NG host can therefore trigger deeply nested recursive calls, which can cause a stack overflow. The vulnerability has not been patched in the current release of Contiki-NG, but is expected to be patched in the next release. The problem can be fixed by applying the patch in Contiki-NG pull request #2264. Users are advised to either apply the patch manually or to wait for the next release. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41125 | Out-of-bounds read in SNMP when decoding a string in Contiki-NG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41125</link><description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for IoT devices. An out-of-bounds read of 1 byte can be triggered when sending a packet to a device running the Contiki-NG operating system with SNMP enabled. The SNMP module is disabled in the default Contiki-NG configuration. The vulnerability exists in the os/net/app-layer/snmp/snmp-ber.c module, where the function snmp_ber_decode_string_len_buffer decodes the string length from a received SNMP packet. In one place, one byte is read from the buffer, without checking that the buffer has another byte available, leading to a possible out-of-bounds read. The problem has been patched in Contiki-NG pull request #2936. It will be included in the next release of Contiki-NG. Users are advised to apply the patch manually or to wait for the next release. A workaround is to disable the SNMP module in the Contiki-NG build configuration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41126 | Out-of-bounds read when decoding SNMP messages in Contiki-NG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41126</link><description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for IoT devices. An out-of-bounds read of 1 byte can be triggered when sending a packet to a device running the Contiki-NG operating system with SNMP enabled. The SNMP module is disabled in the default Contiki-NG configuration. The vulnerability exists in the os/net/app-layer/snmp/snmp-message.c module, where the snmp_message_decode function fails to check the boundary of the message buffer when reading a byte from it immediately after decoding an object identifier (OID). The problem has been patched in Contiki-NG pull request 2937. It will be included in the next release of Contiki-NG. Users are advised to either apply the patch manually or to wait for the next release. A workaround is to disable the SNMP module in the Contiki-NG build configuration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47181 | Unaligned memory access in RPL option processing in Contiki-NG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47181</link><description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for IoT devices. An unaligned memory access can be triggered in the two RPL implementations of the Contiki-NG operating system. The problem can occur when either one of these RPL implementations is enabled and connected to an RPL instance. If an IPv6 packet containing an odd number of padded bytes before the RPL option, it can cause the rpl_ext_header_hbh_update function to read a 16-bit integer from an odd address. The impact of this unaligned read is architecture-dependent, but can potentially cause the system to crash. The problem has not been patched as of release 4.9, but will be included in the next release. One can apply the changes in Contiki-NG pull request #2962 to patch the system or wait for the next release.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53264 | Open Redirect Vulnerability in Loading Page in bunkerweb</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53264</link><description>bunkerweb is an Open-source and next-generation Web Application Firewall (WAF). A open redirect vulnerability exists in the loading endpoint, allowing attackers to redirect authenticated users to arbitrary external URLs via the "next" parameter. The loading endpoint accepts and uses an unvalidated "next" parameter for redirects. Ex. visiting: `/loading?next=https://google.com` while authenticated will cause the page will redirect to google.com. This vulnerability could be used in phishing attacks by redirecting users from a legitimate application URL to malicious sites. This issue has been addressed in version 1.5.11. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53855 | User can view tickets from organizations they&amp;#x27;re not apart of in centurion_erp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53855</link><description>Centurion ERP (Enterprise Rescource Planning) is a simple application developed to provide open source IT management with a large emphasis on the IT Service Management (ITSM) modules. A user who is authenticated and has view permissions for a ticket, can view the tickets of another organization they are not apart of. Users with following permissions are applicable: 1. `view_ticket_change` permission can view change tickets from organizations they are not apart of. 2. `view_ticket_incident` permission can view incident tickets from organizations they are not apart of. 3. `view_ticket_request` permission can view request tickets from organizations they are not apart of. 4. `view_ticket_problem` permission can view problem tickets from organizations they are not apart of. The access to view the tickets from different organizations is only applicable when browsing the API endpoints for the tickets in question. The Centurion UI is not affected. Project Tasks, although a "ticket type" are also **Not** affected. This issue has been addressed in release version 1.3.1 and users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may remove the ticket view permissions from users which would alleviate this vulnerability, if this is deemed not-viable, Upgrading is recommended.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7025 | Integer overflow in Layout in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.89 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7025</link><description>Integer overflow in Layout in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.89 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9369 | Insufficient data validation in Mojo in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.89 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer proc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9369</link><description>Insufficient data validation in Mojo in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.89 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to perform an out of bounds memory write via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21703 | This Medium severity Security Misconfiguration vulnerability was introduced in version 8.8.1 of Confluence Data Center and Server for Window...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21703</link><description>This Medium severity Security Misconfiguration vulnerability was introduced in version 8.8.1 of Confluence Data Center and Server for Windows installations.



This Security Misconfiguration vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 6.4 allows an authenticated attacker of the Windows host to read sensitive information about the Confluence Data Center configuration which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity,  high impact to availability, and no user interaction.



Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to the latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:

* Confluence Data Center and Server 7.19: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 7.19.18 
* Confluence Data Center and Server 8.5: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.5.5
* Confluence Data Center and Server 8.7: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.7.2
* Confluence Data Center and Server 8.8: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.8.0



See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/conf88/confluence-release-notes-1354501008.html ). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives ). 

This vulnerability was reported via our Atlassian Bug Bounty Program by Chris Elliot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 17:12:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54003 | Jenkins Simple Queue Plugin 1.4.4 and earlier does not escape the view name, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54003</link><description>Jenkins Simple Queue Plugin 1.4.4 and earlier does not escape the view name, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exploitable by attackers with View/Create permission.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 17:12:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54004 | Jenkins Filesystem List Parameter Plugin 0.0.14 and earlier does not restrict the path used for the File system objects list Parameter, allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54004</link><description>Jenkins Filesystem List Parameter Plugin 0.0.14 and earlier does not restrict the path used for the File system objects list Parameter, allowing attackers with Item/Configure permission to enumerate file names on the Jenkins controller file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 17:12:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51228 | An issue in TOTOLINK-CX-A3002RU V1.0.4-B20171106.1512 and TOTOLINK-CX-N150RT V2.1.6-B20171121.1002 and TOTOLINK-CX-N300RT V2.1.6-B20170724.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51228</link><description>An issue in TOTOLINK-CX-A3002RU V1.0.4-B20171106.1512 and TOTOLINK-CX-N150RT V2.1.6-B20171121.1002 and TOTOLINK-CX-N300RT V2.1.6-B20170724.1420 and TOTOLINK-CX-N300RT V2.1.8-B20171113.1408 and TOTOLINK-CX-N300RT V2.1.8-B20191010.1107 and TOTOLINK-CX-N302RE V2.0.2-B20170511.1523 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /boafrm/formSysCmd component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 16:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11860 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System POST Request ajax.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11860</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /rental/ajax.php?action=delete_tenant of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 16:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31976 | EnGenius EWS356-FIR 1.1.30 and earlier devices allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands via the Controller connectivity para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31976</link><description>EnGenius EWS356-FIR 1.1.30 and earlier devices allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands via the Controller connectivity parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 16:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37816 | Quectel EC25-EUX EC25EUXGAR08A05M1G was discovered to contain a stack overflow.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37816</link><description>Quectel EC25-EUX EC25EUXGAR08A05M1G was discovered to contain a stack overflow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 16:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53920 | In elisp-mode.el in GNU Emacs through 30.0.92, a user who chooses to invoke elisp-completion-at-point (for code completion) on untrusted Ema...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53920</link><description>In elisp-mode.el in GNU Emacs through 30.0.92, a user who chooses to invoke elisp-completion-at-point (for code completion) on untrusted Emacs Lisp source code can trigger unsafe Lisp macro expansion that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code. (This unsafe expansion also occurs if a user chooses to enable on-the-fly diagnosis that byte compiles untrusted Emacs Lisp source code.)</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11862 | Non constant time cryptographic operation in Devolutions.XTS.NET 2024.11.19 and earlier allows an attacker to render half of the encryption ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11862</link><description>Non constant time cryptographic operation in Devolutions.XTS.NET 2024.11.19 and earlier allows an attacker to render half of the encryption key obsolete via a timing attacks</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46054 | OpenVidReview 1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The /upload route is accessible without authentication, allowing any user to up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46054</link><description>OpenVidReview 1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The /upload route is accessible without authentication, allowing any user to upload files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46055 | OpenVidReview 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in review names.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46055</link><description>OpenVidReview 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in review names.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52951 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting in the Access Request History in Omada Identity before version 15 update 1 allows an authenticated attacker to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52951</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting in the Access Request History in Omada Identity before version 15 update 1 allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code in the browser of a victim via a specially crafted link or by viewing a manipulated Access Request History</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36464 | Media Types: Office365, SMTP passwords are unencrypted and visible in plaintext when exported</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36464</link><description>When exporting media types, the password is exported in the YAML in plain text. This appears to be a best practices type issue and may have no actual impact. The user would need to have permissions to access the media types and therefore would be expected to have access to these passwords.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53635 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /covid-tms/patient-search-report.php in PHPGurukul COVID 19 Testing Manage...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53635</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /covid-tms/patient-search-report.php in PHPGurukul COVID 19 Testing Management System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the searchdata POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 13:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53603 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /covid-tms/password-recovery.php in PHPGurukul COVID 19 Testing Management System v1.0, which all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53603</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /covid-tms/password-recovery.php in PHPGurukul COVID 19 Testing Management System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the contactno POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 13:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53604 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /covid-tms/check_availability.php in PHPGurukul COVID 19 Testing Management System v1.0, which al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53604</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /covid-tms/check_availability.php in PHPGurukul COVID 19 Testing Management System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the mobnumber POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 13:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36468 | Stack buffer overflow in zbx_snmp_cache_handle_engineid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36468</link><description>The reported vulnerability is a stack buffer overflow in the zbx_snmp_cache_handle_engineid function within the Zabbix server/proxy code. This issue occurs when copying data from session-&gt;securityEngineID to local_record.engineid without proper bounds checking.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42326 | Use after free vulnerability in browser.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42326</link><description>There was discovered a use after free bug in browser.c in the es_browser_get_variant function</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42327 | SQL injection in user.get API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42327</link><description>A non-admin user account on the Zabbix frontend with the default User role, or with any other role that gives API access can exploit this vulnerability. An SQLi exists in the CUser class in the addRelatedObjects function, this function is being called from the CUser.get function which is available for every user who has API access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42328 | JS - Crash on empty HTTP server response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42328</link><description>When the webdriver for the Browser object downloads data from a HTTP server, the data pointer is set to NULL and is allocated only in curl_write_cb when receiving data. If the server's response is an empty document, then wd-&gt;data in the code below will remain NULL and an attempt to read from it will result in a crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42329 | JS - Crash on unexpected HTTP server response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42329</link><description>The webdriver for the Browser object expects an error object to be initialized when the webdriver_session_query function fails. But this function can fail for various reasons without an error description and then the wd-&gt;error will be NULL and trying to read from it will result in a crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42330 | JS - Internal strings in HTTP headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42330</link><description>The HttpRequest object allows to get the HTTP headers from the server's response after sending the request. The problem is that the returned strings are created directly from the data returned by the server and are not correctly encoded for JavaScript. This allows to create internal strings that can be used to access hidden properties of objects.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42331 | Use after free in browser_push_error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42331</link><description>In the src/libs/zbxembed/browser.c file, the es_browser_ctor method retrieves a heap pointer from the Duktape JavaScript engine. This heap pointer is subsequently utilized by the browser_push_error method in the src/libs/zbxembed/browser_error.c file. A use-after-free bug can occur at this stage if the wd-&gt;browser heap pointer is freed by garbage collection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42332 | New line injection in Zabbix SNMP traps</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42332</link><description>The researcher is showing that due to the way the SNMP trap log is parsed, an attacker can craft an SNMP trap with additional lines of information and have forged data show in the Zabbix UI. This attack requires SNMP auth to be off and/or the attacker to know the community/auth details. The attack requires an SNMP item to be configured as text on the target host.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42333 | Heap buffer over-read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42333</link><description>The researcher is showing that it is possible to leak a small amount of Zabbix Server memory using an out of bounds read in src/libs/zbxmedia/email.c</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11009 | Internal Linking for SEO traffic &amp;amp; Ranking – Auto internal links (100% automatic) &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via post_id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11009</link><description>The Internal Linking for SEO traffic &amp; Ranking – Auto internal links (100% automatic) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘post_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 11:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10521 | WordPress Contact Forms by Cimatti &amp;lt;= 1.9.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via process_bulk_action Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10521</link><description>The WordPress Contact Forms by Cimatti plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the process_bulk_action function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete forms via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 11:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11025 | SMA: SQL injection in Sunny Central UP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11025</link><description>An authenticated attacker with low privileges may use a SQL Injection vulnerability in the affected products administration panel to gain read and write access to a specific log file of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 10:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52323 | Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52323</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Analytics Plus versions below 6100 are vulnerable to authenticated sensitive data exposure which allows the users to retrieve sensitive tokens associated to the org-admin account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 09:57:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11667 | A directory traversal vulnerability in the web management interface of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions V5.00 through V5.38, USG FLEX seri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11667</link><description>A directory traversal vulnerability in the web management interface of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions V5.00 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware versions V5.00 through V5.38, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions V5.10 through V5.38, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions V5.10 through V5.38 could allow an attacker to download or upload files via a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 09:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10175 | Pricing Tables For WPBakery Page Builder (formerly Visual Composer) &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wdo_pricing_tables Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10175</link><description>The Pricing Tables For WPBakery Page Builder (formerly Visual Composer) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wdo_pricing_tables shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 06:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10580 | Hustle – Email Marketing, Lead Generation, Optins, Popups &amp;lt;= 7.8.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthorized Form Submission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10580</link><description>The Hustle – Email Marketing, Lead Generation, Optins, Popups plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized form submissions due to a missing capability check on the submit_form() function in all versions up to, and including, 7.8.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to submit unpublished forms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 06:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10895 | Counter Up – Animated Number Counter &amp;amp; Milestone Showcase &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10895</link><description>The Counter Up – Animated Number Counter &amp; Milestone Showcase plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'lgx-counter' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 06:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36467 | Authentication privilege escalation via user groups due to missing authorization checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36467</link><description>An authenticated user with API access (e.g.: user with default User role), more specifically a user with access to the user.update API endpoint is enough to be able to add themselves to any group (e.g.: Zabbix Administrators), except to groups that are disabled or having restricted GUI access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 06:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11083 | ProfilePress &amp;lt;= 4.15.18 - Unauthenticated Content Restriction Bypass to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11083</link><description>The ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.15.18 via the WordPress core search feature. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from posts that have been restricted to higher-level roles such as administrator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 05:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11219 | Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp;amp; FSE &amp;lt;= 3.0.6 - Unauthetnicated Path Traversal to Arbitrary Image View</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11219</link><description>The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.6 via the get_image function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view arbitrary images on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 05:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52958 | iota C.ai Conversational Platform - Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52958</link><description>A improper verification of cryptographic signature vulnerability in plugin management in iota C.ai Conversational Platform from 1.0.0 through 2.1.3 allows remote authenticated users to load a malicious DLL via upload plugin function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 05:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52959 | iota C.ai Conversational Platform - Improper Control of Generation of Code (&amp;#x27;Code Injection&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52959</link><description>A Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in plugin management in iota C.ai Conversational Platform from 1.0.0 through 2.1.3 allows remote authenticated users to perform arbitrary system commands via a DLL file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 05:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5921 | GlobalProtect App: Insufficient Certificate Validation Leads to Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5921</link><description>An insufficient certification validation issue in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app enables attackers to connect the GlobalProtect app to arbitrary servers. This can enable a local non-administrative operating system user or an attacker on the same subnet to install malicious root certificates on the endpoint and subsequently install malicious software signed by the malicious root certificates on that endpoint.

GlobalProtect App for Android is under evaluation. Please subscribe to  our RSS feed https://security.paloaltonetworks.com/rss.xml  to be alerted to new updates to this and other advisories.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 03:55:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11820 | code-projects Crud Operation System add.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11820</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Crud Operation System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /add.php. The manipulation of the argument saddress leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53676 | A directory traversal vulnerability in Hewlett Packard Enterprise Insight Remote Support may allow remote code execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53676</link><description>A directory traversal vulnerability in Hewlett Packard Enterprise Insight Remote Support may allow remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11818 | PHPGurukul User Registration &amp;amp; Login and User Management System signup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11818</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /signup.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 23:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11819 | 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA forgot_password_process.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11819</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /forgot_password_process.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 23:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53849 | Several stack buffer overflows and pointer overflows in editorconfig-core-c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53849</link><description>editorconfig-core-c  is  theEditorConfig core library written in C (for use by plugins supporting EditorConfig parsing). In affected versions several overflows may occur in switch case '[' when the input pattern contains many escaped characters. The added backslashes leave too little space in the output pattern when processing nested brackets such that the remaining input length exceeds the output capacity. This issue has been addressed in release version 0.12.7. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 23:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11817 | PHPGurukul User Registration &amp;amp; Login and User Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11817</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 23:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53675 | An XML external entity injection (XXE) vulnerability in HPE Insight Remote Support may allow remote users to disclose information in certain...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53675</link><description>An XML external entity injection (XXE) vulnerability in HPE Insight Remote Support may allow remote users to disclose information in certain cases.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 22:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53674 | An XML external entity injection (XXE) vulnerability in HPE Insight Remote Support may allow remote users to disclose information in certain...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53674</link><description>An XML external entity injection (XXE) vulnerability in HPE Insight Remote Support may allow remote users to disclose information in certain cases.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 21:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53673 | A java deserialization vulnerability in HPE Remote Insight Support allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53673</link><description>A java deserialization vulnerability in HPE Remote Insight Support allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 21:52:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11622 | An XML external entity injection (XXE) vulnerability in HPE Insight Remote Support may allow remote users to disclose information in certain...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11622</link><description>An XML external entity injection (XXE) vulnerability in HPE Insight Remote Support may allow remote users to disclose information in certain cases.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 21:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11745 | Tenda AC8 SetStaticRouteCfg route_static_check stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11745</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.09 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function route_static_check of the file /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 21:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50942 | qiwen-file v1.4.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /mapper/NoticeMapper.xml.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50942</link><description>qiwen-file v1.4.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /mapper/NoticeMapper.xml.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 20:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11744 | 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11744</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 1000 Projects Portfolio Management System MCA 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /register.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 20:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43784 | Re-creating a deleted user in lakeFS will re-enable previous user credentials that existed prior to it&amp;#x27;s deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43784</link><description>lakeFS is an open-source tool that transforms object storage into a Git-like repository. Existing lakeFS users who have issued credentials to users who have been deleted are affected by this vulnerability. When creating a new user with the same username as a deleted user, that user will inherit all of the previous user's credentials. This issue has been addressed in release version 1.33.0 and all users are advised to upgrade. The only known workaround for those who cannot upgrade is to not reuse usernames.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 20:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11742 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System ajax.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11742</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /rental/ajax.php?action=save_tenant. The manipulation of the argument lastname/firstname/middlename leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 20:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11743 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System POST Request ajax.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11743</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /rental/ajax.php?action=delete_user of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 20:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49053 | Microsoft Dynamics 365 Sales Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49053</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49035 | Partner.Microsoft.Com Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49035</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49038 | Microsoft Copilot Studio Elevation Of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49038</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49052 | Microsoft Azure Functions Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49052</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-17082 | Missing Authentication vulnerability in OpenText AccuRev for LDAP Integration, version 2017.1.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17082</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in OpenText™ AccuRev for LDAP Integration allows Authentication Bypass. The vulnerability could allow 

a valid AccuRev username to gain access to AccuRev source control without knowing the user’s password.

This issue affects AccuRev for LDAP Integration: 2017.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10240 | Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10240</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 17.3 before 17.3.7, all versions starting from 17.4 before 17.4.4, all versions starting from 17.5 before 17.5.2 in which an unauthenticated user may be able to read some information about an MR in a private project, under certain circumstances.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11145 | Easy Folder Listing Pro deserialization vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11145</link><description>Valor Apps Easy Folder Listing Pro has a deserialization vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code with the privileges of the Joomla! application. Fixed in versions 3.8 and 4.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8676 | Cri-o: checkpoint restore can be triggered from different namespaces</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8676</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CRI-O, where it can be requested to take a checkpoint archive of a container and later be asked to restore it. When it does that restoration, it attempts to restore the mounts from the restore archive instead of the pod request. As a result, the validations run on the pod spec, verifying that the pod has access to the mounts it specifies are not applicable to a restored container. This flaw allows a malicious user to trick CRI-O into restoring a pod that doesn't have access to host mounts. The user needs access to the kubelet or cri-o socket to call the restore endpoint and trigger the restore.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52008 | Password Policy Bypass Vulnerability in Fides Webserver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52008</link><description>Fides is an open-source privacy engineering platform. The user invite acceptance API endpoint lacks server-side password policy enforcement, allowing users to set arbitrarily weak passwords by bypassing client-side validation. While the UI enforces password complexity requirements, direct API calls can circumvent these checks, enabling the creation of accounts with passwords as short as a single character. When an email messaging provider is enabled and a new user account is created in the system, an invite email containing a special link is sent to the new user's email address. This link directs the new user to a page where they can set their initial password. While the user interface implements password complexity checks, these validations are only performed client-side. The underlying `/api/v1/user/accept-invite` API endpoint does not implement the same password policy validations. This vulnerability allows an invited user to set an extremely weak password for their own account during the initial account setup process. Therefore that specific user's account can be compromised easily by an attacker guessing or brute forcing the password. The vulnerability has been patched in Fides version `2.50.0`. Users are advised to upgrade to this version or later to secure their systems against this threat. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53619 | An authenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Documents module of SPIP v4.3.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53619</link><description>An authenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Documents module of SPIP v4.3.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PDF file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53620 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Article module of SPIP v4.3.3 allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary web scri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53620</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Article module of SPIP v4.3.3 allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the Title parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11669 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11669</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.9.8 before 17.4.5, 17.5 before 17.5.3, and 17.6 before 17.6.1. Certain API endpoints could potentially allow unauthorized access to sensitive data due to overly broad application of token scopes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11828 | Inefficient Algorithmic Complexity in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11828</link><description>A denial of service (DoS) condition was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 13.2.4 before 17.4.5, 17.5 before 17.5.3, and 17.6 before 17.6.1. By leveraging this vulnerability an attacker could create a DoS condition by sending crafted API calls. This was a regression of an earlier patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53267 | Vulnerability with bundle verification in sigstore-java</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53267</link><description>sigstore-java is a sigstore java client for interacting with sigstore infrastructure. sigstore-java has insufficient verification for a situation where a validly-signed but "mismatched" bundle is presented as proof of inclusion into a transparency log. This bug impacts clients using any variation of KeylessVerifier.verify(). The verifier may accept a bundle with an unrelated log entry, cryptographically verifying everything but fails to ensure the log entry applies to the artifact in question, thereby "verifying" a bundle without any proof the signing event was logged. This allows the creation of a bundle without fulcio certificate and private key combined with an unrelated but time-correct log entry to fake logging of a signing event. A malicious actor using a compromised identity may want to do this to prevent discovery via rekor's log monitors. The signer's identity will still be available to the verifier. The signature on the bundle must still be on the correct artifact for the verifier to pass. sigstore-gradle-plugin and sigstore-maven-plugin are not affected by this as they only provide signing functionality. This issue has been patched in v1.1.0 release with PR #856. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53844 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (&amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;) in labsai/eddi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53844</link><description>E.D.D.I (Enhanced Dialog Driven Interface) is a middleware to connect and manage LLM API bots. A path traversal vulnerability exists in the backup export functionality of EDDI, as implemented in `RestExportService.java`. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access sensitive files on the server by manipulating the `botFilename` parameter in requests. The application fails to sanitize user input, enabling malicious inputs such as `..%2f..%2fetc%2fpasswd` to access arbitrary files. However, the **severity of this vulnerability is significantly limited** because EDDI typically runs within a **Docker container**, which provides additional layers of isolation and restricted permissions. As a result, while this vulnerability exposes files within the container, it does not inherently threaten the underlying host system or other containers. A patch is required to sanitize and validate the botFilename input parameter. Users should ensure they are using version 5.4 which contains this patdch. For temporary mitigation, access to the vulnerable endpoint should be restricted through firewall rules or authentication mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11668 | Insufficient Session Expiration in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11668</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.11 before 17.4.5, 17.5 before 17.5.3, and 17.6 before 17.6.1. Long-lived connections could potentially bypass authentication controls, allowing unauthorized access to streaming results.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32965 | ssrf vulnerability in lobe-chat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32965</link><description>Lobe Chat is an open-source, AI chat framework. Versions of lobe-chat prior to 1.19.13 have an unauthorized ssrf vulnerability. An attacker can construct malicious requests to cause SSRF without logging in, attack intranet services, and leak sensitive information. The jwt token header X-Lobe-Chat-Auth strored proxy address and OpenAI API Key, can be modified to scan an internal network in the target lobe-web environment. This issue has been addressed in release version 1.19.13 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8114 | Missing Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8114</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 8.12 before 17.4.5, 17.5 before 17.5.3, and 17.6 before 17.6.1. This issue allows an attacker with access to a victim's Personal Access Token (PAT) to escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8177 | Inefficient Algorithmic Complexity in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8177</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.6 prior to 17.4.5, starting from 17.5 prior to 17.5.3, starting from 17.6 prior to 17.6.1 which could cause Denial of Service via integrating a malicious harbor registry.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8237 | Inefficient Algorithmic Complexity in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8237</link><description>A Denial of Service (DoS) issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions prior to 12.6 prior to 17.4.5, 17.5 prior to 17.5.3, and 17.6 prior to 17.6.1. An attacker could cause a denial of service with a crafted cargo.toml file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51058 | Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability has been discovered in TCPDF 6.7.5. This vulnerability enables a user to read arbitrary files from ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51058</link><description>Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability has been discovered in TCPDF 6.7.5. This vulnerability enables a user to read arbitrary files from the server's file system through &lt;img /&gt; src tag, potentially exposing sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 17:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10878 | Sugar Calendar (Lite) &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10878</link><description>The Sugar Calendar – Simple Event Management plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 17:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11407 | Denial of Service through Data corruption in gRPC-C++</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11407</link><description>There exists a denial of service through Data corruption in gRPC-C++ - gRPC-C++ servers with transmit zero copy enabled through the channel arg GRPC_ARG_TCP_TX_ZEROCOPY_ENABLED can experience data corruption issues. The data sent by the application may be corrupted before transmission over the network thus leading the receiver to receive an incorrect set of bytes causing RPC requests to fail. We recommend upgrading past commit e9046b2bbebc0cb7f5dc42008f807f6c7e98e791</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 17:17:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53365 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in PHPGURUKUL Vehicle Parking Management System v1.13 in /users/profile.php...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53365</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in PHPGURUKUL Vehicle Parking Management System v1.13 in /users/profile.php. This vulnerability allows authenticated users to inject malicious XSS scripts into the profile name field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 16:52:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53555 | A CSV injection vulnerability in Taiga v6.8.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted CSV file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53555</link><description>A CSV injection vulnerability in Taiga v6.8.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted CSV file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 16:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52336 | Tuned: `script_pre` and `script_post` options allow to pass arbitrary scripts executed by root</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52336</link><description>A script injection vulnerability was identified in the Tuned package. The `instance_create()` D-Bus function can be called by locally logged-in users without authentication. This flaw allows a local non-privileged user to execute a D-Bus call with `script_pre` or `script_post` options that permit arbitrary scripts with their absolute paths to be passed. These user or attacker-controlled executable scripts or programs could then be executed by Tuned with root privileges that could allow attackers to local privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52337 | Tuned: improper sanitization of `instance_name` parameter of the `instance_create()` method</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52337</link><description>A log spoofing flaw was found in the Tuned package due to improper sanitization of some API arguments. This flaw allows an attacker to pass a controlled sequence of characters; newlines can be inserted into the log. Instead of the 'evil' the attacker could mimic a valid TuneD log line and trick the administrator. The quotes '' are usually used in TuneD logs citing raw user input, so there will always be the ' character ending the spoofed input, and the administrator can easily overlook this. This logged string is later used in logging and in the output of utilities, for example, `tuned-adm get_instances` or other third-party programs that use Tuned's D-Bus interface for such operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36463 | The implementation of atob in "Zabbix JS" allows to create a string with arbitrary content and use it to access internal properties of objec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36463</link><description>The implementation of atob in "Zabbix JS" allows to create a string with arbitrary content and use it to access internal properties of objects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:23:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22117 | Value of sysmap_element_url can be de-synchronized causing the map element to crash when new URLs is added</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22117</link><description>When a URL is added to the map element, it is recorded in the database with sequential IDs. Upon adding a new URL, the system retrieves the last sysmapelementurlid value and increments it by one. However, an issue arises when a user manually changes the sysmapelementurlid value by adding sysmapelementurlid + 1. This action prevents others from adding URLs to the map element.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 14:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-10408 | Improper Access Control in Core.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10408</link><description>QSEE will randomly experience a fatal error during execution due to speculative instruction fetches from device memory. Device memory is not valid executable memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 14:13:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-18306 | Information Exposure in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18306</link><description>Information disclosure due to uninitialized variable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 14:13:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-18307 | Information Exposure in Kernel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18307</link><description>Information disclosure possible while audio playback.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 14:13:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-11816 | Use After Free in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11816</link><description>Crafted Binder Request Causes Heap UAF in MediaServer</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 14:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-5852 | Buffer Over-read in IPA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5852</link><description>An unsigned integer underflow vulnerability in IPA driver result into a buffer over-read while reading NAT entry using debugfs command 'cat /sys/kernel/debug/ipa/ip4_nat'</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 14:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8236 | Elementor Website Builder – More than Just a Page Builder &amp;lt;= 3.25.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8236</link><description>The Elementor Website Builder – More than Just a Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter of the Icon widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.25.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 14:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9461 | Total Upkeep &amp;lt;= 1.16.6 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Remote Code Execution via Backup Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9461</link><description>The Total Upkeep – WordPress Backup Plugin plus Restore &amp; Migrate by BoldGrid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.16.6 via the cron_interval parameter. This is due to missing input validation and sanitization. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 14:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11691 | An attacker could have caused memory corruption due to a flaw in Apple's GPU driver; this can be avoided by working around the flaw. 
*Note:...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11691</link><description>An attacker could have caused memory corruption due to a flaw in Apple's GPU driver; this can be avoided by working around the flaw. 
*Note: This issue only affected macOS operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 133, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.5, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.18, Thunderbird &lt; 133, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11692 | An attacker could cause a select dropdown to be shown over another tab; this could have led to user confusion and possible spoofing attacks....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11692</link><description>An attacker could cause a select dropdown to be shown over another tab; this could have led to user confusion and possible spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 133, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.5, Thunderbird &lt; 133, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11693 | The executable file warning was not presented when downloading .library-ms files.  
*Note: This issue only affected Windows operating system...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11693</link><description>The executable file warning was not presented when downloading .library-ms files.  
*Note: This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 133, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.5, Thunderbird &lt; 133, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11694 | Enhanced Tracking Protection's Strict mode may have inadvertently allowed a CSP `frame-src` bypass and DOM-based XSS through the Google Safe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11694</link><description>Enhanced Tracking Protection's Strict mode may have inadvertently allowed a CSP `frame-src` bypass and DOM-based XSS through the Google SafeFrame shim in the Web Compatibility extension. This issue could have exposed users to malicious frames masquerading as legitimate content. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 133, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.5, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.18, Thunderbird &lt; 133, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11695 | A crafted URL containing Arabic script and whitespace characters could have hidden the true origin of the page, resulting in a potential spo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11695</link><description>A crafted URL containing Arabic script and whitespace characters could have hidden the true origin of the page, resulting in a potential spoofing attack. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 133, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.5, Thunderbird &lt; 133, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11696 | The application failed to account for exceptions thrown by the `loadManifestFromFile` method during add-on signature verification. This flaw...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11696</link><description>The application failed to account for exceptions thrown by the `loadManifestFromFile` method during add-on signature verification. This flaw, triggered by an invalid or unsupported extension manifest, could have caused runtime errors that disrupted the signature validation process. As a result, the enforcement of signature validation for unrelated add-ons may have been bypassed.  Signature validation in this context is used to ensure that third-party applications on the user's computer have not tampered with the user's extensions, limiting the impact of this issue. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 133, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.5, Thunderbird &lt; 133, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11697 | When handling keypress events, an attacker may have been able to trick a user into bypassing the "Open Executable File?" confirmation dialog...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11697</link><description>When handling keypress events, an attacker may have been able to trick a user into bypassing the "Open Executable File?" confirmation dialog. This could have led to malicious code execution. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 133, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.5, Thunderbird &lt; 133, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11698 | A flaw in handling fullscreen transitions may have inadvertently caused the application to become stuck in fullscreen mode when a modal dial...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11698</link><description>A flaw in handling fullscreen transitions may have inadvertently caused the application to become stuck in fullscreen mode when a modal dialog was opened during the transition. This issue left users unable to exit fullscreen mode using standard actions like pressing "Esc" or accessing right-click menus, resulting in a disrupted browsing experience until the browser is restarted.  
*This bug only affects the application when running on macOS. Other operating systems are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 133, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.5, Thunderbird &lt; 133, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11699 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 132, Firefox ESR 128.4, and Thunderbird 128.4. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11699</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 132, Firefox ESR 128.4, and Thunderbird 128.4. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 133, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.5, Thunderbird &lt; 133, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11700 | Malicious websites may have been able to user intent confirmation through tapjacking. This could have led to users unknowingly approving the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11700</link><description>Malicious websites may have been able to user intent confirmation through tapjacking. This could have led to users unknowingly approving the launch of external applications, potentially exposing them to underlying vulnerabilities. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 133 and Thunderbird &lt; 133.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11701 | The incorrect domain may have been displayed in the address bar during an interrupted navigation attempt. This could have led to user confus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11701</link><description>The incorrect domain may have been displayed in the address bar during an interrupted navigation attempt. This could have led to user confusion and possible spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 133 and Thunderbird &lt; 133.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11702 | Copying sensitive information from Private Browsing tabs on Android, such as passwords, may have inadvertently stored data in the cloud-base...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11702</link><description>Copying sensitive information from Private Browsing tabs on Android, such as passwords, may have inadvertently stored data in the cloud-based clipboard history if enabled. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 133 and Thunderbird &lt; 133.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11703 | On Android, Firefox may have inadvertently allowed viewing saved passwords without the required device PIN authentication. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11703</link><description>On Android, Firefox may have inadvertently allowed viewing saved passwords without the required device PIN authentication. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 133.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11704 | A double-free issue could have occurred in `sec_pkcs7_decoder_start_decrypt()` when handling an error path. Under specific conditions, the s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11704</link><description>A double-free issue could have occurred in `sec_pkcs7_decoder_start_decrypt()` when handling an error path. Under specific conditions, the same symmetric key could have been freed twice, potentially leading to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 133 and Thunderbird &lt; 133.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11705 | `NSC_DeriveKey` inadvertently assumed that the `phKey` parameter is always non-NULL. When it was passed as NULL, a segmentation fault (SEGV)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11705</link><description>`NSC_DeriveKey` inadvertently assumed that the `phKey` parameter is always non-NULL. When it was passed as NULL, a segmentation fault (SEGV) occurred, leading to crashes. This behavior conflicted with the PKCS#11 v3.0 specification, which allows `phKey` to be NULL for certain mechanisms. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 133 and Thunderbird &lt; 133.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11706 | A null pointer dereference may have inadvertently occurred in `pk12util`, and specifically in the `SEC_ASN1DecodeItem_Util` function, when h...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11706</link><description>A null pointer dereference may have inadvertently occurred in `pk12util`, and specifically in the `SEC_ASN1DecodeItem_Util` function, when handling malformed or improperly formatted input files. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 133 and Thunderbird &lt; 133.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11708 | Missing thread synchronization primitives could have led to a data race on members of the PlaybackParams structure. This vulnerability affec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11708</link><description>Missing thread synchronization primitives could have led to a data race on members of the PlaybackParams structure. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 133 and Thunderbird &lt; 133.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53975 | Accessing a non-secure HTTP site that uses a non-existent port may cause the SSL padlock icon in the location URL bar to, misleadingly, appe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53975</link><description>Accessing a non-secure HTTP site that uses a non-existent port may cause the SSL padlock icon in the location URL bar to, misleadingly, appear secure. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 133.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53976 | Under certain circumstances, navigating to a webpage would result in the address missing from the location URL bar, making it unclear what t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53976</link><description>Under certain circumstances, navigating to a webpage would result in the address missing from the location URL bar, making it unclear what the URL was for the loaded webpage. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 133.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9928 | A vulnerability exists in NSD570 login panel that does not restrict excessive authentication attempts. If exploited, this could
cause accoun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9928</link><description>A vulnerability exists in NSD570 login panel that does not restrict excessive authentication attempts. If exploited, this could
cause account takeover and unauthorized access to the system
when an attacker conducts brute-force attacks against the
equipment login. Note that the system supports only one concurrent session and implements a delay of more than a second
between failed login attempts making it difficult to automate the
attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9929 | A vulnerability exists in NSD570 that allows any authenticated
user to access all device logs disclosing login information with
timestamps.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9929</link><description>A vulnerability exists in NSD570 that allows any authenticated
user to access all device logs disclosing login information with
timestamps.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 13:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38833 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability (CVE-2024-38833)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38833</link><description>VMware Aria Operations contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. A malicious actor with editing access to email templates might inject malicious script leading to stored cross-site scripting in the product VMware Aria Operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 12:20:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38834 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability (CVE-2024-38834)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38834</link><description>VMware Aria Operations contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. A malicious actor with editing access to cloud provider might be able to inject malicious script leading to stored cross-site scripting in the product VMware Aria Operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 12:20:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38830 | Local privilege escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38830</link><description>VMware Aria Operations contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with local administrative privileges may trigger this vulnerability to escalate privileges to root user on the appliance running VMware Aria Operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38831 | Local privilege escalation vulnerability (CVE-2024-38831)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38831</link><description>VMware Aria Operations contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability.  A malicious actor with local administrative privileges can insert malicious commands into the properties file to escalate privileges to  a root user on the appliance running VMware Aria Operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38832 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability (CVE-2024-38832)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38832</link><description>VMware Aria Operations contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. A malicious actor with editing access to views may be able to inject malicious script leading to stored cross-site scripting in the product VMware Aria Operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-0163 | Prototype Pollution in convict</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0163</link><description>Improperly Controlled Modification of Object Prototype Attributes ('Prototype Pollution') vulnerability in Mozilla Convict.

This allows an attacker to inject attributes that are used in other components, or to override existing attributes with ones that have incompatible type, which may lead to a crash.


The main use case of Convict is for handling server-side 
configurations written by the admins owning the servers, and not random 
users. So it's unlikely that an admin would deliberately sabotage their 
own server. Still, a situation can happen where an admin not 
knowledgeable about JavaScript could be tricked by an attacker into 
writing the malicious JavaScript code into some config files.



This issue affects Convict: before 6.2.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2142 | Nunjucks autoescape bypass leads to cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2142</link><description>In Nunjucks versions prior to version 3.2.4, it was 
possible to bypass the restrictions which are provided by the autoescape
 functionality. If there are two user-controlled parameters on the same 
line used in the views, it was possible to inject cross site scripting 
payloads using the backslash \ character.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1521 | Local Privilege Escalation in sccache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1521</link><description>On Linux the sccache client can execute arbitrary code with the privileges of a local sccache server, by preloading the code in a shared library passed to LD_PRELOAD.


If the server is run as root (which is the default when installing the  snap package https://snapcraft.io/sccache ), this means a user running the sccache client can get root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47248 | Apache NimBLE: Buffer overflow in NimBLE MESH Bluetooth stack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47248</link><description>Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in Apache NimBLE.

Specially crafted MESH message could result in memory corruption when non-default build configuration is used.
This issue affects Apache NimBLE: through 1.7.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.8.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47249 | Apache NimBLE: Lack of input sanitization leading to out-of-bound reads in multiple advertisement handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47249</link><description>Improper Validation of Array Index vulnerability in Apache NimBLE.

Lack of input validation for HCI events from controller could result in out-of-bound memory corruption and crash.
This issue requires broken or bogus Bluetooth controller and thus severity is considered low.
This issue affects Apache NimBLE: through 1.7.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.8.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47250 | Apache NimBLE: Lack of input validation in HCI advertising report could lead to potential out-of-bound access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47250</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in Apache NimBLE.

Missing proper validation of HCI advertising report could lead to out-of-bound access when parsing HCI event and thus bogus GAP 'device found' events being sent.
This issue requires broken or bogus Bluetooth controller and thus severity is considered low.
This issue affects Apache NimBLE: through 1.7.0.


Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.8.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51569 | Apache NimBLE: Lack of input sanitization leading to out-of-bound reads in Number of Completed Packets HCI event handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51569</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in Apache NimBLE.

Missing proper validation of HCI Number Of Completed Packets could lead to out-of-bound access when parsing HCI event and invalid read from HCI transport memory.
This issue requires broken or bogus Bluetooth controller and thus severity is considered low.
This issue affects Apache NimBLE: through 1.7.0.


Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.8.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10308 | Jeg Elementor Kit &amp;lt;= 2.6.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via JKit - Countdown Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10308</link><description>The Jeg Elementor Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's JKit - Countdown widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10579 | Hustle – Email Marketing, Lead Generation, Optins, Popups &amp;lt;= 7.8.5 - Missing Authorization to Unpublished Form Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10579</link><description>The Hustle – Email Marketing, Lead Generation, Optins, Popups plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the preview_module() function in all versions up to, and including, 7.8.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view unpublished forms.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11024 | AppPresser – Mobile App Framework &amp;lt;= 4.4.6 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via Password Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11024</link><description>The AppPresser – Mobile App Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.6. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's password reset code prior to updating their password. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers, with knowledge of a user's email address, to reset the user's password and gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8899 | Jeg Elementor Kit &amp;lt;= 2.6.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via sg_content_template</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8899</link><description>The Jeg Elementor Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 via the render_content function in class/elements/views/class-tabs-view.php. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive private, pending, and draft template data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50361 | A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50361</link><description>A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The source of the vulnerability relies on multiple parameters belonging to the "certificate_file_remove" API which are not properly sanitized before being concatenated to OS level commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50362 | A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50362</link><description>A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The source of the vulnerability relies on multiple parameters belonging to the "connection_profile_apply" API which are not properly sanitized before being concatenated to OS level commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50363 | A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50363</link><description>A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The source of the vulnerability relies on multiple parameters belonging to the "mp_apply" API which are not properly sanitized before being concatenated to OS level commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50364 | A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50364</link><description>A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The source of the vulnerability relies on multiple parameters belonging to the "export_log" API which are not properly sanitized before being concatenated to OS level commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50365 | A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50365</link><description>A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The source of the vulnerability relies on multiple parameters belonging to the "lan_apply" API which are not properly sanitized before being concatenated to OS level commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50366 | A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50366</link><description>A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The source of the vulnerability relies on multiple parameters belonging to the "applications_apply" API which are not properly sanitized before being concatenated to OS level commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50367 | A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50367</link><description>A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The source of the vulnerability relies on multiple parameters belonging to the "sta_log_htm" API which are not properly sanitized before being concatenated to OS level commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50368 | A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50368</link><description>A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The source of the vulnerability relies on multiple parameters belonging to the "basic_htm" API which are not properly sanitized before being concatenated to OS level commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50369 | A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50369</link><description>A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The source of the vulnerability relies on multiple parameters belonging to the "multiple_ssid_htm" API which are not properly sanitized before being concatenated to OS level commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50370 | A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50370</link><description>A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The vulnerability can be exploited by remote unauthenticated users capable of interacting with the default "edgserver" service enabled on the access point and malicious commands are executed with root privileges. No authentication is enabled on the service and the source of the vulnerability resides in processing code associated to the "cfg_cmd_set_eth_conf" operation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50371 | A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50371</link><description>A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The vulnerability can be exploited by remote unauthenticated users capable of interacting with the default "edgserver" service enabled on the access point and malicious commands are executed with root privileges. No authentication is enabled on the service and the source of the vulnerability resides in processing code associated to the "wlan_scan" operation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50372 | A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50372</link><description>A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The vulnerability can be exploited by remote unauthenticated users capable of interacting with the default "edgserver" service enabled on the access point and malicious commands are executed with root privileges. No authentication is enabled on the service and the source of the vulnerability resides in processing code associated to the "backup_config_to_utility" operation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50373 | A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50373</link><description>A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The vulnerability can be exploited by remote unauthenticated users capable of interacting with the default "edgserver" service enabled on the access point and malicious commands are executed with root privileges. No authentication is enabled on the service and the source of the vulnerability resides in processing code associated to the "restore_config_from_utility" operation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50374 | A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50374</link><description>A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The vulnerability can be exploited by remote unauthenticated users capable of interacting with the default "edgserver" service enabled on the access point and malicious commands are executed with root privileges. No authentication is enabled on the service and the source of the vulnerability resides in processing code associated to the "capture_packages" operation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50375 | A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50375</link><description>A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The vulnerability can be exploited by remote unauthenticated users capable of interacting with the default "edgserver" service enabled on the access point.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50376 | A CWE-79 "Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting')" was discovered affecting the following devic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50376</link><description>A CWE-79 "Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting')" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The vulnerability can be exploited remotely leveraging a rogue Wi-Fi access point with a malicious SSID.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50377 | A CWE-798 "Use of Hard-coded Credentials" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50377</link><description>A CWE-798 "Use of Hard-coded Credentials" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The vulnerability is associated to the backup configuration functionality that by default encrypts the archives using a static password.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50358 | A CWE-15 "External Control of System or Configuration Setting" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50358</link><description>A CWE-15 "External Control of System or Configuration Setting" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The vulnerability can be exploited by authenticated users by restoring a tampered configuration backup.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50359 | A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50359</link><description>A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The source of the vulnerability relies on multiple parameters belonging to the "scan_ap" API which are not properly sanitized before being concatenated to OS level commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50360 | A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50360</link><description>A CWE-78 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')" was discovered affecting the following devices manufactured by Advantech: EKI-6333AC-2G (&lt;= 1.6.3), EKI-6333AC-2GD (&lt;= v1.6.3) and EKI-6333AC-1GPO (&lt;= v1.2.1). The source of the vulnerability relies on multiple parameters belonging to the "snmp_apply" API which are not properly sanitized before being concatenated to OS level commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11680 | ProjectSend Unauthenticated Configuration Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11680</link><description>ProjectSend versions prior to r1720 are affected by an improper authentication vulnerability. Remote, unauthenticated attackers can exploit this flaw by sending crafted HTTP requests to options.php, enabling unauthorized modification of the application's configuration. Successful exploitation allows attackers to create accounts, upload webshells, and embed malicious JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11032 | Parsi Date &amp;lt;= 5.1.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via add_query_arg Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11032</link><description>The Parsi Date plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-10394 | Improper Authentication in Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10394</link><description>Initial xbl_sec revision does not have all the debug policy features and critical checks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-11076 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-11076</link><description>On some hardware revisions where VP9 decoding is hardware-accelerated, the frame size is not programmed correctly into the decoder hardware which can lead to an invalid memory access by the decoder.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-15832 | Buffer overwrite due to improper input validation in WLAN host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15832</link><description>Buffer overwrite in the WLAN host driver by leveraging a compromised WLAN FW</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-17772 | Multiple buffer overread vulnerabilities in WLAN</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17772</link><description>In multiple functions that process 802.11 frames, out-of-bounds reads can occur due to insufficient validation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-18153 | Use After Free in WLAN</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18153</link><description>A race condition exists in a driver potentially leading to a use-after-free condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-11922 | Configurations in Android Build</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11922</link><description>Wrong configuration in Touch Pal application can collect user behavior data without awareness by the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-11952 | Improper Authentication in TrustZone</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11952</link><description>An image with a version lower than the fuse version may potentially be booted lead to improper authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11091 | Support SVG – Upload svg files in wordpress without hassle &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 -  Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11091</link><description>The Support SVG – Upload svg files in wordpress without hassle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via REST API SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 08:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11119 | BNE Gallery Extended &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via gallery Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11119</link><description>The BNE Gallery Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gallery' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 08:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11192 | Spotify Play Button for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.11 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via spotifyplaybutton Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11192</link><description>The Spotify Play Button for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's spotifyplaybutton shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 08:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9170 | Booster for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 7.2.3 - Authenticated (ShopManager+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wcj_product_meta Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9170</link><description>The Booster for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wcj_product_meta shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with ShopManager-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 08:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11202 | Multiple Plugins &amp;lt;= (Various Versions) - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via cminds_free_guide Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11202</link><description>Multiple plugins for WordPress are vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the cminds_free_guide shortcode in various versions due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28038 | The web interface of the affected devices processes a cookie value improperly, leading to a stack buffer overflow. More precisely, giving to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28038</link><description>The web interface of the affected devices processes a cookie value improperly, leading to a stack buffer overflow. More precisely, giving too long character string to MFPSESSIONID parameter results in a stack buffer overflow. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versions, refer to the information provided by the respective vendors listed under [References].</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28955 | Affected devices create coredump files when crashed, storing them with world-readable permission. Any local user of the device can examine t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28955</link><description>Affected devices create coredump files when crashed, storing them with world-readable permission. Any local user of the device can examine the coredump files, and research the memory contents. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versions, refer to the information provided by the respective vendors listed under [References].</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29146 | User passwords are decrypted and stored on memory before any user logged in. Those decrypted passwords can be retrieved from the coredump fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29146</link><description>User passwords are decrypted and stored on memory before any user logged in. Those decrypted passwords can be retrieved from the coredump file. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versions, refer to the information provided by the respective vendors listed under [References].</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29978 | User passwords are decrypted and stored on memory before any user logged in. Those decrypted passwords can be retrieved from the coredump fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29978</link><description>User passwords are decrypted and stored on memory before any user logged in. Those decrypted passwords can be retrieved from the coredump file. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versions, refer to the information provided by the respective vendors listed under [References].</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32151 | User passwords are decrypted and stored on memory before any user logged in. Those decrypted passwords can be retrieved from the coredump fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32151</link><description>User passwords are decrypted and stored on memory before any user logged in. Those decrypted passwords can be retrieved from the coredump file. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versions, refer to the information provided by the respective vendors listed under [References].</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33605 | Improper processing of some parameters of installed_emanual_list.html leads to a path traversal vulnerability. As for the details of affecte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33605</link><description>Improper processing of some parameters of installed_emanual_list.html leads to a path traversal vulnerability. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versions, refer to the information provided by the respective vendors listed under [References].</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33610 | "sessionlist.html" and "sys_trayentryreboot.html" are accessible with no authentication. "sessionlist.html" provides logged-in users' sessio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33610</link><description>"sessionlist.html" and "sys_trayentryreboot.html" are accessible with no authentication. "sessionlist.html" provides logged-in users' session information including session cookies, and "sys_trayentryreboot.html" allows to reboot the device. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versions, refer to the information provided by the respective vendors listed under [References].</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33616 | Admin authentication can be bypassed with some specific invalid credentials, which allows logging in with an administrative privilege. Sharp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33616</link><description>Admin authentication can be bypassed with some specific invalid credentials, which allows logging in with an administrative privilege. Sharp Corporation states the telnet feature is implemented on older models only, and is planning to provide the firmware update to remove the feature. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versions, refer to the information provided by the respective vendors listed under [References].</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34162 | The web interface of the affected devices is designed to hide the LDAP credentials even for administrative users. But configuring LDAP authe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34162</link><description>The web interface of the affected devices is designed to hide the LDAP credentials even for administrative users. But configuring LDAP authentication to "SIMPLE", the device communicates with the LDAP server in clear-text. The LDAP password can be retrieved from this clear-text communication. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versions, refer to the information provided by the respective vendors listed under [References].</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35244 | There are several hidden accounts. Some of them are intended for maintenance engineers, and with the knowledge of their passwords (e.g., by ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35244</link><description>There are several hidden accounts. Some of them are intended for maintenance engineers, and with the knowledge of their passwords (e.g., by examining the coredump), these accounts can be used to re-configure the device. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versions, refer to the information provided by the respective vendors listed under [References].</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36248 | API keys for some cloud services are hardcoded in the "main" binary. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36248</link><description>API keys for some cloud services are hardcoded in the "main" binary. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versions, refer to the information provided by the respective vendors listed under [References].</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36249 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Sharp Corporation and Toshiba Tech Corporation multiple MFPs (multifunction printers). If this ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36249</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Sharp Corporation and Toshiba Tech Corporation multiple MFPs (multifunction printers). If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the administrative page of the affected MFPs. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versions, refer to the information provided by the respective vendors listed under [References].</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36251 | The web interface of the affected devices process some crafted HTTP requests improperly, leading to a device crash. More precisely, a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36251</link><description>The web interface of the affected devices process some crafted HTTP requests improperly, leading to a device crash. More precisely, a crafted parameter to billcodedef_sub_sel.html is not processed properly and device-crash happens. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versions, refer to the information provided by the respective vendors listed under [References].</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36254 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in Sharp Corporation and Toshiba Tec Corporation multiple MFPs (multifunction printers), which may l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36254</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in Sharp Corporation and Toshiba Tec Corporation multiple MFPs (multifunction printers), which may lead to a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9504 | Booking calendar, Appointment Booking System &amp;lt;= 3.2.15 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9504</link><description>The Booking calendar, Appointment Booking System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47257 | Florent Thiéry has found that selected Axis devices were vulnerable to handling certain ethernet frames which could lead to the Axis device ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47257</link><description>Florent Thiéry has found that selected Axis devices were vulnerable to handling certain ethernet frames which could lead to the Axis device becoming unavailable in the network. 
Axis has released patched AXIS OS versions for the highlighted flaw for products that are still under AXIS OS software support. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8160 | Erik de Jong, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX API ftptest.cgi did not have a sufficient input validation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8160</link><description>Erik de Jong, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX API ftptest.cgi did not have a sufficient input validation allowing for a possible command injection leading to being able to transfer files from/to the Axis device. This flaw can only be exploited after authenticating with an administrator-privileged service account. 
Axis has released patched AXIS OS versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8772 | 51l3nc3, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX API managedoverlayimages.cgi was vulnerable to a race condition ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8772</link><description>51l3nc3, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX API managedoverlayimages.cgi was vulnerable to a race condition attack allowing for an attacker to block access to the overlay configuration page in the web interface of the Axis device. This flaw can only be exploited after authenticating with an operator- or administrator-privileged service account. Axis has released patched AXIS OS versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6831 | Seth Fogie, member of AXIS Camera Station Pro Bug Bounty Program has found that it is possible to edit and/or remove views without the neces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6831</link><description>Seth Fogie, member of AXIS Camera Station Pro Bug Bounty Program has found that it is possible to edit and/or remove views without the necessary permission due to a client-side-only check. 
Axis has released patched versions for the highlighted flaw. Please 
refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6476 | Gee-netics, member of the AXIS Camera Station Pro Bug Bounty Program has found that it is possible for a non-admin user to gain system privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6476</link><description>Gee-netics, member of the AXIS Camera Station Pro Bug Bounty Program has found that it is possible for a non-admin user to gain system privileges by redirecting a file deletion upon service restart. 
 Axis has released patched versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6749 | Seth Fogie, member of the AXIS Camera Station Pro Bug Bounty Program, has found that the Incident report feature may expose sensitive creden...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6749</link><description>Seth Fogie, member of the AXIS Camera Station Pro Bug Bounty Program, has found that the Incident report feature may expose sensitive credentials on the AXIS Camera Station windows client. If Incident report is not being used with credentials configured this flaw does not apply. 

 Axis has released patched versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10857 | Product Input Fields for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.9 -  Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10857</link><description>The Product Input Fields for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.9 via the handle_downloads() function due to insufficient file path validation/sanitization. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:53:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11002 | InPost Gallery &amp;lt;= 2.1.4.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via inpost_gallery_get_shortcode_template</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11002</link><description>The The InPost Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution via the inpost_gallery_get_shortcode_template AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4.2. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10471 | Everest Forms &amp;lt; 3.0.4.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10471</link><description>The Everest Forms  WordPress plugin before 3.0.4.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10542 | Spam protection, Anti-Spam, FireWall by CleanTalk &amp;lt;= 6.43.2 - Authorization Bypass via Reverse DNS Spoofing to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10542</link><description>The Spam protection, Anti-Spam, FireWall by CleanTalk plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized Arbitrary Plugin Installation due to an authorization bypass via reverse DNS spoofing on the checkWithoutToken function in all versions up to, and including, 6.43.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to install and activate arbitrary plugins which can be leveraged to achieve remote code execution if another vulnerable plugin is installed and activated.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 05:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10570 | Security &amp;amp; Malware scan by CleanTalk &amp;lt;= 2.145 - Authorization Bypass via Reverse DNS Spoofing to Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10570</link><description>The Security &amp; Malware scan by CleanTalk plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized SQL Injection due to an authorization bypass via reverse DNS spoofing on the checkWithoutToken function in all versions up to, and including, 2.145, as well as insufficient input sanitization and validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 05:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10781 | Spam protection, Anti-Spam, FireWall by CleanTalk &amp;lt;= 6.44 - Authorization Bypass due to Missing Empty Value Check to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10781</link><description>The Spam protection, Anti-Spam, FireWall by CleanTalk plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized Arbitrary Plugin Installation due to an missing empty value check on the 'api_key' value in the 'perform' function in all versions up to, and including, 6.44. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to install and activate arbitrary plugins which can be leveraged to achieve remote code execution if another vulnerable plugin is installed and activated.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 05:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53278 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in WP Admin UI Customize versions prior to ver 1.5.14. If a malicious admin user customizes the ad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53278</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in WP Admin UI Customize versions prior to ver 1.5.14. If a malicious admin user customizes the admin screen with some malicious contents, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the other users who are accessing the admin screen.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 04:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11342 | Skt NURCaptcha &amp;lt;= 3.5.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery  to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11342</link><description>The Skt NURCaptcha plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation in the skt-nurc-admin.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 03:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11418 | Additional Order Filters for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.21 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11418</link><description>The Additional Order Filters for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'shipping_method_filter' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 03:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49353 | IBM Watson Speech Services Cartridge for IBM Cloud Pak for Data denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49353</link><description>IBM Watson Speech Services Cartridge for IBM Cloud Pak for Data 4.0.0 through 5.0.2 does not properly check inputs to resources that are used concurrently, which might lead to unexpected states, possibly resulting in a crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 03:45:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49351 | IBM Workload Scheduler information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49351</link><description>IBM Workload Scheduler 9.5, 10.1, and 10.2 stores user credentials in plain text which can be read by a local user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 03:45:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49595 | Dell Wyse Management Suite, version WMS 4.4 and before, contain an Authentication Bypass by Capture-replay vulnerability. A high privileged ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49595</link><description>Dell Wyse Management Suite, version WMS 4.4 and before, contain an Authentication Bypass by Capture-replay vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 03:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49596 | Dell Wyse Management Suite, version WMS 4.4 and prior, contain a Missing Authorization vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49596</link><description>Dell Wyse Management Suite, version WMS 4.4 and prior, contain a Missing Authorization vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Denial of service and arbitrary file deletion</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 03:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49597 | Dell Wyse Management Suite, versions WMS 4.4 and prior, contain an Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49597</link><description>Dell Wyse Management Suite, versions WMS 4.4 and prior, contain an Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Protection mechanism bypass.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 03:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10729 | Booking &amp;amp; Appointment Plugin for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 6.9.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Option Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10729</link><description>The Booking &amp; Appointment Plugin for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'save_google_calendar_data' function in versions up to, and including, 6.9.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions or above to update the site options arbitrarily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 02:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11677 | CodeAstro Hospital Management System Add Vendor Details Page his_admin_add_vendor.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11677</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Hospital Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /backend/admin/his_admin_add_vendor.php of the component Add Vendor Details Page. The manipulation of the argument v_name/v_adr/v_number/v_email/v_phone/v_desc leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 02:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11678 | CodeAstro Hospital Management System his_doc_register_patient.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11678</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Hospital Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /backend/doc/his_doc_register_patient.php. The manipulation of the argument pat_fname/pat_ailment/pat_lname/pat_age/pat_dob/pat_number/pat_phone/pat_type/pat_addr leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 02:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52899 | IBM Data Virtualization Manager code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52899</link><description>IBM Data Virtualization Manager for z/OS 1.1 and 1.2 could allow an authenticated user to inject malicious JDBC URL parameters and execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 01:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11675 | CodeAstro Hospital Management System Add Patient Details Page his_admin_register_patient.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11675</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CodeAstro Hospital Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /backend/admin/his_admin_register_patient.php of the component Add Patient Details Page. The manipulation of the argument pat_fname/pat_ailment/pat_lname/pat_age/pat_dob/pat_number/pat_phone/pat_type/pat_addr leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 01:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11676 | CodeAstro Hospital Management System Add Laboratory Equipment Page his_admin_add_lab_equipment.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11676</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Hospital Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /backend/admin/his_admin_add_lab_equipment.php of the component Add Laboratory Equipment Page. The manipulation of the argument eqp_code/eqp_name/eqp_vendor/eqp_desc/eqp_dept/eqp_status/eqp_qty leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 01:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11674 | CodeAstro Hospital Management System his_doc_update-account.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11674</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in CodeAstro Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /backend/doc/his_doc_update-account.php. The manipulation of the argument doc_dpic leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 23:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53843 | Reflected XSS Vulnerability in Authentication Flow URL Handling in @dapperduckling/keycloak-connector-server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53843</link><description>@dapperduckling/keycloak-connector-server is an opinionated series of libraries for Node.js applications and frontend clients to interface with keycloak. A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the authentication flow of the application. This issue arises due to improper sanitization of the URL parameters, allowing the URL bar's contents to be injected and reflected into the HTML page. An attacker could craft a malicious URL to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the browser of a victim who visits the link. Any application utilizing this authentication library is vulnerable. Users of the application are at risk if they can be lured into clicking on a crafted malicious link. The vulnerability has been patched in version 2.5.5 by ensuring proper sanitization and escaping of user input in the affected URL parameters. Users are strongly encouraged to upgrade. If upgrading is not immediately possible, users can implement the following workarounds: 1. Employ a Web Application Firewall (WAF) to block malicious requests containing suspicious URL parameters. or 2. Apply input validation and escaping directly within the application’s middleware or reverse proxy layer, specifically targeting the affected parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 23:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11673 | 1000 Projects Bookstore Management System cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11673</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in 1000 Projects Bookstore Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 23:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53096 | mm: resolve faulty mmap_region() error path behaviour</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53096</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: resolve faulty mmap_region() error path behaviour

The mmap_region() function is somewhat terrifying, with spaghetti-like
control flow and numerous means by which issues can arise and incomplete
state, memory leaks and other unpleasantness can occur.

A large amount of the complexity arises from trying to handle errors late
in the process of mapping a VMA, which forms the basis of recently
observed issues with resource leaks and observable inconsistent state.

Taking advantage of previous patches in this series we move a number of
checks earlier in the code, simplifying things by moving the core of the
logic into a static internal function __mmap_region().

Doing this allows us to perform a number of checks up front before we do
any real work, and allows us to unwind the writable unmap check
unconditionally as required and to perform a CONFIG_DEBUG_VM_MAPLE_TREE
validation unconditionally also.

We move a number of things here:

1. We preallocate memory for the iterator before we call the file-backed
   memory hook, allowing us to exit early and avoid having to perform
   complicated and error-prone close/free logic. We carefully free
   iterator state on both success and error paths.

2. The enclosing mmap_region() function handles the mapping_map_writable()
   logic early. Previously the logic had the mapping_map_writable() at the
   point of mapping a newly allocated file-backed VMA, and a matching
   mapping_unmap_writable() on success and error paths.

   We now do this unconditionally if this is a file-backed, shared writable
   mapping. If a driver changes the flags to eliminate VM_MAYWRITE, however
   doing so does not invalidate the seal check we just performed, and we in
   any case always decrement the counter in the wrapper.

   We perform a debug assert to ensure a driver does not attempt to do the
   opposite.

3. We also move arch_validate_flags() up into the mmap_region()
   function. This is only relevant on arm64 and sparc64, and the check is
   only meaningful for SPARC with ADI enabled. We explicitly add a warning
   for this arch if a driver invalidates this check, though the code ought
   eventually to be fixed to eliminate the need for this.

With all of these measures in place, we no longer need to explicitly close
the VMA on error paths, as we place all checks which might fail prior to a
call to any driver mmap hook.

This eliminates an entire class of errors, makes the code easier to reason
about and more robust.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53097 | mm: krealloc: Fix MTE false alarm in __do_krealloc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53097</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: krealloc: Fix MTE false alarm in __do_krealloc

This patch addresses an issue introduced by commit 1a83a716ec233 ("mm:
krealloc: consider spare memory for __GFP_ZERO") which causes MTE
(Memory Tagging Extension) to falsely report a slab-out-of-bounds error.

The problem occurs when zeroing out spare memory in __do_krealloc. The
original code only considered software-based KASAN and did not account
for MTE. It does not reset the KASAN tag before calling memset, leading
to a mismatch between the pointer tag and the memory tag, resulting
in a false positive.

Example of the error:
==================================================================
swapper/0: BUG: KASAN: slab-out-of-bounds in __memset+0x84/0x188
swapper/0: Write at addr f4ffff8005f0fdf0 by task swapper/0/1
swapper/0: Pointer tag: [f4], memory tag: [fe]
swapper/0:
swapper/0: CPU: 4 UID: 0 PID: 1 Comm: swapper/0 Not tainted 6.12.
swapper/0: Hardware name: MT6991(ENG) (DT)
swapper/0: Call trace:
swapper/0:  dump_backtrace+0xfc/0x17c
swapper/0:  show_stack+0x18/0x28
swapper/0:  dump_stack_lvl+0x40/0xa0
swapper/0:  print_report+0x1b8/0x71c
swapper/0:  kasan_report+0xec/0x14c
swapper/0:  __do_kernel_fault+0x60/0x29c
swapper/0:  do_bad_area+0x30/0xdc
swapper/0:  do_tag_check_fault+0x20/0x34
swapper/0:  do_mem_abort+0x58/0x104
swapper/0:  el1_abort+0x3c/0x5c
swapper/0:  el1h_64_sync_handler+0x80/0xcc
swapper/0:  el1h_64_sync+0x68/0x6c
swapper/0:  __memset+0x84/0x188
swapper/0:  btf_populate_kfunc_set+0x280/0x3d8
swapper/0:  __register_btf_kfunc_id_set+0x43c/0x468
swapper/0:  register_btf_kfunc_id_set+0x48/0x60
swapper/0:  register_nf_nat_bpf+0x1c/0x40
swapper/0:  nf_nat_init+0xc0/0x128
swapper/0:  do_one_initcall+0x184/0x464
swapper/0:  do_initcall_level+0xdc/0x1b0
swapper/0:  do_initcalls+0x70/0xc0
swapper/0:  do_basic_setup+0x1c/0x28
swapper/0:  kernel_init_freeable+0x144/0x1b8
swapper/0:  kernel_init+0x20/0x1a8
swapper/0:  ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
==================================================================</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53098 | drm/xe/ufence: Prefetch ufence addr to catch bogus address</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53098</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/xe/ufence: Prefetch ufence addr to catch bogus address

access_ok() only checks for addr overflow so also try to read the addr
to catch invalid addr sent from userspace.

(cherry picked from commit 9408c4508483ffc60811e910a93d6425b8e63928)</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53099 | bpf: Check validity of link-&amp;gt;type in bpf_link_show_fdinfo()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53099</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: Check validity of link-&gt;type in bpf_link_show_fdinfo()

If a newly-added link type doesn't invoke BPF_LINK_TYPE(), accessing
bpf_link_type_strs[link-&gt;type] may result in an out-of-bounds access.

To spot such missed invocations early in the future, checking the
validity of link-&gt;type in bpf_link_show_fdinfo() and emitting a warning
when such invocations are missed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53100 | nvme: tcp: avoid race between queue_lock lock and destroy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53100</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nvme: tcp: avoid race between queue_lock lock and destroy

Commit 76d54bf20cdc ("nvme-tcp: don't access released socket during
error recovery") added a mutex_lock() call for the queue-&gt;queue_lock
in nvme_tcp_get_address(). However, the mutex_lock() races with
mutex_destroy() in nvme_tcp_free_queue(), and causes the WARN below.

DEBUG_LOCKS_WARN_ON(lock-&gt;magic != lock)
WARNING: CPU: 3 PID: 34077 at kernel/locking/mutex.c:587 __mutex_lock+0xcf0/0x1220
Modules linked in: nvmet_tcp nvmet nvme_tcp nvme_fabrics iw_cm ib_cm ib_core pktcdvd nft_fib_inet nft_fib_ipv4 nft_fib_ipv6 nft_fib nft_reject_inet nf_reject_ipv4 nf_reject_ipv6 nft_reject nft_ct nft_chain_nat nf_nat nf_conntrack nf_defrag_ipv6 nf_defrag_ipv4 ip_set nf_tables qrtr sunrpc ppdev 9pnet_virtio 9pnet pcspkr netfs parport_pc parport e1000 i2c_piix4 i2c_smbus loop fuse nfnetlink zram bochs drm_vram_helper drm_ttm_helper ttm drm_kms_helper xfs drm sym53c8xx floppy nvme scsi_transport_spi nvme_core nvme_auth serio_raw ata_generic pata_acpi dm_multipath qemu_fw_cfg [last unloaded: ib_uverbs]
CPU: 3 UID: 0 PID: 34077 Comm: udisksd Not tainted 6.11.0-rc7 #319
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.16.3-2.fc40 04/01/2014
RIP: 0010:__mutex_lock+0xcf0/0x1220
Code: 08 84 d2 0f 85 c8 04 00 00 8b 15 ef b6 c8 01 85 d2 0f 85 78 f4 ff ff 48 c7 c6 20 93 ee af 48 c7 c7 60 91 ee af e8 f0 a7 6d fd &lt;0f&gt; 0b e9 5e f4 ff ff 48 b8 00 00 00 00 00 fc ff df 4c 89 f2 48 c1
RSP: 0018:ffff88811305f760 EFLAGS: 00010286
RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffff88812c652058 RCX: 0000000000000000
RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: 0000000000000004 RDI: 0000000000000001
RBP: ffff88811305f8b0 R08: 0000000000000001 R09: ffffed1075c36341
R10: ffff8883ae1b1a0b R11: 0000000000010498 R12: 0000000000000000
R13: 0000000000000000 R14: dffffc0000000000 R15: ffff88812c652058
FS:  00007f9713ae4980(0000) GS:ffff8883ae180000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 00007fcd78483c7c CR3: 0000000122c38000 CR4: 00000000000006f0
DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
Call Trace:
 
 ? __warn.cold+0x5b/0x1af
 ? __mutex_lock+0xcf0/0x1220
 ? report_bug+0x1ec/0x390
 ? handle_bug+0x3c/0x80
 ? exc_invalid_op+0x13/0x40
 ? asm_exc_invalid_op+0x16/0x20
 ? __mutex_lock+0xcf0/0x1220
 ? nvme_tcp_get_address+0xc2/0x1e0 [nvme_tcp]
 ? __pfx___mutex_lock+0x10/0x10
 ? __lock_acquire+0xd6a/0x59e0
 ? nvme_tcp_get_address+0xc2/0x1e0 [nvme_tcp]
 nvme_tcp_get_address+0xc2/0x1e0 [nvme_tcp]
 ? __pfx_nvme_tcp_get_address+0x10/0x10 [nvme_tcp]
 nvme_sysfs_show_address+0x81/0xc0 [nvme_core]
 dev_attr_show+0x42/0x80
 ? __asan_memset+0x1f/0x40
 sysfs_kf_seq_show+0x1f0/0x370
 seq_read_iter+0x2cb/0x1130
 ? rw_verify_area+0x3b1/0x590
 ? __mutex_lock+0x433/0x1220
 vfs_read+0x6a6/0xa20
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on+0x78/0x100
 ? __pfx_vfs_read+0x10/0x10
 ksys_read+0xf7/0x1d0
 ? __pfx_ksys_read+0x10/0x10
 ? __x64_sys_openat+0x105/0x1d0
 do_syscall_64+0x93/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on_prepare+0x16d/0x400
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on+0x78/0x100
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? __pfx_ksys_read+0x10/0x10
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on_prepare+0x16d/0x400
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on+0x78/0x100
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on_prepare+0x16d/0x400
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on+0x78/0x100
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on_prepare+0x16d/0x400
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on+0x78/0x100
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on_prepare+0x16d/0x400
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on+0x78/0x100
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x76/0x7e
RIP: 0033:0x7f9713f55cfa
Code: 55 48 89 e5 48 83 ec 20 48 89 55 e8 48 89 75 f0 89 7d f8 e8 e8 74 f8 ff 48 8b 55 e8 48 8b 75 f0 4
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53101 | fs: Fix uninitialized value issue in from_kuid and from_kgid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53101</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fs: Fix uninitialized value issue in from_kuid and from_kgid

ocfs2_setattr() uses attr-&gt;ia_mode, attr-&gt;ia_uid and attr-&gt;ia_gid in
a trace point even though ATTR_MODE, ATTR_UID and ATTR_GID aren't set.

Initialize all fields of newattrs to avoid uninitialized variables, by
checking if ATTR_MODE, ATTR_UID, ATTR_GID are initialized, otherwise 0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53102 | nvme: make keep-alive synchronous operation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53102</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nvme: make keep-alive synchronous operation

The nvme keep-alive operation, which executes at a periodic interval,
could potentially sneak in while shutting down a fabric controller.
This may lead to a race between the fabric controller admin queue
destroy code path (invoked while shutting down controller) and hw/hctx
queue dispatcher called from the nvme keep-alive async request queuing
operation. This race could lead to the kernel crash shown below:

Call Trace:
    autoremove_wake_function+0x0/0xbc (unreliable)
    __blk_mq_sched_dispatch_requests+0x114/0x24c
    blk_mq_sched_dispatch_requests+0x44/0x84
    blk_mq_run_hw_queue+0x140/0x220
    nvme_keep_alive_work+0xc8/0x19c [nvme_core]
    process_one_work+0x200/0x4e0
    worker_thread+0x340/0x504
    kthread+0x138/0x140
    start_kernel_thread+0x14/0x18

While shutting down fabric controller, if nvme keep-alive request sneaks
in then it would be flushed off. The nvme_keep_alive_end_io function is
then invoked to handle the end of the keep-alive operation which
decrements the admin-&gt;q_usage_counter and assuming this is the last/only
request in the admin queue then the admin-&gt;q_usage_counter becomes zero.
If that happens then blk-mq destroy queue operation (blk_mq_destroy_
queue()) which could be potentially running simultaneously on another
cpu (as this is the controller shutdown code path) would forward
progress and deletes the admin queue. So, now from this point onward
we are not supposed to access the admin queue resources. However the
issue here's that the nvme keep-alive thread running hw/hctx queue
dispatch operation hasn't yet finished its work and so it could still
potentially access the admin queue resource while the admin queue had
been already deleted and that causes the above crash.

This fix helps avoid the observed crash by implementing keep-alive as a
synchronous operation so that we decrement admin-&gt;q_usage_counter only
after keep-alive command finished its execution and returns the command
status back up to its caller (blk_execute_rq()). This would ensure that
fabric shutdown code path doesn't destroy the fabric admin queue until
keep-alive request finished execution and also keep-alive thread is not
running hw/hctx queue dispatch operation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53597 | masterstack_imgcap v0.0.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the endpoint /submit.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53597</link><description>masterstack_imgcap v0.0.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the endpoint /submit.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53554 | A Client-Side Template Injection (CSTI) vulnerability in the component /project/new/scrum of Taiga v 8.6.1 allows remote attackers to execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53554</link><description>A Client-Side Template Injection (CSTI) vulnerability in the component /project/new/scrum of Taiga v 8.6.1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code by injecting a malicious payload within the new project details.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50671 | Incorrect access control in Adapt Learning Adapt Authoring Tool &lt;= 0.11.3 allows attackers with Authenticated User roles to obtain email add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50671</link><description>Incorrect access control in Adapt Learning Adapt Authoring Tool &lt;= 0.11.3 allows attackers with Authenticated User roles to obtain email addresses via the "Get users" feature. The vulnerability occurs due to a flaw in permission verification logic, where the wildcard character in permitted URLs grants unintended access to endpoints restricted to users with Super Admin roles. This makes it possible for attackers to disclose the email addresses of all users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 20:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50672 | A NoSQL injection vulnerability in Adapt Learning Adapt Authoring Tool &lt;= 0.11.3 allows unauthenticated attackers to reset user and administ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50672</link><description>A NoSQL injection vulnerability in Adapt Learning Adapt Authoring Tool &lt;= 0.11.3 allows unauthenticated attackers to reset user and administrator account passwords via the "Reset password" feature. The vulnerability occurs due to insufficient validation of user input, which is used as a query in Mongoose's find() function. This makes it possible for attackers to perform a full takeover of the administrator account. Attackers can then use the newly gained administrative privileges to upload a custom plugin to perform remote code execution (RCE) on the server hosting the web application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 20:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53556 | An Open Redirect vulnerability in Taiga v6.8.1 allows attackers to redirect users to arbitrary websites via appending a crafted link to /log...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53556</link><description>An Open Redirect vulnerability in Taiga v6.8.1 allows attackers to redirect users to arbitrary websites via appending a crafted link to /login?next= in the login page URL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 20:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53258 | download_all_submissions allows student to download another student&amp;#x27;s submissions in Autolab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53258</link><description>Autolab is a course management service that enables auto-graded programming assignments. From Autolab versions v.3.0.0 onward students can download all assignments from another student, as long as they are logged in, using the download_all_submissions feature. This can allow for leakage of submissions to unauthorized users, such as downloading submissions from other students in the class, or even instructor test submissions, given they know their user IDs. This issue has been patched in commit `1aa4c769` which is not yet in a release version, but is expected to be included in version 3.0.3. Users are advised to either manually patch or to wait for version 3.0.3. As a workaround administrators can disable the feature.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53268 | Lack of validation on openExternal allows 1 click remote code execution in joplin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53268</link><description>Joplin is an open source, privacy-focused note taking app with sync capabilities for Windows, macOS, Linux, Android and iOS. In affected versions attackers are able to abuse the fact that openExternal is used without any filtering of URI schemes to obtain remote code execution in Windows environments. This issue has been addressed in version 3.0.3 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53261 | Cross-Site Scripting attack (XSS) on dev mode 404 page in SvelteKit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53261</link><description>SvelteKit is a framework for rapidly developing robust, performant web applications using Svelte. "Unsanitized input from *the request URL* flows into `end`, where it is used to render an HTML page returned to the user. This may result in a Cross-Site Scripting attack (XSS)." The files `packages/kit/src/exports/vite/dev/index.js` and `packages/kit/src/exports/vite/utils.js` both contain user controllable data which under specific conditions may flow to dev mode pages. There is little to no expected impact. The Vite development is not exposed to the network by default and even if someone were able to trick a developer into executing an XSS against themselves, a development database should not have any sensitive data. None the less this issue has been addressed in version 2.8.3 and all users are advised to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:22:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53262 | Unescaped error message included on error page in SvelteKit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53262</link><description>SvelteKit is a framework for rapidly developing robust, performant web applications using Svelte. The static error.html template for errors contains placeholders that are replaced without escaping the content first. error.html is the page that is rendered when everything else fails. It can contain the following placeholders: %sveltekit.status% — the HTTP status, and %sveltekit.error.message% — the error message.  This leads to possible injection if an app explicitly creates an error with a message that contains user controlled content. Only applications where user provided input is used in the `Error` message will be vulnerable, so the vast majority of applications will not be vulnerable This issue has been addressed in version 2.8.3 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:22:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53255 | Reflected Cross-site Scripting in /admin?page=media via file Parameter in BoidCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53255</link><description>BoidCMS is a free and open-source flat file CMS for building simple websites and blogs, developed using PHP and uses JSON as a database. In affected versions a reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the /admin?page=media endpoint in the file parameter, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary JavaScript code. This code could be used to steal the user's session cookie, perform phishing attacks, or deface the website. This issue has been addressed in version 2.1.2 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52811 | Acks not validated before logged to qlog leads to buffer overflow in ngtcp2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52811</link><description>The ngtcp2 project is an effort to implement IETF QUIC protocol in C. In affected versions acks are not validated before being written to the qlog leading to a buffer overflow. In `ngtcp2_conn::conn_recv_pkt` for an ACK, there was new logic that got added to skip `conn_recv_ack` if an ack has already been processed in the payload. However, this causes us to also skip `ngtcp2_pkt_validate_ack`. The ack which was skipped still got written to qlog. The bug occurs in `ngtcp2_qlog::write_ack_frame`. It is now possible to reach this code with an invalid ack, suppose `largest_ack=0` and `first_ack_range=15`. Subtracting `largest_ack - first_ack_range` will lead to an integer underflow which is 20 chars long. However, the ngtcp2 qlog code assumes the number written is a signed integer and only accounts for 19 characters of overhead (see `NGTCP2_QLOG_ACK_FRAME_RANGE_OVERHEAD`). Therefore, we overwrite the buffer causing a heap overflow. This is high priority and could potentially impact many users if they enable qlog. qlog is disabled by default. Due to its overhead, it is most likely used for debugging purpose, but the actual use is unknown. ngtcp2 v1.9.1 fixes the bug and users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should not turn on qlog.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32468 | Improper neutralization of input during web page generation (&amp;quot;Cross-site Scripting&amp;quot;) in deno_doc HTML generator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32468</link><description>Deno is a runtime for JavaScript and TypeScript written in rust. Several cross-site scripting vulnerabilities existed in the `deno_doc` crate which lead to Self-XSS with deno doc --html. 1.) XSS in generated `search_index.js`, `deno_doc` outputs a JavaScript file for searching. However, the generated file used `innerHTML` on unsanitzed HTML input. 2.) XSS via property, method and enum names, `deno_doc` did not sanitize property names, method names and enum names. The first XSS most likely didn't have an impact since `deno doc --html` is expected to be used locally with own packages.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 18:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51723 | Vulnerability in Management Console Impacts BlackBerry AtHoc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51723</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Management Console of BlackBerry AtHoc version 7.15 could allow an attacker to potentially execute actions in the context of the victim's session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 18:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52529 | Layer 7 policy enforcement may not occur in policies with wildcarded port ranges in Cilium</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52529</link><description>Cilium is a networking, observability, and security solution with an eBPF-based dataplane. For users with the following configuration: 1. An allow policy that selects a Layer 3 destination and a port range `AND` 2. A Layer 7 allow policy that selects a specific port within the first policy's range the Layer 7 enforcement would not occur for the traffic selected by the Layer 7 policy. This issue only affects users who use Cilium's port range functionality, which was introduced in Cilium v1.16. This issue is patched in PR #35150. This issue affects Cilium v1.16 between v1.16.0 and v1.16.3 inclusive. This issue is patched in Cilium v1.16.4. Users are advised to upgrade. Users with network policies that match the pattern described above can work around the issue by rewriting any policies that use port ranges to individually specify the ports permitted for traffic.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 18:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53599 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /scroll.php endpoint of LafeLabs Chaos v0.0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web sc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53599</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /scroll.php endpoint of LafeLabs Chaos v0.0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8272 | macOS Universal Audio (UAConnect) &amp;lt;= 2.7.0  - Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8272</link><description>The com.uaudio.bsd.helper service, responsible for handling privileged operations, fails to implement critical client validation during XPC inter-process communication (IPC). Specifically, the service does not verify the code requirements, entitlements, or security flags of any client attempting to establish a connection. This lack of proper validation allows unauthorized clients to exploit the service's methods and escalate privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 17:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7915 | macOS Sensei Mac Cleaner Local Privilege Escalation via PID Reuse - Race Condition Attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7915</link><description>The application Sensei Mac Cleaner contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability, allowing an attacker to perform multiple operations as the root user. These operations include arbitrary file deletion and writing, loading and unloading daemons, manipulating file permissions, and loading extensions, among other actions.


The vulnerable module org.cindori.SenseiHelper can be contacted via XPC. While the module performs client validation, it relies on the client's PID obtained through the public processIdentifier property of the NSXPCConnection class. This approach makes the module susceptible to a PID Reuse Attack, enabling an attacker to impersonate a legitimate client and send crafted XPC messages to invoke arbitrary methods exposed by the HelperProtocol interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 17:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52787 | An issue in the upload_documents method of libre-chat v0.0.6 allows attackers to execute a path traversal via supplying a crafted filename i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52787</link><description>An issue in the upload_documents method of libre-chat v0.0.6 allows attackers to execute a path traversal via supplying a crafted filename in an uploaded file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 17:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45756 | An issue was discovered in Centreon centreon-open-tickets 24.10.x before 24.10.0, 24.04.x before 24.04.2, 23.10.x before 23.10.1, 23.04.x be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45756</link><description>An issue was discovered in Centreon centreon-open-tickets 24.10.x before 24.10.0, 24.04.x before 24.04.2, 23.10.x before 23.10.1, 23.04.x before 23.04.3, and 22.10.x before 22.10.2. SQL injection can occur in the form to create a ticket. Exploitation is only accessible to authenticated users with high-privileged access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 17:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45755 | An issue was discovered in Centreon centreon-dsm-server 24.10.x before 24.10.0, 24.04.x before 24.04.3, 23.10.x before 23.10.1, 23.04.x befo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45755</link><description>An issue was discovered in Centreon centreon-dsm-server 24.10.x before 24.10.0, 24.04.x before 24.04.3, 23.10.x before 23.10.1, 23.04.x before 23.04.3, and 22.10.x before 22.10.2. SQL injection can occur in the form to configure Centreon DSM slots. Exploitation is only accessible to authenticated users with high-privileged access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 17:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26280 | IBM Jazz Foundation improper access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26280</link><description>IBM Jazz Foundation 7.0.2 and 7.0.3

 could allow a user to change their dashboard using a specially crafted HTTP request due to improper access control.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 16:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45181 | IBM Jazz Foundation cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45181</link><description>IBM Jazz Foundation 7.0.2 and below are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 15:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11670 | Incorrect authorization in the permission validation component of Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.2.21 and earlier on Windows allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11670</link><description>Incorrect authorization in the permission validation component of Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.2.21 and earlier on Windows allows a malicious authenticated user to bypass the "View Password" permission via specific actions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 14:52:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11671 | Improper authentication in SQL data source MFA validation in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.3.17 and earlier on Windows allows an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11671</link><description>Improper authentication in SQL data source MFA validation in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.3.17 and earlier on Windows allows an authenticated user to bypass the MFA validation via data source switching.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 14:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11672 | Incorrect authorization in the add permission component in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.2.21 and earlier on Windows allows an aut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11672</link><description>Incorrect authorization in the add permission component in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.2.21 and earlier on Windows allows an authenticated malicious user to bypass the "Add" permission via the import in vault feature.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 14:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27134 | Excessive directory permissions in MLflow leads to local privilege escalation when using spark_udf</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27134</link><description>Excessive directory permissions in MLflow leads to local privilege escalation when using spark_udf. This behavior can be exploited by a local attacker to gain elevated permissions by using a ToCToU attack. The issue is only relevant when the spark_udf() MLflow API is called.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 13:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11403 | Out of Bounds Memory Read/Write in libjxl</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11403</link><description>There exists an out of bounds read/write in LibJXL versions prior to commit 9cc451b91b74ba470fd72bd48c121e9f33d24c99. The JPEG decoder used by the JPEG XL encoder when doing JPEG recompression (i.e. if using JxlEncoderAddJPEGFrame on untrusted input) does not properly check bounds in the presence of incomplete codes. This could lead to an out-of-bounds write. In jpegli which is released as part of the same project, the same vulnerability is present. However, the relevant buffer is part of a bigger structure, and the code makes no assumptions on the values that could be overwritten. The issue could however cause jpegli to read uninitialised memory, or addresses of functions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11498 | Resource exhaustion via Stack overflow in libjxl</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11498</link><description>There exists a stack buffer overflow in libjxl. A specifically-crafted file can cause the JPEG XL decoder to use large amounts of stack space (up to 256mb is possible, maybe 512mb), potentially exhausting the stack. An attacker can craft a file that will cause excessive memory usage. We recommend upgrading past commit 65fbec56bc578b6b6ee02a527be70787bbd053b0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-12491 | Framework Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12491</link><description>Improper control of framework service permissions with possibility of some sensitive device information leakage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 10:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-12492 | Wifi information acquisition vulnerability in Framework Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12492</link><description>Improper handling of WiFi information by framework services can allow certain malicious applications to obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 10:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-33862 | Improper access control mechanism in IPP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33862</link><description>IPP software prior to v1.71 is vulnerable to default credential vulnerability. This could
lead attackers to identify and access vulnerable systems.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 09:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11664 | eNMS TGZ File controller.py multiselect_filtering path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11664</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in eNMS up to 4.2. Affected by this issue is the function multiselect_filtering of the file eNMS/controller.py of the component TGZ File Handler. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is identified as 22b0b443acca740fc83b5544165c1f53eff3f529. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 09:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-33861 | Insufficient verification of authenticity in IPP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33861</link><description>IPP software versions prior to v1.71 do not sufficiently verify the authenticity of data, in a
way that causes it to accept invalid data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 09:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-23282 | Stored Cross-site Scripting reported in Intelligent Power Manager v1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23282</link><description>Eaton Intelligent Power Manager (IPM) prior to 1.70 is vulnerable to stored Cross site scripting. The
vulnerability exists due to insufficient validation of input from certain resources by the IPM software.
The attacker would need access to the local Subnet and an administrator interaction to compromise
the system</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 08:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11663 | Codezips E-Commerce Site search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11663</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Codezips E-Commerce Site 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file search.php. The manipulation of the argument keywords leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 08:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11662 | welliamcao OpsManage API Endpoint deploy_api.py deploy_host_vars deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11662</link><description>A vulnerability was found in welliamcao OpsManage 3.0.1/3.0.2/3.0.3/3.0.4/3.0.5. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function deploy_host_vars of the file /apps/api/views/deploy_api.py of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 08:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10270 | Org.keycloak:keycloak-services: keycloak denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10270</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the Keycloak-services package. If untrusted data is passed to the SearchQueryUtils method, it could lead to a denial of service (DoS) scenario by exhausting system resources due to a Regex complexity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10451 | Org.keycloak:keycloak-quarkus-server: sensitive data exposure in keycloak build process</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10451</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. This issue occurs because sensitive runtime values, such as passwords, may be captured during the Keycloak build process and embedded as default values in bytecode, leading to unintended information disclosure. In Keycloak 26, sensitive data specified directly in environment variables during the build process is also stored as a default values, making it accessible during runtime. Indirect usage of environment variables for SPI options and Quarkus properties is also vulnerable due to unconditional expansion by PropertyMapper logic, capturing sensitive data as default values in all Keycloak versions up to 26.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10492 | Keycloak-quarkus-server: keycloak path trasversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10492</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Keycloak. A user with high privileges could read sensitive information from a Vault file that is not within the expected context. This attacker must have previous high access to the Keycloak server in order to perform resource creation, for example, an LDAP provider configuration and set up a Vault read file, which will only inform whether that file exists or not.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11661 | Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System Profile Image profile.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11661</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file profile.php of the component Profile Image Handler. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The researcher submit confuses the vulnerability class of this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9666 | Org.keycloak/keycloak-quarkus-server: keycloak proxy header handling denial-of-service (dos) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9666</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the Keycloak Server. The Keycloak Server is vulnerable to a denial of service (DoS) attack due to improper handling of proxy headers. When Keycloak is configured to accept incoming proxy headers, it may accept non-IP values, such as obfuscated identifiers, without proper validation. This issue can lead to costly DNS resolution operations, which an attacker could exploit to tie up IO threads and potentially cause a denial of service.
The attacker must have access to send requests to a Keycloak instance that is configured to accept proxy headers, specifically when reverse proxies do not overwrite incoming headers, and Keycloak is configured to trust these headers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11660 | code-projects Farmacia usuario.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11660</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Farmacia 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file usuario.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11659 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_iperf command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11659</link><description>A vulnerability was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/network/diag_iperf. The manipulation of the argument iperf leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6538 | Openshift-console: openshift console:  server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6538</link><description>A flaw was found in OpenShift Console. A Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) attack can happen if an attacker supplies all or part of a URL to the server to query. The server is considered to be in a privileged network position and can often reach exposed services that aren't readily available to clients due to network filtering. Leveraging such an attack vector, the attacker can have an impact on other services and potentially disclose information or have other nefarious effects on the system.
The /api/dev-console/proxy/internet endpoint on the OpenShit Console allows authenticated users to have the console's pod perform arbitrary and fully controlled HTTP(s) requests. The full response to these requests is returned by the endpoint.
While the name of this endpoint suggests the requests are only bound to the internet, no such checks are in place. An authenticated user can therefore ask the console to perform arbitrary HTTP requests from outside the cluster to a service inside the cluster.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10709 | YaDisk Files &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Contributor+ Stored XSS via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10709</link><description>The YaDisk Files WordPress plugin through 1.2.5 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10710 | YaDisk Files &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10710</link><description>The YaDisk Files WordPress plugin through 1.2.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11658 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT ajax_getChannelList command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11658</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/network/ajax_getChannelList. The manipulation of the argument countryCode leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6393 | NextGEN Gallery &amp;lt; 3.59.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6393</link><description>The Photo Gallery, Sliders, Proofing and   WordPress plugin before 3.59.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its Images settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7056 | WPForms &amp;lt; 1.9.1.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7056</link><description>The WPForms  WordPress plugin before 1.9.1.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11657 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_nslookup command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11657</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/network/diag_nslookup. The manipulation of the argument diag_nslookup leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 05:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11656 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_ping6 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11656</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/network/diag_ping6. The manipulation of the argument diag_ping6 leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 05:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-11311 | Information Exposure in Kernel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11311</link><description>This record is rejected as duplicate. All references should point to CVE-2021-1904.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 04:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11655 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_pinginterface command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11655</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/network/diag_pinginterface. The manipulation of the argument diag_ping leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 04:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11654 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_traceroute6 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11654</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/network/diag_traceroute6. The manipulation of the argument diag_traceroute6 leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 04:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11483 | Automation-gateway: improper scope handling in oauth2 tokens for aap 2.5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11483</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the Ansible Automation Platform (AAP). This flaw allows attackers to escalate privileges by improperly leveraging read-scoped OAuth2 tokens to gain write access. This issue affects API endpoints that rely on ansible_base.oauth2_provider for OAuth2 authentication. While the impact is limited to actions within the user’s assigned permissions, it undermines scoped access controls, potentially allowing unintended modifications in the application and consuming services.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 04:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11653 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_traceroute command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11653</link><description>A vulnerability was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/network/diag_traceroute. The manipulation of the argument diag_traceroute leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 03:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11652 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT sn_https command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11652</link><description>A vulnerability was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/sn_package/sn_https. The manipulation of the argument https_enable leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 03:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53930 | WikiDocs before 1.0.65 allows stored XSS by authenticated users via data that comes after $$\\, which is mishandled by a KaTeX parser.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53930</link><description>WikiDocs before 1.0.65 allows stored XSS by authenticated users via data that comes after $$\\, which is mishandled by a KaTeX parser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 03:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11651 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT wifi_schedule command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11651</link><description>A vulnerability was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/network/wifi_schedule. The manipulation of the argument wifi_schedule_day_em_5 leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 03:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11650 | Tenda i9 GetIPTV websReadEvent null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11650</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda i9 1.0.0.8(3828) and classified as critical. This issue affects the function websReadEvent of the file /goform/GetIPTV. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 02:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11649 | 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System search-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11649</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/search-appointment.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 02:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11648 | 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System add-customer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11648</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/add-customer.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 01:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11647 | 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System view-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11647</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/view-appointment.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 01:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>