<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 05:44:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-8776 | INTUMIT SmartRobot - Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8776</link><description>SmartRobot from INTUMIT does not properly validate a specific page parameter, allowing unautheticated remote attackers to inject JavaScript code to the parameter for Reflected Cross-site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 05:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46958 | In Nextcloud Desktop Client 3.13.1 through 3.13.3 on Linux, synchronized files (between the server and client) may become world writable or ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46958</link><description>In Nextcloud Desktop Client 3.13.1 through 3.13.3 on Linux, synchronized files (between the server and client) may become world writable or world readable. This is fixed in 3.13.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 02:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8880 | playSMS Template index.php code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8880</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in playSMS 1.4.4/1.4.5/1.4.6/1.4.7. Affected is an unknown function of the file /playsms/index.php?app=main&amp;amp;inc=core_auth&amp;amp;route=forgot&amp;amp;op=forgot of the component Template Handler. The manipulation of the argument username/email/captcha leads to code injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The project maintainer was informed early about the issue. Investigation shows that playSMS up to 1.4.3 contained a fix but later versions re-introduced the flaw. As long as the latest version of the playsms/tpl package is used, the software is not affected. Version &gt;=1.4.4 shall fix this issue for sure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 01:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46942 | In OpenDaylight Model-Driven Service Abstraction Layer (MD-SAL) through 13.0.1, a controller with a follower role can configure flow entries...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46942</link><description>In OpenDaylight Model-Driven Service Abstraction Layer (MD-SAL) through 13.0.1, a controller with a follower role can configure flow entries in an OpenDaylight clustering deployment.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 23:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46943 | An issue was discovered in OpenDaylight Authentication, Authorization and Accounting (AAA) through 0.19.3. A rogue controller can join a clu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46943</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenDaylight Authentication, Authorization and Accounting (AAA) through 0.19.3. A rogue controller can join a cluster to impersonate an offline peer, even if this rogue controller does not possess the complete cluster configuration information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 23:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8876 | xiaohe4966 TpMeCMS lang path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8876</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in xiaohe4966 TpMeCMS up to 1.3.3.1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index/ajax/lang. The manipulation of the argument lang leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.3.3.2 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 22:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46938 | An issue was discovered in Sitecore Experience Platform (XP), Experience Manager (XM), and Experience Commerce (XC) 8.0 Initial Release thro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46938</link><description>An issue was discovered in Sitecore Experience Platform (XP), Experience Manager (XM), and Experience Commerce (XC) 8.0 Initial Release through 10.4 Initial Release. An unauthenticated attacker can read arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 21:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8875 | vedees wcms finder.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8875</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in vedees wcms up to 0.3.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /wex/finder.php. The manipulation of the argument p leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 21:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46918 | app/Controller/UserLoginProfilesController.php in MISP before 2.4.198 does not prevent an org admin from viewing sensitive login fields of a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46918</link><description>app/Controller/UserLoginProfilesController.php in MISP before 2.4.198 does not prevent an org admin from viewing sensitive login fields of another org admin in the same org.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8869 | TOTOLINK A720R exportOvpn os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8869</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A720R 4.1.5. Affected is the function exportOvpn. The manipulation leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44053 | WordPress Opor Ayam theme &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44053</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mohammad Arif Opor Ayam allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Opor Ayam: from n/a through 1.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44054 | WordPress Fluida theme &amp;lt;= 1.8.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44054</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CryoutCreations Fluida allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Fluida: from n/a through 1.8.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44056 | WordPress Mantra theme &amp;lt;= 3.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44056</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CryoutCreations Mantra allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mantra: from n/a through 3.3.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44057 | WordPress Nirvana theme &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44057</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CryoutCreations Nirvana allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Nirvana: from n/a through 1.6.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44058 | WordPress Parabola theme &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44058</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CryoutCreations Parabola allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Parabola: from n/a through 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44059 | WordPress Custom Query Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44059</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MediaRon LLC Custom Query Blocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Custom Query Blocks: from n/a through 5.3.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44060 | WordPress filmix theme &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44060</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jennifer Hall Filmix allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Filmix: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44062 | WordPress Custom Field Template plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44062</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Hiroaki Miyashita Custom Field Template allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Custom Field Template: from n/a through 2.6.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44063 | WordPress Happyforms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.26.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44063</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Happyforms allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Happyforms: from n/a through 1.26.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45455 | WordPress WP Meta SEO plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.13 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45455</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in JoomUnited WP Meta SEO allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Meta SEO: from n/a through 4.5.13.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45456 | WordPress WP Meta SEO plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.13 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45456</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in JoomUnited WP Meta SEO allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Meta SEO: from n/a through 4.5.13.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 07:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45457 | WordPress Spiffy Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.13 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45457</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Spiffy Plugins Spiffy Calendar allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Spiffy Calendar: from n/a through 4.9.13.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 07:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45458 | WordPress Spiffy Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.13 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45458</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Spiffy Plugins Spiffy Calendar allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Spiffy Calendar: from n/a through 4.9.13.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 07:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45459 | WordPress Product Slider for WooCommerce by PickPlugins plugin &amp;lt;= 1.13.50 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45459</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PickPlugins Product Slider for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Product Slider for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.13.50.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 07:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45460 | WordPress Flipping Cards plugin &amp;lt;= 1.30 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45460</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Manu225 Flipping Cards allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Flipping Cards: from n/a through 1.30.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 07:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8868 | code-projects Crud Operation System savedata.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8868</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Crud Operation System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file savedata.php. The manipulation of the argument sname leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 03:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8867 | Perfex CRM Parameter Clients.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8867</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Perfex CRM 3.1.6. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file application/controllers/Clients.php of the component Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 02:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8866 | AutoCMS robot.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8866</link><description>A vulnerability was found in AutoCMS 5.4. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/robot.php. The manipulation of the argument sidebar leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 01:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8865 | composiohq composio api.py path path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8865</link><description>A vulnerability was found in composiohq composio up to 0.5.8 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function path of the file composio\server\api.py. The manipulation of the argument file leads to path traversal. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 01:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8864 | composiohq composio calculator.py Calculator code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8864</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in composiohq composio up to 0.5.6 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Calculator of the file python/composio/tools/local/mathematical/actions/calculator.py. The manipulation leads to code injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 01:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8863 | aimhubio aim Text Explorer textbox.tsx dangerouslySetInnerHTML cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8863</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in aimhubio aim up to 3.24. Affected is the function dangerouslySetInnerHTML of the file textbox.tsx of the component Text Explorer. The manipulation of the argument query leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 23:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8862 | h2oai h2o-3 JDBC Connection 1 getConnectionSafe deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8862</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in h2oai h2o-3 3.46.0.4. This issue affects the function getConnectionSafe of the file /dtale/chart-data/1 of the component JDBC Connection Handler. The manipulation of the argument query leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 19:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6482 | Login with phone number &amp;lt;= 1.7.49 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Authorization Bypass to Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6482</link><description>The Login with phone number plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.49. This is due to a lack of validation and missing capability check on user-supplied data in the 'lwp_update_password_action' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update their role to any other role, including Administrator. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 1.7.40. The login with phone number pro plugin was required to exploit the vulnerability in versions 1.7.40 - 1.7.49.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 12:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3410 | Bricks &amp;lt;= 1.10.1 - Authenticated (Bricks Page Builder Access+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3410</link><description>The Bricks theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘customTag' attribute in versions up to, and including, 1.10.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with access to the Bricks Builder (admin-only by default), to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This becomes more of an issue when Bricks Builder access is granted to lower-privileged users.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 08:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8797 | WP Booking System – Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 2.0.19.8 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8797</link><description>The WP Booking System – Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.19.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 05:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8039 | Improper permission configurationDomain configuration vulnerability of the mobile application (com.afmobi.boomplayer) can lead to account ta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8039</link><description>Improper permission configurationDomain configuration vulnerability of the mobile application (com.afmobi.boomplayer) can lead to account takeover risks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 03:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8669 | Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8669</link><description>The Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'options' parameter passed to the backuply_wp_clone_sql() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 03:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8246 | Post Form – Registration Form – Profile Form for User Profiles – Frontend Content Forms for User Submissions (UGC) &amp;lt;= 2.8.11 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8246</link><description>The Post Form – Registration Form – Profile Form for User Profiles – Frontend Content Forms for User Submissions (UGC) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.11. This is due to plugin not properly restricting what users have access to set the default role on registration forms. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to create a registration form with a custom role that allows them to register as administrators.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 03:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8479 | Simple Spoiler 1.2 - 1.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8479</link><description>The The Simple Spoiler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in versions 1.2 to 1.3. This is due to the plugin adding the filter add_filter('comment_text', 'do_shortcode'); which will run all shortcodes in comments. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 03:23:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8724 | Waitlist Woocommerce ( Back in stock notifier ) &amp;lt;= 2.7.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8724</link><description>The Waitlist Woocommerce ( Back in stock notifier ) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 03:23:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-3459 | WooCommerce Multiple Free Gift &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Insufficient Server-Side Validation to Arbitrary Gift Adding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3459</link><description>The WooCommerce Multiple Free Gift plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to gift manipulation in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3. This is due to plugin not enforcing server-side checks on the products that can be added as a gift. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add non-gift items to their cart as a gift.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 02:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8271 | FOX – Currency Switcher Professional for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.4.2.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8271</link><description>The The FOX – Currency Switcher Professional for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2.1. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode in the 'woocs_get_custom_price_html' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 02:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8775 | Ansible: exposure of sensitive information in ansible vault files due to improper logging</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8775</link><description>A flaw was found in Ansible, where sensitive information stored in Ansible Vault files can be exposed in plaintext during the execution of a playbook. This occurs when using tasks such as include_vars to load vaulted variables without setting the no_log: true parameter, resulting in sensitive data being printed in the playbook output or logs. This can lead to the unintentional disclosure of secrets like passwords or API keys, compromising security and potentially allowing unauthorized access or actions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 02:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>