<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 23:40:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-10432 | Project Worlds Simple Web-Based Chat Application index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10432</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Project Worlds Simple Web-Based Chat Application 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 23:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50623 | In Cleo Harmony before 5.8.0.20, VLTrader before 5.8.0.20, and LexiCom before 5.8.0.20, there is a JavaScript Injection vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50623</link><description>In Cleo Harmony before 5.8.0.20, VLTrader before 5.8.0.20, and LexiCom before 5.8.0.20, there is a JavaScript Injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 23:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10430 | Codezips Pet Shop Management System animalsupdate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10430</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Codezips Pet Shop Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /animalsupdate.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 23:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10431 | Codezips Pet Shop Management System deletebird.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10431</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Codezips Pet Shop Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /deletebird.php. The manipulation of the argument t1 leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 23:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50616 | Ironman PowerShell Universal 5.x before 5.0.12 allows an authenticated attacker to elevate their privileges and view job information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50616</link><description>Ironman PowerShell Universal 5.x before 5.0.12 allows an authenticated attacker to elevate their privileges and view job information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 22:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50612 | libsndfile through 1.2.2 has an ogg_vorbis.c vorbis_analysis_wrote out-of-bounds read.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50612</link><description>libsndfile through 1.2.2 has an ogg_vorbis.c vorbis_analysis_wrote out-of-bounds read.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 22:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50613 | libsndfile through 1.2.2 has a reachable assertion, that may lead to application exit, in mpeg_l3_encode.c mpeg_l3_encoder_close.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50613</link><description>libsndfile through 1.2.2 has a reachable assertion, that may lead to application exit, in mpeg_l3_encode.c mpeg_l3_encoder_close.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 22:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50614 | TinyXML2 through 10.0.0 has a reachable assertion for UINT_MAX/16, that may lead to application exit, in tinyxml2.cpp XMLUtil::GetCharacterR...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50614</link><description>TinyXML2 through 10.0.0 has a reachable assertion for UINT_MAX/16, that may lead to application exit, in tinyxml2.cpp XMLUtil::GetCharacterRef.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 22:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50615 | TinyXML2 through 10.0.0 has a reachable assertion for UINT_MAX/digit, that may lead to application exit, in tinyxml2.cpp XMLUtil::GetCharact...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50615</link><description>TinyXML2 through 10.0.0 has a reachable assertion for UINT_MAX/digit, that may lead to application exit, in tinyxml2.cpp XMLUtil::GetCharacterRef.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 22:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50611 | CycloneDX cdxgen through 10.10.7, when run against an untrusted codebase, may execute code contained within build-related files such as buil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50611</link><description>CycloneDX cdxgen through 10.10.7, when run against an untrusted codebase, may execute code contained within build-related files such as build.gradle.kts, a similar issue to CVE-2022-24441. cdxgen is used by, for example, OWASP dep-scan. NOTE: this has been characterized as a design limitation, rather than an implementation mistake.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 21:46:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50610 | GSL (GNU Scientific Library) through 2.8 has an integer signedness error in gsl_siman_solve_many in siman/siman.c. When params.n_tries is ne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50610</link><description>GSL (GNU Scientific Library) through 2.8 has an integer signedness error in gsl_siman_solve_many in siman/siman.c. When params.n_tries is negative, incorrect memory allocation occurs.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 21:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10429 | WAVLINK WN530H4/WN530HG4/WN572HG3 internet.cgi set_ipv6 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10429</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in WAVLINK WN530H4, WN530HG4 and WN572HG3 up to 20221028. Affected is the function set_ipv6 of the file internet.cgi. The manipulation of the argument IPv6OpMode/IPv6IPAddr/IPv6WANIPAddr/IPv6GWAddr leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 21:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10428 | WAVLINK WN530H4/WN530HG4/WN572HG3 firewall.cgi set_ipv6 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10428</link><description>A vulnerability was found in WAVLINK WN530H4, WN530HG4 and WN572HG3 up to 20221028. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function set_ipv6 of the file firewall.cgi. The manipulation of the argument dhcpGateway leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 20:44:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10427 | Codezips Pet Shop Management System deleteanimal.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10427</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Pet Shop Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /deleteanimal.php. The manipulation of the argument t1 leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions the parameter "refno" to be affected. But further inspection indicates that the name of the affected parameter is "t1".</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 20:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10426 | Codezips Pet Shop Management System animalsadd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10426</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Pet Shop Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /animalsadd.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions the parameter "refno" to be affected. But further inspection indicates that the name of the affected parameter is "id".</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 19:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10425 | Project Worlds Student Project Allocation System Project Selection Page move_up_project.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10425</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Project Worlds Student Project Allocation System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /student/project_selection/move_up_project.php of the component Project Selection Page. The manipulation of the argument up leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 19:10:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10424 | Project Worlds Student Project Allocation System Project Selection Page remove_project.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10424</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Project Worlds Student Project Allocation System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /student/project_selection/remove_project.php of the component Project Selection Page. The manipulation of the argument no leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 18:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10423 | Project Worlds Student Project Allocation System Project Selection Page project_selection.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10423</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Project Worlds Student Project Allocation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /student/project_selection/project_selection.php of the component Project Selection Page. The manipulation of the argument project_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 18:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10422 | SourceCodester Attendance and Payroll System overtime_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10422</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Attendance and Payroll System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/overtime_add.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 17:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10421 | SourceCodester Attendance and Payroll System overtime_row.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10421</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Attendance and Payroll System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/overtime_row.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 17:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10420 | SourceCodester Attendance and Payroll System update.php upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10420</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Attendance and Payroll System 1.0. This affects the function upload of the file /marimar/guest/update.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 15:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10419 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System bloodrequest.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10419</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /bloodrequest.php. The manipulation of the argument msg leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 14:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10418 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System infoAdd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10418</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /file/infoAdd.php. The manipulation of the argument bg leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 13:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10417 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10417</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /file/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument bid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 13:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10416 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System cancel.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10416</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /file/cancel.php. The manipulation of the argument reqid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 13:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10415 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System accept.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10415</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /file/accept.php. The manipulation of the argument reqid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 11:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10414 | PHPGurukul Vehicle Record System edit-brand.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10414</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in PHPGurukul Vehicle Record System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit-brand.php. The manipulation of the argument Brand Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions the parameter "phone_number" to be affected. But this might be a mistake because the textbox field label is "Brand Name".</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 10:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10413 | SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System update.php upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10413</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function upload of the file /guest/update.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 09:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10412 | Poco-z Guns-Medical File Upload upload cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10412</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Poco-z Guns-Medical 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function upload of the file /mgr/upload of the component File Upload. The manipulation of the argument picture leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 08:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10411 | SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System controller.php doCheckout sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10411</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function doCancelRoom/doCancel/doConfirm/doCancel/doCheckin/doCheckout of the file /marimar/admin/mod_room/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 05:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50602 | An issue was discovered in libexpat before 2.6.4. There is a crash within the XML_ResumeParser function because XML_StopParser can stop/susp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50602</link><description>An issue was discovered in libexpat before 2.6.4. There is a crash within the XML_ResumeParser function because XML_StopParser can stop/suspend an unstarted parser.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 04:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10410 | SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System controller.php upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10410</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function upload of the file /admin/mod_room/controller.php?action=add. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 03:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10409 | code-projects Blood Bank Management accept.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10409</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /file/accept.php. The manipulation of the argument reqid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 02:55:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10408 | code-projects Blood Bank Management abs.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10408</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Blood Bank Management up to 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /abs.php. The manipulation of the argument search leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 02:55:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10407 | SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software edit_customer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10407</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit_customer.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 23:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10406 | SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software edit_fuel.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10406</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit_fuel.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 22:22:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-26303 | GHSL-2020-289: Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in insane</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26303</link><description>insane is a whitelist-oriented HTML sanitizer. Versions 2.6.2 and prior contain one or more regular expressions that are vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS). As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 20:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-26304 | GHSL-2020-290: Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in foundation-sites</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26304</link><description>Foundation is a front-end framework. Versions 6.3.3 and prior contain one or more regular expressions that are vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS). As of time of publication, it is unknown if any fixes are available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 20:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-26305 | GHSL-2020-291: Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in CommonRegexJS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26305</link><description>CommonRegexJS is a CommonRegex port for JavaScript. All available versions contain one or more regular expressions that are vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS). As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 20:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-26306 | GHSL-2020-296: Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in Knwl.js</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26306</link><description>Knwl.js is a Javascript library that parses through text for dates, times, phone numbers, emails, places, and more. Versions 1.0.2 and prior contain one or more regular expressions that are vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS). As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 20:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-26307 | GHSL-2020-301: Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in HTML2Markdown</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26307</link><description>HTML2Markdown is a Javascript implementation for converting HTML to Markdown text. All available versions contain one or more regular expressions that are vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS). As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 20:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-26308 | GHSL-2020-302: Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in validate.js</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26308</link><description>Validate.js provides a declarative way of validating javascript objects. Versions 0.13.1 and prior contain one or more regular expressions that are vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS). As of time of publication, no known patches are available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 20:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-26309 | GHSL-2020-303: Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in nope-validator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26309</link><description>Validate.js provides a declarative way of validating javascript objects. Versions 0.11.3 and prior contain one or more regular expressions that are vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS). As of time of publication, it is unknown if any patches are available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 20:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-26310 | GHSL-2020-305: Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in Pure JavaScript HTML5 Parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26310</link><description>Validate.js provides a declarative way of validating javascript objects. All versions as of 30 November 2020 contain one or more regular expressions that are vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS). As of time of publication, it is unknown if any patches are available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 20:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-26311 | GHSL-2020-312: Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in useragent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26311</link><description>Useragent is a user agent parser for Node.js. All versions as of time of publication contain one or more regular expressions that are vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS). As of time of publication, no patches are available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 20:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9501 | Wp Social Login and Register Social Counter &amp;lt;= 3.0.7 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9501</link><description>The Wp Social Login and Register Social Counter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.7. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being returned by the social login token. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the email and the user does not have an already-existing account for the service returning the token.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 13:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10402 | Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp;amp; Custom Form Builder &amp;lt;= 1.35.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Form Update and Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10402</link><description>The Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp; Custom Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on a function in all versions up to, and including, 1.35.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, and permissions granted by an Administrator, to create new or edit existing forms, including updating the default registration role to Administrator on User Registration forms.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 11:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10117 | WP Crowdfunding &amp;lt;= 2.1.11 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wpcf_donate Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10117</link><description>The WP Crowdfunding plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wpcf_donate shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 11:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10357 | Clever Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Elementor Templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10357</link><description>The Clever Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 via the getTemplateContent function in src/widgets/class-clever-widget-base.php. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive private, pending, and draft template data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 09:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9116 | Monkee-Boy Essentials &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9116</link><description>The Monkee-Boy Essentials plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 09:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9772 | Uix Shortcodes – Compatible with Gutenberg &amp;lt;= 1.9.9 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9772</link><description>The The Uix Shortcodes – Compatible with Gutenberg plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.9. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 09:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8392 | WordPress Post Grid Layouts with Pagination – Sogrid &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8392</link><description>The WordPress Post Grid Layouts with Pagination – Sogrid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 via the 'tab' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included. This can also be exploited via CSRF techniques.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9637 | School Management System – WPSchoolPress &amp;lt;= 2.2.10 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Teacher+) Account Takeover/Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9637</link><description>The School Management System – WPSchoolPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.10. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their details like email. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with teacher-level access and above, to change arbitrary user's email addresses, including administrators, and leverage that to reset the user's password and gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9642 | Editor Custom Color Palette &amp;lt;= 3.3.7 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9642</link><description>The Editor Custom Color Palette plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9853 | ID-SK Toolkit &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9853</link><description>The ID-SK Toolkit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9967 | WP show more &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via show_more Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9967</link><description>The WP show more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's show_more shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0127 | NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the GPU kernel driver of the vGPU Manager for all supported hypervisors, where a user of th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0127</link><description>NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the GPU kernel driver of the vGPU Manager for all supported hypervisors, where a user of the guest OS can cause an improper input validation by compromising the guest OS kernel. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, data tampering, denial of service, and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0128 | NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager that allows a user of the guest OS to access global resources. A su...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0128</link><description>NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager that allows a user of the guest OS to access global resources. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, and escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0117 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0117</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-of-bounds read. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0118 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0118</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-of-bounds read. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0119 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0119</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-of-bounds read. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0120 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0120</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-of-bounds read. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0121 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0121</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-of-bounds read. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0126 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability which could allow a privileged attacker to escalate permissions. A ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0126</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability which could allow a privileged attacker to escalate permissions. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10092 | Download Monitor &amp;lt;= 5.0.12 - Missing Authorization to API Key Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10092</link><description>The Download Monitor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ajax_handle_api_key_actions function in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.12. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to revoke existing API keys and generate new ones.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 07:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9456 | WP Awesome Login &amp;lt;= 0.4.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9456</link><description>The WP Awesome Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 04:46:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8870 | Forms for Mailchimp by Optin Cat – Grow Your MailChimp List &amp;lt;= 2.5.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8870</link><description>The Forms for Mailchimp by Optin Cat – Grow Your MailChimp List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 03:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10091 | ElementsKit Elementor addons &amp;lt;= 3.2.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Image Comparison Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10091</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Comparison Widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9454 | PriPre &amp;lt;= 0.4.11 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9454</link><description>The PriPre plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9613 | FormFacade – WordPress plugin for Google Forms &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9613</link><description>The FormFacade – WordPress plugin for Google Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'userId' and 'publishId' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 03:02:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9462 | Poll Maker – Versus Polls, Anonymous Polls, Image Polls &amp;lt;= 5.4.6 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Poll Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9462</link><description>The Poll Maker – Versus Polls, Anonymous Polls, Image Polls plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via poll settings in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 02:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9475 | Poll Maker – Versus Polls, Anonymous Polls, Image Polls &amp;lt;= 5.4.6 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via Order_by Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9475</link><description>The Poll Maker – Versus Polls, Anonymous Polls, Image Polls plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to generic SQL Injection via the order_by parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.6  due to insufficient escaping on the user-supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 02:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9626 | Editorial Assistant by Sovrn &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Attachment Upload and Set Post Featured Image</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9626</link><description>The Editorial Assistant by Sovrn plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ajax_zemanta_set_featured_image' function in versions up to, and including, 1.3.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to upload attachment files (such as jpg, png, txt, zip), and set the post featured image.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 02:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9890 | User Toolkit &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9890</link><description>The User Toolkit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 1.2.3. This is due to an improper capability check in the 'switchUser' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 02:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9930 | Extensions by HocWP Team &amp;lt;= 0.2.3.2 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9930</link><description>The Extensions by HocWP Team plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 0.2.3.2. This is due to missing validation on the user being supplied in the 'verify_email' action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator. The vulnerability is in the Account extension.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 02:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9931 | Wux Blog Editor &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Authentication Bypass to Administrator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9931</link><description>The Wux Blog Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This is due to missing validation on the token being supplied during the autologin through the plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in to the first administrator user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 02:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9932 | Wux Blog Editor &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9932</link><description>The Wux Blog Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the 'wuxbt_insertImageNew' function in versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 02:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9933 | WatchTowerHQ &amp;lt;= 3.9.6 - Authentication Bypass to Administrator due to Missing Empty Value Check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9933</link><description>The WatchTowerHQ plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 3.9.6. This is due to the 'watchtower_ota_token' default value is empty, and the not empty check is missing in the 'Password_Less_Access::login' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in to the WatchTowerHQ client administrator user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 02:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47821 | pyLoad vulnerable to remote code execution by download to /.pyload/scripts using /flashgot API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47821</link><description>pyLoad is a free and open-source Download Manager. The folder `/.pyload/scripts` has scripts which are run when certain actions are completed, for e.g. a download is finished. By downloading a executable file to a folder in /scripts and performing the respective action, remote code execution can be achieved in versions on the 0.5 branch prior to 0.5.0b3.dev87. A file can be downloaded to such a folder by changing the download folder to a folder in `/scripts` path and using the `/flashgot` API to download the file. This vulnerability allows an attacker with access to change the settings on a pyload server to execute arbitrary code and completely compromise the system. Version 0.5.0b3.dev87 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 23:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48237 | WTCMS 1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control in \Common\Controller\HomebaseController.class.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48237</link><description>WTCMS 1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control in \Common\Controller\HomebaseController.class.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 21:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48238 | WTCMS 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the edit_post method of /Admin\Controller\NavControl.class.php via the parentid parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48238</link><description>WTCMS 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the edit_post method of /Admin\Controller\NavControl.class.php via the parentid parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 21:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48239 | An issue was discovered in WTCMS 1.0. In the plupload method in \AssetController.class.php, the app parameters aren't processed, resulting i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48239</link><description>An issue was discovered in WTCMS 1.0. In the plupload method in \AssetController.class.php, the app parameters aren't processed, resulting in Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 21:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48228 | An issue was found in funadmin 5.0.2. The selectfiles method in \backend\controller\sys\Attachh.php directly stores the passed parameters an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48228</link><description>An issue was found in funadmin 5.0.2. The selectfiles method in \backend\controller\sys\Attachh.php directly stores the passed parameters and values into the param parameter without filtering, resulting in Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 21:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48234 | An issue was discovered in mipjz 5.0.5. In the push method of app\tag\controller\ApiAdminTag.php the value of the postAddress parameter is n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48234</link><description>An issue was discovered in mipjz 5.0.5. In the push method of app\tag\controller\ApiAdminTag.php the value of the postAddress parameter is not processed and is directly passed into curl_exec execution and output, resulting in Server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability that can read server files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 21:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48235 | An issue in ofcms 1.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the save method of the TemplateController.java file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48235</link><description>An issue in ofcms 1.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the save method of the TemplateController.java file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 21:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48236 | An issue in ofcms 1.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the FileOutputStream function in the write String method of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48236</link><description>An issue in ofcms 1.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the FileOutputStream function in the write String method of the ofcms-admin\src\main\java\com\ofsoft\cms\core\uitle\FileUtils.java file</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 21:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48229 | funadmin 5.0.2 has a SQL injection vulnerability in the Curd one click command mode plugin.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48229</link><description>funadmin 5.0.2 has a SQL injection vulnerability in the Curd one click command mode plugin.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48230 | funadmin 5.0.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the parentField parameter in the index method of \backend\controller\auth\Auth.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48230</link><description>funadmin 5.0.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the parentField parameter in the index method of \backend\controller\auth\Auth.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48232 | An issue was found in mipjz 5.0.5. In the mipPost method of \app\setting\controller\ApiAdminTool.php, the value of the postAddress parameter...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48232</link><description>An issue was found in mipjz 5.0.5. In the mipPost method of \app\setting\controller\ApiAdminTool.php, the value of the postAddress parameter is not processed and is directly passed into curl_exec execution and output, resulting in a Server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability that can read server files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48233 | mipjz 5.0.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in \app\setting\controller\ApiAdminSetting.php via the ICP parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48233</link><description>mipjz 5.0.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in \app\setting\controller\ApiAdminSetting.php via the ICP parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48396 | AIML Chatbot 1.0 (fixed in 2.0) is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). The vulnerability is exploited through the message input field,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48396</link><description>AIML Chatbot 1.0 (fixed in 2.0) is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). The vulnerability is exploited through the message input field, where attackers can inject malicious HTML or JavaScript code. The chatbot fails to sanitize these inputs, leading to the execution of malicious scripts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48218 | Funadmin v5.0.2 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /curd/table/list.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48218</link><description>Funadmin v5.0.2 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /curd/table/list.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48222 | Funadmin v5.0.2 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /curd/table/edit.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48222</link><description>Funadmin v5.0.2 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /curd/table/edit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48223 | Funadmin v5.0.2 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /curd/table/fieldlist.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48223</link><description>Funadmin v5.0.2 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /curd/table/fieldlist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48224 | Funadmin v5.0.2 has an arbitrary file read vulnerability in /curd/index/editfile.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48224</link><description>Funadmin v5.0.2 has an arbitrary file read vulnerability in /curd/index/editfile.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48225 | Funadmin v5.0.2 has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in /curd/index/delfile.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48225</link><description>Funadmin v5.0.2 has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in /curd/index/delfile.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48226 | Funadmin 5.0.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in curd/table/savefield.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48226</link><description>Funadmin 5.0.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in curd/table/savefield.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48227 | Funadmin 5.0.2 has a logical flaw in the Curd one click command deletion function, which can result in a Denial of Service (DOS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48227</link><description>Funadmin 5.0.2 has a logical flaw in the Curd one click command deletion function, which can result in a Denial of Service (DOS).</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49767 | Werkzeug possible resource exhaustion when parsing file data in forms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49767</link><description>Werkzeug is a Web Server Gateway Interface web application library. Applications using `werkzeug.formparser.MultiPartParser` corresponding to a version of Werkzeug prior to 3.0.6 to parse `multipart/form-data` requests (e.g. all flask applications) are vulnerable to a relatively simple but effective resource exhaustion (denial of service) attack. A specifically crafted form submission request can cause the parser to allocate and block 3 to 8 times the upload size in main memory. There is no upper limit; a single upload at 1 Gbit/s can exhaust 32 GB of RAM in less than 60 seconds. Werkzeug version 3.0.6 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 19:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49766 | Werkzeug safe_join not safe on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49766</link><description>Werkzeug is a Web Server Gateway Interface web application library. On Python &lt; 3.11 on Windows, os.path.isabs() does not catch UNC paths like //server/share. Werkzeug's safe_join() relies on this check, and so can produce a path that is not safe, potentially allowing unintended access to data. Applications using Python &gt;= 3.11, or not using Windows, are not vulnerable. Werkzeug version 3.0.6 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 19:29:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37845 | MangoOS before 5.2.0 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the Active Process Command fea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37845</link><description>MangoOS before 5.2.0 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the Active Process Command feature.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 18:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37846 | MangoOS before 5.2.0 was discovered to contain a Client-Side Template Injection (CSTI) vulnerability via the Platform Management Edit page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37846</link><description>MangoOS before 5.2.0 was discovered to contain a Client-Side Template Injection (CSTI) vulnerability via the Platform Management Edit page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 18:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37847 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in MangoOS before 5.1.4 and Mango API before 4.5.5 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37847</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in MangoOS before 5.1.4 and Mango API before 4.5.5 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 18:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48450 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Huly Platform v0.6.295 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted HTML fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48450</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Huly Platform v0.6.295 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted HTML file into chat group.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 18:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37844 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MangoOS before 5.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37844</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MangoOS before 5.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 18:21:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48448 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Huly Platform v0.6.295 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted HTML fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48448</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Huly Platform v0.6.295 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted HTML file into the tracker comments page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 17:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48700 | Kliqqi-CMS has a background arbitrary code execution vulnerability that attackers can exploit to implant backdoors or getShell via the edit_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48700</link><description>Kliqqi-CMS has a background arbitrary code execution vulnerability that attackers can exploit to implant backdoors or getShell via the edit_page.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 17:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9584 | Image Map Pro &amp;lt;= 6.0.20 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Map Project Add/Update/Delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9584</link><description>The Image Map Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the AJAX functions in versions up to, and including, 6.0.20. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level privileges or above, to add, update or delete map projects.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 17:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9585 | Image Map Pro &amp;lt;= 6.0.20 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9585</link><description>The Image Map Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'save_project' function with an arbitrary shortcode in versions up to, and including, 6.0.20 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 17:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48343 | A SQL Injection vulnerability in ESAFENET CDG 5 and earlier allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the id parameter of the dataSea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48343</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability in ESAFENET CDG 5 and earlier allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the id parameter of the dataSearch.jsp page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 17:21:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10386 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk ThinManager Authentication Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10386</link><description>CVE-2024-10386 IMPACT



An authentication
vulnerability exists in the affected product. The vulnerability could allow a
threat actor with network access to send crafted messages to the device, potentially
resulting in database manipulation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 17:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10387 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk ThinManager Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10387</link><description>CVE-2024-10387 IMPACT



A Denial-of-Service
vulnerability exists in the affected product. The vulnerability could allow a
threat actor with network access to send crafted messages to the device,
potentially resulting in Denial-of-Service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 17:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8036 | Unauthorized Modifications of Firmware and Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8036</link><description>ABB is aware of privately reported vulnerabilities in the product versions referenced in this CVE. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a specially crafted firmware or configuration to the system node, causing the node to stop, become inaccessible, or allowing the attacker to take control of the node.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 17:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48655 | An issue in Total.js CMS v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the func.js file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48655</link><description>An issue in Total.js CMS v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the func.js file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48743 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Sentry v.6.0.9 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the z parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48743</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Sentry v.6.0.9 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the z parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48654 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Blood Bank v.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the login.ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48654</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Blood Bank v.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the login.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30359 | OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability via a GET request to /user/getUserList. Authentication i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30359</link><description>OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability via a GET request to /user/getUserList. Authentication is required. The information disclosed is associated with the all registered users, including user ID, status, email address, role(s), user type, license type, and personal details such as first name, last name, gender, and user preferences.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30360 | OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by multiple Stored XSS (AKA Persistent or Type II) vulnerabilities via a POST request to /profile/u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30360</link><description>OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by multiple Stored XSS (AKA Persistent or Type II) vulnerabilities via a POST request to /profile/updateProfile via the slackid or phone parameters. Authentication is required.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30361 | OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability via a GET request to /user/getUserType. No authenticatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30361</link><description>OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability via a GET request to /user/getUserType. No authentication is required. The information disclosed is associated with the registered user ID, status, email address, role(s), user type, license type, and personal details such as first name, last name, gender, and user preferences.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48459 | A command execution vulnerability exists in the AX2 Pro home router produced by Shenzhen Tenda Technology Co., Ltd. (Jixiang Tenda) v.DI_700...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48459</link><description>A command execution vulnerability exists in the AX2 Pro home router produced by Shenzhen Tenda Technology Co., Ltd. (Jixiang Tenda) v.DI_7003G-19.12.24A1V16.03.29.50;V16.03.29.50;V16.03.29.50. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by constructing a malicious payload to execute commands and further obtain shell access to the router's file system with the highest privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30356 | OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by a Privilege Escalation vulnerability via a POST request to /user/assignuserrole via the userid a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30356</link><description>OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by a Privilege Escalation vulnerability via a POST request to /user/assignuserrole via the userid and role parameters . Authentication is required with OE_ADMIN role privilege.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30357 | OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by an Account Takeover vulnerability via a POST request to /profile/updateProfile via the userId an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30357</link><description>OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by an Account Takeover vulnerability via a POST request to /profile/updateProfile via the userId and email parameters. Authentication is required.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30358 | OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by an Account Takeover vulnerability via a POST request to /user/updatePassword via the userId and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30358</link><description>OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by an Account Takeover vulnerability via a POST request to /user/updatePassword via the userId and newPsw parameters. Authentication is required.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30354 | OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability via a GET request to /user/getUserWithTeam. Authenticati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30354</link><description>OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability via a GET request to /user/getUserWithTeam. Authentication is required. The information disclosed is associated with all registered user ID numbers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30355 | OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by an Account Takeover vulnerability via a POST request to /profile/updateProfile via the userId an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30355</link><description>OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by an Account Takeover vulnerability via a POST request to /profile/updateProfile via the userId and email parameters. Authentication is required.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48204 | SQL injection vulnerability in Hanzhou Haobo network management system 1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48204</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Hanzhou Haobo network management system 1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48580 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Best courier management system in php v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the email ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48580</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Best courier management system in php v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the email parameter of the login request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 15:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48579 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Best House rental management system project in php v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48579</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Best House rental management system project in php v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the username parameter of the login request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 15:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48581 | File Upload vulnerability in Best courier management system in php v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the admin_cl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48581</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in Best courier management system in php v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the admin_class.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 15:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26248 | The Kademlia DHT (go-libp2p-kad-dht 0.20.0 and earlier) used in IPFS (0.18.1 and earlier) assigns routing information for content (i.e., inf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26248</link><description>The Kademlia DHT (go-libp2p-kad-dht 0.20.0 and earlier) used in IPFS (0.18.1 and earlier) assigns routing information for content (i.e., information about who holds the content) to be stored by peers whose peer IDs have a small DHT distance from the content ID. This allows an attacker to censor content by generating many Sybil peers whose peer IDs have a small distance from the content ID, thus hijacking the content resolution process.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 15:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48428 | An issue in Olive VLE allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the reset password function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48428</link><description>An issue in Olive VLE allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the reset password function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 14:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49757 | Zitadel User Registration Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49757</link><description>The open-source identity infrastructure software Zitadel allows administrators to disable the user self-registration. Due to a missing security check in versions prior to 2.64.0, 2.63.5, 2.62.7, 2.61.4, 2.60.4, 2.59.5, and 2.58.7, disabling the "User Registration allowed" option only hid the registration button on the login page. Users could bypass this restriction by directly accessing the registration URL (/ui/login/loginname) and register a user that way. Versions 2.64.0, 2.63.5, 2.62.7, 2.61.4, 2.60.4, 2.59.5, and 2.58.7 contain a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 14:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49753 | Denied Host Validation Bypass in Zitadel Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49753</link><description>Zitadel is open-source identity infrastructure software. Versions prior to 2.64.1, 2.63.6, 2.62.8, 2.61.4, 2.60.4, 2.59.5, and 2.58.7 have a flaw in the URL validation mechanism of Zitadel actions allows bypassing restrictions intended to block requests to localhost (127.0.0.1). The isHostBlocked check, designed to prevent such requests, can be circumvented by creating a DNS record that resolves to 127.0.0.1. This enables actions to send requests to localhost despite the intended security measures. This vulnerability potentially allows unauthorized access to unsecured internal endpoints, which may contain sensitive information or functionalities. Versions 2.64.1, 2.63.6, 2.62.8, 2.61.4, 2.60.4, 2.59.5, and 2.58.7 contain a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 14:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49380 | Plenti arbitrary file write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49380</link><description>Plenti, a static site generator, has an arbitrary file write vulnerability in versions prior to 0.7.2. The `/postLocal` endpoint is vulnerable to an arbitrary file write vulnerability when a plenti user serves their website. This issue may lead to Remote Code Execution. Version 0.7.2 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49381 | Plenti arbitrary file deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49381</link><description>Plenti, a static site generator, has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in versions prior to 0.7.2. The `/postLocal` endpoint is vulnerable to an arbitrary file write deletion when a plenti user serves their website. This issue may lead to information loss. Version 0.7.2 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10380 | SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software ajax_product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10380</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/ajax_product.php. The manipulation of the argument drop_services leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:04:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49376 | Autolab Has Misconfigured Reset Password Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49376</link><description>Autolab, a course management service that enables auto-graded programming assignments, has misconfigured reset password permissions in version 3.0.0. For email-based accounts, users with insufficient privileges could reset and theoretically access privileged users' accounts by resetting their passwords. This issue is fixed in version 3.0.1. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:04:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49378 | smartUp Cross-site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49378</link><description>smartUp, a web browser mouse gestures extension, has a universal cross-site scripting issue in the Edge and Firefox versions of smartUp 7.2.622.1170. The vulnerability allows another extension to execute arbitrary code in the context of the user’s tab. As of time of publication, no known patches exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:04:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10381 | Authentication Bypass Vulnerability in Matrix Door Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10381</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Matrix Door Controller Cosec Vega FAXQ due to improper implementation of session management at the web-based management interface. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted http request on the vulnerable device.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow remote attacker to gain unauthorized access and take complete control of the targeted device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:04:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9991 | Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information Vulnerability in Philips Lighting Devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9991</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Philips lighting devices due to storage of Wi-Fi credentials in plain text within the device firmware. An attacker with physical access could exploit this by extracting the firmware and analyzing the binary data to obtain the plaintext Wi-Fi credentials stored on the vulnerable device.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to gain unauthorized access to the Wi-Fi network to which vulnerable device is connected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10378 | ESAFENET CDG CDGRenewApplicationService.java actionViewCDGRenewFile sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10378</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in ESAFENET CDG 5. Affected is the function actionViewCDGRenewFile of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/client/CDGRenewApplicationService.java. The manipulation of the argument CDGRenewFileId leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10379 | ESAFENET CDG DecryptApplicationService.java actionViewDecyptFile path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10379</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. Affected by this vulnerability is the function actionViewDecyptFile of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/client/DecryptApplicationService.java. The manipulation of the argument decryptFileId with the input ../../../Windows/System32/drivers/etc/hosts leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The affected function has a typo and is missing an R. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10374 | WP-Members &amp;lt;= 3.4.9.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wpmem_loginout Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10374</link><description>The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wpmem_loginout shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.9.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10376 | ESAFENET CDG AutoSignService.java actionPassOrNotAutoSign sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10376</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function actionPassOrNotAutoSign of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/service/processsign/AutoSignService.java. The manipulation of the argument UniqueId leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10377 | ESAFENET CDG DecryptApplicationService.java actionPassDecryptApplication1 sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10377</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function actionPassDecryptApplication1 of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/client/DecryptApplicationService.java. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This is a different issue than CVE-2024-10069. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47483 | Dell Data Lakehouse, version(s) 1.0.0.0 and 1.1.0.0, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47483</link><description>Dell Data Lakehouse, version(s) 1.0.0.0 and 1.1.0.0, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47481 | Dell Data Lakehouse, version(s) 1.0.0.0, 1.1.0., contain(s) an Improper Access Control vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with adjac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47481</link><description>Dell Data Lakehouse, version(s) 1.0.0.0, 1.1.0., contain(s) an Improper Access Control vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with adjacent network access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44098 | In lwis_device_event_states_clear_locked of lwis_event.c, there is a possible privilege escalation due to a double free. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44098</link><description>In lwis_device_event_states_clear_locked of lwis_event.c, there is a possible privilege escalation due to a double free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44099 | There is a possible Local bypass of user interaction due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local information disclosure with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44099</link><description>There is a possible Local bypass of user interaction due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44100 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44100</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44101 | there is a possible Null Pointer Dereference (modem crash) due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44101</link><description>there is a possible Null Pointer Dereference (modem crash) due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47012 | In mm_GetMobileIdIndexForNsUpdate of mm_GmmPduCodec.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47012</link><description>In mm_GetMobileIdIndexForNsUpdate of mm_GmmPduCodec.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47013 | In pmucal_rae_handle_seq_int of flexpmu_cal_rae.c, there is a possible arbitrary write due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47013</link><description>In pmucal_rae_handle_seq_int of flexpmu_cal_rae.c, there is a possible arbitrary write due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47014 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47014</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47015 | In ProtocolMiscHwConfigChangeAdapter::GetData() of protocolmiscadapter.cpp, there is a possible out-of-bounds read due to a missing bounds c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47015</link><description>In ProtocolMiscHwConfigChangeAdapter::GetData() of protocolmiscadapter.cpp, there is a possible out-of-bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with baseband firmware compromise required. User Interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47016 | there is a possible privilege escalation due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47016</link><description>there is a possible privilege escalation due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47017 | In ufshc_scsi_cmd of ufs.c, there is a possible stack variable use after free due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47017</link><description>In ufshc_scsi_cmd of ufs.c, there is a possible stack variable use after free due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47018 | In pmucal_rae_handle_seq_int of flexpmu_cal_rae.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a buffer overflow. This could lead to local...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47018</link><description>In pmucal_rae_handle_seq_int of flexpmu_cal_rae.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a buffer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47019 | In ProtocolEmbmsSaiListAdapter::Init() of protocolembmsadapter.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47019</link><description>In ProtocolEmbmsSaiListAdapter::Init() of protocolembmsadapter.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with baseband firmware compromise required. User Interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47020 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47020</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47021 | In sms_ExtractCbLanguage of sms_CellBroadcast.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47021</link><description>In sms_ExtractCbLanguage of sms_CellBroadcast.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47022 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47022</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47023 | there is a possible man-in-the-middle attack due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47023</link><description>there is a possible man-in-the-middle attack due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47024 | In vring_size of external/headers/include/virtio/virtio_ring.h, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47024</link><description>In vring_size of external/headers/include/virtio/virtio_ring.h, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47025 | In ppmp_protect_buf of drm_fw.c, there is a possible information disclosure due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local infor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47025</link><description>In ppmp_protect_buf of drm_fw.c, there is a possible information disclosure due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47026 | In gsc_gsa_rescue of gsc_gsa.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47026</link><description>In gsc_gsa_rescue of gsc_gsa.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47027 | In sm_mem_compat_get_vmm_obj of lib/sm/shared_mem.c, there is a possible arbitrary physical memory access due to improper input validation. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47027</link><description>In sm_mem_compat_get_vmm_obj of lib/sm/shared_mem.c, there is a possible arbitrary physical memory access due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47028 | In ffu_flash_pack of ffu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47028</link><description>In ffu_flash_pack of ffu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47029 | In TrustySharedMemoryManager::GetSharedMemory of ondevice/trusty/trusty_shared_memory_manager.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47029</link><description>In TrustySharedMemoryManager::GetSharedMemory of ondevice/trusty/trusty_shared_memory_manager.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47030 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47030</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47031 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47031</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47033 | In lwis_allocator_free of lwis_allocator.c, there is a possible memory corruption due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47033</link><description>In lwis_allocator_free of lwis_allocator.c, there is a possible memory corruption due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47034 | there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47034</link><description>there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47035 | In vring_init of external/headers/include/virtio/virtio_ring.h, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a logic error in the code. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47035</link><description>In vring_init of external/headers/include/virtio/virtio_ring.h, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47041 | In valid_address of syscall.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47041</link><description>In valid_address of syscall.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10016 | File Upload Types by WPForms &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10016</link><description>The File Upload Types by WPForms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10112 | Simple News &amp;lt;= 2.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via news Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10112</link><description>The Simple News plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'news' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10343 | Beek Widget Extention &amp;lt;= 0.9.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10343</link><description>The Beek Widget Extention plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 0.9.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8666 | Shoutcast Icecast HTML5 Radio Player &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8666</link><description>The Shoutcast Icecast HTML5 Radio Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'html5radio' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45785 | MUSASI version 3 contains an issue with use of client-side authentication. If this vulnerability is exploited, other users' credential and s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45785</link><description>MUSASI version 3 contains an issue with use of client-side authentication. If this vulnerability is exploited, other users' credential and sensitive information may be retrieved.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47158 | N-LINE 2.0.6 and prior versions contain a code injection vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary code may be executed o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47158</link><description>N-LINE 2.0.6 and prior versions contain a code injection vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary code may be executed on the instructor's browser, or the instructor may be directed to a malicious website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10150 | Bamazoo – Button Generator &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via dgs Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10150</link><description>The Bamazoo – Button Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's dgs shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10341 | League of Legends Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10341</link><description>The League of Legends Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10342 | League of Legends Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10342</link><description>The League of Legends Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9598 | AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages &amp;lt;= 1.0.99.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9598</link><description>The AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.99.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'proxy' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send the logged in user's cookies to their own server via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9628 | WPS Telegram Chat &amp;lt;= 4.5.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Unauthorized Access to Telegram Bot API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9628</link><description>The WPS Telegram Chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'Wps_Telegram_Chat_Admin::checkСonnection' function in versions up to, and including, 4.5.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to have full access to the Telegram Bot API endpoint and communicate with it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9630 | WPS Telegram Chat &amp;lt;= 4.5.4 - Missing Authorization to Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9630</link><description>The WPS Telegram Chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to a missing capability check when accessing messages in versions up to, and including, 4.5.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view the messages that are sent through the Telegram Bot API.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50583 | Whale browser Installer before 3.1.0.0 allows an attacker to execute a malicious DLL in the user environment due to improper permission sett...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50583</link><description>Whale browser Installer before 3.1.0.0 allows an attacker to execute a malicious DLL in the user environment due to improper permission settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10011 | BuddyPress &amp;lt;= 14.1.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Directory Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10011</link><description>The BuddyPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 14.1.0 via the id parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to perform actions on files outside of the originally intended directory and enables file uploads to directories outside of the web root. Depending on server configuration it may be possible to upload files with double extensions. This vulnerability only affects Windows.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10148 | Awesome buttons &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via btn2 Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10148</link><description>The Awesome buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's btn2 shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9235 | Mapster WP Maps &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9235</link><description>The Mapster WP Maps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to an insufficient capability check on the mapster_wp_maps_set_option_from_js() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9302 | App Builder – Create Native Android &amp;amp; iOS Apps On The Flight &amp;lt;= 5.3.7 - Privilege Escalation and Account Takeover via Weak OTP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9302</link><description>The App Builder – Create Native Android &amp; iOS Apps On The Flight plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.7. This is due to the verify_otp_forgot_password() and update_password() functions not having enough controls to prevent a successful brute force attack of the OTP to change a password, or verify that a password reset request came from an authorized user. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to generate and brute force an OTP that makes it possible to change any users passwords, including an administrator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9607 | 10Web Social Post Feed &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9607</link><description>The 10Web Social Post Feed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Please note this is only exploitable when the leave a review notice is present.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42420 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs contain multiple Out-of-bounds Read vulnerabilities, due to improper processing of keyword search input and impro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42420</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs contain multiple Out-of-bounds Read vulnerabilities, due to improper processing of keyword search input and improper processing of SOAP messages.
Crafted HTTP requests may cause affected products crashed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43424 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process HTTP request headers, resulting in an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability.&#13;
Crafted HTTP requests...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43424</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process HTTP request headers, resulting in an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability.
Crafted HTTP requests may cause affected products crashed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45829 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs provide the web page to download data, where query parameters in HTTP requests are improperly processed and resul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45829</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs provide the web page to download data, where query parameters in HTTP requests are improperly processed and resulting in an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability.
Crafted HTTP requests may cause affected products crashed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45842 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process URI data in HTTP PUT requests resulting in a path Traversal vulnerability.&#13;
Unintended interna...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45842</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process URI data in HTTP PUT requests resulting in a path Traversal vulnerability.
Unintended internal files may be retrieved when processing crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47005 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs provide configuration related APIs. They are expected to be called by administrative users only, but insufficient...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47005</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs provide configuration related APIs. They are expected to be called by administrative users only, but insufficiently restricted.
A non-administrative user may execute some configuration APIs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47406 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process HTTP authentication requests, resulting in an authentication bypass vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47406</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process HTTP authentication requests, resulting in an authentication bypass vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47549 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process query parameters in HTTP requests, which may allow contamination of unintended data to HTTP re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47549</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process query parameters in HTTP requests, which may allow contamination of unintended data to HTTP response headers.
Accessing a crafted URL which points to an affected product may cause malicious script executed on the web browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47801 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process query parameters in HTTP requests, resulting in a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47801</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process query parameters in HTTP requests, resulting in a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability.
Accessing a crafted URL which points to an affected product may cause malicious script executed on the web browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48870 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly validate input data in URI data registration, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48870</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly validate input data in URI data registration, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability.
If crafted input is stored by an administrative user, malicious script may be executed on the web browsers of other victim users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9109 | UPS Live Rates and Access Points &amp;lt;= 2.3.11 - Missing Authorization to Plugin API key reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9109</link><description>The WooCommerce UPS Shipping – Live Rates and Access Points plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the delete_oauth_data function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.11. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete the plugin's API key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 05:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9488 | Comments – wpDiscuz &amp;lt;= 7.6.24 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9488</link><description>The Comments – wpDiscuz plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 7.6.24. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being returned by the social login token. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the email and the user does not have an already-existing account for the service returning the token.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 05:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9686 | Order Notification for Telegram &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Send Telegram Test Message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9686</link><description>The Order Notification for Telegram plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized test message sending due to a missing capability check on the 'nktgnfw_send_test_message' function in versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send a test message via the Telegram Bot API to the user configured in the settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 04:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10372 | chidiwilliams buzz model_loader.py download_model temp file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10372</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in chidiwilliams buzz 1.1.0. This vulnerability affects the function download_model of the file buzz/model_loader.py. The manipulation leads to insecure temporary file. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 02:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10368 | Codezips Sales Management System addstock.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10368</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Sales Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /addstock.php. The manipulation of the argument prodtype leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10369 | Codezips Sales Management System addcustcom.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10369</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Sales Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /addcustcom.php. The manipulation of the argument refno leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10370 | Codezips Sales Management System addcustind.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10370</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Sales Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /addcustind.php. The manipulation of the argument refno leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10371 | SourceCodester Payroll Management System main login buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10371</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Payroll Management System 1.0. This affects the function login of the file main. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10354 | SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software print.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10354</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/print.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10355 | SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software invoice.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10355</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/invoice.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>