<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 19:40:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-49195 | Mbed TLS 3.5.x through 3.6.x before 3.6.2 has a buffer underrun in pkwrite when writing an opaque key pair</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49195</link><description>Mbed TLS 3.5.x through 3.6.x before 3.6.2 has a buffer underrun in pkwrite when writing an opaque key pair</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 19:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41344 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in Codeigniter 3.1.13 allows attackers to arbitrarily change the Administrator password and escalate pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41344</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in Codeigniter 3.1.13 allows attackers to arbitrarily change the Administrator password and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 18:59:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35584 | SQL injection vulnerability in Ajax.php, ForWindow.php, ForExport.php, Modules.php, functions/HackingLogFnc.php in OpenSis Community Edition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35584</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Ajax.php, ForWindow.php, ForExport.php, Modules.php, functions/HackingLogFnc.php in OpenSis Community Edition 9.1, 8.0, and possibly earlier versions. It is possible for an authenticated user to perform SQL Injection due to the lack to sanitisation. The application takes arbitrary value from "X-Forwarded-For" header and appends it to a SQL INSERT statement directly, leading to SQL Injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 18:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5749 | Certain HP DesignJet products – Credential reflection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5749</link><description>Certain HP DesignJet products may be vulnerable to credential reflection which allow viewing SMTP server credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 17:42:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48915 | Agent Dart missing certificate verification checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48915</link><description>Agent Dart is an agent library built for Internet Computer for Dart and Flutter apps. Prior to version 1.0.0-dev.29, certificate verification in `lib/agent/certificate.dart` does not occur properly. During the delegation verification in the `_checkDelegation` function, the canister_ranges aren't verified. The impact of not checking the canister_ranges is that a subnet can sign canister responses in behalf of another subnet. The certificate’s timestamp, i.e /time path, is also not verified, meaning that the certificate effectively has no expiration time. Version 1.0.0-dev.29 implements appropriate certificate verification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 17:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48914 | Vendure asset server plugin has local file read vulnerability with AssetServerPlugin &amp;amp; LocalAssetStorageStrategy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48914</link><description>Vendure is an open-source headless commerce platform. Prior to versions 3.0.5 and 2.3.3, a vulnerability in Vendure's asset server plugin allows an attacker to craft a request which is able to traverse the server file system and retrieve the contents of arbitrary files, including sensitive data such as configuration files, environment variables, and other critical data stored on the server. In the same code path is an additional vector for crashing the server via a malformed URI. Patches are available in versions 3.0.5 and 2.3.3. Some workarounds are also available. One may use object storage rather than the local file system, e.g. MinIO or S3, or define middleware which detects and blocks requests with urls containing `/../`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48913 | Honor vulnerable to bypass of CSRF Middleware by a request without Content-Type header.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48913</link><description>Hono, a web framework, prior to version 4.6.5 is vulnerable to bypass of cross-site request forgery (CSRF) middleware by a request without Content-Type header. Although the CSRF middleware verifies the Content-Type Header, Hono always considers a request without a Content-Type header to be safe. This can allow an attacker to bypass CSRF protection implemented with Hono CSRF middleware. Version 4.6.5 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:16:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47874 | Starlette Denial of service (DoS) via multipart/form-data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47874</link><description>Starlette is an Asynchronous Server Gateway Interface (ASGI) framework/toolkit. Prior to version 0.40.0, Starlette treats `multipart/form-data` parts without a `filename` as text form fields and buffers those in byte strings with no size limit. This allows an attacker to upload arbitrary large form fields and cause Starlette to both slow down significantly due to excessive memory allocations and copy operations, and also consume more and more memory until the server starts swapping and grinds to a halt, or the OS terminates the server process with an OOM error. Uploading multiple such requests in parallel may be enough to render a service practically unusable, even if reasonable request size limits are enforced by a reverse proxy in front of Starlette. This Denial of service (DoS) vulnerability affects all applications built with Starlette (or FastAPI) accepting form requests. Verison 0.40.0 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 15:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47876 | Sakai: Kernel users created with type roleview can login as a normal user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47876</link><description>Sakai is a Collaboration and Learning Environment. Starting in version 23.0 and prior to version 23.2, kernel users created with type roleview can log in as a normal user. This can result in illegal access being granted to the system. Version 23.3 fixes this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 15:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47824 | Malicious homeservers can steal message keys when the matrix-react-sdk user invites another user to a room</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47824</link><description>matrix-react-sdk is react-based software development kit for inserting a Matrix chat/VOIP client into a web page. Starting in version 3.18.0 and before 3.102.0, matrix-react-sdk allows a malicious homeserver to potentially steal message keys for a room when a user invites another user to that room, via injection of a malicious device controlled by the homeserver. This is possible because matrix-react-sdk before 3.102.0 shared historical message keys on invite. Version 3.102.0 fixes this issue by disabling sharing message keys on invite by removing calls to the vulnerable functionality. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 15:44:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9506 | Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9506</link><description>Improper regular expression in Vue's parseHTML function leads to a potential regular expression denial of service vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 15:44:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47779 | Element Web vulnerable to potential exposure of access token via authenticated media</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47779</link><description>Element is a Matrix web client built using the Matrix React SDK .Element Web versions 1.11.70 through 1.11.80 contain a vulnerability which can, under specially crafted conditions, lead to the access token becoming exposed to third parties. At least one vector has been identified internally, involving malicious widgets, but other vectors may exist. Note that despite superficial similarity to CVE-2024-47771, this is an entirely separate vulnerability, caused by a separate piece of code included only in Element Web. Element Web and Element Desktop share most but not all, of their code and this vulnerability exists in the part of the code base which is not shared between the projects. Users are strongly advised to upgrade to version 1.11.81 to remediate the issue. As a workaround, avoid granting permissions to untrusted widgets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 15:44:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48622 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) issue in DomainMOD below v4.12.0 allows remote attackers to inject JavaScript code via admin/domain-fields/edit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48622</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) issue in DomainMOD below v4.12.0 allows remote attackers to inject JavaScript code via admin/domain-fields/edit.php and the cdfid parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 15:44:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48623 | In queue\index.php of DomainMOD below v4.12.0, the list_id and domain_id parameters in the GET request can be exploited to cause a reflected...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48623</link><description>In queue\index.php of DomainMOD below v4.12.0, the list_id and domain_id parameters in the GET request can be exploited to cause a reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 15:44:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48624 | In segments\edit.php of DomainMOD below v4.12.0, the segid parameter in the GET request can be exploited to cause a reflected Cross Site Scr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48624</link><description>In segments\edit.php of DomainMOD below v4.12.0, the segid parameter in the GET request can be exploited to cause a reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 15:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9676 | Podman: buildah: cri-o: symlink traversal vulnerability in the containers/storage library can cause denial of service (dos)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9676</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Podman, Buildah, and CRI-O. A symlink traversal vulnerability in the containers/storage library can cause Podman, Buildah, and CRI-O to hang and result in a denial of service via OOM kill when running a malicious image using an automatically assigned user namespace (`--userns=auto` in Podman and Buildah). The containers/storage library will read /etc/passwd inside the container, but does not properly validate if that file is a symlink, which can be used to cause the library to read an arbitrary file on the host.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 15:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47771 | Element Desktop vulnerable to potential exposure of access token via authenticated media</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47771</link><description>Element Desktop is a Matrix client for desktop platforms. Element Desktop versions 1.11.70 through 1.11.80 contain a vulnerability which can, under specially crafted conditions, lead to the access token becoming exposed to third parties. At least one vector has been identified internally, involving malicious widgets, but other vectors may exist. Users are strongly advised to upgrade to version 1.11.81 to remediate the issue. As a workaround, avoid granting permissions to untrusted widgets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 15:17:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47080 | matrix-js-sdk keys sent via `sendSharedHistoryKeys` vulnerable to interception by malicious homeserver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47080</link><description>matrix-js-sdk is the Matrix Client-Server SDK for JavaScript and TypeScript. In matrix-js-sdk versions versions 9.11.0 through 34.7.0, the method `MatrixClient.sendSharedHistoryKeys` is vulnerable to interception by malicious homeservers.  The method was introduced by MSC3061) and is commonly used to share historical message keys with newly invited users, granting them access to past messages in the room. However, it unconditionally sends these "shared" keys to all of the invited user's devices, regardless of whether the user's cryptographic identity is verified or whether the user's devices are signed by that identity. This allows the attacker to potentially inject its own devices to receive sensitive historical keys without proper security checks. Note that this only affects clients running the SDK with the legacy crypto stack. Clients using the new Rust cryptography stack (i.e. those that call `MatrixClient.initRustCrypto()` instead of `MatrixClient.initCrypto()`) are unaffected by this vulnerability, because `MatrixClient.sendSharedHistoryKeys()` raises an exception in such environments. The vulnerability was fixed in matrix-js-sdk 34.8.0 by removing the vulnerable functionality. As a workaround, remove use of affected functionality from clients.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 14:55:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31493 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Languages folder of Zoneminder up to v1.36.33 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31493</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Languages folder of Zoneminder up to v1.36.33 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PHP file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 14:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9979 | Pyo3: risk of use-after-free in `borrowed` reads from python weak references</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9979</link><description>A flaw was found in PyO3. This vulnerability causes a use-after-free issue, potentially leading to memory corruption or crashes via unsound borrowing from weak Python references.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 14:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48948 | The Elliptic package 6.5.7 for Node.js, in its for ECDSA implementation, does not correctly verify valid signatures if the hash contains at ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48948</link><description>The Elliptic package 6.5.7 for Node.js, in its for ECDSA implementation, does not correctly verify valid signatures if the hash contains at least four leading 0 bytes and when the order of the elliptic curve's base point is smaller than the hash, because of an _truncateToN anomaly. This leads to valid signatures being rejected. Legitimate transactions or communications may be incorrectly flagged as invalid.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 13:36:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9986 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System member_register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9986</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file member_register.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname/username/password/email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "password" to be affected. But it must be assumed that other parameters are affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 13:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48278 | Phpgurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System 3.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /edit-profile.php...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48278</link><description>Phpgurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System 3.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /edit-profile.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 13:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48283 | Phpgurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System 3.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /admin//search-result.php via the sear...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48283</link><description>Phpgurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System 3.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /admin//search-result.php via the searchkey parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 13:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9977 | MitraStar GPT-2541GNAC Firewall Settings Page settings-firewall.cgi os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9977</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in MitraStar GPT-2541GNAC BR_g5.6_1.11(WVK.0)b26. Affected is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/settings-firewall.cgi of the component Firewall Settings Page. The manipulation of the argument SrcInterface leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. We tried to contact the vendor early about the disclosure but the official mail address was not working properly.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 13:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48279 | A HTML Injection vulnerability was found in /search-result.php of PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System 3.2. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48279</link><description>A HTML Injection vulnerability was found in /search-result.php of PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System 3.2. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary HTML code via the searchkey parameter in a POST HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 12:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48280 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /search-result.php of PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System 3.2, which ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48280</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /search-result.php of PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System 3.2, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL command via the fromdate parameter in a POST HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 12:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48282 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /password-recovery.php of PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System 3.2, wh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48282</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /password-recovery.php of PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System 3.2, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands to get unauthorized database access via the femail parameter in a POST HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 12:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9975 | SourceCodester Drag and Drop Image Upload upload.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9975</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Drag and Drop Image Upload 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /upload.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 11:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9976 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System manage_customer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9976</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /php/manage_customer.php?action=search. The manipulation of the argument text leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 11:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47674 | mm: avoid leaving partial pfn mappings around in error case</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47674</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: avoid leaving partial pfn mappings around in error case

As Jann points out, PFN mappings are special, because unlike normal
memory mappings, there is no lifetime information associated with the
mapping - it is just a raw mapping of PFNs with no reference counting of
a 'struct page'.

That's all very much intentional, but it does mean that it's easy to
mess up the cleanup in case of errors.  Yes, a failed mmap() will always
eventually clean up any partial mappings, but without any explicit
lifetime in the page table mapping itself, it's very easy to do the
error handling in the wrong order.

In particular, it's easy to mistakenly free the physical backing store
before the page tables are actually cleaned up and (temporarily) have
stale dangling PTE entries.

To make this situation less error-prone, just make sure that any partial
pfn mapping is torn down early, before any other error handling.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 10:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45271 | MB connect line/Helmholz: Remote code execution due to improper input validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45271</link><description>An unauthenticated local attacker can gain admin privileges by deploying a config file due to improper input validation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 10:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45272 | MB connect line/Helmholz: Generation of weak passwords vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45272</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can perform a brute-force attack on the credentials of the remote service portal with a high chance of success, resulting in connection lost.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 10:35:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45273 | MB connect line/Helmholz: Weak encryption of configuration file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45273</link><description>An unauthenticated local attacker can decrypt the devices config file and therefore compromise the device due to a weak implementation of the encryption used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 10:35:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45274 | MB connect line/Helmholz: Remote code execution via confnet service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45274</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can execute OS commands via UDP on the device due to missing authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 10:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45275 | MB connect line/Helmholz: Hardcoded user accounts with hard-coded passwords</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45275</link><description>The devices contain two hard coded user accounts with hardcoded passwords that allow an unauthenticated remote attacker for full control of the affected devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 10:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45276 | MB connect line/Helmholz: tmp directory exposed via webservice</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45276</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can get read access to files in the "/tmp" directory due to missing authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 10:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49382 | Excessive attack surface in archive-server service due to binding to an unrestricted IP address. The following products are affected: Acroni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49382</link><description>Excessive attack surface in archive-server service due to binding to an unrestricted IP address. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Linux, Windows) before build 38690.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 10:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49383 | Excessive attack surface in acep-importer service due to binding to an unrestricted IP address. The following products are affected: Acronis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49383</link><description>Excessive attack surface in acep-importer service due to binding to an unrestricted IP address. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Linux, Windows) before build 38690.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 10:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49384 | Excessive attack surface in acep-collector service due to binding to an unrestricted IP address. The following products are affected: Acroni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49384</link><description>Excessive attack surface in acep-collector service due to binding to an unrestricted IP address. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Linux, Windows) before build 38690.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 10:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49387 | Cleartext transmission of sensitive information in acep-collector service. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Li...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49387</link><description>Cleartext transmission of sensitive information in acep-collector service. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Linux, Windows) before build 38690.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 10:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49388 | Sensitive information manipulation due to improper authorization. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Linux, Wind...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49388</link><description>Sensitive information manipulation due to improper authorization. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Linux, Windows) before build 38690.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 10:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47945 | Predictable Session ID</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47945</link><description>The devices are vulnerable to session hijacking due to insufficient 
entropy in its session ID generation algorithm. The session IDs are 
predictable, with only 32,768 possible values per user, which allows 
attackers to pre-generate valid session IDs, leading to unauthorized 
access to user sessions. This is not only due to the use of an 
(insecure) rand() function call but also because of missing 
initialization via srand(). As a result only the PIDs are effectively 
used as seed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 10:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9973 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop Report Viewing Page page sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9973</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/?page=reports of the component Report Viewing Page. The manipulation of the argument date leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 09:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9974 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop POST Request Master.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9974</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file classes/Master.php?f=add_to_card of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument product_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 09:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47943 | Improper signature verification of firmware upgrade files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47943</link><description>The firmware upgrade function in the admin web interface of the Rittal IoT Interface &amp; CMC III Processing Unit devices checks if 
the patch files are signed before executing the containing run.sh 
script. The signing process is kind of an HMAC with a long string as key
 which is hard-coded in the firmware and is freely available for 
download. This allows crafting malicious "signed" .patch files in order 
to compromise the device and execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 09:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47944 | Missing Protection Mechanism for Alternate Hardware Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47944</link><description>The device directly executes .patch firmware upgrade files on a USB stick without any prior authentication in the admin interface. This leads to an unauthenticated code execution via the firmware upgrade function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 09:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9925 | SQL injection in QPLANT by TAI Smart Factory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9925</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in TAI Smart Factory's QPLANT SF version 1.0. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to retrieve all database information by sending a specially crafted SQL query to the ‘email’ parameter on the ‘RequestPasswordChange’ endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 08:52:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9895 | Smart Online Order for Clover &amp;lt;= 1.5.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via moo_receipt_link Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9895</link><description>The Smart Online Order for Clover plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's moo_receipt_link shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 08:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9983 | Ragic Enterprise Cloud Database - Arbitrary File Read through Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9983</link><description>Enterprise Cloud Database from Ragic does not properly validate a specific page parameter, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit this vulnerability to read arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 08:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9984 | Ragic Enterprise Cloud Database - Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9984</link><description>Enterprise Cloud Database from Ragic does not authenticate access to specific functionality, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to use this functionality to obtain any user's session cookie.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 08:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9985 | Ragic Enterprise Cloud Database - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9985</link><description>Enterprise Cloud Database from Ragic does not properly validate the file type for uploads. Attackers with regular privileges can upload a webshell and use it to execute arbitrary code on the remote server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 08:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9982 | ESi Technology AIM LINE Marketing Platform - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9982</link><description>AIM LINE Marketing Platform from Esi Technology does not properly validate a specific query parameter. When the LINE Campaign Module is enabled, unauthenticated remote attackers can inject arbitrary FetchXml commands to read, modify, and delete database content.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 08:21:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9980 | FormosaSoft ee-class - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9980</link><description>The ee-class from FormosaSoft does not properly validate a specific page parameter, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 08:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9981 | FormosaSoft ee-class - Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9981</link><description>The ee-class from FormosaSoft does not properly validate a specific page parameter, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to upload a malicious PHP file first and then exploit this vulnerability to include the file, resulting in arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 08:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9837 | AADMY – Add Auto Date Month Year Into Posts &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9837</link><description>The The AADMY – Add Auto Date Month Year Into Posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 07:36:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9972 | ChanGate Property Management System - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9972</link><description>Property Management System from ChanGate has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 06:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46898 | SHIRASAGI prior to v1.19.1 processes URLs in HTTP requests improperly, resulting in a path traversal vulnerability. If this vulnerability is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46898</link><description>SHIRASAGI prior to v1.19.1 processes URLs in HTTP requests improperly, resulting in a path traversal vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary files on the server may be retrieved when processing crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 06:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0129 | NVIDIA NeMo contains a vulnerability in SaveRestoreConnector where a user may cause a path traversal issue via an unsafe .tar file extractio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0129</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo contains a vulnerability in SaveRestoreConnector where a user may cause a path traversal issue via an unsafe .tar file extraction. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 05:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9944 | WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 9.0.2 - Unauthenticated HTML Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9944</link><description>The WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to HTML Injection in all versions up to, and including, 9.0.2. This is due to the plugin not properly neutralizing HTML elements from submitted order forms. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary HTML that will render when the administrator views order form submissions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 05:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21535 | Versions of the package markdown-to-jsx before 7.4.0 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the src property due to improper input...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21535</link><description>Versions of the package markdown-to-jsx before 7.4.0 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the src property due to improper input sanitization. An attacker can execute arbitrary code by injecting a malicious iframe element in the markdown.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 05:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9971 | NewType FlowMaster BPM Plus - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9971</link><description>The specific query functionality in the FlowMaster BPM Plus from NewType does not properly restrict user input, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to inject SQL commands to read, modify, or delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 03:55:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9970 | NewType FlowMaster BPM Plus - Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9970</link><description>The FlowMaster BPM Plus system from NewType has a privilege escalation vulnerability. Remote attackers with regular privileges can elevate their privileges to administrator by tampering with a specific cookie.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 03:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9969 | NewType WebEIP v3.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9969</link><description>NewType WebEIP v3.0 does not properly validate user input, allowing a remote attacker with regular privileges to insert JavaScript into specific parameters, resulting in a Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) attack. The affected product is no longer maintained. It is recommended to upgrade to the new product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 03:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9968 | NewType WebEIP v3.0 - SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9968</link><description>WebEIP v3.0 from 

NewType does not properly validate user input, allowing remote attackers with regular privilege to inject SQL commands to read, modify, and delete data stored in database. The affected product is no longer maintained. It is recommended to upgrade to the new product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 02:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6757 | Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.23.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Basic Information Exposure via get_image_alt Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6757</link><description>The Elementor Website Builder – More than Just a Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Basic Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.23.5 via the get_image_alt function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract either excerpt data or titles of private or password-protected posts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 02:11:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9687 | WP 2FA with Telegram &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9687</link><description>The WP 2FA with Telegram plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in versions up to, and including, 3.0. This is due to insufficient validation of the user-controlled key on the 'validate_tg' action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 02:11:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9820 | WP 2FA with Telegram &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Two-Factor Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9820</link><description>The WP 2FA with Telegram plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Two-Factor Authentication Bypass in versions up to, and including, 3.0. This is due to the two-factor code being stored in a cookie, which makes it possible to bypass two-factor authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 02:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9952 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop Contact Information Page contact_info cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9952</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/?page=system_info/contact_info of the component Contact Information Page. The manipulation of the argument Address leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 02:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9546 | WPIDE &amp;lt;= 3.4.9 - Unauthenticated Full Path Dislcosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9546</link><description>The WPIDE – File Manager &amp; Code Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.9. This is due to the plugin utilizing the PHP-Parser library, which outputs parser rebuild command execution results. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 23:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9548 | Slimstat Analytics &amp;lt;= 5.2.6 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9548</link><description>The SlimStat Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the resource parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping when logging visitor requests. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 23:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30117 | HCL BigFix Platform is affected by a DLL Hijack vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30117</link><description>A dynamic search for a prerequisite library could allow the possibility for an attacker to replace the correct file under some circumstances.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 22:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9953 | A Potential DOS Vulnerability exists in CERT software prior to version 3.0.8</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9953</link><description>A Potential DOS Vulnerability exists in CERT VINCE software prior to version 3.0.8. An authenticated administrative user can inject an arbitrary pickle object as part of a user's profile. This can lead to a potential DoS on the server when the user's profile is accessed. Django server does restrict unpickling from crashing the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 21:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35518 | Netgear EX6120 v1.0.0.68 is vulnerable to Command Injection in genie_fix2.cgi via the wan_dns1_pri parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35518</link><description>Netgear EX6120 v1.0.0.68 is vulnerable to Command Injection in genie_fix2.cgi via the wan_dns1_pri parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 21:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35519 | Netgear EX6120 v1.0.0.68, Netgear EX6100 v1.0.2.28, and Netgear EX3700 v1.0.0.96 are vulnerable to command injection in operating_mode.cgi v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35519</link><description>Netgear EX6120 v1.0.0.68, Netgear EX6100 v1.0.2.28, and Netgear EX3700 v1.0.0.96 are vulnerable to command injection in operating_mode.cgi via the ap_mode parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 21:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35520 | Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136 is vulnerable to Command Injection in RMT_invite.cgi via device_name2 parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35520</link><description>Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136 is vulnerable to Command Injection in RMT_invite.cgi via device_name2 parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 21:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6207 | CVE 2021-22681 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1550.html  and send a specially crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6207</link><description>CVE 2021-22681 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1550.html  and send a specially crafted CIP message to the device.  If exploited, a threat actor could help prevent access to the legitimate user and end connections to connected devices including the workstation.  To recover the controllers, a download is required which ends any process that the controller is running.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 21:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48822 | Privilege escalation in Automatic Systems Maintenance SlimLane 29565_d74ecce0c1081d50546db573a499941b10799fb7 allows a remote attacker to es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48822</link><description>Privilege escalation in Automatic Systems Maintenance SlimLane 29565_d74ecce0c1081d50546db573a499941b10799fb7 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the FtpConfig.php page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 20:56:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48823 | Local file inclusion in Automatic Systems Maintenance SlimLane 29565_d74ecce0c1081d50546db573a499941b10799fb7 allows a remote attacker to es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48823</link><description>Local file inclusion in Automatic Systems Maintenance SlimLane 29565_d74ecce0c1081d50546db573a499941b10799fb7 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the PassageAutoServer.php page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 20:56:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48824 | An issue in Automatic Systems Maintenance SlimLane 29565_d74ecce0c1081d50546db573a499941b10799fb7 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensiti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48824</link><description>An issue in Automatic Systems Maintenance SlimLane 29565_d74ecce0c1081d50546db573a499941b10799fb7 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the Racine &amp; FileName parameters in the download-file.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 20:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48911 | OpenCanary Executes Commands From Potentially Writable Config File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48911</link><description>OpenCanary, a multi-protocol network honeypot, directly executed commands taken from its config file. Prior to version 0.9.4, where the config file is stored in an unprivileged user directory but the daemon is executed by root, it’s possible for the unprivileged user to change the config file and escalate permissions when root later runs the daemon. Version 0.9.4 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 20:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48821 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Automatic Systems Maintenance SlimLane 29565_d74ecce0c1081d50546db573a499941b10799fb7 allows a remote ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48821</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Automatic Systems Maintenance SlimLane 29565_d74ecce0c1081d50546db573a499941b10799fb7 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the FtpConfig.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 20:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48909 | SpiceDB calls to LookupResources using LookupResources2 with caveats may return context is missing when it is not</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48909</link><description>SpiceDB is an open source database for scalably storing and querying fine-grained authorization data. Starting in version 1.35.0 and prior to version 1.37.1, clients that have enabled `LookupResources2` and have caveats in the evaluation path for their requests can return a permissionship of `CONDITIONAL` with context marked as missing, even then the context was supplied. LookupResources2 is the new default in SpiceDB 1.37.0 and has been opt-in since SpiceDB 1.35.0. The bug is patched as part of SpiceDB 1.37.1. As a workaround, disable LookupResources2 via the `--enable-experimental-lookup-resources` flag by setting it to `false`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 20:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47885 | astro&amp;#x27;s client-side router has DOM Clobbering Gadget that leads to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47885</link><description>The Astro web framework has a DOM Clobbering gadget in the client-side router starting in version 3.0.0 and prior to version 4.16.1. It can lead to cross-site scripting (XSS) in websites enables Astro's client-side routing and has *stored* attacker-controlled scriptless HTML elements (i.e., `iframe` tags with unsanitized `name` attributes) on the destination pages. This vulnerability can result in cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks on websites that built with Astro that enable the client-side routing with `ViewTransitions` and store the user-inserted scriptless HTML tags without properly sanitizing the `name` attributes on the page. Version 4.16.1 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 19:18:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48082 | Nagios XI before 5.11.3 2024R1 was discovered to improperly handle API keys generation (randomly-generated), allowing attackers to possibly ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48082</link><description>Nagios XI before 5.11.3 2024R1 was discovered to improperly handle API keys generation (randomly-generated), allowing attackers to possibly generate the same set of API keys for all users and utilize them to authenticate.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 18:49:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46528 | An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in KubeSphere v3.4.1 and v4.1.1 allows low-privileged authenticated attackers to ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46528</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in KubeSphere v3.4.1 and v4.1.1 allows low-privileged authenticated attackers to access sensitive resources without proper authorization checks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 18:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47831 | Next.js image optimization has Denial of Service condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47831</link><description>Next.js is a React Framework for the Web. Cersions on the 10.x, 11.x, 12.x, 13.x, and 14.x branches before version 14.2.7 contain a vulnerability in the image optimization feature which allows for a potential Denial of Service (DoS) condition which could lead to excessive CPU consumption. Neither the `next.config.js` file that is configured with `images.unoptimized` set to `true` or `images.loader` set to a non-default value nor the Next.js application that is hosted on Vercel are affected. This issue was fully patched in Next.js `14.2.7`. As a workaround, ensure that the `next.config.js` file has either `images.unoptimized`, `images.loader` or `images.loaderFile` assigned.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 18:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47766 | Permissions are incorrectly verified for project administrators in the cross tracker search widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47766</link><description>Tuleap is a tool for end to end traceability of application and system developments. Prior to Tuleap Community Edition 15.13.99.110, Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.13-5, and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.12-5, administrators of a project can access the content of trackers with permissions restrictions of project they are members of but not admin via the cross tracker search widget. Tuleap Community Edition 15.13.99.110, Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.13-5, and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.12-8 fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 18:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47767 | Tuleap lists trackers in the quick add actions of the backlog without any permissions check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47767</link><description>Tuleap is a tool for end to end traceability of application and system developments. Prior to Tuleap Community Edition 15.13.99.113, Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.13-5, and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.12-5, users might see tracker names they should not have access to. Tuleap Community Edition 15.13.99.113, Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.13-5, and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.12-8 fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 18:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47826 | eLabFTW vulnerable to HTML Injection in extended search error message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47826</link><description>eLabFTW is an open source electronic lab notebook for research labs. A vulnerability in versions prior to 5.1.5 allows an attacker to inject arbitrary HTML tags in the pages: "experiments.php" (show mode), "database.php" (show mode) or "search.php". It works by providing HTML code in the extended search string, which will then be displayed back to the user in the error message. This means that injected HTML will appear in a red "alert/danger" box, and be part of an error message. Due to some other security measures, it is not possible to execute arbitrary javascript from this attack. As such, this attack is deemed low impact. Users should upgrade to at least version 5.1.5 to receive a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 18:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46988 | Tuleap does not properly check permissions for email notifications in trackers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46988</link><description>Tuleap is a tool for end to end traceability of application and system developments. Prior to Tuleap Community Edition 15.13.99.40, Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.13-3, and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.12-6, users might receive email notification with information they should not have access to. Tuleap Community Edition 15.13.99.40, Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.13-3, and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.12-6 fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 18:37:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46980 | Tuleap vulnerable to XSS in the HTML mail content of the cross reference field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46980</link><description>Tuleap is a tool for end to end traceability of application and system developments. Prior to Tuleap Community Edition 15.13.99.37, Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.13-3, and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.12-6, a site administrator could create an artifact link type with a forward label allowing them to execute uncontrolled code (or at least achieve content injection) in a mail client. Tuleap Community Edition 15.13.99.37, Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.13-3, and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.12-6 fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48789 | An issue in INATRONIC com.inatronic.drivedeck.home 2.6.23 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitve information via the firmware update pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48789</link><description>An issue in INATRONIC com.inatronic.drivedeck.home 2.6.23 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitve information via the firmware update process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48792 | An issue in Hideez com.hideez 2.7.8.3 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the firmware update process.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48792</link><description>An issue in Hideez com.hideez 2.7.8.3 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the firmware update process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48790 | An issue in ILIFE com.ilife.home.global 1.8.7 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the firmware update process.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48790</link><description>An issue in ILIFE com.ilife.home.global 1.8.7 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the firmware update process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48793 | An issue in INATRONIC com.inatronic.bmw 2.7.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the firmware update process.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48793</link><description>An issue in INATRONIC com.inatronic.bmw 2.7.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the firmware update process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48791 | An issue in Plug n Play Camera com.starvedia.mCamView.zwave 5.5.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the firmware ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48791</link><description>An issue in Plug n Play Camera com.starvedia.mCamView.zwave 5.5.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the firmware update process</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48795 | An issue in Creative Labs Pte Ltd com.creative.apps.xficonnect 2.00.02 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the firm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48795</link><description>An issue in Creative Labs Pte Ltd com.creative.apps.xficonnect 2.00.02 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the firmware update process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45732 | Low-privileged user could run search as nobody in SplunkDeploymentServerConfig app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45732</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.3.1, and 9.2.0 versions below 9.2.3, and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.2.2403.103, 9.1.2312.200, 9.1.2312.110 and 9.1.2308.208, a low-privileged user that does not hold the "admin" or "power" Splunk roles could run a search as the "nobody" Splunk user in the SplunkDeploymentServerConfig app. This could let the low-privileged user access potentially restricted data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45733 | Remote Code Execution (RCE) due to insecure session storage configuration in Splunk Enterprise on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45733</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise for Windows versions below 9.2.3 and 9.1.6, a low-privileged user that does not hold the "admin" or "power" Splunk roles could perform a Remote Code Execution (RCE) due to an insecure session storage configuration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45734 | Low Privilege User can View Images on the Host Machine by using the PDF Export feature in Splunk Classic Dashboard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45734</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions 9.3.0, 9.2.3, and 9.1.6, a low-privileged user that does not hold the "admin" or "power" Splunk roles could view images on the machine that runs Splunk Enterprise by using the PDF export feature in Splunk classic dashboards. The images on the  machine could be exposed by exporting the dashboard as a PDF, using the local image path in the img tag in the source extensible markup language (XML) code for the Splunk classic dashboard.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45736 | Improperly Formatted ‘INGEST_EVAL’ Parameter Crashes Splunk Daemon</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45736</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.3.1, 9.2.3, and 9.1.6 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.2.2403.107, 9.1.2312.204, and 9.1.2312.111, a low-privileged user that does not hold the "admin" or "power" Splunk roles could craft a search query with an improperly formatted  "INGEST_EVAL" parameter as part of a [Field Transformation](https://docs.splunk.com/Documentation/Splunk/latest/Knowledge/Managefieldtransforms) which could crash the Splunk daemon (splunkd).</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45737 | Maintenance mode state change of App Key Value Store (KVStore) through Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45737</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.3.1, 9.2.3, and 9.1.6 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.2.2403.108, and 9.1.2312.204, a low-privileged user that does not hold the "admin" or "power" Splunk roles could change the maintenance mode state of App Key Value Store (KVStore) through a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF).</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45738 | Sensitive information disclosure in REST_Calls logging channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45738</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.3.1, 9.2.3, and 9.1.6, the software potentially exposes sensitive HTTP parameters to the `_internal` index. This exposure could happen if you configure the Splunk Enterprise `REST_Calls` log channel at the DEBUG logging level.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45739 | Sensitive information disclosure in AdminManager logging channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45739</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.3.1, 9.2.3, and 9.1.6, the software potentially exposes plaintext passwords for local native authentication Splunk users. This exposure could happen when you configure the Splunk Enterprise AdminManager log channel at the DEBUG logging level.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45740 | Persistent Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) through Scheduled Views on Splunk Enterprise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45740</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.3 and 9.1.6 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.2.2403, a low-privileged user that does not hold the "admin" or "power" Splunk roles could craft a malicious payload through Scheduled Views that could result in execution of unauthorized JavaScript code in the browser of a user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45741 | Persistent Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via props.conf on Splunk Enterprise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45741</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.3 and 9.1.6 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 9.2.2403.108 and 9.1.2312.205, a low-privileged user that does not hold the "admin" or "power" Splunk roles could create a malicious payload through a custom configuration file that the "api.uri" parameter from the "/manager/search/apps/local" endpoint in Splunk Web calls. This could result in execution of unauthorized JavaScript code in the browser of a user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48799 | An issue in LOREX TECHNOLOGY INC com.lorexcorp.lorexping 1.4.22 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the firmware up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48799</link><description>An issue in LOREX TECHNOLOGY INC com.lorexcorp.lorexping 1.4.22 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the firmware update process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48796 | An issue in EQUES com.eques.plug 1.0.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the firmware update process.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48796</link><description>An issue in EQUES com.eques.plug 1.0.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the firmware update process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48797 | An issue in PCS Engineering Preston Cinema (com.prestoncinema.app) 0.2.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48797</link><description>An issue in PCS Engineering Preston Cinema (com.prestoncinema.app) 0.2.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the firmware update process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45731 | Potential Remote Command Execution (RCE) through arbitrary file write to Windows system root directory when Splunk Enterprise for Windows is installed on a separate disk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45731</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise for Windows versions below 9.3.1, 9.2.3, and 9.1.6, a low-privileged user that does not hold the "admin" or "power" Splunk roles could write a file to the Windows system root directory, which has a default location in the Windows System32 folder, when Splunk Enterprise for Windows is installed on a separate drive.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 16:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45735 | Improper Access Control for low-privileged user in Splunk Secure Gateway App</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45735</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.3 and 9.1.6, and Splunk Secure Gateway versions on Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 3.4.259, 3.6.17, and 3.7.0, a low-privileged user that does not hold the "admin" or "power" Splunk roles can see App Key Value Store (KV Store) deployment configuration and public/private keys in the Splunk Secure Gateway App.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 16:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46535 | Jepaas v7.2.8 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the orderSQL parameter at /homePortal/loadUserMsg.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46535</link><description>Jepaas v7.2.8 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the orderSQL parameter at /homePortal/loadUserMsg.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 16:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48168 | A stack overflow vulnerability exists in the sub_402280 function of the HNAP service of D-Link DCS-960L 1.09, allowing an attacker to execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48168</link><description>A stack overflow vulnerability exists in the sub_402280 function of the HNAP service of D-Link DCS-960L 1.09, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 16:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48798 | An issue in Hubble Connected (com.hubbleconnected.vervelife) 2.00.81 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the firmwa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48798</link><description>An issue in Hubble Connected (com.hubbleconnected.vervelife) 2.00.81 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the firmware update process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 16:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50780 | Apache ActiveMQ Artemis: Authenticated users could perform RCE via Jolokia MBeans</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50780</link><description>Apache ActiveMQ Artemis allows access to diagnostic information and controls through MBeans, which are also exposed through the authenticated Jolokia endpoint. Before version 2.29.0, this also included the Log4J2 MBean. This MBean is not meant for exposure to non-administrative users. This could eventually allow an authenticated attacker to write arbitrary files to the filesystem and indirectly achieve RCE.


Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.29.0 or later, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 16:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48150 | D-Link DIR-820L 1.05B03 has a stack overflow vulnerability in the sub_451208 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48150</link><description>D-Link DIR-820L 1.05B03 has a stack overflow vulnerability in the sub_451208 function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 16:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41997 | An issue was discovered in version of Warp Terminal prior to 2024.07.18 (v0.2024.07.16.08.02). A command injection vulnerability exists in t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41997</link><description>An issue was discovered in version of Warp Terminal prior to 2024.07.18 (v0.2024.07.16.08.02). A command injection vulnerability exists in the Docker integration functionality. An attacker can create a specially crafted hyperlink using the `warp://action/docker/open_subshell` intent that when clicked by the victim results in command execution on the victim's machine.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 16:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48153 | DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 allows attackers to inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48153</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 allows attackers to inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the get_subconfig function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 15:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6762 | Jetty  PushSessionCacheFilter can cause remote DoS attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6762</link><description>Jetty PushSessionCacheFilter can be exploited by unauthenticated users 
to launch remote DoS attacks by exhausting the server’s memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 15:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6763 | Jetty URI parsing of invalid authority</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6763</link><description>Summary
Eclipse Jetty is a lightweight, highly scalable, Java-based web server and Servlet engine . It includes a utility class, HttpURI, for URI/URL parsing.


The HttpURI class does insufficient validation on the authority segment of a URI.  However the behaviour of HttpURI
 differs from the common browsers in how it handles a URI that would be 
considered invalid if fully validated against the RRC.  Specifically HttpURI
 and the browser may differ on the value of the host extracted from an 
invalid URI and thus a combination of Jetty and a vulnerable browser may
 be vulnerable to a open redirect attack or to a SSRF attack if the URI 
is used after passing validation checks.


Details
Affected components
The vulnerable component is the HttpURI class when used as a utility class in an application.  The Jetty usage of the class is not vulnerable.


Attack overview
The HttpURI class does 
not well validate the authority section of a URI. When presented with an
 illegal authority that may contain user info (eg username:password# @hostname https://github.com/hostname :port),
 then the parsing of the URI is not failed.  Moreover, the 
interpretation of what part of the authority is the host name differs 
from a common browser in  that they also do not fail, but they select a 
different host name from the illegal URI.


Attack scenario
A typical attack scenario is illustrated in the diagram 
below. The Validator checks whether the attacker-supplied URL is on the 
blocklist. If not, the URI is passed to the Requester for redirection. 
The Requester is responsible for sending requests to the hostname 
specified by the URI.


This attack occurs when the Validator is the org.eclipse.jetty.http.HttpURI class and the Requester is the Browser (include chrome, firefox and Safari). An attacker can send a malformed URI to the Validator (e.g., http://browser.check%23%40vulndetector.com/
 ). After validation, the Validator finds that the hostname is not on 
the blocklist. However, the Requester can still send requests to the 
domain with the hostname vulndetector.com.



Impact
The impact of this vulnerability is limited to developers 
that use the Jetty HttpURI directly.  Example: your project implemented a
 blocklist to block on some hosts based on HttpURI's handling of 
authority section.  The vulnerability will help attackers bypass the 
protections that developers have set up for hosts. The vulnerability 
will lead to SSRF[1] and URL Redirection[2] vulnerabilities in several cases.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 15:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8184 | Jetty ThreadLimitHandler.getRemote() vulnerable to remote DoS attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8184</link><description>Impact
Remote DOS attack can cause out of memory


Description
There exists a security vulnerability in Jetty's ThreadLimitHandler.getRemote() which

can be exploited by unauthorized users to cause remote denial-of-service (DoS) attack.  By

repeatedly sending crafted requests, attackers can trigger OutofMemory errors and exhaust the

server's memory.


Affected Versions

  *  Jetty 12.0.0-12.0.8 (Supported)

  *  Jetty 11.0.0-11.0.23 (EOL)

  *  Jetty 10.0.0-10.0.23 (EOL)

  *  Jetty 9.3.12-9.4.55 (EOL)




Patched Versions

  *  Jetty 12.0.9

  *  Jetty 11.0.24

  *  Jetty 10.0.24

  *  Jetty 9.4.56</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 15:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9823 | Jetty DOS vulnerability on DosFilter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9823</link><description>Description
There exists a security vulnerability in Jetty's DosFilter which can be exploited by unauthorized

users to cause remote denial-of-service (DoS) attack on the server using DosFilter. By repeatedly sending crafted requests,

attackers can trigger OutofMemory errors and exhaust the server's memory finally.


Vulnerability details
The Jetty DoSFilter (Denial of Service Filter) is a security filter designed to protect web

applications against certain types of Denial of Service (DoS) attacks and other abusive behavior. It

helps to mitigate excessive resource consumption by limiting the rate at which clients can make

requests to the server.  The DoSFilter monitors and tracks client request patterns, including

request rates, and can take actions such as blocking or delaying requests from clients that exceed

predefined thresholds.  The internal tracking of requests in DoSFilter is the source of this OutOfMemory

condition.


Impact
Users of the DoSFilter may be subject to DoS attacks that 
will ultimately exhaust the memory of the server if they have not 
configured session passivation or an aggressive session inactivation 
timeout.


Patches
The DoSFilter has been patched in all active releases to no longer support the session tracking mode, even if configured.


Patched releases:



  *  9.4.54

  *  10.0.18

  *  11.0.18

  *  12.0.3</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 15:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48251 | Wavelog 1.8.5 allows Activated_gridmap_model.php get_band_confirmed SQL injection via band, sat, propagation, or mode.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48251</link><description>Wavelog 1.8.5 allows Activated_gridmap_model.php get_band_confirmed SQL injection via band, sat, propagation, or mode.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 14:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48257 | Wavelog 1.8.5 allows Oqrs_model.php get_worked_modes station_id SQL injectioin.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48257</link><description>Wavelog 1.8.5 allows Oqrs_model.php get_worked_modes station_id SQL injectioin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 14:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48249 | Wavelog 1.8.5 allows Gridmap_model.php get_band_confirmed SQL injection via band, sat, propagation, or mode.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48249</link><description>Wavelog 1.8.5 allows Gridmap_model.php get_band_confirmed SQL injection via band, sat, propagation, or mode.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 14:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48259 | Cloudlog 2.6.15 allows Oqrs.php request_form SQL injection via station_id or callsign.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48259</link><description>Cloudlog 2.6.15 allows Oqrs.php request_form SQL injection via station_id or callsign.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 14:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48255 | Cloudlog 2.6.15 allows Oqrs.php get_station_info station_id SQL injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48255</link><description>Cloudlog 2.6.15 allows Oqrs.php get_station_info station_id SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 14:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48253 | Cloudlog 2.6.15 allows Oqrs.php delete_oqrs_line id SQL injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48253</link><description>Cloudlog 2.6.15 allows Oqrs.php delete_oqrs_line id SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 14:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48119 | Vtiger CRM v8.2.0 has a HTML Injection vulnerability in the module parameter. Authenticated users can inject arbitrary HTML.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48119</link><description>Vtiger CRM v8.2.0 has a HTML Injection vulnerability in the module parameter. Authenticated users can inject arbitrary HTML.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 13:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48120 | X2CRM v8.5 is vulnerable to a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "Opportunities" module. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48120</link><description>X2CRM v8.5 is vulnerable to a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "Opportunities" module. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript code into the "Name" field when creating a list.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 13:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7847 | RSLogix™ 5 and RSLogix 500® Remote Code Execution Via VBA Embedded Script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7847</link><description>VULNERABILITY DETAILS

Rockwell Automation used the latest versions of the CVSS scoring system to assess the following vulnerabilities. The following vulnerabilities were reported to us by Sharon Brizinov of Claroty Research - Team82. 

A feature in the affected products enables users to prepare a project file with an embedded VBA script and can be configured to run once the project file has been opened without user intervention.  This feature can be abused to trick a legitimate user into executing malicious code upon opening an infected RSP/RSS project file. If exploited, a threat actor may be able to perform a remote code execution. Connected devices may also be impacted by exploitation of this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 13:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9936 | When manipulating the selection node cache, an attacker may have been able to cause unexpected behavior, potentially leading to an exploitab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9936</link><description>When manipulating the selection node cache, an attacker may have been able to cause unexpected behavior, potentially leading to an exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 131.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 13:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8602 | XML Eternal Entity Attack in the Software Library taxstatement.jar</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8602</link><description>When the XML is read from the codes in the PDF and parsed using a DocumentBuilder, the default settings of the DocumentBuilder allow for an XXE (XML External Entity) attack. Further information on this can be found on the website of the Open Worldwide Application Security Project (OWASP). An attacker could theoretically leverage this by delivering a manipulated PDF file to the target, and depending on the environment, various actions can be executed. These actions include:

  *  Reading files from the operating system
  *  Crashing the thread handling the parsing or causing it to enter an infinite loop
  *  Executing HTTP requests
  *  Loading additional DTDs or XML files
  *  Under certain conditions, executing OS commands</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9139 | OS Command Injection in Restricted Command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9139</link><description>The affected product permits OS command injection through improperly restricted commands, potentially allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 08:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43701 | GPU DDK - PowerVR: TLB invalidate UAF of dma_buf imported into multiple GPU devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43701</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct GPU system calls to read and write freed physical memory from the GPU.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 08:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46911 | Apache Roller: Weakness in CSRF protection allows privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46911</link><description>Cross-site Resource Forgery (CSRF), Privilege escalation vulnerability in Apache Roller. On multi-blog/user Roller websites, by default weblog owners are trusted to publish arbitrary weblog content and this combined with a deficiency in Roller's CSRF protections allowed an escalation of privileges attack. This issue affects Apache Roller before 6.1.4.

Roller users who run multi-blog/user Roller websites are recommended to upgrade to version 6.1.4, which fixes the issue.

Roller 6.1.4 release announcement:  https://lists.apache.org/thread/3c3f6rwqptyw6wdc95654fq5vlosqdpw</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 08:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9137 | Moxa Service Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9137</link><description>The affected product lacks an authentication check when sending commands to the server via the Moxa service. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute specified commands, potentially leading to unauthorized downloads or uploads of configuration files and system compromise.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 08:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38862 | SNMP and IMPI secrets written to audit log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38862</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File in Checkmk GmbH's Checkmk versions &lt;2.3.0p18, &lt;2.2.0p35, &lt;2.1.0p48 and &lt;=2.0.0p39 (EOL) causes SNMP and IMPI secrets of host and folder properties to be written to audit log files accessible to administrators.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 07:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38863 | CSRF token leaked in URL parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38863</link><description>Exposure of CSRF tokens in query parameters on specific requests in Checkmk GmbH's Checkmk versions &lt;2.3.0p18, &lt;2.2.0p35 and &lt;2.1.0p48 could lead to a leak of the token to facilitate targeted phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 07:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49214 | QUIC in HAProxy 3.1.x before 3.1-dev7, 3.0.x before 3.0.5, and 2.9.x before 2.9.11 allows opening a 0-RTT session with a spoofed IP address....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49214</link><description>QUIC in HAProxy 3.1.x before 3.1-dev7, 3.0.x before 3.0.5, and 2.9.x before 2.9.11 allows opening a 0-RTT session with a spoofed IP address. This can bypass the IP allow/block list functionality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 03:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9924 | Hgiga OAKlouds - Arbitrary File Read And Delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9924</link><description>The fix for CVE-2024-26261 was incomplete, and and the specific package for OAKlouds from Hgiga remains at risk. Unauthenticated remote attackers still can download arbitrary system files, which may be deleted subsequently .</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 03:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9923 | TEAMPLUS TECHNOLOGY Team+ - Arbitrary File Move through Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9923</link><description>The Team+ from TEAMPLUS TECHNOLOGY does not properly validate a specific page parameter, allowing remote attackers with administrator privileges to move arbitrary system files to the website root directory and access them.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 03:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9921 | TEAMPLUS TECHNOLOGY Team+ - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9921</link><description>The Team+ from TEAMPLUS TECHNOLOGY does not properly validate specific page parameter, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 03:03:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9922 | TEAMPLUS TECHNOLOGY Team+ - Arbitrary File Read through Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9922</link><description>The Team+ from TEAMPLUS TECHNOLOGY does not properly validate a specific page parameter, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit this vulnerability to read arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 03:03:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7099 | SQL Injection in netease-youdao/qanything</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7099</link><description>netease-youdao/qanything version 1.4.1 contains a vulnerability where unsafe data obtained from user input is concatenated in SQL queries, leading to SQL injection. The affected functions include `get_knowledge_base_name`, `from_status_to_status`, `delete_files`, and `get_file_by_status`. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary SQL queries, potentially stealing information from the database. The issue is fixed in version 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 21:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9918 | HuangDou UTCMS sql.php RunSql sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9918</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in HuangDou UTCMS V9 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function RunSql of the file app/modules/ut-data/admin/sql.php. The manipulation of the argument sql leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 20:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8070 | CWE-312: Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability exists that exposes test
credentials in the firmware binary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8070</link><description>CWE-312: Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability exists that exposes test
credentials in the firmware binary</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 20:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9917 | HuangDou UTCMS template_creat.php deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9917</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in HuangDou UTCMS V9. This affects an unknown part of the file app/modules/ut-template/admin/template_creat.php. The manipulation of the argument content leads to deserialization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 19:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9916 | HuangDou UTCMS cli.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9916</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in HuangDou UTCMS V9. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file app/modules/ut-cac/admin/cli.php. The manipulation of the argument o leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 19:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9915 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formVirtualServ buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9915</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formVirtualServ of the file /goform/formVirtualServ. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 18:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9914 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formSetWizardSelectMode buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9914</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06. Affected is the function formSetWizardSelectMode of the file /goform/formSetWizardSelectMode. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 18:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9913 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formSetRoute buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9913</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function formSetRoute of the file /goform/formSetRoute. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9912 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formSetQoS buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9912</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formSetQoS of the file /goform/formSetQoS. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 16:46:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9911 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formSetPortTr buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9911</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function formSetPortTr of the file /goform/formSetPortTr. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 16:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9910 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formSetPassword buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9910</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formSetPassword of the file /goform/formSetPassword. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 14:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9909 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formSetMuti buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9909</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetMuti of the file /goform/formSetMuti. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 14:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6959 | Denial of Service (DOS) in multipart boundary while uploading file in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6959</link><description>A vulnerability in parisneo/lollms-webui version 9.8 allows for a Denial of Service (DOS) attack when uploading an audio file. If an attacker appends a large number of characters to the end of a multipart boundary, the system will continuously process each character, rendering lollms-webui inaccessible. This issue is exacerbated by the lack of Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) protection, enabling remote exploitation. The vulnerability leads to service disruption, resource exhaustion, and extended downtime.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 12:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9908 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formSetMACFilter buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9908</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06. Affected is the function formSetMACFilter of the file /goform/formSetMACFilter. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 12:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9907 | QileCMS Verification Code Forget.php sendEmail password recovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9907</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in QileCMS up to 1.1.3. This vulnerability affects the function sendEmail of the file /qilecms/user/controller/Forget.php of the component Verification Code Handler. The manipulation leads to weak password recovery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 04:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9906 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9906</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/?page=inventory/view_inventory&amp;amp;id=2. The manipulation of the argument Code leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 04:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9905 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9905</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/?page=inventory/view_inventory&amp;amp;id=2. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 02:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9904 | 07FLYCMS/07FLY-CMS/07FlyCRM pictureUpload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9904</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in 07FLYCMS, 07FLY-CMS and 07FlyCRM up to 1.2.0. This vulnerability affects the function pictureUpload of the file /admin/File/pictureUpload. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The affected product is known with different names like 07FLYCMS, 07FLY-CMS, and 07FlyCRM. It was not possible to reach out to the vendor before assigning a CVE due to a not working mail address.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 01:56:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>