<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 05:39:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-31397 | Improper handling of extra values issue exists in Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 5.15.2. If this vulnerability is exploited, a user who can log in t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31397</link><description>Improper handling of extra values issue exists in Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 5.15.2. If this vulnerability is exploited, a user who can log in to the product with the administrative privilege may be able to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 05:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31399 | Excessive platform resource consumption within a loop issue exists in Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 5.15.2. If this vulnerability is exploited, pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31399</link><description>Excessive platform resource consumption within a loop issue exists in Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 5.15.2. If this vulnerability is exploited, processing a crafted mail may cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 05:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3723 | Advanced Contact form 7 DB &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3723</link><description>The Advanced Contact form 7 DB plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.2 via the wp-content/uploads/advanced-cf7-upload directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data uploaded via this plugin through a form.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 05:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4319 | Advanced Contact form 7 DB &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4319</link><description>The Advanced Contact form 7 DB plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'vsz_cf7_export_to_excel' function in versions up to, and including, 2.0.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download the entry data for submitted forms.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 05:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31398 | Insertion of sensitive information into sent data issue exists in Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 5.15.2. If this vulnerability is exploited, a user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31398</link><description>Insertion of sensitive information into sent data issue exists in Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 5.15.2. If this vulnerability is exploited, a user who can log in to the product may obtain information on the list of users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 05:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31402 | Incorrect authorization vulnerability in Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 5.15.2 allows a remote authenticated attacker to delete the data of Shared T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31402</link><description>Incorrect authorization vulnerability in Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 5.15.2 allows a remote authenticated attacker to delete the data of Shared To-Dos.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 05:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31400 | Insertion of sensitive information into sent data issue exists in Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 5.15.0. If this vulnerability is exploited, uninten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31400</link><description>Insertion of sensitive information into sent data issue exists in Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 5.15.0. If this vulnerability is exploited, unintended data may be left in forwarded mail.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 04:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31401 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability in Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 5.15.2 allows a remote authenticated attacker with an administrative privilege ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31401</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability in Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 5.15.2 allows a remote authenticated attacker with an administrative privilege to inject an arbitrary script on the web browser of the user who is logging in to the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 04:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31403 | Incorrect authorization vulnerability in Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 6.0.0 allows a remote authenticated attacker to alter and/or obtain the data...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31403</link><description>Incorrect authorization vulnerability in Cybozu Garoon 5.0.0 to 6.0.0 allows a remote authenticated attacker to alter and/or obtain the data of Memo.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 04:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31404 | Insertion of sensitive information into sent data issue exists in Cybozu Garoon 5.5.0 to 6.0.0, which may allow a user who can log in to the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31404</link><description>Insertion of sensitive information into sent data issue exists in Cybozu Garoon 5.5.0 to 6.0.0, which may allow a user who can log in to the product to view the data of Scheduler.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 04:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35329 | libyaml 0.2.5 is vulnerable to a heap-based Buffer Overflow in yaml_document_add_sequence in api.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35329</link><description>libyaml 0.2.5 is vulnerable to a heap-based Buffer Overflow in yaml_document_add_sequence in api.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 04:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5530 | ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp;amp; Gutenberg +12 Modules – All in One Solution (formerly WooLentor) &amp;lt;= 2.9.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via WL Product Horizontal Filter Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5530</link><description>The ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg +12 Modules – All in One Solution (formerly WooLentor) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's WL: Product Horizontal Filter widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 04:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36360 | OS command injection vulnerability exists in awkblog v0.0.1 (commit hash:7b761b192d0e0dc3eef0f30630e00ece01c8d552) and earlier. If a remote ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36360</link><description>OS command injection vulnerability exists in awkblog v0.0.1 (commit hash:7b761b192d0e0dc3eef0f30630e00ece01c8d552) and earlier. If a remote unauthenticated attacker sends a specially crafted HTTP request, an arbitrary OS command may be executed with the privileges of the affected product on the machine running the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 04:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29855 | Hard-coded JWT secret allows authentication bypass in Veeam Recovery Orchestrator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29855</link><description>Hard-coded JWT secret allows authentication bypass in Veeam Recovery Orchestrator</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 04:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7264 | Build App Online &amp;lt;= 1.0.21 - Account Takeover via Weak Password Reset Mechanism</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7264</link><description>The Build App Online plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to account takeover due to a weak password reset mechanism in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.21. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the password of arbitrary users by guessing an 4-digit numeric reset code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 03:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6745 | Custom Field Template &amp;lt;= 2.6.1 - Authenticated(Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6745</link><description>The Custom Field Template plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'cpt' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied post meta. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6748 | Custom Field Template &amp;lt;= 2.6.1 - Authenticated(Contributor+) Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6748</link><description>The Custom Field Template plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.1 via the 'cft' shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor access and above, to extract sensitive data including arbitrary post metadata.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0627 | Custom Field Template &amp;lt;= 2.6.1 - Authenticated(Constibutor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom Field Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0627</link><description>The Custom Field Template plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's custom field name column in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied custom fields. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0653 | Custom Field Template &amp;lt;= 2.6.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scritping</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0653</link><description>The Custom Field Template plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28164 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver AS Java (Guided Procedures)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28164</link><description>SAP NetWeaver AS Java (CAF - Guided Procedures)
allows an unauthenticated user to access non-sensitive information about the
server which would otherwise be restricted causing low impact on
confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2473 | WPS Hide Login &amp;lt;= 1.9.15.2 - Login Page Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2473</link><description>The WPS Hide Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Login Page Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.15.2. This is due to a bypass that is created when the 'action=postpass' parameter is supplied. This makes it possible for attackers to easily discover any login page that may have been hidden by the plugin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33001 | Denial of service (DOS) in SAP NetWeaver and ABAP platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33001</link><description>SAP NetWeaver and ABAP platform allows an
attacker to impede performance for legitimate users by crashing or flooding the
service.



An
impact of this Denial of Service vulnerability might be long response delays
and service interruptions, thus degrading the service quality experienced by
legitimate users causing high impact on availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34683 | Unrestricted file upload in SAP Document Builder (HTTP service)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34683</link><description>An authenticated attacker can upload malicious
file to SAP Document Builder service. When the victim accesses this file, the
attacker is allowed to access, modify, or make the related information
unavailable in the victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34684 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Scheduling)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34684</link><description>On Unix, SAP BusinessObjects Business
Intelligence Platform (Scheduling) allows an authenticated attacker with
administrator access on the local server to access the password of a local
account. As a result, an attacker can obtain non-administrative user
credentials, which will allow them to read or modify the remote server files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34686 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP CRM (WebClient UI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34686</link><description>Due to insufficient input validation, SAP CRM
WebClient UI allows an unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL link which
embeds a malicious script. When a victim clicks on this link, the script will
be executed in the victim's browser giving the attacker the ability to access
and/or modify information with no effect on availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34688 | Denial of service (DOS) in SAP NetWeaver AS Java (Meta Model Repository)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34688</link><description>Due to unrestricted access to the Meta Model
Repository services in SAP NetWeaver AS Java, attackers can perform DoS attacks
on the application, which may prevent legitimate users from accessing it. This
can result in no impact on confidentiality and integrity but a high impact on
the availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34690 | Missing Authorization check in SAP Student Life Cycle Management (SLcM)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34690</link><description>SAP Student Life Cycle
Management (SLcM) fails to conduct proper authorization checks for
authenticated users, leading to the potential escalation of privileges. On
successful exploitation it could allow an attacker to access and edit
non-sensitive report variants that are typically restricted, causing minimal
impact on the confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34691 | Missing Authorization check in SAP S/4HANA (Manage Incoming Payment Files)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34691</link><description>Manage Incoming Payment Files (F1680) of SAP
S/4HANA does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated
user, resulting in escalation of privileges. As a result, it has high impact on
integrity and no impact on the confidentiality and availability of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37176 | Missing Authorization check in SAP BW/4HANA Transformation and DTP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37176</link><description>SAP BW/4HANA Transformation and Data Transfer
Process (DTP) allows an authenticated attacker to gain higher access levels
than they should have by exploiting improper authorization checks. This results
in escalation of privileges. It has no impact on the confidentiality of data
but may have low impacts on the integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5090 | SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle &amp;lt;= 1.61.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SiteOrigin Blog Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5090</link><description>The SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's SiteOrigin Blog Widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.61.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37177 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in SAP Financial Consolidation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37177</link><description>SAP Financial Consolidation allows data to enter
a Web application through an untrusted source. These endpoints are exposed over
the network and it allows the user to modify the content from the web site. On
successful exploitation, an attacker can cause significant impact to
confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:05:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37178 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in SAP Financial Consolidation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37178</link><description>SAP Financial Consolidation does not
sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting
(XSS) vulnerability. These endpoints are exposed over the network. The
vulnerability can exploit resources beyond the vulnerable component. On
successful exploitation, an attacker can cause limited impact to
confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:05:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37130 | Dell OpenManage Server Administrator, versions 11.0.1.0 and prior, contains a Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability via XSL Hijacking. A ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37130</link><description>Dell OpenManage Server Administrator, versions 11.0.1.0 and prior, contains a Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability via XSL Hijacking. A local low-privileged malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability and escalate their privilege to the admin user and gain full control of the machine. Exploitation may lead to a complete system compromise.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:05:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22261 | SQL Injection in Harbor scan log API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22261</link><description>SQL-Injection in Harbor allows priviledge users to leak the task IDs</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 23:36:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22244 | Harbor Open Redirect URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22244</link><description>Open Redirect in Harbor  &lt;=v2.8.4, &lt;=v2.9.2, and &lt;=v2.10.0 may redirect a user to a malicious site.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 23:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-37019 | HP PC BIOS May 2024 Security Updates for Potential Stack Buffer Overflows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-37019</link><description>Potential vulnerabilities have been identified in the system BIOS for certain HP PC products which may allow escalation of privileges and code execution.  HP is releasing firmware updates to mitigate the potential vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 22:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-37020 | HP PC BIOS May 2024 Security Updates for Potential Stack Buffer Overflows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-37020</link><description>Potential vulnerabilities have been identified in the system BIOS for certain HP PC products, which might allow escalation of privileges and code execution. HP is releasing firmware updates to mitigate the potential vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 22:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36471 | Apache Allura: sensitive information exposure via DNS rebinding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36471</link><description>Import functionality is vulnerable to DNS rebinding attacks between verification and processing of the URL.  Project administrators can run these imports, which could cause Allura to read from internal services and expose them.

This issue affects Apache Allura from 1.0.1 through 1.16.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.17.0, which fixes the issue.  If you are unable to upgrade, set "disable_entry_points.allura.importers = forge-tracker, forge-discussion" in your .ini config file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 22:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37168 | @grpc/grpc-js can allocate memory for incoming messages well above configured limits</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37168</link><description>@grpc/grps-js implements the core functionality of gRPC purely in JavaScript, without a C++ addon. Prior to versions 1.10.9, 1.9.15, and 1.8.22, there are two separate code paths in which memory can be allocated per message in excess of the `grpc.max_receive_message_length` channel option: If an incoming message has a size on the wire greater than the configured limit, the entire message is buffered before it is discarded; and/or if an incoming message has a size within the limit on the wire but decompresses to a size greater than the limit, the entire message is decompressed into memory, and on the server is not discarded. This has been patched in versions 1.10.9, 1.9.15, and 1.8.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37169 | @jmondi/url-to-png arbitrary file read via Playwright&amp;#x27;s screenshot feature exploiting file wrapper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37169</link><description>@jmondi/url-to-png is a self-hosted URL to PNG utility. Versions prior to 2.0.3 are vulnerable to arbitrary file read if a threat actor uses the Playright's screenshot feature to exploit the file wrapper. Version 2.0.3 mitigates this issue by requiring input URLs to be of protocol `http` or `https`. No known workarounds are available aside from upgrading.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35242 | Composer vulnerable to command injection via malicious git/hg branch names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35242</link><description>Composer is a dependency manager for PHP. On the 2.x branch prior to versions 2.2.24 and 2.7.7, the `composer install` command running inside a git/hg repository which has specially crafted branch names can lead to command injection. This requires cloning untrusted repositories. Patches are available in version 2.2.24 for 2.2 LTS or 2.7.7 for mainline. As a workaround, avoid cloning potentially compromised repositories.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37166 | ghtml Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37166</link><description>ghtml is software that uses tagged templates for template engine functionality. It is possible to introduce user-controlled JavaScript code and trigger a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in some cases. Version 2.0.0 introduces changes to mitigate this issue. Version 2.0.0 contains updated documentation to clarify that while ghtml escapes characters with special meaning in HTML, it does not provide comprehensive protection against all types of XSS attacks in every scenario. This aligns with the approach taken by other template engines. Developers should be cautious and take additional measures to sanitize user input and prevent potential vulnerabilities. Additionally, the backtick character (`) is now also escaped to prevent the creation of strings in most cases where a malicious actor somehow gains the ability to write JavaScript. This does not provide comprehensive protection either.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32849 | Trend Micro Security 17.x (Consumer) is vulnerable to a Privilege Escalation vulnerability that could allow a local attacker to unintentiona...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32849</link><description>Trend Micro Security 17.x (Consumer) is vulnerable to a Privilege Escalation vulnerability that could allow a local attacker to unintentionally delete privileged Trend Micro files including its own.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35241 | Composer vulnerable to command injection via malicious git branch name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35241</link><description>Composer is a dependency manager for PHP. On the 2.x branch prior to versions 2.2.24 and 2.7.7, the `status`, `reinstall` and `remove` commands with packages installed from source via git containing specially crafted branch names in the repository can be used to execute code. Patches for this issue are available in version 2.2.24 for 2.2 LTS or 2.7.7 for mainline. As a workaround, avoid installing dependencies via git by using `--prefer-dist` or the `preferred-install: dist` config setting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36302 | An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affecte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36302</link><description>An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to, CVE-2024-36303.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36303 | An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affecte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36303</link><description>An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to, CVE-2024-36302.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36304 | A Time-of-Check Time-Of-Use vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service agent could allow a local attacker to escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36304</link><description>A Time-of-Check Time-Of-Use vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36305 | A security agent link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected instal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36305</link><description>A security agent link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36306 | A link following vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service Damage Cleanup Engine could allow a local attacker to c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36306</link><description>A link following vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service Damage Cleanup Engine could allow a local attacker to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36307 | A security agent link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service could allow a local attacker to disclose sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36307</link><description>A security agent link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service could allow a local attacker to disclose sensitive information about the agent on affected installations.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36358 | A link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security 20.x agents below build 20.0.1-3180 could allow a local attacker to escalate pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36358</link><description>A link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security 20.x agents below build 20.0.1-3180 could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36359 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance (IWSVA) 6.5 could allow an attacker to es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36359</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance (IWSVA) 6.5 could allow an attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:29:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36419 | SuiteCRM-Core Host Header Injection in /legacy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36419</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. A vulnerability in versions prior to 8.6.1 allows for Host Header Injection when directly accessing the `/legacy` route. Version 8.6.1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:29:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36473 | Trend Micro VPN Proxy One Pro, version 5.8.1012 and below is vulnerable to an arbitrary file overwrite or create attack but is limited to lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36473</link><description>Trend Micro VPN Proxy One Pro, version 5.8.1012 and below is vulnerable to an arbitrary file overwrite or create attack but is limited to local Denial of Service (DoS) and under specific conditions can lead to elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:29:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37289 | An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37289</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33850 | Pexip Infinity before 34.1 has Improper Access Control for persons in a waiting room. They can see the conference roster list, and perform c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33850</link><description>Pexip Infinity before 34.1 has Improper Access Control for persons in a waiting room. They can see the conference roster list, and perform certain actions that should not be allowed before they are admitted to the meeting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23251 | An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.5, watchOS 10.5, iOS 17.5 and i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23251</link><description>An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.5, watchOS 10.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8. An attacker with physical access may be able to leak Mail account credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23282 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.5, watchOS 10.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, iOS 16.7.8 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23282</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.5, watchOS 10.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8. A maliciously crafted email may be able to initiate FaceTime calls without user authorization.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27799 | This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.5, macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Monterey ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27799</link><description>This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.5, macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Monterey 12.7.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8. An unprivileged app may be able to log keystrokes in other apps including those using secure input mode.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27800 | This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Monterey 12.7.5, iOS 16.7.8 and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27800</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Monterey 12.7.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8, tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, watchOS 10.5, macOS Sonoma 14.5. Processing a maliciously crafted message may lead to a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27801 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, watchOS 10.5, macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27801</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, watchOS 10.5, macOS Sonoma 14.5. An app may be able to elevate privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27802 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Monterey 12.7.5, iOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27802</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Monterey 12.7.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8, tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, macOS Sonoma 14.5. Processing a maliciously crafted file may lead to unexpected app termination or arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27805 | An issue was addressed with improved validation of environment variables. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Monterey 12.7.5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27805</link><description>An issue was addressed with improved validation of environment variables. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Monterey 12.7.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8, tvOS 17.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, watchOS 10.5, macOS Sonoma 14.5. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27806 | This issue was addressed with improved environment sanitization. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Monterey 12.7.5, iOS 16....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27806</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved environment sanitization. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Monterey 12.7.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8, tvOS 17.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, watchOS 10.5, macOS Sonoma 14.5. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27807 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8. An app may be a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27807</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8. An app may be able to circumvent App Privacy Report logging.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27808 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, Safari 17.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27808</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, Safari 17.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, watchOS 10.5, macOS Sonoma 14.5. Processing web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27811 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, watchOS 10.5, macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27811</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, watchOS 10.5, macOS Sonoma 14.5. An app may be able to elevate privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27812 | The issue was addressed with improvements to the file handling protocol. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.2. Processing web content may lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27812</link><description>The issue was addressed with improvements to the file handling protocol. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.2. Processing web content may lead to a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27814 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.5. A person with physical access to a device m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27814</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.5. A person with physical access to a device may be able to view contact information from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27815 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, iOS 17.5 and iPad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27815</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, watchOS 10.5, macOS Sonoma 14.5. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27817 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Monterey 12.7.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27817</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Monterey 12.7.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8, tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, macOS Sonoma 14.5. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27819 | The issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5. An attacker with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27819</link><description>The issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5. An attacker with physical access may be able to access contacts from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27820 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8, visionOS 1.2, Safari ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27820</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8, visionOS 1.2, Safari 17.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, watchOS 10.5, macOS Sonoma 14.5. Processing web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27828 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.2, watchOS 10.5, tvOS 17.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27828</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.2, watchOS 10.5, tvOS 17.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27830 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, Safari 17.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27830</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, Safari 17.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, watchOS 10.5, macOS Sonoma 14.5. A maliciously crafted webpage may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27831 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Monterey 12.7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27831</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Monterey 12.7.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8, tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, macOS Sonoma 14.5. Processing a file may lead to unexpected app termination or arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27832 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, watchOS 10.5, macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27832</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, watchOS 10.5, macOS Sonoma 14.5. An app may be able to elevate privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27833 | An integer overflow was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8, visionOS 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27833</link><description>An integer overflow was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8, visionOS 1.2, Safari 17.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27836 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.2, macOS Sonoma 14.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5. Processing a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27836</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.2, macOS Sonoma 14.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27838 | The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8, visionOS 1.2, Safari 17....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27838</link><description>The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8, visionOS 1.2, Safari 17.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, watchOS 10.5, macOS Sonoma 14.5. A maliciously crafted webpage may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27840 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Monterey 12.7.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27840</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Monterey 12.7.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8, tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, watchOS 10.5. An attacker that has already achieved kernel code execution may be able to bypass kernel memory protections.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27844 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.2, macOS Sonoma 14.5, Safari 17.5. A website's permission di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27844</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.2, macOS Sonoma 14.5, Safari 17.5. A website's permission dialog may persist after navigation away from the site.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27845 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5. An app may be able...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27845</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5. An app may be able to access Notes attachments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27848 | This issue was addressed with improved permissions checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5. A malicious...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27848</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved permissions checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5. A malicious app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27850 | This issue was addressed with improvements to the noise injection algorithm. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.2, macOS Sonoma 14.5, Safari ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27850</link><description>This issue was addressed with improvements to the noise injection algorithm. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.2, macOS Sonoma 14.5, Safari 17.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5. A maliciously crafted webpage may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27851 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, Safari 17.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27851</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.5, visionOS 1.2, Safari 17.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, watchOS 10.5, macOS Sonoma 14.5. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27855 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.5, macOS Ventura 13.6.7, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, iOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27855</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.5, macOS Ventura 13.6.7, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, iOS 16.7.8 and iPadOS 16.7.8. A shortcut may be able to use sensitive data with certain actions without prompting the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27857 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.2, macOS Sonoma 14.5, tvOS 17.5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27857</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.2, macOS Sonoma 14.5, tvOS 17.5, iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5. A remote attacker may be able to cause unexpected app termination or arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27885 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.5, macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Montere...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27885</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.5, macOS Ventura 13.6.7, macOS Monterey 12.7.5. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36418 | SuiteCRM authenticated RCE using connectors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36418</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Prior to versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1, a vulnerability in connectors allows an authenticated user to perform a remote code execution attack. Versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 20:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36416 | SuiteCRM v4 API Excessive log data DOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36416</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Prior to versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1, a deprecated v4 API example with no log rotation allows denial of service by logging excessive data. Versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 20:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36417 | SuiteCRM Stored XSS Vulnerability Allows Code Execution via Malicious iFrame</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36417</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Prior to versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1, an unverified IFrame can be added some some inputs, which could allow for a cross-site scripting attack. Versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 20:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37393 | Multiple LDAP injections vulnerabilities exist in SecurEnvoy MFA before 9.4.514 due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An unauth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37393</link><description>Multiple LDAP injections vulnerabilities exist in SecurEnvoy MFA before 9.4.514 due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An unauthenticated remote attacker could exfiltrate data from Active Directory through blind LDAP injection attacks against the DESKTOP service exposed on the /secserver HTTP endpoint. This may include ms-Mcs-AdmPwd, which has a cleartext password for the Local Administrator Password Solution (LAPS) feature.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 20:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22279 | GoRouter Denial of Service Attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22279</link><description>Improper handling of requests in Routing Release &gt; v0.273.0 and &lt;= v0.297.0 allows an unauthenticated attacker to degrade
 the service availability of the Cloud Foundry deployment if performed at scale.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36415 | SuiteCRM Improper Control of Filename for Include Statement in PHP and Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous content leads to authenticated remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36415</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Prior to versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1, a vulnerability in uploaded file verification in products allows for remote code execution. Versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36413 | SuiteCRM authenticated Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36413</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Prior to versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1, a vulnerability in the import module error view allows for a cross-site scripting attack. Versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36414 | SuiteCRM authenticated Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36414</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Prior to versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1, a vulnerability in the connectors file verification allows for a server-side request forgery attack. Versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32167 | Sourcecodester Online Medicine Ordering System 1.0 is vulnerable to Arbitrary file deletion vulnerability as the backend settings have the f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32167</link><description>Sourcecodester Online Medicine Ordering System 1.0 is vulnerable to Arbitrary file deletion vulnerability as the backend settings have the function of deleting pictures to delete any files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36411 | SuiteCRM authenticated SQL Injection in EmailUIAjax displayView controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36411</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. In versions prior to 7.14.4 and 8.6.1, poor input validation allows for SQL Injection in EmailUIAjax displayView controller. Versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36412 | SuiteCRM unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36412</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Prior to versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1, a vulnerability in events response entry point allows for a SQL injection attack. Versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37014 | Langflow through 0.6.19 allows remote code execution if untrusted users are able to reach the "POST /api/v1/custom_component" endpoint and p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37014</link><description>Langflow through 0.6.19 allows remote code execution if untrusted users are able to reach the "POST /api/v1/custom_component" endpoint and provide a Python script.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32897 | A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.5. Processing a maliciously craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32897</link><description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.5. Processing a maliciously crafted tiff file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32933 | An information disclosure issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.5. A website may be ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32933</link><description>An information disclosure issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.5. A website may be able to track the websites a user visited in Safari private browsing mode.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48578 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.5. Processing an AppleScript may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48578</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.5. Processing an AppleScript may result in unexpected termination or disclosure of process memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48683 | An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13. An app may be able to break out...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48683</link><description>An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40389 | The issue was addressed with improved restriction of data container access. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Monterey 12.7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40389</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved restriction of data container access. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Monterey 12.7.4. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23299 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Monterey 12.7.4. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23299</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4, macOS Ventura 13.6.5, macOS Monterey 12.7.4. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27792 | This issue was addressed by adding an additional prompt for user consent. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27792</link><description>This issue was addressed by adding an additional prompt for user consent. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.4. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31612 | Emlog pro2.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via twitter.php which can be used with a XSS vulnerability to access adminis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31612</link><description>Emlog pro2.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via twitter.php which can be used with a XSS vulnerability to access administrator information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 18:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36409 | SuiteCRM authenticated SQL Injection in TreeData entrypoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36409</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. In versions prior to 7.14.4 and 8.6.1, poor input validation allows for SQL Injection in Tree data entry point. Versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 17:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36410 | SuiteCRM authenticated SQL Injection in EmailUIAjax messages count controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36410</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. In versions prior to 7.14.4 and 8.6.1, poor input validation allows for SQL Injection in EmailUIAjax messages count controller. Versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 17:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5597 | Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT Type Confusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5597</link><description>Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT is vulnerable to a type confusion, which could cause a crash or code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 17:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36408 | SuiteCRM authenticated SQL Injection in Alerts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36408</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. In versions prior to 7.14.4 and 8.6.1, poor input validation allows for SQL Injection in the `Alerts` controller. Versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3850 | Uniview NVR301-04S2-P4 Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3850</link><description>Uniview NVR301-04S2-P4 is vulnerable to reflected cross-site scripting attack (XSS). An attacker could send a user a URL that if clicked on could execute malicious JavaScript in their browser. This vulnerability also requires authentication before it can be exploited, so the scope and severity is limited. Also, even if JavaScript is executed, no additional benefits are obtained.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35745 | WordPress Strategery Migrations plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35745</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Gabriel Somoza / Joseph Fitzgibbons Strategery Migrations allows Path Traversal, File Manipulation.This issue affects Strategery Migrations: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35746 | WordPress BuddyPress Cover plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.4.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35746</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Asghar Hatampoor BuddyPress Cover allows Code Injection.This issue affects BuddyPress Cover: from n/a through 2.1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35747 | WordPress Contact Form Builder, Contact Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.7 - Bypass Vulnerability vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35747</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in wpdevart Contact Form Builder, Contact Widget allows Functionality Bypass.This issue affects Contact Form Builder, Contact Widget: from n/a through 2.1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35749 | WordPress Under Construction / Maintenance Mode from Acurax plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6 - IP Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35749</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in Acurax Under Construction / Maintenance Mode from Acurax allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Under Construction / Maintenance Mode from Acurax: from n/a through 2.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35754 | WordPress Ovic Importer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35754</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Ovic Team Ovic Importer allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Ovic Importer: from n/a through 1.6.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36407 | SuiteCRM unauthenticated user password reset on php7</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36407</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. In versions prior to 7.14.4 and 8.6.1, a user password can be reset from an unauthenticated attacker. The attacker does not get access to the new password. But this can be annoying for the user. This attack is also dependent on some password reset functionalities being enabled. It also requires the system using php 7, which is not an officially supported version. Versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:51:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31611 | SeaCMS 12.9 has a file deletion vulnerability via admin_template.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31611</link><description>SeaCMS 12.9 has a file deletion vulnerability via admin_template.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35728 | WordPress Product Addons &amp;amp; Fields for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 32.0.20 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35728</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements in Output Used by a Downstream Component ('Injection') vulnerability in Themeisle PPOM for WooCommerce allows Code Inclusion.This issue affects PPOM for WooCommerce: from n/a through 32.0.20.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35743 | WordPress SC filechecker plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35743</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Siteclean SC filechecker allows Path Traversal, File Manipulation.This issue affects SC filechecker: from n/a through 0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35744 | WordPress Upunzipper plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35744</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Ravidhu Dissanayake Upunzipper allows Path Traversal, File Manipulation.This issue affects Upunzipper: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:41:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5102 | Elevation of Privelage via symlinked file in Avast Antivirus</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5102</link><description>A sym-linked file accessed via the repair function in Avast Antivirus &lt;24.2 on Windows may allow user to elevate privilege to delete arbitrary files or run processes as NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM. The vulnerability exists within the "Repair" (settings -&gt; troubleshooting -&gt; repair) feature, which attempts to delete a file in the current user's AppData directory as NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM. A low-privileged user can make a pseudo-symlink and a junction folder and point to a file on the system. This can provide a low-privileged user an Elevation of Privilege to win a race-condition which will re-create the system files and make Windows callback to a specially-crafted file which could be used to launch a privileged shell instance.

This issue affects Avast Antivirus prior to 24.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31613 | BOSSCMS v3.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in name="head_code" or name="foot_code."</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31613</link><description>BOSSCMS v3.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in name="head_code" or name="foot_code."</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37051 | GitHub access token could be exposed to third-party sites in JetBrains IDEs after version 2023.1 and less than: IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1.7, 2023...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37051</link><description>GitHub access token could be exposed to third-party sites in JetBrains IDEs after version 2023.1 and less than: IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1.7, 2023.2.7, 2023.3.7, 2024.1.3, 2024.2 EAP3; Aqua 2024.1.2; CLion 2023.1.7, 2023.2.4, 2023.3.5, 2024.1.3, 2024.2 EAP2; DataGrip 2023.1.3, 2023.2.4, 2023.3.5, 2024.1.4; DataSpell 2023.1.6, 2023.2.7, 2023.3.6, 2024.1.2, 2024.2 EAP1; GoLand 2023.1.6, 2023.2.7, 2023.3.7, 2024.1.3, 2024.2 EAP3; MPS 2023.2.1, 2023.3.1, 2024.1 EAP2; PhpStorm 2023.1.6, 2023.2.6, 2023.3.7, 2024.1.3, 2024.2 EAP3; PyCharm 2023.1.6, 2023.2.7, 2023.3.6, 2024.1.3, 2024.2 EAP2; Rider 2023.1.7, 2023.2.5, 2023.3.6, 2024.1.3; RubyMine 2023.1.7, 2023.2.7, 2023.3.7, 2024.1.3, 2024.2 EAP4; RustRover 2024.1.1; WebStorm 2023.1.6, 2023.2.7, 2023.3.7, 2024.1.4</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35474 | A Directory Traversal vulnerability in iceice666 ResourcePack Server before v1.0.8 allows a remote attacker to disclose files on the server,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35474</link><description>A Directory Traversal vulnerability in iceice666 ResourcePack Server before v1.0.8 allows a remote attacker to disclose files on the server, via setPath in ResourcePackFileServer.kt.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35712 | WordPress Database Cleaner: Clean, Optimize &amp;amp; Repair plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Arbitrary File Read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35712</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Jordy Meow Database Cleaner allows Relative Path Traversal.This issue affects Database Cleaner: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34332 | An issue in SiSoftware SANDRA v31.66 (SANDRA.sys 15.18.1.1) and before allows an attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted buffer sent t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34332</link><description>An issue in SiSoftware SANDRA v31.66 (SANDRA.sys 15.18.1.1) and before allows an attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted buffer sent to the Kernel Driver using the DeviceIoControl Windows API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35650 | WordPress MelaPress Login Security plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Remote File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35650</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Melapress MelaPress Login Security allows PHP Remote File Inclusion.This issue affects MelaPress Login Security: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35658 | WordPress Checkout Field Editor for WooCommerce (Pro) plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35658</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in ThemeHigh Checkout Field Editor for WooCommerce (Pro) allows Functionality Misuse, File Manipulation.This issue affects Checkout Field Editor for WooCommerce (Pro): from n/a through 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35677 | WordPress MegaMenu plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.12 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35677</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in StylemixThemes MegaMenu allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects MegaMenu: from n/a through 2.3.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:51:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35680 | WordPress YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.2 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35680</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements in Output Used by a Downstream Component ('Injection') vulnerability in YITH YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons allows Code Injection.This issue affects YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons: from n/a through 4.9.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:51:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26507 | An issue in FinalWire AIRDA Extreme, AIDA64 Engineer, AIDA64 Business, AIDA64 Network Audit v.7.00.6700 and before allows a local attacker t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26507</link><description>An issue in FinalWire AIRDA Extreme, AIDA64 Engineer, AIDA64 Business, AIDA64 Network Audit v.7.00.6700 and before allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the DeviceIoControl call associated with MmMapIoSpace, IoAllocateMdl, MmBuildMdlForNonPagedPool, or MmMapLockedPages components.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34761 | Wordpress Advanced Custom Fields Pro plugin &amp;lt; 6.2.10 - Contributor+ Arbitrary Function Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34761</link><description>Vulnerability discovered by executing a planned security audit.

Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in WPENGINE INC Advanced Custom Fields PRO allows Code Injection.This issue affects Advanced Custom Fields PRO: from n/a before 6.2.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34762 | Wordpress Advanced Custom Fields Pro plugin &amp;lt; 6.2.10 - Contributor+ Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34762</link><description>Vulnerability discovered by executing a planned security audit.

Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in WPENGINE INC Advanced Custom Fields PRO allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Advanced Custom Fields PRO: from n/a before 6.2.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34800 | WordPress Crafthemes Demo Import plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Arbitrary Plugin Installation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34800</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in Aruphash Crafthemes Demo Import allows Functionality Misuse.This issue affects Crafthemes Demo Import: from n/a through 3.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:51:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36406 | SuiteCRM vulnerable to open redirects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36406</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. In versions prior to 7.14.4 and 8.6.1, unchecked input allows for open re-direct. Versions 7.14.4 and 8.6.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:18:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36528 | nukeviet v.4.5 and before and nukeviet-egov v.1.2.02 and before have a Deserialization vulnerability which results in code execution via /ad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36528</link><description>nukeviet v.4.5 and before and nukeviet-egov v.1.2.02 and before have a Deserialization vulnerability which results in code execution via /admin/extensions/download.php and /admin/extensions/upload.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36531 | nukeviet v.4.5 and before and nukeviet-egov v.1.2.02 and before are vulnerable to arbitrary code execution via the /admin/extensions/upload....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36531</link><description>nukeviet v.4.5 and before and nukeviet-egov v.1.2.02 and before are vulnerable to arbitrary code execution via the /admin/extensions/upload.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36972 | af_unix: Update unix_sk(sk)-&amp;gt;oob_skb under sk_receive_queue lock.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36972</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

af_unix: Update unix_sk(sk)-&gt;oob_skb under sk_receive_queue lock.

Billy Jheng Bing-Jhong reported a race between __unix_gc() and
queue_oob().

__unix_gc() tries to garbage-collect close()d inflight sockets,
and then if the socket has MSG_OOB in unix_sk(sk)-&gt;oob_skb, GC
will drop the reference and set NULL to it locklessly.

However, the peer socket still can send MSG_OOB message and
queue_oob() can update unix_sk(sk)-&gt;oob_skb concurrently, leading
NULL pointer dereference. [0]

To fix the issue, let's update unix_sk(sk)-&gt;oob_skb under the
sk_receive_queue's lock and take it everywhere we touch oob_skb.

Note that we defer kfree_skb() in manage_oob() to silence lockdep
false-positive (See [1]).

[0]:
BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000008
 PF: supervisor write access in kernel mode
 PF: error_code(0x0002) - not-present page
PGD 8000000009f5e067 P4D 8000000009f5e067 PUD 9f5d067 PMD 0
Oops: 0002 [#1] PREEMPT SMP PTI
CPU: 3 PID: 50 Comm: kworker/3:1 Not tainted 6.9.0-rc5-00191-gd091e579b864 #110
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS rel-1.16.0-0-gd239552ce722-prebuilt.qemu.org 04/01/2014
Workqueue: events delayed_fput
RIP: 0010:skb_dequeue (./include/linux/skbuff.h:2386 ./include/linux/skbuff.h:2402 net/core/skbuff.c:3847)
Code: 39 e3 74 3e 8b 43 10 48 89 ef 83 e8 01 89 43 10 49 8b 44 24 08 49 c7 44 24 08 00 00 00 00 49 8b 14 24 49 c7 04 24 00 00 00 00 &lt;48&gt; 89 42 08 48 89 10 e8 e7 c5 42 00 4c 89 e0 5b 5d 41 5c c3 cc cc
RSP: 0018:ffffc900001bfd48 EFLAGS: 00000002
RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffff8880088f5ae8 RCX: 00000000361289f9
RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: 0000000000000206 RDI: ffff8880088f5b00
RBP: ffff8880088f5b00 R08: 0000000000080000 R09: 0000000000000001
R10: 0000000000000003 R11: 0000000000000001 R12: ffff8880056b6a00
R13: ffff8880088f5280 R14: 0000000000000001 R15: ffff8880088f5a80
FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffff88807dd80000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 0000000000000008 CR3: 0000000006314000 CR4: 00000000007506f0
PKRU: 55555554
Call Trace:
 
 unix_release_sock (net/unix/af_unix.c:654)
 unix_release (net/unix/af_unix.c:1050)
 __sock_release (net/socket.c:660)
 sock_close (net/socket.c:1423)
 __fput (fs/file_table.c:423)
 delayed_fput (fs/file_table.c:444 (discriminator 3))
 process_one_work (kernel/workqueue.c:3259)
 worker_thread (kernel/workqueue.c:3329 kernel/workqueue.c:3416)
 kthread (kernel/kthread.c:388)
 ret_from_fork (arch/x86/kernel/process.c:153)
 ret_from_fork_asm (arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:257)
 
Modules linked in:
CR2: 0000000000000008</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4403 | CSRF in restart_program in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4403</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the restart_program function of the parisneo/lollms-webui v9.6. This vulnerability allows attackers to trick users into performing unintended actions, such as resetting the program without their knowledge, by sending specially crafted CSRF forms. This issue affects the installation process, including the installation of Binding zoo and Models zoo, by unexpectedly resetting programs. The vulnerability is due to the lack of CSRF protection in the affected function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 14:57:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35307 | Argument Injection Leading to Remote Code Execution in Realtime Graph Extension</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35307</link><description>Argument Injection Leading to Remote Code Execution in Realtime Graph Extension, allowing unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code on the server. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through &lt;777.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 14:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45168 | An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v018. A Bypass of Two-Factor Authentication can occur under the /login/backup...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45168</link><description>An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v018. A Bypass of Two-Factor Authentication can occur under the /login/backup_code endpoint and the /api/v1/vdeskintegration/createbackupcodes endpoint, because the application allows a user to generate or regenerate the backup codes before checking the TOTP.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 14:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45176 | An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v018. Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) can occur under the /api/v1/getbodyfi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45176</link><description>An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v018. Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) can occur under the /api/v1/getbodyfile endpoint via the uri parameter. The web application (through its vShare functionality section) doesn't properly check parameters, sent in HTTP requests as input, before saving them on the server. In addition, crafted JavaScript content can then be reflected back to the end user and executed by the web browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 14:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35305 | Unauth Time-Based SQL Injection via API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35305</link><description>Unauth Time-Based SQL Injection in API allows to exploit HTTP request Authorization header. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through &lt;777.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 14:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35306 | OS Command injection in Ajax PHP files through HTTP Request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35306</link><description>OS Command injection in Ajax PHP files via HTTP Request, allows to execute system commands by exploiting variables. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through &lt;777.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 14:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35304 | System command injection through Netflow function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35304</link><description>System command injection through Netflow function due to improper input validation, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary system commands. This issue affects Pandora FMS: from 700 through &lt;777.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 14:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36405 | Control-flow timing leak in Kyber reference implementation when compiled with Clang 15-18 for -Os, -O1 and other options</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36405</link><description>liboqs is a C-language cryptographic library that provides implementations of post-quantum cryptography algorithms. A control-flow timing lean has been identified in the reference implementation of the Kyber key encapsulation mechanism when it is compiled with Clang 15-18 for `-Os`, `-O1`, and other compilation options. A proof-of-concept local attack on the reference implementation leaks the entire ML-KEM 512 secret key in ~10 minutes using end-to-end decapsulation timing measurements. The issue has been fixed in version 0.10.1. As a possible workaround, some compiler options may produce vectorized code that does not leak secret information, however relying on these compiler options as a workaround may not be reliable.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5785 | Command injection vulnerability in Comtrend router</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5785</link><description>Command injection vulnerability in Comtrend router WLD71-T1_v2.0.201820, affecting the GRG-4280us version. This vulnerability could allow an authenticated user to execute commands inside the router by making a POST request to the URL “/boaform/admin/formUserTracert”.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5786 | Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Comtrend router</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5786</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Comtrend router WLD71-T1_v2.0.201820, affecting the GRG-4280us version. This vulnerability allows an attacker to force an end user to execute unwanted actions in a web application to which he is authenticated.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28833 | Missing brute-force protection for two factor authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28833</link><description>Improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts with two factor authentication methods in Checkmk 2.3 before 2.3.0p6 facilitates brute-forcing of second factor mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1228 | Hardcoded password in Eurosoft Przychodnia</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1228</link><description>Use of hard-coded password to the patients' database allows an attacker to retrieve sensitive data stored in the database. The password is the same among all Eurosoft Przychodnia installations.

This issue affects Eurosoft Przychodnia software before version 20240417.001 (from that version vulnerability is fixed).</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 11:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3699 | Hardcoded password in drEryk Gabinet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3699</link><description>Use of hard-coded password to the patients' database allows an attacker to retrieve sensitive data stored in the database. The password is the same among all drEryk Gabinet installations.This issue affects drEryk Gabinet software versions from 7.0.0.0 through 9.17.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 11:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3700 | Hardcoded password in Estomed Sp. z o.o. Simple Care software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3700</link><description>Use of hard-coded password to the patients' database allows an attacker to retrieve sensitive data stored in the database. The password is the same among all Simple Care software installations.

This issue affects Estomed Sp. z o.o. Simple Care software in all versions. The software is no longer supported.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 11:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36971 | net: fix __dst_negative_advice() race</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36971</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: fix __dst_negative_advice() race

__dst_negative_advice() does not enforce proper RCU rules when
sk-&gt;dst_cache must be cleared, leading to possible UAF.

RCU rules are that we must first clear sk-&gt;sk_dst_cache,
then call dst_release(old_dst).

Note that sk_dst_reset(sk) is implementing this protocol correctly,
while __dst_negative_advice() uses the wrong order.

Given that ip6_negative_advice() has special logic
against RTF_CACHE, this means each of the three -&gt;negative_advice()
existing methods must perform the sk_dst_reset() themselves.

Note the check against NULL dst is centralized in
__dst_negative_advice(), there is no need to duplicate
it in various callbacks.

Many thanks to Clement Lecigne for tracking this issue.

This old bug became visible after the blamed commit, using UDP sockets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 09:12:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21751 | WordPress RabbitLoader plugin &amp;lt;= 2.19.13 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21751</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in RabbitLoader.This issue affects RabbitLoader: from n/a through 2.19.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 08:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22296 | WordPress 12 Step Meeting List plugin &amp;lt;= 3.14.28 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22296</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Code for Recovery 12 Step Meeting List.This issue affects 12 Step Meeting List: from n/a through 3.14.28.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 08:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22298 | WordPress Amelia plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.98 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22298</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in TMS Amelia ameliabooking.This issue affects Amelia: from n/a through 1.0.98.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 08:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23524 | WordPress PilotPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.30 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23524</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ONTRAPORT Inc. PilotPress.This issue affects PilotPress: from n/a through 2.0.30.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 08:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4744 | WordPress iPages Flipbook plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4744</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Avirtum iPages Flipbook.This issue affects iPages Flipbook: from n/a through 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 08:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4745 | WordPress Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.12.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4745</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in RafflePress Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress.This issue affects Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress: from n/a through 1.12.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 08:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35717 | WordPress Media Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35717</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in A WP Life Media Slider – Photo Sleder, Video Slider, Link Slider, Carousal Slideshow.This issue affects Media Slider – Photo Sleder, Video Slider, Link Slider, Carousal Slideshow: from n/a through 1.3.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 08:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35720 | WordPress Album Gallery – WordPress Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35720</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in A WP Life Album Gallery – WordPress Gallery.This issue affects Album Gallery – WordPress Gallery: from n/a through 1.5.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 08:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35721 | WordPress Image Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35721</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in A WP Life Image Gallery – Lightbox Gallery, Responsive Photo Gallery, Masonry Gallery.This issue affects Image Gallery – Lightbox Gallery, Responsive Photo Gallery, Masonry Gallery: from n/a through 1.4.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 08:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35722 | WordPress Slider Responsive Slideshow – Image slider, Gallery slideshow plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35722</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in A WP Life Slider Responsive Slideshow – Image slider, Gallery slideshow.This issue affects Slider Responsive Slideshow – Image slider, Gallery slideshow: from n/a through 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 08:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4746 | WordPress Netgsm plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.16 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4746</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Netgsm.This issue affects Netgsm: from n/a through 2.9.16.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 08:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35723 | WordPress Dashboard To-Do List plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35723</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Andrew Rapps Dashboard To-Do List.This issue affects Dashboard To-Do List: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 08:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35724 | WordPress Bosa Elementor Addons and Templates for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.12 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35724</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Bosa Themes Bosa Elementor Addons and Templates for WooCommerce.This issue affects Bosa Elementor Addons and Templates for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.0.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 08:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35725 | WordPress LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35725</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in LA-Studio LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor.This issue affects LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 08:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35726 | WordPress WooBuddy plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.19 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35726</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThemeKraft WooBuddy.This issue affects WooBuddy: from n/a through 3.4.19.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:53:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35727 | WordPress Extra Product Options for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35727</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in actpro Extra Product Options for WooCommerce.This issue affects Extra Product Options for WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:53:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35729 | WordPress Tickera – WordPress Event Ticketing plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.2.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35729</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tickera.This issue affects Tickera: from n/a through 3.5.2.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:53:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35735 | WordPress WP Time Slots Booking Form plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.11 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35735</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CodePeople WP Time Slots Booking Form.This issue affects WP Time Slots Booking Form: from n/a through 1.2.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35741 | WordPress Awesome Support plugin &amp;lt;= 6.1.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35741</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Awesome Support Team Awesome Support.This issue affects Awesome Support: from n/a through 6.1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35742 | WordPress Easy Forms for Mailchimp plugin &amp;lt;= 6.9.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35742</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Code Parrots Easy Forms for Mailchimp.This issue affects Easy Forms for Mailchimp: from n/a through 6.9.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4328 | CSRF in clear_personality_files_list in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4328</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the clear_personality_files_list function of the parisneo/lollms-webui v9.6. The vulnerability arises from the use of a GET request to clear personality files list, which lacks proper CSRF protection. This flaw allows attackers to trick users into performing actions without their consent, such as deleting important files on the system. The issue is present in the application's handling of requests, making it susceptible to CSRF attacks that could lead to unauthorized actions being performed on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37880 | The Kyber reference implementation before 9b8d306, when compiled by LLVM Clang through 18.x with some common optimization options, has a tim...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37880</link><description>The Kyber reference implementation before 9b8d306, when compiled by LLVM Clang through 18.x with some common optimization options, has a timing side channel that allows attackers to recover an ML-KEM 512 secret key in minutes. This occurs because poly_frommsg in poly.c does not prevent Clang from emitting a vulnerable secret-dependent branch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 02:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5389 | Insufficient Access Control in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5389</link><description>In lunary-ai/lunary version 1.2.13, an insufficient granularity of access control vulnerability allows users to create, update, get, and delete prompt variations for datasets not owned by their organization. This issue arises due to the application not properly validating the ownership of dataset prompts and their variations against the organization or project of the requesting user. As a result, unauthorized modifications to dataset prompts can occur, leading to altered or removed dataset prompts without proper authorization. This vulnerability impacts the integrity and consistency of dataset information, potentially affecting the results of experiments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 22:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2408 | PHP is vulnerable to the Marvin Attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2408</link><description>The openssl_private_decrypt function in PHP, when using PKCS1 padding (OPENSSL_PKCS1_PADDING, which is the default), is vulnerable to the Marvin Attack unless it is used with an OpenSSL version that includes the changes from this pull request:  https://github.com/openssl/openssl/pull/13817  (rsa_pkcs1_implicit_rejection). These changes are part of OpenSSL 3.2 and have also been backported to stable versions of various Linux distributions, as well as to the PHP builds provided for Windows since the previous release. All distributors and builders should ensure that this version is used to prevent PHP from being vulnerable.

PHP Windows builds for the versions 8.1.29, 8.2.20 and 8.3.8 and above include OpenSSL patches that fix the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 20:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37569 | An issue was discovered on Mitel 6869i through 4.5.0.41 and 5.x through 5.0.0.1018 devices. A command injection vulnerability exists in the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37569</link><description>An issue was discovered on Mitel 6869i through 4.5.0.41 and 5.x through 5.0.0.1018 devices. A command injection vulnerability exists in the hostname parameter taken in by the provis.html endpoint. The provis.html endpoint performs no sanitization on the hostname parameter (sent by an authenticated user), which is subsequently written to disk. During boot, the hostname parameter is executed as part of a series of shell commands. Attackers can achieve remote code execution in the root context by placing shell metacharacters in the hostname parameter.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 19:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37570 | On Mitel 6869i 4.5.0.41 devices, the Manual Firmware Update (upgrade.html) page does not perform sanitization on the username and path param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37570</link><description>On Mitel 6869i 4.5.0.41 devices, the Manual Firmware Update (upgrade.html) page does not perform sanitization on the username and path parameters (sent by an authenticated user) before appending flags to the busybox ftpget command. This leads to $() command execution.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 19:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4577 | Argument Injection in PHP-CGI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4577</link><description>In PHP versions 8.1.* before 8.1.29, 8.2.* before 8.2.20, 8.3.* before 8.3.8, when using Apache and PHP-CGI on Windows, if the system is set up to use certain code pages, Windows may use "Best-Fit" behavior to replace characters in command line given to Win32 API functions. PHP CGI module may misinterpret those characters as PHP options, which may allow a malicious user to pass options to PHP binary being run, and thus reveal the source code of scripts, run arbitrary PHP code on the server, etc.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 19:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37568 | lepture Authlib before 1.3.1 has algorithm confusion with asymmetric public keys. Unless an algorithm is specified in a jwt.decode call, HMA...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37568</link><description>lepture Authlib before 1.3.1 has algorithm confusion with asymmetric public keys. Unless an algorithm is specified in a jwt.decode call, HMAC verification is allowed with any asymmetric public key. (This is similar to CVE-2022-29217 and CVE-2024-33663.)</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 19:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35748 | WordPress WooCommerce Dropshipping plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Email Sending vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35748</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in OPMC WooCommerce Dropshipping.This issue affects WooCommerce Dropshipping: from n/a through 5.0.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:55:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32081 | WordPress Filter Custom Fields &amp;amp; Taxonomies Light plugin &amp;lt;= 1.05 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32081</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Websupporter Filter Custom Fields &amp; Taxonomies Light.This issue affects Filter Custom Fields &amp; Taxonomies Light: from n/a through 1.05.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34802 | WordPress AdFoxly plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34802</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AdFoxly AdFoxly – Ad Manager, AdSense Ads &amp; Ads.Txt.This issue affects AdFoxly – Ad Manager, AdSense Ads &amp; Ads.Txt: from n/a through 1.8.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35661 | WordPress Upload Fields for WPForms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35661</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in SoftLab Upload Fields for WPForms.This issue affects Upload Fields for WPForms: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35662 | WordPress Simple COD Fees for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35662</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Andreas Sofantzis Simple COD Fees for WooCommerce.This issue affects Simple COD Fees for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5585 | Command injection via array-ish $command parameter of proc_open() (bypass CVE-2024-1874 fix)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5585</link><description>In PHP versions 8.1.* before 8.1.29, 8.2.* before 8.2.20, 8.3.* before 8.3.8, the fix for CVE-2024-1874 does not work if the command name includes trailing spaces. Original issue: when using proc_open() command with array syntax, due to insufficient escaping, if the arguments of the executed command are controlled by a malicious user, the user can supply arguments that would execute arbitrary commands in Windows shell.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5458 | Filter bypass in filter_var (FILTER_VALIDATE_URL)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5458</link><description>In PHP versions 8.1.* before 8.1.29, 8.2.* before 8.2.20, 8.3.* before 8.3.8, due to a code logic error, filtering functions such as filter_var when validating URLs (FILTER_VALIDATE_URL) for certain types of URLs the function will result in invalid user information (username + password part of URLs) being treated as valid user information. This may lead to the downstream code accepting invalid URLs as valid and parsing them incorrectly.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31275 | WordPress EventPrime plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.4 - Booking Price Manipulation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31275</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Metagauss EventPrime.This issue affects EventPrime: from n/a through 3.3.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31276 | WordPress Products, Order &amp;amp; Customers Export for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31276</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPFactory Products, Order &amp; Customers Export for WooCommerce.This issue affects Products, Order &amp; Customers Export for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.0.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31283 | WordPress Advanced Local Pickup for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;=1.6.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31283</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in zorem Advanced Local Pickup for WooCommerce.This issue affects Advanced Local Pickup for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31284 | WordPress EmbedPress plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31284</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPDeveloper EmbedPress.This issue affects EmbedPress: from n/a through 3.9.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31304 | WordPress MultiVendorX Marketplace &amp;lt;= 4.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31304</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in MultiVendorX WC Marketplace.This issue affects WC Marketplace: from n/a through 4.1.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31307 | WordPress Easy Social Share Buttons plugin &amp;lt;= 9.4 - Multiple Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31307</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in appscreo Easy Social Share Buttons.This issue affects Easy Social Share Buttons: from n/a through 9.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31347 | WordPress Tracking Code Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31347</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Data443 Tracking Code Manager.This issue affects Tracking Code Manager: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31350 | WordPress AWP Classifieds plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31350</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AWP Classifieds Team AWP Classifieds.This issue affects AWP Classifieds: from n/a through 4.3.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31352 | WordPress Icegram Express plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7.13 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31352</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Email Subscribers &amp; Newsletters.This issue affects Email Subscribers &amp; Newsletters: from n/a through 5.7.13.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 17:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31359 | WordPress Premmerce Product Filter for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31359</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Premmerce Premmerce Product Filter for WooCommerce.This issue affects Premmerce Product Filter for WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.7.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 17:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32701 | WordPress InstaWP Connect plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.0.24 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32701</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in InstaWP Team InstaWP Connect.This issue affects InstaWP Connect: from n/a through 0.1.0.24.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 17:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32703 | WordPress ARForms plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32703</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in reputeinfosystems ARForms.This issue affects ARForms: from n/a through 6.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 17:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31423 | WordPress WP Accessibility Helper (WAH) plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.2.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31423</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Alex Volkov WP Accessibility Helper (WAH).This issue affects WP Accessibility Helper (WAH): from n/a through 0.6.2.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 17:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32704 | WordPress ARForms plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary WordPress Options Removal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32704</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in reputeinfosystems ARForms.This issue affects ARForms: from n/a through 6.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 17:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32705 | WordPress ARForms plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Plugin Activation/Deactivation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32705</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in reputeinfosystems ARForms.This issue affects ARForms: from n/a through 6.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 17:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32713 | WordPress AI Post Generator | AutoWriter plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32713</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AutoWriter AI Post Generator | AutoWriter.This issue affects AI Post Generator | AutoWriter: from n/a through 3.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 17:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32714 | WordPress Academy LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.16 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32714</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Academy LMS academy.This issue affects Academy LMS: from n/a through 1.9.16.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 17:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32715 | WordPress Olive One Click Demo Import plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32715</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Olive Themes Olive One Click Demo Import.This issue affects Olive One Click Demo Import: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 17:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32725 | WordPress 5 Stars Rating Funnel plugin 1.2.67 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32725</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Saleswonder 5 Stars Rating Funnel.This issue affects 5 Stars Rating Funnel: from n/a through 1.2.67.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 17:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37535 | GNOME VTE before 0.76.3 allows an attacker to cause a denial of service (memory consumption) via a window resize escape sequence, a related ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37535</link><description>GNOME VTE before 0.76.3 allows an attacker to cause a denial of service (memory consumption) via a window resize escape sequence, a related issue to CVE-2000-0476.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 15:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32727 | WordPress RomethemeForm For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32727</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Rometheme RomethemeForm For Elementor.This issue affects RomethemeForm For Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 15:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32777 | WordPress BizPrint plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.39 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32777</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BizSwoop a CPF Concepts, LLC Brand BizPrint.This issue affects BizPrint: from n/a through 4.3.39.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 13:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32778 | WordPress Contest Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 21.3.4 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32778</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Contest Gallery.This issue affects Contest Gallery: from n/a through 21.3.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 13:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32779 | WordPress Vision – Image Map Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32779</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Avirtum Vision Interactive.This issue affects Vision Interactive: from n/a through 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 13:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32783 | WordPress Advanced Testimonial Carousel for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32783</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wpcreativeidea Advanced Testimonial Carousel for Elementor.This issue affects Advanced Testimonial Carousel for Elementor: from n/a through 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 13:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32784 | WordPress CookieHub plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32784</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CookieHub.This issue affects CookieHub: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 13:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32787 | WordPress Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32787</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Copy Content Protection Team Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking.This issue affects Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking: from n/a through 3.7.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 13:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32792 | WordPress Hummingbird plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32792</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPMU DEV Hummingbird.This issue affects Hummingbird: from n/a through 3.7.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 13:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32797 | WordPress WP LinkedIn Auto Publish plugin &amp;lt;= 8.11 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32797</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Martin Gibson WP LinkedIn Auto Publish.This issue affects WP LinkedIn Auto Publish: from n/a through 8.11.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32798 | WordPress WP Travel Engine plugin &amp;lt;= 5.8.0 - Price Manipulation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32798</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Travel Engine.This issue affects WP Travel Engine: from n/a through 5.8.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32799 | WordPress Easy Property Listings plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32799</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Merv Barrett Easy Property Listings.This issue affects Easy Property Listings: from n/a through 3.5.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32804 | WordPress WP GoToWebinar plugin &amp;lt;= 14.46 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32804</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Martin Gibson WP GoToWebinar.This issue affects WP GoToWebinar: from n/a through 14.46.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32805 | WordPress Social Snap plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32805</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Social Snap.This issue affects Social Snap: from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32811 | WordPress USPS Shipping for WooCommerce – Live Rates plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.4 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Log File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32811</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Octolize USPS Shipping for WooCommerce – Live Rates.This issue affects USPS Shipping for WooCommerce – Live Rates: from n/a through 1.9.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32813 | WordPress Integrate Google Drive plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32813</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in SoftLab Integrate Google Drive.This issue affects Integrate Google Drive: from n/a through 1.3.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32814 | WordPress Advanced Local Pickup for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32814</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Zorem Advanced Local Pickup for WooCommerce.This issue affects Advanced Local Pickup for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32818 | WordPress MDTF – Meta Data and Taxonomies Filter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32818</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in realmag777 WordPress Meta Data and Taxonomies Filter (MDTF).This issue affects WordPress Meta Data and Taxonomies Filter (MDTF): from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32820 | WordPress Social Share Icons &amp;amp; Social Share Buttons plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 - Broken Access Control lead to Notice Dismissal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32820</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Social Share Pro Social Share Icons &amp; Social Share Buttons.This issue affects Social Share Icons &amp; Social Share Buttons: from n/a through 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45188 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization Publishing file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45188</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization Publishing 7.0.2 and 7.03 could allow a remote attacker to upload arbitrary files, caused by the improper validation of file extensions.  By sending a specially crafted request, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to upload a malicious file, which could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the vulnerable system.  IBM X-Force ID:  268751.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32821 | WordPress Total Poll Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32821</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in TotalSuite Total Poll Lite.This issue affects Total Poll Lite: from n/a through 4.9.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32824 | WordPress Evergreen Content Poster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32824</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Evergreen Content Poster.This issue affects Evergreen Content Poster: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33543 | WordPress WP Time Slots Booking Form plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.06 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33543</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CodePeople WP Time Slots Booking Form.This issue affects WP Time Slots Booking Form: from n/a through 1.2.06.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33545 | WordPress WZone plugin &amp;lt;= 14.0.10 - Unauthenticated Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33545</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AA-Team WZone.This issue affects WZone: from n/a through 14.0.10.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33547 | WordPress WZone plugin &amp;lt;= 14.0.10 - Site Wide Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33547</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AA-Team WZone.This issue affects WZone: from n/a through 14.0.10.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33555 | WordPress XStore Core plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.8 - Multiple Authenticated Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33555</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in 8theme XStore Core.This issue affects XStore Core: from n/a through 5.3.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33561 | WordPress XStore theme &amp;lt;= 9.3.8 - Unauthenticated Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33561</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in 8theme XStore.This issue affects XStore: from n/a through 9.3.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33563 | WordPress XStore theme &amp;lt;= 9.3.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33563</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in 8theme XStore.This issue affects XStore: from n/a through 9.3.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33564 | WordPress XStore theme &amp;lt;= 9.3.8 - Arbitrary Option Update vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33564</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in 8theme XStore.This issue affects XStore: from n/a through 9.3.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33565 | WordPress Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp;amp; Order Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 - Unauthenticated Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33565</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in UkrSolution Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager.This issue affects Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager: from n/a through 1.5.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33572 | WordPress The Plus Blocks for Block Editor | Gutenberg plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33572</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in POSIMYTH The Plus Blocks for Block Editor | Gutenberg.This issue affects The Plus Blocks for Block Editor | Gutenberg: from n/a through 3.2.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34435 | WordPress Aiomatic plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34435</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CodeRevolution Aiomatic.This issue affects Aiomatic: from n/a through 1.9.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35660 | WordPress Master Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.5.4.1 - Broken Access Control on API vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35660</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jewel Theme Master Addons for Elementor.This issue affects Master Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 2.0.5.4.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35669 | WordPress Debug Log Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35669</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Bowo Debug Log Manager.This issue affects Debug Log Manager: from n/a through 2.3.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 12:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31273 | WordPress JS Help Desk plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31273</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in JS Help Desk JS Help Desk – Best Help Desk &amp; Support Plugin.This issue affects JS Help Desk – Best Help Desk &amp; Support Plugin: from n/a through 2.8.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31274 | WordPress EmbedPress plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.11 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31274</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPDeveloper EmbedPress.This issue affects EmbedPress: from n/a through 3.9.11.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31243 | WordPress Bricksforge plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.17 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary WordPress Setting Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31243</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Bricksforge.This issue affects Bricksforge: from n/a through 2.0.17.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31244 | WordPress Bricksforge plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.17 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary WordPress Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31244</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Bricksforge.This issue affects Bricksforge: from n/a through 2.0.17.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31248 | WordPress All-in-One Video Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31248</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Team Plugins360 All-in-One Video Gallery.This issue affects All-in-One Video Gallery: from n/a through 3.5.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31252 | WordPress Responsive Lightbox &amp;amp; Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31252</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in dFactory Responsive Lightbox.This issue affects Responsive Lightbox: from n/a through 2.4.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31261 | WordPress Announcer – Notification &amp;amp; message bars plugin &amp;lt;= 6.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31261</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Aakash Chakravarthy Announcer – Notification &amp; message bars.This issue affects Announcer – Notification &amp; message bars: from n/a through 6.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31267 | WordPress Flexible Checkout Fields for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31267</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Desk Flexible Checkout Fields for WooCommerce.This issue affects Flexible Checkout Fields for WooCommerce: from n/a through 4.1.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30485 | WordPress Finale Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 2.18.0 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Plugin Installation/Activation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30485</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in XLPlugins Finale Lite.This issue affects Finale Lite: from n/a through 2.18.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30512 | WordPress weForms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.20 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30512</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in weForms.This issue affects weForms: from n/a through 1.6.20.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30515 | WordPress Events Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.6.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30515</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Pixelite Events Manager.This issue affects Events Manager: from n/a through 6.4.6.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30517 | WordPress Sliced Invoices plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30517</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Sliced Invoices.This issue affects Sliced Invoices: from n/a through 3.9.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30529 | WordPress Tainacan plugin &amp;lt;= 0.20.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30529</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tainacan.Org Tainacan.This issue affects Tainacan: from n/a through 0.20.7.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30544 | WordPress Whizzy plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.18 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30544</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in UPQODE Whizzy.This issue affects Whizzy: from n/a through 1.1.18.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30467 | WordPress Essential Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30467</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPDeveloper Essential Blocks for Gutenberg.This issue affects Essential Blocks for Gutenberg: from n/a through 4.4.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30470 | WordPress YITH WooCommerce Account Funds Premium plugin &amp;lt;= 1.32.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30470</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in YITH YITH WooCommerce Account Funds Premium.This issue affects YITH WooCommerce Account Funds Premium: from n/a through 1.33.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30481 | WordPress JCH Optimize plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30481</link><description>Broken Access Control vulnerability in Samuel Marshall JCH Optimize.This issue affects JCH Optimize: from n/a through 4.0.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30464 | WordPress Social Icons Widget &amp;amp; Block by WPZOOM plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.15 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30464</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPZOOM Social Icons Widget &amp; Block by WPZOOM.This issue affects Social Icons Widget &amp; Block by WPZOOM: from n/a through 4.2.15.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 10:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30465 | WordPress PageLayer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30465</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Pagelayer Team PageLayer.This issue affects PageLayer: from n/a through 1.8.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 10:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30466 | WordPress WooCommerce Multilingual &amp;amp; Multicurrency plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30466</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in OnTheGoSystems WooCommerce Multilingual &amp; Multicurrency.This issue affects WooCommerce Multilingual &amp; Multicurrency: from n/a through 5.3.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 10:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25092 | WordPress NextMove Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 2.17.0 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Plugin Installation/Activation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25092</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in XLPlugins NextMove Lite.This issue affects NextMove Lite: from n/a through 2.17.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 10:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25929 | WordPress Product Catalog Mode For Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25929</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in MultiVendorX Product Catalog Enquiry for WooCommerce by MultiVendorX.This issue affects Product Catalog Enquiry for WooCommerce by MultiVendorX: from n/a through 5.0.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 10:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34003 | WordPress WooCommerce Box Office plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.51 - Unauthenticated Save Ticket Barcode vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34003</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Woo WooCommerce Box Office.This issue affects WooCommerce Box Office: from n/a through 1.1.51.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 10:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24716 | WordPress Awesome Support plugin &amp;lt;= 6.1.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24716</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Awesome Support Team Awesome Support.This issue affects Awesome Support: from n/a through 6.1.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 10:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31080 | WordPress Unlimited Elements For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.65 - Multiple Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31080</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Unlimited Elements Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates).This issue affects Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates): from n/a through 1.5.65.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23639 | WordPress MainWP Staging Extension Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Plugin Activation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23639</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in MainWP MainWP Staging Extension.This issue affects MainWP Staging Extension: from n/a through 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:31:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23640 | WordPress MainWP UpdraftPlus Extension Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.6 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Plugin Activation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23640</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in MainWP MainWP UpdraftPlus Extension.This issue affects MainWP UpdraftPlus Extension: from n/a through 4.0.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:31:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51494 | WordPress WooCommerce Product Vendors plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51494</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Woo WooCommerce Product Vendors.This issue affects WooCommerce Product Vendors: from n/a through 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52230 | WordPress Booster Plus for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt; 7.1.3 - Authenticated Arbitrary WordPress Option Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52230</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Pluggabl LLC Booster Plus for WooCommerce.This issue affects Booster Plus for WooCommerce: from n/a before 7.1.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52232 | WordPress Booster Plus for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt; 7.1.2 - Authenticated Arbitrary Post/Page Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52232</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Pluggabl LLC Booster Plus for WooCommerce.This issue affects Booster Plus for WooCommerce: from n/a before 7.1.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30534 | WordPress Calendarista Basic Edition plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30534</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in typps Calendarista Basic Edition.This issue affects Calendarista Basic Edition: from n/a through 3.0.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30539 | WordPress Awesome Support plugin &amp;lt;= 6.1.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30539</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Awesome Support Team Awesome Support.This issue affects Awesome Support: from n/a through 6.1.7.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30537 | WordPress WPC Badge Management for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30537</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPClever WPC Badge Management for WooCommerce.This issue affects WPC Badge Management for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30538 | WordPress DELUCKS SEO plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30538</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in DELUCKS GmbH DELUCKS SEO.This issue affects DELUCKS SEO: from n/a through 2.5.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31098 | WordPress New Order Notification for Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31098</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mr.Ebabi New Order Notification for Woocommerce.This issue affects New Order Notification for Woocommerce: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31246 | WordPress Post Grid Gutenberg Blocks and WordPress Blog Plugin – PostX plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.3 - Author+ Post/Page Duplication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31246</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Post Grid Team by WPXPO PostX – Gutenberg Blocks for Post Grid.This issue affects PostX – Gutenberg Blocks for Post Grid: from n/a through 3.2.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31294 | WordPress WP Sort Order plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31294</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Fahad Mahmood WP Sort Order.This issue affects WP Sort Order: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 08:59:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5775 | SourceCodester Vehicle Management System updatebill.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5775</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Vehicle Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file updatebill.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-267458 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 07:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5774 | SourceCodester Stock Management System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5774</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Stock Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-267457 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 06:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5773 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway deletemacbind.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5773</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /protocol/firewall/deletemacbind.php. The manipulation of the argument messagecontent leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-267456. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 03:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5772 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway deleteiscuser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5772</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /protocol/iscuser/deleteiscuser.php. The manipulation of the argument messagecontent leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-267455. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 02:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>