<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:29:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-48305 | Nextcloud Server user_ldap app logs user passwords in the log file on level debug</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48305</link><description>Nextcloud Server provides data storage for Nextcloud, an open source cloud platform. Starting in version 25.0.0 and prior to versions 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 of Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server, when the log level was set to debug, the user_ldap app logged user passwords in plaintext into the log file. If the log file was then leaked or shared in any way the users' passwords would be leaked. Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server versions 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 contain a patch for this issue. As a workaround, change config setting `loglevel` to `1` or higher (should always be higher than 1 in production environments).</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48306 | Nextcloud Server DNS pin middleware can be tricked into DNS rebinding allowing SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48306</link><description>Nextcloud Server provides data storage for Nextcloud, an open source cloud platform. Starting in version 25.0.0 and prior to versions 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 of Nextcloud Server and starting in version 22.0.0 and prior to versions 22.2.10.16, 23.0.12.11, 24.0.12.7, 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 of Nextcloud Enterprise Server, the DNS pin middleware was vulnerable to DNS rebinding allowing an attacker to perform SSRF as a final result. Nextcloud Server 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server 22.2.10.16, 23.0.12.11, 24.0.12.7, 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 contain patches for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48307 | Nextcloud Mail app vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48307</link><description>Nextcloud Mail is the mail app for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. Starting in version 1.13.0 and prior to version 2.2.8 and 3.3.0, an attacker can use an unprotected endpoint in the Mail app to perform a SSRF attack. Nextcloud Mail app versions 2.2.8 and 3.3.0 contain a patch for this issue. As a workaround, disable the mail app.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48303 | Nextcloud Server admins can change authentication details of user configured external storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48303</link><description>Nextcloud Server provides data storage for Nextcloud, an open source cloud platform. Starting in version 25.0.0 and prior to versions 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 of Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server, admins can change authentication details of user configured external storage. Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server versions 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 contain a patch for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48304 | Nextcloud Server vulnerable to attacker enabling/disabling birthday calendar for any user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48304</link><description>Nextcloud Server provides data storage for Nextcloud, an open source cloud platform. Starting in version 25.0.0 and prior to versions 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 of Nextcloud Server and starting in version 22.0.0 and prior to versions 22.2.10.16, 23.0.12.11, 24.0.12.7, 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 of Nextcloud Enterprise Server, an attacker could enable and disable the birthday calendar for any user on the same server. Nextcloud Server 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server 22.2.10.16, 23.0.12.11, 24.0.12.7, 25.0.11, 26.0.6, and 27.1.0 contain patches for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48302 | Nextcloud Server vulnerable to Self XSS when pasting HTML into Text app with Ctrl+Shift+V</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48302</link><description>Nextcloud Server provides data storage for Nextcloud, an open source cloud platform. Starting in version 25.0.0 and prior to versions 25.0.13, 26.0.8, and 27.1.3 of Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server, when a user is tricked into copy pasting HTML code without markup (Ctrl+Shift+V) the markup will actually render. Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server versions 25.0.13, 26.0.8, and 27.1.3 contain a fix for this issue. As a workaround, disable app text.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6248 | Data leakage and arbitrary remote code execution in Syrus cloud devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6248</link><description>The Syrus4 IoT gateway utilizes an unsecured MQTT server to download and execute arbitrary commands, allowing a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute code on any Syrus4 device connected to the cloud service. The MQTT server also leaks the location, video and diagnostic data from each connected device. An attacker who knows the IP address of the server is able to connect and perform the following operations:

  *  Get location data of the vehicle the device is connected to
  *  Send CAN bus messages via the ECU module ( https://syrus.digitalcomtech.com/docs/ecu-1 https://syrus.digitalcomtech.com/docs/ecu-1 )

  *  Immobilize the vehicle via the safe-immobilizer module ( https://syrus.digitalcomtech.com/docs/system-tools#safe-immobilization https://syrus.digitalcomtech.com/docs/system-tools#safe-immobilization )

  *  Get live video through the connected video camera

  *  Send audio messages to the driver ( https://syrus.digitalcomtech.com/docs/system-tools#apx-tts https://syrus.digitalcomtech.com/docs/system-tools#apx-tts )</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48301 | Nextcloud Server HTML injection in search UI when selecting a circle with HTML in the display name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48301</link><description>Nextcloud Server provides data storage for Nextcloud, an open source cloud platform. Starting in version 25.0.0 and prior to versions 25.0.13, 26.0.8, and 27.1.3 of Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server, an attacker could insert links into circles name that would be opened when clicking the circle name in a search filter. Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server versions 25.0.13, 26.0.8, and 27.1.3 contain a fix for this issue. As a workaround, disable app circles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 21:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49103 | An issue was discovered in ownCloud owncloud/graphapi 0.2.x before 0.2.1 and 0.3.x before 0.3.1. The graphapi app relies on a third-party Ge...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49103</link><description>An issue was discovered in ownCloud owncloud/graphapi 0.2.x before 0.2.1 and 0.3.x before 0.3.1. The graphapi app relies on a third-party GetPhpInfo.php library that provides a URL. When this URL is accessed, it reveals the configuration details of the PHP environment (phpinfo). This information includes all the environment variables of the webserver. In containerized deployments, these environment variables may include sensitive data such as the ownCloud admin password, mail server credentials, and license key. Simply disabling the graphapi app does not eliminate the vulnerability. Additionally, phpinfo exposes various other potentially sensitive configuration details that could be exploited by an attacker to gather information about the system. Therefore, even if ownCloud is not running in a containerized environment, this vulnerability should still be a cause for concern. Note that Docker containers from before February 2023 are not vulnerable to the credential disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49104 | An issue was discovered in ownCloud owncloud/oauth2 before 0.6.1, when Allow Subdomains is enabled. An attacker is able to pass in a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49104</link><description>An issue was discovered in ownCloud owncloud/oauth2 before 0.6.1, when Allow Subdomains is enabled. An attacker is able to pass in a crafted redirect-url that bypasses validation, and consequently allows an attacker to redirect callbacks to a Top Level Domain controlled by the attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49105 | An issue was discovered in ownCloud owncloud/core before 10.13.1. An attacker can access, modify, or delete any file without authentication ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49105</link><description>An issue was discovered in ownCloud owncloud/core before 10.13.1. An attacker can access, modify, or delete any file without authentication if the username of a victim is known, and the victim has no signing-key configured. This occurs because pre-signed URLs can be accepted even when no signing-key is configured for the owner of the files. The earliest affected version is 10.6.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 21:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48239 | Nextcloud Server users can make external storage mount points inaccessible for other users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48239</link><description>Nextcloud Server provides data storage for Nextcloud, an open source cloud platform. Starting in version 25.0.0 and prior to versions 25.0.13, 26.0.8, and 27.1.3 of Nextcloud Server and starting in version 20.0.0 and prior to versions 20.0.14.16, 21.0.9.13, 22.2.10.15, 23.0.12.12, 24.0.12.8, 25.0.13, 26.0.8, and 27.1.3 of Nextcloud Enterprise Server, a malicious user could update any personal or global external storage, making them inaccessible for everyone else as well. Nextcloud Server 25.0.13, 26.0.8, and 27.1.3 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 20.0.14.16, 21.0.9.13, 22.2.10.15, 23.0.12.12, 24.0.12.8, 25.0.13, 26.0.8, and 27.1.3 contain a patch for this issue. As a workaround, disable app files_external. This workaround also makes the external storage inaccessible but retains the configurations until a patched version has been deployed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 21:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48230 | Cap&amp;#x27;n Proto WebSocket message can cause crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48230</link><description>Cap'n Proto is a data interchange format and capability-based RPC system. In versions 1.0 and 1.0.1, when using the KJ HTTP library with WebSocket compression enabled, a buffer underrun can be caused by a remote peer. The underrun always writes a constant value that is not attacker-controlled, likely resulting in a crash, enabling a remote denial-of-service attack. Most Cap'n Proto and KJ users are unlikely to have this functionality enabled and so unlikely to be affected. Maintainers suspect only the Cloudflare Workers Runtime is affected.

If KJ HTTP is used with WebSocket compression enabled, a malicious peer may be able to cause a buffer underrun on a heap-allocated buffer. KJ HTTP is an optional library bundled with Cap'n Proto, but is not directly used by Cap'n Proto. WebSocket compression is disabled by default. It must be enabled via a setting passed to the KJ HTTP library via `HttpClientSettings` or `HttpServerSettings`. The bytes written out-of-bounds are always a specific constant 4-byte string `{ 0x00, 0x00, 0xFF, 0xFF }`. Because this string is not controlled by the attacker, maintainers believe it is unlikely that remote code execution is possible. However, it cannot be ruled out. This functionality first appeared in Cap'n Proto 1.0. Previous versions are not affected.

This issue is fixed in Cap'n Proto 1.0.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 21:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48299 | TorchServe ZipSlip</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48299</link><description>TorchServe is a tool for serving and scaling PyTorch models in production. Starting in version 0.1.0 and prior to version 0.9.0, using the model/workflow management API, there is a chance of uploading potentially harmful archives that contain files that are extracted to any location on the filesystem that is within the process permissions. Leveraging this issue could aid third-party actors in hiding harmful code in open-source/public models, which can be downloaded from the internet, and take advantage of machines running Torchserve. The ZipSlip issue in TorchServe has been fixed by validating the paths of files contained within a zip archive before extracting them. TorchServe release 0.9.0 includes fixes to address the ZipSlip vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 21:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48228 | OAuth2: PKCE can be fully circumvented</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48228</link><description>authentik is an open-source identity provider. When initialising a oauth2 flow with a `code_challenge` and `code_method` (thus requesting PKCE), the single sign-on provider (authentik) must check if there is a matching and existing `code_verifier` during the token step. Prior to versions 2023.10.4 and 2023.8.5, authentik checks if the contents of `code_verifier` is matching only when it is provided. When it is left out completely, authentik simply accepts the token request with out it; even when the flow was started with a `code_challenge`. authentik 2023.8.5 and 2023.10.4 fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 20:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6238 | Kernel: nvme: memory corruption via unprivileged user passthrough</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6238</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was found in the NVM Express (NVMe) driver in the Linux kernel. An unprivileged user could specify a small meta buffer and let the device perform larger Direct Memory Access (DMA) into the same buffer, overwriting unrelated kernel memory, causing random kernel crashes and memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 20:24:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48226 | OpenReplay HTML Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48226</link><description>OpenReplay is a self-hosted session replay suite. In version 1.14.0, due to lack of validation Name field - Account Settings (for registration looks like validation is correct), a bad actor can send emails with HTML injected code to the victims. Bad actors can use this to phishing actions for example. Email is really send from OpenReplay, but bad actors can add there HTML code injected (content spoofing). Please notice that during Registration steps for FullName looks like is validated correct - can not type there, but using this kind of bypass/workaround - bad actors can achieve own goal. As of time of publication, no known fixes or workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 19:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47643 | SuiteCRM has Unauthenticated Graphql Introspection Enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47643</link><description>SuiteCRM is a Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Prior to version 8.4.2, Graphql Introspection is enabled without authentication, exposing the scheme defining all object types, arguments, and functions. An attacker can obtain the GraphQL schema and understand the entire attack surface of the API, including sensitive fields such as UserHash. This issue is patched in version 8.4.2. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 19:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20208 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack ag...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20208</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20272 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20272</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload malicious files to the web root of the application. This vulnerability is due to insufficient file input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a malicious file to the web interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to replace files and gain access to sensitive server-side information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20274 | A vulnerability in the installer script of Cisco AppDynamics PHP Agent could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20274</link><description>A vulnerability in the installer script of Cisco AppDynamics PHP Agent could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient permissions that are set by the PHP Agent Installer on the PHP Agent install directory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by modifying objects in the PHP Agent install directory, which would run with the same privileges as PHP. A successful exploit could allow a lower-privileged attacker to elevate their privileges to root on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20265 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of a small subset of Cisco IP Phones could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20265</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of a small subset of Cisco IP Phones could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of an affected interface to view a page containing malicious HTML or script content. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid credentials to access the web-based management interface of the affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-38405 | Siemens Solid Edge, JT2Go, and Teamcenter Visualization Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38405</link><description>The Datalogics APDFL library used in affected products is vulnerable to memory corruption condition while parsing specially crafted PDF files. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22516 | This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in versions 8.1.0, 8.2.0, 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, and 9.3.0 of Bamb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22516</link><description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in versions 8.1.0, 8.2.0, 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, and 9.3.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.&#13;
&#13;
This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.5, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.&#13;
&#13;
Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:&#13;
 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.2: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.2.7.&#13;
  JDK 1.8u121+ should be used in case Java 8 used to run Bamboo Data Center and Server. See Bamboo 9.2 Upgrade notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-9-2-upgrade-notes-1207179212.html)&#13;
&#13;
 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.3: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.3.4&#13;
&#13;
See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html]). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives]).&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability was discovered by a private user and reported via our Bug Bounty program</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22521 | This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 3.4.6 of Crowd Data Center and Server.&#13;
&#13;
This RCE (R...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22521</link><description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 3.4.6 of Crowd Data Center and Server.&#13;
&#13;
This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.0, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.&#13;
&#13;
Atlassian recommends that Crowd Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:&#13;
 Crowd Data Center and Server 3.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 5.1.6&#13;
 Crowd Data Center and Server 5.2: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 5.2.1&#13;
&#13;
See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/crowd/crowd-release-notes-199094.html]). You can download the latest version of Crowd Data Center and Server from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/crowd/download-archive]).&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability was discovered by m1sn0w and reported via our Bug Bounty program</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5055 | L2CAP: Possible Stack based buffer overflow in le_ecred_reconf_req()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5055</link><description>Possible variant of CVE-2021-3434 in function le_ecred_reconf_req.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-27504 | Texas Instruments FREERTOS Integer Overflow or Wraparound</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-27504</link><description>Texas Instruments devices running FREERTOS, malloc returns a valid 
pointer to a small buffer on extremely large values, which can trigger 
an integer overflow vulnerability in 'malloc' for FreeRTOS, resulting in
 code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-27502 | Texas Instruments TI-RTOS Integer Overflow or Wraparound</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-27502</link><description>Texas Instruments TI-RTOS, when configured to use HeapMem heap(default),
 malloc returns a valid pointer to a small buffer on extremely large 
values, which can trigger an integer overflow vulnerability in 
'HeapMem_allocUnprotected' and result in code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49060 | An attacker could have accessed internal pages or data by ex-filtrating a security key from ReaderMode via the `referrerpolicy` attribute. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49060</link><description>An attacker could have accessed internal pages or data by ex-filtrating a security key from ReaderMode via the `referrerpolicy` attribute. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 120.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49061 | An attacker could have performed HTML template injection via Reader Mode and exfiltrated user information. This vulnerability affects Firefo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49061</link><description>An attacker could have performed HTML template injection via Reader Mode and exfiltrated user information. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 120.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6204 | On some systems—depending on the graphics settings and drivers—it was possible to force an out-of-bounds read and leak memory data into the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6204</link><description>On some systems—depending on the graphics settings and drivers—it was possible to force an out-of-bounds read and leak memory data into the images created on the canvas element. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120, Firefox &lt; 115.5, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.5.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6205 | It was possible to cause the use of a MessagePort after it had already been freed, which could potentially have led to an exploitable crash....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6205</link><description>It was possible to cause the use of a MessagePort after it had already been freed, which could potentially have led to an exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120, Firefox &lt; 115.5, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.5.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6206 | The black fade animation when exiting fullscreen is roughly the length of the anti-clickjacking delay on permission prompts. It was possible...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6206</link><description>The black fade animation when exiting fullscreen is roughly the length of the anti-clickjacking delay on permission prompts. It was possible to use this fact to surprise users by luring them to click where the permission grant button would be about to appear. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120, Firefox &lt; 115.5, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.5.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6207 | Ownership mismanagement led to a use-after-free in ReadableByteStreams This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120, Firefox &lt; 115.5, and Thunde...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6207</link><description>Ownership mismanagement led to a use-after-free in ReadableByteStreams This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120, Firefox &lt; 115.5, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.5.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6208 | When using X11, text selected by the page using the Selection API was erroneously copied into the primary selection, a temporary storage not...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6208</link><description>When using X11, text selected by the page using the Selection API was erroneously copied into the primary selection, a temporary storage not unlike the clipboard.
*This bug only affects Thunderbird on X11. Other systems are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120, Firefox &lt; 115.5, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.5.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6209 | Relative URLs starting with three slashes were incorrectly parsed, and a path-traversal "/../" part in the path could be used to override th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6209</link><description>Relative URLs starting with three slashes were incorrectly parsed, and a path-traversal "/../" part in the path could be used to override the specified host. This could contribute to security problems in web sites. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120, Firefox &lt; 115.5, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.5.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6210 | When an https: web page created a pop-up from a "javascript:" URL, that pop-up was incorrectly allowed to load blockable content such as ifr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6210</link><description>When an https: web page created a pop-up from a "javascript:" URL, that pop-up was incorrectly allowed to load blockable content such as iframes from insecure http: URLs This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6211 | If an attacker needed a user to load an insecure http: page and knew that user had enabled HTTPS-only mode, the attacker could have tricked ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6211</link><description>If an attacker needed a user to load an insecure http: page and knew that user had enabled HTTPS-only mode, the attacker could have tricked the user into clicking to grant an HTTPS-only exception if they could get the user to participate in a clicking game. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6212 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 119, Firefox 115.4, and Thunderbird 115.4. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6212</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 119, Firefox 115.4, and Thunderbird 115.4. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120, Firefox &lt; 115.5, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.5.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6213 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 119. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort so...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6213</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 119. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 120.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48124 | Cross Site Scripting in SUP Online Shopping v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Name, Email and Address paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48124</link><description>Cross Site Scripting in SUP Online Shopping v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Name, Email and Address parameters in the Register New Account component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6235 | Arbitrary code execution in Duet Display</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6235</link><description>An uncontrolled search path element vulnerability has been found in the Duet Display product, affecting version 2.5.9.1. An attacker could place an arbitrary libusk.dll file in the C:\Users\user\AppData\Local\Microsoft\WindowsApps\ directory, which could lead to the execution and persistence of arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 12:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28802 | Disable Zscaler using machine tunnel restart</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28802</link><description>An Improper Validation of Integrity Check Value in Zscaler Client Connector on Windows allows an authenticated user to disable ZIA/ZPA by interrupting the service restart from Zscaler Diagnostics. This issue affects Client Connector: before 4.2.0.149.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 11:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5598 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities affecting 3DSwym in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5598</link><description>Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilitiesÂ affecting 3DSwym in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x allow an attacker to execute arbitrary script code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 09:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5599 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DDashboard in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5599</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DDashboard in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 09:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5776 | The Post Meta Data Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5776</link><description>The Post Meta Data Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1. This is due to missing nonce validation on the pmdm_wp_ajax_delete_meta, pmdm_wp_delete_user_meta, and pmdm_wp_delete_user_meta functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary user, term, and post meta via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 08:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4149 | WAGO: OS Command Injection Vulnerability in Managed Switch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4149</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to inject arbitrary system commands and gain full system control. Those commands are executed with root privileges. The vulnerability is located in the user request handling of the web-based management.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 07:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5553 | During internal Axis Security Development Model (ASDM) threat-modelling, a flaw was found in the protection for device tampering (commonly k...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5553</link><description>During internal Axis Security Development Model (ASDM) threat-modelling, a flaw was found in the protection for device tampering (commonly known as Secure Boot) in AXIS OS making it vulnerable to a sophisticated attack to bypass this protection. To Axis' knowledge, there are no known exploits of the vulnerability at this time. Axis has released patched AXIS OS versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 07:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21417 | Sandro Poppi, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program,

has found that the VAPIX API manageoverlayimage.cgi was vulnerable to path traversa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21417</link><description>Sandro Poppi, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program,

has found that the VAPIX API manageoverlayimage.cgi was vulnerable to path traversal attacks that allows for file/folder deletion. This flaw can only be exploited after authenticating with an operator- or administrator- privileged service account. The impact of exploiting this vulnerability is lower with operator service accounts and limited to non-system files compared to administrator-privileges.
 Axis has released patched AXIS OS versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 07:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21418 | Sandro Poppi, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX API irissetup.cgi was vulnerable to path traversal attacks ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21418</link><description>Sandro Poppi, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX API irissetup.cgi was vulnerable to path traversal attacks that allows for file deletion. This flaw can only be exploited after authenticating with an operator- or administrator-privileged service account. The impact of exploiting this vulnerability is lower with operator service accounts and limited to non-system files compared to administrator-privileges. Axis has released patched AXIS OS versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 07:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21416 | Sandro Poppi, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX API dynamicoverlay.cgi was vulnerable to a Denial-of-Servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21416</link><description>Sandro Poppi, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX API dynamicoverlay.cgi was vulnerable to a Denial-of-Service attack allowing for an attacker to block access to the overlay configuration page in the web interface of the Axis device. This flaw can only be exploited after authenticating with an operator- or administrator-privileged service account however the impact is equal. Axis has released patched AXIS OS versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 06:53:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4424 | bt: hci: DoS and possible RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4424</link><description>An malicious BLE device can cause buffer overflow by sending malformed advertising packet BLE device using Zephyr OS, leading to DoS or potential RCE on the victim BLE device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 06:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46935 | eyoucms v1.6.4 is vulnerable Cross Site Scripting (XSS), which can lead to stealing sensitive information of logged-in users.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46935</link><description>eyoucms v1.6.4 is vulnerable Cross Site Scripting (XSS), which can lead to stealing sensitive information of logged-in users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 06:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45886 | The BGP daemon (bgpd) in IP Infusion ZebOS through 7.10.6 allow remote attackers to cause a denial of service by sending crafted BGP update ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45886</link><description>The BGP daemon (bgpd) in IP Infusion ZebOS through 7.10.6 allow remote attackers to cause a denial of service by sending crafted BGP update messages containing a malformed attribute.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 05:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5274 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability in simulation function of GX Works2 allows an attacker to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5274</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in simulation function of GX Works2 allows an attacker to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition on the function by sending specially crafted packets. However, the attacker would need to send the packets from within the same personal computer where the function is running.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 03:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5275 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability in simulation function of GX Works2 allows an attacker to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5275</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in simulation function of GX Works2 allows an attacker to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition on the function by sending specially crafted packets. However, the attacker would need to send the packets from within the same personal computer where the function is running.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 03:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42770 | Red Lion Controls Sixnet RTU Authentication Bypass Using An Alternative Path Or Channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42770</link><description>Red Lion SixTRAK and VersaTRAK Series RTUs with authenticated users enabled (UDR-A) any Sixnet UDR message will meet an authentication challenge over UDP/IP. When the same message is received over TCP/IP the RTU will simply accept the message with no authentication challenge.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 02:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40151 | Red Lion Controls Sixnet RTU Exposed Dangerous Method Or Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40151</link><description>When user authentication is not enabled the shell can execute commands with the highest privileges. Red Lion SixTRAK and VersaTRAK Series RTUs with authenticated users enabled (UDR-A) any Sixnet UDR message will meet an authentication challenge over UDP/IP. When the same message comes over TCP/IP the RTU will simply accept the message with no authentication challenge.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 02:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6142 | Dev Blog v1.0 - Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6142</link><description>Dev blog v1.0 allows to exploit an XSS through an unrestricted file upload, together with a bad entropy of filenames. With this an attacker can upload a malicious HTML file, then guess the filename of the uploaded file and send it to a potential victim.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 23:37:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6144 | Dev Blog v1.0 - ATO</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6144</link><description>Dev blog v1.0 allows to exploit an account takeover through the "user" cookie. With this, an attacker can access any user's session just by knowing their username.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 23:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48310 | Ability to DoS the testing infrastructure by overwriting files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48310</link><description>TestingPlatform is a testing platform for Internet Security Standards. Prior to version 2.1.1, user input is not filtered correctly. Nmap options are accepted. In this particular case, the option to create log files is accepted in addition to a host name (and even without). A log file is created at the location specified. These files are created as root. If the file exists, the existing file is being rendered useless. This can result in denial of service. Version 2.1.1 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 23:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48051 | An issue in /upydev/keygen.py in upydev v0.4.3 allows attackers to decrypt sensitive information via weak encryption padding.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48051</link><description>An issue in /upydev/keygen.py in upydev v0.4.3 allows attackers to decrypt sensitive information via weak encryption padding.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 22:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6199 | Book Stack v23.10.2 - LFR via Blind SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6199</link><description>Book Stack version 23.10.2 allows filtering local files on the server. This is possible because the application is vulnerable to SSRF.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 22:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48192 | An issue in TOTOlink A3700R v.9.1.2u.6134_B20201202 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the setTracerouteCfg function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48192</link><description>An issue in TOTOlink A3700R v.9.1.2u.6134_B20201202 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the setTracerouteCfg function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 21:52:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48176 | An Insecure Permissions issue in WebsiteGuide v.0.2 allows a remote attacker to gain escalated privileges via crafted jwt (JSON web token).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48176</link><description>An Insecure Permissions issue in WebsiteGuide v.0.2 allows a remote attacker to gain escalated privileges via crafted jwt (JSON web token).</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 21:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47172 | Certain WithSecure products allow Local Privilege Escalation. This affects WithSecure Client Security 15, WithSecure Server Security 15, Wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47172</link><description>Certain WithSecure products allow Local Privilege Escalation. This affects WithSecure Client Security 15, WithSecure Server Security 15, WithSecure Email and Server Security 15, and WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection 17 and later.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 20:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47311 | An issue in Yamcs 5.8.6 allows attackers to send aribitrary telelcommands in a Command Stack via Clickjacking.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47311</link><description>An issue in Yamcs 5.8.6 allows attackers to send aribitrary telelcommands in a Command Stack via Clickjacking.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 20:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6178 | An arbitrary file write vulnerability exists where an authenticated attacker with privileges on the managing application could alter Nessus ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6178</link><description>An arbitrary file write vulnerability exists where an authenticated attacker with privileges on the managing application could alter Nessus Rules variables to overwrite arbitrary files on the remote host, which could lead to a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 20:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46471 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Space Applications Services Yamcs v.5.8.6 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46471</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Space Applications Services Yamcs v.5.8.6 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the text variable scriptContainer of the ScriptViewer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 20:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6062 | Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6062</link><description>An arbitrary file write vulnerability exists where an authenticated, remote attacker with administrator privileges on the Nessus application could alter Nessus Rules variables to overwrite arbitrary files on the remote host, which could lead to a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 20:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46470 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Space Applications Services Yamcs v.5.8.6 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46470</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Space Applications Services Yamcs v.5.8.6 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via crafted telecommand in the timeline view of the ArchiveBrowser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 20:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48109 | Tenda AX1803 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a heap overflow via the deviceId parameter in the function saveParentControlInfo . This vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48109</link><description>Tenda AX1803 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a heap overflow via the deviceId parameter in the function saveParentControlInfo . This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 20:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48110 | Tenda AX1803 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a heap overflow via the urls parameter in the function saveParentControlInfo . This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48110</link><description>Tenda AX1803 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a heap overflow via the urls parameter in the function saveParentControlInfo . This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 20:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48111 | Tenda AX1803 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the time parameter in the function saveParentControlInfo . This vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48111</link><description>Tenda AX1803 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the time parameter in the function saveParentControlInfo . This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 20:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46990 | Deserialization of Untrusted Data in PublicCMS v.4.0.202302.e allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46990</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data in PublicCMS v.4.0.202302.e allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the writeReplace function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38823 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Tenda Ac19 v.1.0, AC18, AC9 v.1.0, AC6 v.2.0 and v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38823</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Tenda Ac19 v.1.0, AC18, AC9 v.1.0, AC6 v.2.0 and v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the formSetCfm function in bin/httpd.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47417 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /shells/embedder.html of DZSlides after v2011.07.25 allows attackers to execute ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47417</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /shells/embedder.html of DZSlides after v2011.07.25 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22636 | Texas Instruments TI-RTOS Integer Overflow or Wraparound</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22636</link><description>Texas Instruments TI-RTOS, when configured to use HeapMem heap(default), malloc returns a valid pointer to a small buffer on extremely large values, which can trigger an integer overflow vulnerability in 'HeapMem_allocUnprotected' and result in code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:17:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-27429 | Texas Instruments TI-RTOS Integer Overflow or Wraparound</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-27429</link><description>Texas Instruments TI-RTOS returns a valid pointer to a small buffer on extremely large values. This can trigger an integer overflow vulnerability in 'HeapTrack_alloc' and result in code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4799 | Magic Embeds &amp;lt; 3.1.2 - Contributor+ Stored XSS via shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4799</link><description>The Magic Embeds WordPress plugin before 3.1.2 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4808 | WP Post Popup &amp;lt;= 3.7.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4808</link><description>The WP Post Popup WordPress plugin through 3.7.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its inputs, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4824 | WooHoo Newspaper Magazine Theme &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4824</link><description>The WooHoo Newspaper Magazine theme does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4970 | PubyDoc &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4970</link><description>The PubyDoc WordPress plugin through 2.0.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5119 | Forminator and Forminator Pro &amp;lt; 1.27.0 - Admin+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5119</link><description>The Forminator WordPress plugin before 1.27.0 does not properly sanitize the redirect-url field in the form submission settings, which could allow high-privilege users such as an administrator to inject arbitrary web scripts even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in a multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5140 | Bonus for Woo &amp;lt; 5.8.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5140</link><description>The Bonus for Woo WordPress plugin before 5.8.3 does not sanitise and escape some parameters before outputting them back in pages, leading to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5340 | Five Star Restaurant Menu and Food Ordering &amp;lt; 2.4.11 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5340</link><description>The Five Star Restaurant Menu and Food Ordering WordPress plugin before 2.4.11 unserializes user input via an AJAX action available to unauthenticated users, allowing them to perform PHP Object Injection when a suitable gadget is present on the blog.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5343 | Popup Box &amp;lt; 3.7.9 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5343</link><description>The Popup box WordPress plugin before 3.7.9 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5509 | myStickymenu &amp;lt; 2.6.5 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Form Leads Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5509</link><description>The myStickymenu WordPress plugin before 2.6.5 does not adequately authorize some ajax calls, allowing any logged-in user to perform the actions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5609 | Seraphinite Accelerator &amp;lt; 2.20.29 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5609</link><description>The Seraphinite Accelerator WordPress plugin before 2.2.29 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5610 | Seraphinite Accelerator &amp;lt; 2.20.29 - Authenticated Arbitrary Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5610</link><description>The Seraphinite Accelerator WordPress plugin before 2.2.29 does not validate the URL to redirect any authenticated user to, leading to an arbitrary redirect</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5640 | Article Analytics &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Unauthenticated SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5640</link><description>The Article Analytics WordPress plugin does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement via an AJAX action available to unauthenticated users, leading to a SQL injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5651 | WP Hotel Booking &amp;lt; 2.0.8 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5651</link><description>The WP Hotel Booking WordPress plugin before 2.0.8 does not have authorisation and CSRF checks, as well as does not ensure that the package to be deleted is a package, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber to delete arbitrary posts</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5652 | WP Hotel Booking &amp;lt; 2.0.8 - Unauthenticated SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5652</link><description>The WP Hotel Booking WordPress plugin before 2.0.8 does not have authorisation and CSRF checks, as well as does not escape user input before using it in a SQL statement of a function hooked to admin_init, allowing unauthenticated users to perform SQL injections</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5799 | WP Hotel Booking &amp;lt; 2.0.9 - Contributor+ Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5799</link><description>The WP Hotel Booking WordPress plugin before 2.0.8 does not have proper authorisation when deleting a package, allowing Contributor and above roles to delete posts that do no belong to them</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38879 | The Community Edition version 9.0 of OS4ED's openSIS Classic allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a directory traversal vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38879</link><description>The Community Edition version 9.0 of OS4ED's openSIS Classic allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a directory traversal vulnerability in the 'filename' parameter of 'DownloadWindow.php'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38880 | The Community Edition version 9.0 of OS4ED's openSIS Classic has a broken access control vulnerability in the database backup functionality....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38880</link><description>The Community Edition version 9.0 of OS4ED's openSIS Classic has a broken access control vulnerability in the database backup functionality. Whenever an admin generates a database backup, the backup is stored in the web root while the file name has a format of "opensisBackup&lt;date&gt;.sq|" (e.g. "opensisBackup07-20-2023.sql"), i.e. can easily be guessed. This file can be accessed by any unauthenticated actor and contains a dump of the whole database including password hashes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38881 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Community Edition version 9.0 of OS4ED's openSIS Classic allows remote attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38881</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Community Edition version 9.0 of OS4ED's openSIS Classic allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the web browser of a user, by including a malicious payload into any of the 'calendar_id', 'school_date', 'month' or 'year' parameters in 'CalendarModal.php'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38882 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Community Edition version 9.0 of OS4ED's openSIS Classic allows remote attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38882</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Community Edition version 9.0 of OS4ED's openSIS Classic allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the web browser of a user, by including a malicious payload into the 'include' parameter in 'ForExport.php'</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38883 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Community Edition version 9.0 of OS4ED's openSIS Classic allows remote attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38883</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Community Edition version 9.0 of OS4ED's openSIS Classic allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the web browser of a user, by including a malicious payload into the 'ajax' parameter in 'ParentLookup.php'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38884 | An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in the Community Edition version 9.0 of openSIS Classic allows an unauthenticated r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38884</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in the Community Edition version 9.0 of openSIS Classic allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to access any student's files by visiting '/assets/studentfiles/&lt;studentId&gt;-&lt;filename&gt;'</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38885 | OpenSIS Classic Community Edition version 9.0 lacks cross-site request forgery (CSRF) protection throughout the whole app. This may allow an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38885</link><description>OpenSIS Classic Community Edition version 9.0 lacks cross-site request forgery (CSRF) protection throughout the whole app. This may allow an attacker to trick an authenticated user into performing any kind of state changing request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48309 | next-auth vulnerable to possible user mocking that bypasses basic authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48309</link><description>NextAuth.js provides authentication for Next.js. `next-auth` applications prior to version 4.24.5 that rely on the default Middleware authorization are affected by a vulnerability. A bad actor could create an empty/mock user, by getting hold of a NextAuth.js-issued JWT from an interrupted OAuth sign-in flow (state, PKCE or nonce). Manually overriding the `next-auth.session-token` cookie value with this non-related JWT would let the user simulate a logged in user, albeit having no user information associated with it. (The only property on this user is an opaque randomly generated string). This vulnerability does not give access to other users' data, neither to resources that require proper authorization via scopes or other means. The created mock user has no information associated with it (ie. no name, email, access_token, etc.) This vulnerability can be exploited by bad actors to peek at logged in user states (e.g. dashboard layout). `next-auth` `v4.24.5` contains a patch for the vulnerability. As a workaround, using a custom authorization callback for Middleware, developers can manually do a basic authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48293 | XWiki Admin Tools Application CSRF with QueryOnXWiki allows arbitrary database queries</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48293</link><description>The XWiki Admin Tools Application provides tools to help the administration of XWiki. Prior to version 4.5.1, a cross-site request forgery vulnerability in the query on XWiki tool allows executing arbitrary database queries on the database of the XWiki installation. Among other things, this allows modifying and deleting all data of the wiki. This could be both used to damage the wiki and to create an account with elevated privileges for the attacker, thus impacting the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki instance. A possible attack vector are comments on the wiki, by embedding an image with wiki syntax like `[[image:path:/xwiki/bin/view/Admin/QueryOnXWiki?query=DELETE%20FROM%20xwikidoc]]`, all documents would be deleted from the database when an admin user views this comment. This has been patched in Admin Tools Application 4.5.1 by adding form token checks. Some workarounds are available. The patch can also be applied manually to the affected pages. Alternatively, if the query tool is not needed, by deleting the document `Admin.SQLToolsGroovy`, all database query tools can be deactivated.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48300 | Embed Privacy missing escaping for show_all attribute in opt-out shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48300</link><description>The `Embed Privacy` plugin for WordPress that prevents the loading of embedded external content is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via `embed_privacy_opt_out` shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Version 1.8.1 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48241 | XWiki exposed whole content of all documents of all wikis to anybody with view right on Solr suggest service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48241</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 6.3-milestone-2 and prior to versions 14.10.15, 15.5.1, and 15.6RC1, the Solr-based search suggestion provider that also duplicates as generic JavaScript API for search results in XWiki exposes the content of all documents of all wikis to anybody who has access to it, by default it is public. This exposes all information stored in the wiki (but not some protected information like password hashes). While there is a right check normally, the right check can be circumvented by explicitly requesting fields from Solr that don't include the data for the right check. This has been fixed in XWiki 15.6RC1, 15.5.1 and 14.10.15 by not listing documents whose rights cannot be checked. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48292 | XWiki Admin Tools Application Run Shell Command allows CSRF RCE attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48292</link><description>The XWiki Admin Tools Application provides tools to help the administration of XWiki. Starting in version 4.4 and prior to version 4.5.1, a cross site request forgery vulnerability in the admin tool for executing shell commands on the server allows an attacker to execute arbitrary shell commands by tricking an admin into loading the URL with the shell command. A very simple possibility for an attack are comments. When the attacker can leave a comment on any page in the wiki it is sufficient to include an image with an URL like  `/xwiki/bin/view/Admin/RunShellCommand?command=touch%20/tmp/attacked` in the comment. When an admin views the comment, the file `/tmp/attacked` will be created on the server. The output of the command is also vulnerable to XWiki syntax injection which offers a simple way to execute Groovy in the context of the XWiki installation and thus an even easier way to compromise the integrity and confidentiality of the whole XWiki installation. This has been patched by adding a form token check in version 4.5.1 of the admin tools. Some workarounds are available. The patch can be applied manually to the affected wiki pages. Alternatively, the document `Admin.RunShellCommand` can also be deleted if the possibility to run shell commands isn't needed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48240 | XWiki Platform sends cookies to external images in rendered diff and is vulnerable to server side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48240</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. The rendered diff in XWiki embeds images to be able to compare the contents and not display a difference for an actually unchanged image. For this, XWiki requests all embedded images on the server side. These requests are also sent for images from other domains and include all cookies that were sent in the original request to ensure that images with restricted view right can be compared. Starting in version 11.10.1 and prior to versions 14.10.15, 15.5.1, and 15.6, this allows an attacker to steal login and session cookies that allow impersonating the current user who views the diff. The attack can be triggered with an image that references the rendered diff, thus making it easy to trigger. Apart from stealing login cookies, this also allows server-side request forgery (the result of any successful request is returned in the image's source) and viewing protected content as once a resource is cached, it is returned for all users. As only successful requests are cached, the cache will be filled by the first user who is allowed to access the resource. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.15, 15.5.1 and 15.6. The rendered diff now only downloads images from trusted domains. Further, cookies are only sent when the image's domain is the same the requested domain. The cache has been changed to be specific for each user. As a workaround, the image embedding feature can be disabled by deleting `xwiki-platform-diff-xml-&lt;version&gt;.jar` in `WEB-INF/lib/`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 17:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48223 | fast-jwt JWT Algorithm Confusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48223</link><description>fast-jwt provides fast JSON Web Token (JWT) implementation. Prior to version 3.3.2, the fast-jwt library does not properly prevent JWT algorithm confusion for all public key types. The 'publicKeyPemMatcher' in 'fast-jwt/src/crypto.js' does not properly match all common PEM formats for public keys. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker needs to craft a malicious JWT token containing the HS256 algorithm, signed with the public RSA key of the victim application. This attack will only work if the victim application utilizes a public key containing the `BEGIN RSA PUBLIC KEY` header. Applications using the RS256 algorithm, a public key with a `BEGIN RSA PUBLIC KEY` header, and calling the verify function without explicitly providing an algorithm, are vulnerable to this algorithm confusion attack which allows attackers to sign arbitrary payloads which will be accepted by the verifier. Version 3.3.2 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, change line 29 of `blob/master/src/crypto.js` to include a regular expression.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 17:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48221 | wire-avs remote format string vulnerability </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48221</link><description>wire-avs provides Audio, Visual, and Signaling (AVS) functionality sure the secure messaging software Wire. Prior to versions 9.2.22 and 9.3.5, a remote format string vulnerability could potentially allow an attacker to cause a denial of service or possibly execute arbitrary code. The issue has been fixed in wire-avs 9.2.22 &amp; 9.3.5 and is already included on all Wire products. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 17:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48218 | Strapi Protected Populate Plugin leaking fields if the request fields where empty or only fields selected where not populatable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48218</link><description>The Strapi Protected Populate Plugin protects `get` endpoints from revealing too much information. Prior to version 1.3.4, users were able to bypass the field level security. Users who tried to populate something that they didn't have access to could populate those fields anyway. This issue has been patched in version 1.3.4. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 17:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29155 | Improper Authentication INEA ME RTU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29155</link><description>Versions of INEA ME RTU firmware 3.36b and prior do not require authentication to the "root" account on the host system of the device. This could allow an attacker to obtain admin-level access to the host system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 16:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35762 | OS Command Injection in INEA ME RTU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35762</link><description>Versions of INEA ME RTU firmware 3.36b and prior are vulnerable to operating system (OS) command injection, which could allow remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 16:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36013 | PowerShell Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36013</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 16:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48039 | GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev617-g671976fcc-master is vulnerable to memory leak in gf_mpd_parse_string media_tools/mpd.c:75.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48039</link><description>GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev617-g671976fcc-master is vulnerable to memory leak in gf_mpd_parse_string media_tools/mpd.c:75.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 15:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48090 | GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev617-g671976fcc-master is vulnerable to memory leaks in extract_attributes media_tools/m3u8.c:329.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48090</link><description>GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev617-g671976fcc-master is vulnerable to memory leaks in extract_attributes media_tools/m3u8.c:329.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 15:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6196 | The Audio Merchant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.4. This is due...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6196</link><description>The Audio Merchant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the function audio_merchant_add_audio_file function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 14:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6197 | The Audio Merchant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.4. This is due...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6197</link><description>The Audio Merchant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the audio_merchant_save_settings function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 14:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47772 | WordPress Slider Revolution Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.6.14 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47772</link><description>Contributor+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Slider Revolution &lt;= 6.6.14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 14:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5593 | The out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the Windows-based SecuExtender SSL VPN Client software version 4.0.4.0 could allow an authenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5593</link><description>The out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the Windows-based SecuExtender SSL VPN Client software version 4.0.4.0 could allow an authenticated local user to gain a privilege escalation by sending a crafted CREATE message.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 12:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42774 | Liteos-A has a incorrect default permissions vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42774</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.2 and prior versions allow a local attacker get confidential information through  incorrect default permissions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 12:00:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43612 | Hiview has an improper preservation of permissions vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43612</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.2 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary file read and write through improper preservation of permissions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 12:00:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46100 | Cert manager has a use of uninitialized resource vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46100</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.2 and prior versions allow a local attacker get sensitive buffer information through use of uninitialized resource.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 12:00:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46705 | Arkruntime has a type confusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46705</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.2 and prior versions allow a local attacker causes system information leak through type confusion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 12:00:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47217 | Arkruntime has a buffer overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47217</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.2 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause DOS through buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 12:00:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6045 | Arkruntime has a type confusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6045</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.2 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through type confusion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 12:00:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3116 | Liteos-A has a incorrect default permissions vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3116</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.2 and prior versions allow a local attacker get confidential information or rewrite sensitive file through  incorrect default permissions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 11:49:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46337 | Apache Derby: LDAP injection vulnerability in authenticator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46337</link><description>A cleverly devised username might bypass LDAP authentication checks. In 
LDAP-authenticated Derby installations, this could let an attacker fill 
up the disk by creating junk Derby databases. In LDAP-authenticated 
Derby installations, this could also allow the attacker to execute 
malware which was visible to and executable by the account which booted 
the Derby server. In LDAP-protected databases which weren't also 
protected by SQL GRANT/REVOKE authorization, this vulnerability could 
also let an attacker view and corrupt sensitive data and run sensitive 
database functions and procedures.

Mitigation:

Users should upgrade to Java 21 and Derby 10.17.1.0.

Alternatively, users who wish to remain on older Java versions should 
build their own Derby distribution from one of the release families to 
which the fix was backported: 10.16, 10.15, and 10.14. Those are the 
releases which correspond, respectively, with Java LTS versions 17, 11, 
and 8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 08:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46302 | Apache Submarine: Fix CVE-2022-1471 SnakeYaml unsafe deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46302</link><description>Apache Software Foundation Apache Submarine has a bug when serializing against yaml. The bug is caused by snakeyaml  https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2022-1471 .

Apache Submarine uses JAXRS to define REST endpoints.  In order to
handle YAML requests (using application/yaml content-type), it defines
a YamlEntityProvider entity provider that will process all incoming
YAML requests.  In order to unmarshal the request, the readFrom method
is invoked, passing the entityStream containing the user-supplied data in `submarine-server/server-core/src/main/java/org/apache/submarine/server/utils/YamlUtils.java`.
 
We have now fixed this issue in the new version by replacing to `jackson-dataformat-yaml`.
This issue affects Apache Submarine: from 0.7.0 before 0.8.0. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.8.0, which fixes this issue.
If using the version smaller than 0.8.0  and not want to upgrade, you can try cherry-pick PR  https://github.com/apache/submarine/pull/1054  and rebuild the submart-server image to fix this.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 08:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3379 | WAGO: Improper Privilege Management in web-based management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3379</link><description>Wago web-based management of multiple products has a vulnerability which allows an local authenticated attacker  to change the passwords of other non-admin users and thus to escalate non-root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 07:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46700 | SQL injection vulnerability in LuxCal Web Calendar prior to 5.2.4M (MySQL version) and LuxCal Web Calendar prior to 5.2.4L (SQLite version) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46700</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in LuxCal Web Calendar prior to 5.2.4M (MySQL version) and LuxCal Web Calendar prior to 5.2.4L (SQLite version) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute an arbitrary SQL command by sending a crafted request, and obtain or alter information stored in the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 04:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47175 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability in LuxCal Web Calendar prior to 5.2.4M (MySQL version) and LuxCal Web Calendar prior to 5.2.4L (SQLite ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47175</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability in LuxCal Web Calendar prior to 5.2.4M (MySQL version) and LuxCal Web Calendar prior to 5.2.4L (SQLite version) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute an arbitrary script on the web browser of the user who is accessing the product.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 04:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5341 | Imagemagick: heap use-after-free in coders/bmp.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5341</link><description>A heap use-after-free flaw was found in coders/bmp.c in ImageMagick.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 09:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>