<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 01:16:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-58357 | 5ire Chat Message XSS Vulnerability Enables Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58357</link><description>5ire is a cross-platform desktop artificial intelligence assistant and model context protocol client. Version 0.13.2 contains a vulnerability in the chat page's script gadgets that enables content injection attacks through multiple vectors: malicious prompt injection pages, compromised MCP servers, and exploited tool integrations. This is fixed in version 0.14.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 01:16:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58358 | Markdownify is vulnerable to command injection through pptx-to-markdown tool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58358</link><description>Markdownify is a Model Context Protocol server for converting almost anything to Markdown. Versions below 0.0.2 contain a command injection vulnerability, caused by the unsanitized use of input parameters within a call to child_process.exec, enabling an attacker to inject arbitrary system commands. Successful exploitation can lead to remote code execution under the server process's privileges. The server constructs and executes shell commands using unvalidated user input directly within command-line strings. This introduces the possibility of shell metacharacter injection (|, &gt;, &amp;&amp;, etc.). This issue is fixed in version 0.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 01:16:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9941 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System register.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9941</link><description>A flaw has been found in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /register.php. Executing manipulation of the argument uimage can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 01:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9942 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System submitproperty.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9942</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /submitproperty.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 01:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9939 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System propertyview.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9939</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /propertyview.php. Such manipulation of the argument msg leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 01:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9940 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System feature.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9940</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /feature.php. Performing manipulation of the argument msg results in cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 01:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58355 | Soft Serve is vulnerable to arbitrary file writing through its SSH API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58355</link><description>Soft Serve is a self-hostable Git server for the command line. In versions 0.9.1 and below, attackers can create or override arbitrary files with uncontrolled data through its SSH API. This issue is fixed in version 0.10.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 23:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9937 | elunez eladmin LocalStorageController deleteFile improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9937</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in elunez eladmin 1.1. Impacted is the function deleteFile of the component LocalStorageController. The manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 23:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9938 | D-Link DI-8400 yyxz.asp yyxz_dlink_asp stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9938</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DI-8400 16.07.26A1. The affected element is the function yyxz_dlink_asp of the file /yyxz.asp. This manipulation of the argument ID causes stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 23:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9935 | TOTOLINK N600R cstecgi.cgi sub_4159F8 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9935</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in TOTOLINK N600R 4.3.0cu.7866_B20220506. This vulnerability affects the function sub_4159F8 of the file /web_cste/cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Executing manipulation can lead to command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 23:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9936 | fuyang_lipengjun platform queryAll AdController improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9936</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in fuyang_lipengjun platform 1.0.0. This issue affects the function AdController of the file /ad/queryAll. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 23:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9933 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System view-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9933</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/view-appointment.php. Such manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 22:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9934 | TOTOLINK X5000R cstecgi.cgi sub_410C34 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9934</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X5000R 9.1.0cu.2415_B20250515. This affects the function sub_410C34 of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Performing manipulation of the argument pid results in command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 22:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58064 | CKEditor is susceptible to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) through its clipboard package</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58064</link><description>CKEditor 5 is a modern JavaScript rich-text editor with an MVC architecture. ckeditor5 and ckeditor5-clipboard versions 46.0.0 through 46.0.2 and 44.2.0 through 45.2.1 contain a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. Ability to exploit could be triggered by a specific user action (leading to unauthorized JavaScript code execution) if the attacker managed to insert a malicious content into the editor, which might happen with a very specific editor configuration. This vulnerability affects installations where the editor configuration meets one of the following criteria: the HTML embed plugin is enabled, or there is a custom plugin introducing an editable element where view RawElement is enabled. This issue is fixed in versions 45.2.2 and 46.0.3 of both ckeditor5 and ckeditor5-clipboard.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 22:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9931 | Jinher OA POST Request login!changePassWord.action cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9931</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Jinher OA 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /jc6/platform/sys/login!changePassWord.action of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument Account results in cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 22:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9932 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System update-image.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9932</link><description>A flaw has been found in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/update-image.php. This manipulation of the argument lid causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 22:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58057 | Netty&amp;#x27;s BrotliDecoder is vulnerable to DoS via zip bomb style attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58057</link><description>Netty is an asynchronous event-driven network application framework for rapid development of maintainable high performance protocol servers &amp; clients. In netty-codec-compression versions 4.1.124.Final and below, and netty-codec versions 4.2.4.Final and below, when supplied with specially crafted input, BrotliDecoder and certain other decompression decoders will allocate a large number of reachable byte buffers, which can lead to denial of service. BrotliDecoder.decompress has no limit in how often it calls pull, decompressing data 64K bytes at a time. The buffers are saved in the output list, and remain reachable until OOM is hit. This is fixed in versions 4.1.125.Final of netty-codec and 4.2.5.Final of netty-codec-compression.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 21:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9929 | code-projects Responsive Blog Site blogs_view.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9929</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Responsive Blog Site 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file blogs_view.php. Executing manipulation of the argument product_code/gen_name/product_name/supplier can lead to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 21:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9930 | 1000projects Beauty Parlour Management System contact-us.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9930</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in 1000projects Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/contact-us.php. The manipulation of the argument mobnumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 21:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9928 | projectworlds Travel Management System viewcategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9928</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in projectworlds Travel Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /viewcategory.php. Performing manipulation of the argument t1 results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 21:09:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58056 | Netty is vulnerable to request smuggling due to incorrect parsing of chunk extensions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58056</link><description>Netty is an asynchronous event-driven network application framework for development of maintainable high performance protocol servers and clients. In versions 4.1.124.Final, and 4.2.0.Alpha3 through 4.2.4.Final, Netty incorrectly accepts standalone newline characters (LF) as a chunk-size line terminator, regardless of a preceding carriage return (CR), instead of requiring CRLF per HTTP/1.1 standards. When combined with reverse proxies that parse LF differently (treating it as part of the chunk extension), attackers can craft requests that the proxy sees as one request but Netty processes as two, enabling request smuggling attacks. This is fixed in versions 4.1.125.Final and 4.2.5.Final.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 21:09:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9927 | projectworlds Travel Management System viewpackage.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9927</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in projectworlds Travel Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /viewpackage.php. Such manipulation of the argument t1 leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 20:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8268 | Ai Engine &amp;lt;= 2.9.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Uploaded Files Disclosure And Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8268</link><description>The AI Engine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the rest_list and delete_files functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to list and delete files uploaded by other users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 20:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55747 | XWiki Platform&amp;#x27;s configuration files can be accessed through the webjars API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55747</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. In versions  6.1-milestone-2 through 16.10.6, configuration files are accessible through the webjars API. This is fixed in version 16.10.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 20:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55748 | XWiki Platform&amp;#x27;s configuration files can be accessed through jsx and sx endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55748</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. In versions 4.2-milestone-2 through 16.10.6, configuration files are accessible through jsx and sx endpoints. It's possible to access and read configuration files by using URLs such as `http://localhost:8080/bin/ssx/Main/WebHome?resource=../../WEB-INF/xwiki.cfg&amp;amp;minify=false`. This is fixed in version 16.10.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 20:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57833 | An issue was discovered in Django 4.2 before 4.2.24, 5.1 before 5.1.12, and 5.2 before 5.2.6. FilteredRelation is subject to SQL injection i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57833</link><description>An issue was discovered in Django 4.2 before 4.2.24, 5.1 before 5.1.12, and 5.2 before 5.2.6. FilteredRelation is subject to SQL injection in column aliases, using a suitably crafted dictionary, with dictionary expansion, as the **kwargs passed QuerySet.annotate() or QuerySet.alias().</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 20:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53690 | Sitecore Products ViewState Deserialization Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53690</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Sitecore Experience Manager (XM), Sitecore Experience Platform (XP) allows Code Injection.This issue affects Experience Manager (XM): through 9.0; Experience Platform (XP): through 9.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 20:18:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9926 | projectworlds Travel Management System viewsubcategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9926</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in projectworlds Travel Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /viewsubcategory.php. This manipulation of the argument t1 causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 20:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55162 | Envoy: oAuth2 Filter Signout route will not clear cookies because of missing &amp;quot;secure;&amp;quot; flag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55162</link><description>Envoy is an open source L7 proxy and communication bus designed for large modern service oriented architectures. In versions below 1.32.10 and 1.33.0 through 1.33.6, 1.34.0 through 1.34.4 and 1.35.0, insufficient Session Expiration in the Envoy OAuth2 filter leads to failed logout operations. When configured with __Secure- or __Host- prefixed cookie names, the filter fails to append the required Secure attribute to the Set-Cookie header during deletion. Modern browsers ignore this invalid request, causing the session cookie to persist. This allows a user to remain logged in after they believe they have logged out, creating a session hijacking risk on shared computers. The current implementation iterates through the configured cookie names to generate deletion headers but does not check for these prefixes. This failure to properly construct the deletion header means the user's session cookies are never removed by the browser, leaving the session active and allowing the next user of the same browser to gain unauthorized access to the original user's account and data. This is fixed in versions 1.32.10, 1.33.7, 1.34.5 and 1.35.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 19:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9365 | Fuji Electric FRENIC-Loader 4 Deserialization of Untrusted Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9365</link><description>Fuji Electric FRENIC-Loader 4 is vulnerable to a deserialization of untrusted data when importing a file through a specified window, which may allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 19:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9925 | projectworlds Travel Management System detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9925</link><description>A vulnerability was found in projectworlds Travel Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /detail.php. The manipulation of the argument pid results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 19:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56139 | LinkedIn Mobile Application for Android version 4.1.1087.2 fails to update link preview metadata (image, title, description) when a user rep...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56139</link><description>LinkedIn Mobile Application for Android version 4.1.1087.2 fails to update link preview metadata (image, title, description) when a user replaces the original URL in a post or comment before publishing. As a result, the stale preview remains visible while the clickable link points to a different URL, which can be malicious. This UI misrepresentation enables attackers to deceive users by displaying trusted previews for harmful links, facilitating phishing attacks and user confusion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 19:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36193 | IBM Transformation Advisor incorrect permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36193</link><description>IBM Transformation Advisor 2.0.1 through 4.3.1 incorrectly assigns privileges to security critical files which could allow a local root escalation inside a container running the IBM Transformation Advisor Operator Catalog image.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 19:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9923 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9923</link><description>A flaw has been found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php. Executing manipulation of the argument page can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 18:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9924 | projectworlds Travel Management System enquiry.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9924</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in projectworlds Travel Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /enquiry.php. The manipulation of the argument t2 leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 18:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20270 | Cisco Evolved Programmable Network Manager Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20270</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Evolved Programmable Network Manager (EPNM) and Cisco Prime Infrastructure could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain sensitive information from an affected system.

This vulnerability is due to improper validation of requests to API endpoints. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a valid request to a specific API endpoint within the affected system. A successful exploit could allow a low-privileged user to view sensitive configuration information on the affected system that should be restricted. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have access as a low-privileged user.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20280 | Cisco Evolved Programmable Network Manager and Cisco Prime Infrastructure Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20280</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Evolved Programmable Network Manager (EPNM) and Cisco Prime Infrastructure could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against users of the interface of an affected system.

This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious code into specific data fields in the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have valid administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20287 | Cisco Evolved Programmable Network Manager Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20287</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Evolved Programmable Network Manager (EPNM) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted file upload request to a specific API endpoint. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have at least valid Config Managers credentials on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20291 | A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings could have allowed an unauthenticated, remote attacker to redirect a targeted Webex Meetings user to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20291</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings could have allowed an unauthenticated, remote attacker to redirect a targeted Webex Meetings user to an untrusted website. Cisco has addressed this vulnerability in the Cisco Webex Meetings service, and no customer action is needed.
&#13; This vulnerability existed because of insufficient validation of URLs that were included in a meeting-join URL. Prior to this vulnerability being addressed, an attacker could have exploited this vulnerability by including a URL to a website of their choosing in a specific value of a Cisco Webex Meetings join URL. A successful exploit could have allowed the attacker to redirect a targeted user to a website that was controlled by the attacker, possibly making the user more likely to believe the website was trusted by Webex and perform additional actions as part of phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20326 | Cisco Unified Communications Manager Cross-Site Request Forgery Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20326</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager (Unified CM) Software and Cisco Unified CM Session Management Edition (SME) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the affected user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20328 | A vulnerability in the user profile component of Cisco Webex Meetings could have allowed an authenticated, remote attacker with low privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20328</link><description>A vulnerability in the user profile component of Cisco Webex Meetings could have allowed an authenticated, remote attacker with low privileges to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based interface. Cisco has addressed this vulnerability in the Cisco Webex Meetings service, and no customer action is needed.
&#13; This vulnerability existed because of insufficient validation of user-supplied input to the user profile component of Cisco Webex Meetings. Prior to this vulnerability being addressed, an attacker could have exploited this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could have allowed the attacker to conduct an XSS attack against the targeted user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20330 | Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM and Presence Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20330</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp;amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20335 | Cisco Desk Phone 9800 Series, IP Phone 7800 and 8800 Series, and Video Phone 8875 with SIP Firmware Information Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20335</link><description>A vulnerability in the directory permissions of Cisco Desk Phone 9800 Series, Cisco IP Phone 7800 and 8800 Series, and Cisco Video Phone 8875 could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to write arbitrary files on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper authentication controls. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary file writes to specific directories in the underlying operating system.
Note: To exploit this vulnerability, Web Access must be enabled on the phone. Web Access is disabled by default.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20336 | Cisco Desk Phone 9800 Series, IP Phone 7800 and 8800 Series, and Video Phone 8875 with SIP Firmware Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20336</link><description>A vulnerability in the directory permissions of Cisco Desk Phone 9800 Series, Cisco IP Phone 7800 and 8800 Series, and Cisco Video Phone 8875 could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive information on an affected device.

This vulnerability exists because the product exposes sensitive information to an actor that is not explicitly authorized to have access to that information. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted packet to the IP address of a device that has Web Access enabled. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access sensitive information from the device.
Note: To exploit this vulnerability, Web Access must be enabled on the phone. Web Access is disabled by default.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45805 | In phpgurukul Doctor Appointment Management System 1.0, an authenticated doctor user can inject arbitrary JavaScript code into their profile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45805</link><description>In phpgurukul Doctor Appointment Management System 1.0, an authenticated doctor user can inject arbitrary JavaScript code into their profile name. This payload is subsequently rendered without proper sanitization, when a user visits the website and selects the doctor to book an appointment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52494 | Adacore Ada Web Server (AWS) before 25.2 is vulnerable to a denial-of-service (DoS) condition due to improper handling of SSL handshakes dur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52494</link><description>Adacore Ada Web Server (AWS) before 25.2 is vulnerable to a denial-of-service (DoS) condition due to improper handling of SSL handshakes during connection initialization. When a client initiates an HTTPS connection, the server performs the SSL handshake before assigning the connection to a processing slot. However, there is no specific timeout set for this phase, and the server uses the default socket timeout, which is effectively infinite. An attacker can exploit this by sending a malformed TLS ClientHello message with incorrect length values. This causes the server to wait indefinitely for data that never arrives, blocking the worker thread (Line) handling the connection. By opening multiple such connections, up to the server's maximum limit, the attacker can exhaust all available working threads, preventing the server from handling new, legitimate requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56752 | A vulnerability in the Ruijie RG-ES series switch firmware ESW_1.0(1)B1P39 enables remote attackers to fully bypass authentication mechanism...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56752</link><description>A vulnerability in the Ruijie RG-ES series switch firmware ESW_1.0(1)B1P39 enables remote attackers to fully bypass authentication mechanisms, providing them with unrestricted access to alter administrative settings and potentially seize control of affected devices via crafted HTTP POST request to /user.cgi.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56803 | Figma Desktop for Windows version 125.6.5 contains a command injection vulnerability in the local plugin loader. An attacker can execute arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56803</link><description>Figma Desktop for Windows version 125.6.5 contains a command injection vulnerability in the local plugin loader. An attacker can execute arbitrary OS commands by setting a crafted build field in the plugin's manifest.json. This field is passed to child_process.exec without validation, leading to possible RCE.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:22:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56689 | An issue was discovered in Quest One Identity 7.5.1.20903. A crafted response manipulation can bypass the OTP on MFA page which leads to acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56689</link><description>An issue was discovered in Quest One Identity 7.5.1.20903. A crafted response manipulation can bypass the OTP on MFA page which leads to access the PAM portal without OTP allowing attackers to control an arbitrary account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9921 | code-projects POS Pharmacy System products.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9921</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects POS Pharmacy System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /main/products.php. This manipulation of the argument product_code/gen_name/product_name/supplier causes cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9922 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9922</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php. Such manipulation of the argument page leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9959 | Sandbox escape in smolagents Local Python execution environment via dunder attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9959</link><description>Incomplete validation of dunder attributes allows an attacker to escape from the Local Python execution environment sandbox, enforced by smolagents. The attack requires a Prompt Injection in order to trick the agent to create malicious code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56760 | When Memos 0.22 is configured to store objects locally, an attacker can create a file via the CreateResource endpoint containing a path trav...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56760</link><description>When Memos 0.22 is configured to store objects locally, an attacker can create a file via the CreateResource endpoint containing a path traversal sequence in the name, allowing arbitrary file write on the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56761 | Memos 0.22 is vulnerable to Stored Cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities by the upload attachment and user avatar features. Memos does ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56761</link><description>Memos 0.22 is vulnerable to Stored Cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities by the upload attachment and user avatar features. Memos does not verify the content type of the uploaded data and serve it back as is. An authenticated attacker can use this to elevate their privileges when the stored XSS is viewed by an admin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9864 | Use after free in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9864</link><description>Use after free in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9865 | Inappropriate implementation in Toolbar in Google Chrome on Android prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9865</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Toolbar in Google Chrome on Android prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform domain spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9866 | Inappropriate implementation in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to bypass content security poli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9866</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to bypass content security policy via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9867 | Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome on Android prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9867</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome on Android prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9919 | 1000projects Beauty Parlour Management System bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9919</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in 1000projects Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9920 | Campcodes Recruitment Management System index.php include file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9920</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes Recruitment Management System 1.0. This impacts the function include of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument page results in file inclusion. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56498 | An OS command injection vulnerability exists in PLDT WiFi Router's Prolink PGN6401V Firmware 8.1.2 web management interface. The ping6.asp p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56498</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability exists in PLDT WiFi Router's Prolink PGN6401V Firmware 8.1.2 web management interface. The ping6.asp page submits user input to the /boaform/formPing6 endpoint via the pingAddr parameter, which is not properly sanitized. An authenticated attacker can exploit this flaw by injecting arbitrary system commands, which are executed by the underlying operating system with root privileges. The router uses the Boa web server (version 0.93.15) to handle the request. Successful exploitation can lead to full system compromise and unauthorized control of the network device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0280 | HCL Compass is affected by a security vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0280</link><description>A security vulnerability in HCL Compass can allow attacker to gain unauthorized database access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:34:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56435 | SQL Injection vulnerability in FoxCMS v1.2.6 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the. file /DataBackup.php and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56435</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in FoxCMS v1.2.6 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the. file /DataBackup.php and the operation on the parameter id.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:34:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55852 | Tenda AC8 v16.03.34.06 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the formWifiBasicSet function via the parameter security or security_5g.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55852</link><description>Tenda AC8 v16.03.34.06 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the formWifiBasicSet function via the parameter security or security_5g.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:34:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55944 | Slink v1.4.9 allows stored cross-site scripting (XSS) via crafted SVG uploads. When a user views the shared image in a new browser tab, the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55944</link><description>Slink v1.4.9 allows stored cross-site scripting (XSS) via crafted SVG uploads. When a user views the shared image in a new browser tab, the embedded JavaScript executes. The issue affects both authenticated and unauthenticated users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:34:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58458 | In Jenkins Git client Plugin 6.3.2 and earlier, Git URL field form validation responses differ based on whether the specified file path exis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58458</link><description>In Jenkins Git client Plugin 6.3.2 and earlier, Git URL field form validation responses differ based on whether the specified file path exists on the controller when specifying `amazon-s3` protocol for use with JGit, allowing attackers with Overall/Read permission to check for the existence of an attacker-specified file path on the Jenkins controller file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58459 | Jenkins global-build-stats Plugin 322.v22f4db_18e2dd and earlier does not perform permission checks in its REST API endpoints, allowing atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58459</link><description>Jenkins global-build-stats Plugin 322.v22f4db_18e2dd and earlier does not perform permission checks in its REST API endpoints, allowing attackers with Overall/Read permission to enumerate graph IDs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:16:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58460 | A missing permission check in Jenkins OpenTelemetry Plugin 3.1543.v8446b_92b_cd64 and earlier allows attackers with Overall/Read permission ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58460</link><description>A missing permission check in Jenkins OpenTelemetry Plugin 3.1543.v8446b_92b_cd64 and earlier allows attackers with Overall/Read permission to connect to an attacker-specified URL using attacker-specified credentials IDs obtained through another method, capturing credentials stored in Jenkins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:16:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56608 | The SourceCodester Android application "Corona Virus Tracker App India" 1.0 uses MD5 for digest authentication in `OkHttpClientWrapper.java`...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56608</link><description>The SourceCodester Android application "Corona Virus Tracker App India" 1.0 uses MD5 for digest authentication in `OkHttpClientWrapper.java`. The `handleDigest()` function employs `MessageDigest.getInstance("MD5")` to hash credentials. MD5 is a broken cryptographic algorithm known to allow hash collisions. This makes the authentication mechanism vulnerable to replay, spoofing, or brute-force attacks, potentially leading to unauthorized access. The vulnerability corresponds to CWE-327 and aligns with OWASP M5: Insufficient Cryptography and MASVS MSTG-CRYPTO-4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:16:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57146 | phpgurukul Complaint Management System in PHP 2.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in user/reset-password.php via the mobileno parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57146</link><description>phpgurukul Complaint Management System in PHP 2.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in user/reset-password.php via the mobileno parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:55:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57148 | phpgurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload in /admin/insert-product.php, due to the lack of extension vali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57148</link><description>phpgurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload in /admin/insert-product.php, due to the lack of extension validation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:55:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57052 | cJSON 1.5.0 through 1.7.18 allows out-of-bounds access via the decode_array_index_from_pointer function in cJSON_Utils.c, allowing remote at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57052</link><description>cJSON 1.5.0 through 1.7.18 allows out-of-bounds access via the decode_array_index_from_pointer function in cJSON_Utils.c, allowing remote attackers to bypass array bounds checking and access restricted data via malformed JSON pointer strings containing alphanumeric characters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57147 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in phpgurukul Complaint Management System 2.0. The vulnerability is due to lack of input validation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57147</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in phpgurukul Complaint Management System 2.0. The vulnerability is due to lack of input validation of multiple parameters including fullname, email, and contactno in user/registration.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57149 | phpgurukul Complaint Management System 2.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /complaint-details.php via the cid parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57149</link><description>phpgurukul Complaint Management System 2.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /complaint-details.php via the cid parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57150 | phpgurukul Complaint Management System in PHP 2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in admin/subcategory.php via the categoryName ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57150</link><description>phpgurukul Complaint Management System in PHP 2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in admin/subcategory.php via the categoryName parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58593 | WordPress Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58593</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themeisle Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle: from n/a through 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58594 | WordPress Brizy Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.12 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58594</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in themefusecom Brizy allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Brizy: from n/a through 2.7.12.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58596 | WordPress MailOptin Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.75.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58596</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in properfraction MailOptin allows Stored XSS. This issue affects MailOptin: from n/a through 1.2.75.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58597 | WordPress wpForo Forum Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58597</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Tomdever wpForo Forum allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects wpForo Forum: from n/a through 2.4.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58598 | WordPress Klarna Order Management for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58598</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Debugging Code vulnerability in Klarna Klarna Order Management for WooCommerce allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Klarna Order Management for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.9.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58599 | WordPress Order Delivery Date for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58599</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in tychesoftwares Order Delivery Date for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Order Delivery Date for WooCommerce: from n/a through 4.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58600 | WordPress Paid Member Subscriptions Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.15.9 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58600</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Cozmoslabs Paid Member Subscriptions allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Paid Member Subscriptions: from n/a through 2.15.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58601 | WordPress Classified Listing Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.6 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58601</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in RadiusTheme Classified Listing allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Classified Listing: from n/a through 5.0.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58602 | WordPress If-So Dynamic Content Personalization Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58602</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in IfSo Dynamic Content If-So Dynamic Content Personalization allows Stored XSS. This issue affects If-So Dynamic Content Personalization: from n/a through 1.9.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58603 | WordPress Surfer Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.4.574 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58603</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Surfer Surfer allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Surfer: from n/a through 1.6.4.574.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58604 | WordPress Mail Mint Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.18.5 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58604</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WPFunnels Mail Mint allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Mail Mint: from n/a through 1.18.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58605 | WordPress WP Delicious Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58605</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Delicious WP Delicious allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Delicious: from n/a through 1.8.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58606 | WordPress SaasLauncher Theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58606</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CozyThemes SaasLauncher allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects SaasLauncher: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58607 | WordPress Cookie Notice &amp;amp; Consent Banner for GDPR &amp;amp; CCPA Compliance Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58607</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GDPR Info Cookie Notice &amp;amp; Consent Banner for GDPR &amp;amp; CCPA Compliance allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Cookie Notice &amp;amp; Consent Banner for GDPR &amp;amp; CCPA Compliance: from n/a through 1.7.11.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58608 | WordPress MediaPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.9.1 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58608</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in BuddyDev MediaPress allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects MediaPress: from n/a through 1.5.9.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58609 | WordPress Latest Post Shortcode Plugin &amp;lt;= 14.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58609</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Iulia Cazan Latest Post Shortcode allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Latest Post Shortcode: from n/a through 14.0.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58610 | WordPress Gallery PhotoBlocks Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58610</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Chill Gallery PhotoBlocks allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Gallery PhotoBlocks: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58611 | WordPress Tickera Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.5.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58611</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Tickera Tickera allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Tickera: from n/a through 3.5.5.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58612 | WordPress PropertyHive Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58612</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Property Hive PropertyHive allows Stored XSS. This issue affects PropertyHive: from n/a through 2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58613 | WordPress Posts Table with Search &amp;amp; Sort Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.10 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58613</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Barn2 Plugins Posts Table with Search &amp; Sort allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Posts Table with Search &amp; Sort: from n/a through 1.4.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58614 | WordPress Tooltipy Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.5.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58614</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jamel.Z Tooltipy allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Tooltipy: from n/a through 5.5.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58615 | WordPress WP Bannerize Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10.0 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58615</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in gfazioli WP Bannerize Pro allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Bannerize Pro: from n/a through 1.10.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58616 | WordPress Frisbii Pay Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.2.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58616</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Frisbii Frisbii Pay allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Frisbii Pay: from n/a through 1.8.2.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58617 | WordPress F4 Media Taxonomies Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58617</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in FAKTOR VIER F4 Media Taxonomies allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects F4 Media Taxonomies: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58618 | WordPress Pie Calendar Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58618</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jonathan Jernigan Pie Calendar allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Pie Calendar: from n/a through 1.2.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58620 | WordPress PDF for WPForms Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58620</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in add-ons.org PDF for WPForms allows Stored XSS. This issue affects PDF for WPForms: from n/a through 6.2.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58621 | WordPress PuzzleMe for WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58621</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Amuse Labs PuzzleMe for WordPress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects PuzzleMe for WordPress: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58622 | WordPress Mobile Contact Line Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58622</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in yydevelopment Mobile Contact Line allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Mobile Contact Line: from n/a through 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58623 | WordPress Event Feed for Eventbrite Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58623</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bohemia Plugins Event Feed for Eventbrite allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Event Feed for Eventbrite: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58624 | WordPress Exchange Rates Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58624</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in falselight Exchange Rates allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Exchange Rates: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58625 | WordPress WP Flow Plus Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58625</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Spiffy Plugins WP Flow Plus allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Flow Plus: from n/a through 5.2.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58626 | WordPress RumbleTalk Live Group Chat Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58626</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in RumbleTalk RumbleTalk Live Group Chat allows Stored XSS. This issue affects RumbleTalk Live Group Chat: from n/a through 6.3.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58630 | WordPress Simple Matomo Tracking Code Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58630</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in rbaer Simple Matomo Tracking Code allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Simple Matomo Tracking Code: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58631 | WordPress IssueM Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58631</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ZEEN101 IssueM allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects IssueM: from n/a through 2.9.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58632 | WordPress Dadevarzan WordPress Common Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58632</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dadevarzan Dadevarzan WordPress Common allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Dadevarzan WordPress Common: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58633 | WordPress Booking Ultra Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.21 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58633</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Deetronix Booking Ultra Pro allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Booking Ultra Pro: from n/a through 1.1.21.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58634 | WordPress PeachPay Payments Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.117.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58634</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in peachpay PeachPay Payments allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects PeachPay Payments: from n/a through 1.117.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58635 | WordPress Support Genix Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.23 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58635</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in PalsCode Support Genix allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Support Genix: from n/a through 1.4.23.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58637 | WordPress immonex Kickstart Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11.6 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58637</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in immonex immonex Kickstart allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects immonex Kickstart: from n/a through 1.11.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58639 | WordPress Contact Form By Mega Forms Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58639</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ali Khallad Contact Form By Mega Forms allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Contact Form By Mega Forms: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58640 | WordPress Document Engine Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58640</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MatrixAddons Document Engine allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Document Engine: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58641 | WordPress Exit Intent Popup Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58641</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in kamleshyadav Exit Intent Popup allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects Exit Intent Popup: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58642 | WordPress LTL Freight Quotes  Day &amp;amp; Ross Edition Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.11 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58642</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in enituretechnology LTL Freight Quotes  Day &amp; Ross Edition allows Object Injection. This issue affects LTL Freight Quotes  Day &amp; Ross Edition: from n/a through 2.1.11.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58643 | WordPress LTL Freight Quotes  Daylight Edition Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.7 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58643</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in enituretechnology LTL Freight Quotes  Daylight Edition allows Object Injection. This issue affects LTL Freight Quotes  Daylight Edition: from n/a through 2.2.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58644 | WordPress LTL Freight Quotes - TQL Edition Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58644</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in enituretechnology LTL Freight Quotes - TQL Edition allows Object Injection. This issue affects LTL Freight Quotes - TQL Edition: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9823 | Reflected XSS in lead:addLeadTags - Quick Add</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9823</link><description>SummaryA Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of another users session. This occurs because user-supplied input is reflected back in the servers response without proper sanitization or escaping, potentially enabling malicious actions such as session hijacking, credential theft, or unauthorized actions in the application.

DetailsThe vulnerability resides in the Tags input field on the /s/ajax?action=lead:addLeadTags endpoint. Although the server applies sanitization before storing the data or returning it later, the payload is executed immediately in the victims browser upon reflection, allowing an attacker to run arbitrary JavaScript in the users session.

ImpactA Reflected XSS attack can have a significant impact, allowing attackers to steal sensitive user data like cookies, redirect users to malicious websites, manipulate the web page content, and essentially take control of a user's session within an application by executing malicious JavaScript code within the victim's browser, even if the server-side code is secure; essentially enabling them to perform actions as if they were the logged-in user.

References  *   Web Security Academy: Cross-site scripting https://portswigger.net/web-security/cross-site-scripting 
  *   Web Security Academy: Reflected cross-site scripting https://portswigger.net/web-security/cross-site-scripting/reflected</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57151 | phpgurukul Complaint Management System 2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in admin/userprofile.php via the fullname parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57151</link><description>phpgurukul Complaint Management System 2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in admin/userprofile.php via the fullname parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9824 | User Enumeration via Response Timing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9824</link><description>ImpactThe attacker can validate if a user exists by checking the time login returns. This timing difference can be used to enumerate valid usernames, after which an attacker could attempt brute force attacks.

PatchesThis vulnerability has been patched, implementing a timing-safe form login authenticator that ensures consistent response times regardless of whether a user exists or not.

Technical DetailsThe vulnerability was caused by different response times when:

  *  A valid username was provided (password hashing occurred)
  *  An invalid username was provided (no password hashing occurred)


The fix introduces a TimingSafeFormLoginAuthenticatorthat performs a dummy password hash verification even for non-existent users, ensuring consistent timing.

WorkaroundsNo workarounds are available. Users should upgrade to the patched version.

References  *   https://owasp.org/www-project-web-security-testing-guide/latest/4-Web_Application_Security_Testing/03-Identity_Management_Testing/04-Testing_for_Account_Enumeration_and_Guessable_User_Account</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9822 | Secret data extraction via elfinder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9822</link><description>SummaryA user with administrator rights can change the configuration of the mautic application and extract secrets that are not normally available.

ImpactAn administrator who usually does not have access to certain parameters, such as database credentials, can disclose them.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47421 | Privilege escalation via SCP login</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47421</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection') vulnerability in CRESTRON TOUCHSCREENS x70 allows Argument Injection.This issue affects TOUCHSCREENS x70: from 3.001.0031.001 through 3.001.0034.001.

A specially crafted SCP command sent via SSH login string can lead a valid administrator user to gain Privileged Operating System access on the device.


Following Products Models are affected:

TSW-x70 
TSW-x60 
TST-1080
AM-3000/3100/3200
Soundbar VB70
HD-PS622/621/402
HD-TXU-RXU-4kZ-211
HD-MDNXM-4KZ-E

*Note: additional firmware updates will be published once made available</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26210 | An Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in DeepSeek R1 through V3.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via unspecified i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26210</link><description>An Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in DeepSeek R1 through V3.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via unspecified input fields.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:35:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2416 | OTP Bypass in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s LimonDesk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2416</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Akinsoft LimonDesk allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects LimonDesk: from s1.02.14 before v1.02.17.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:35:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13068 | Host Header Injection in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s LimonDesk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13068</link><description>Origin Validation Error vulnerability in Akinsoft LimonDesk allows Forceful Browsing.This issue affects LimonDesk: from s1.02.14 before v1.02.17.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0878 | XSS in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s LimonDesk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0878</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Akinsoft LimonDesk allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects LimonDesk: from s1.02.14 before v1.02.17.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13066 | iFrame Injection in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s LimonDesk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13066</link><description>Improper Restriction of Rendered UI Layers or Frames vulnerability in Akinsoft LimonDesk allows iFrame Overlay, CAPEC - 103 - Clickjacking.This issue affects LimonDesk: from s1.02.14 before v1.02.17.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:07:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38678 | netfilter: nf_tables: reject duplicate device on updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38678</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nf_tables: reject duplicate device on updates

A chain/flowtable update with duplicated devices in the same batch is
possible. Unfortunately, netdev event path only removes the first
device that is found, leaving unregistered the hook of the duplicated
device.

Check if a duplicated device exists in the transaction batch, bail out
with EEXIST in such case.

WARNING is hit when unregistering the hook:

 [49042.221275] WARNING: CPU: 4 PID: 8425 at net/netfilter/core.c:340 nf_hook_entry_head+0xaa/0x150
 [49042.221375] CPU: 4 UID: 0 PID: 8425 Comm: nft Tainted: G S                  6.16.0+ #170 PREEMPT(full)
 [...]
 [49042.221382] RIP: 0010:nf_hook_entry_head+0xaa/0x150</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:07:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3701 | WordPress Malcure Malware Scanner plugin &amp;lt;= 16.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3701</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Malcure Web Security Malcure Malware Scanner allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Malcure Malware Scanner: from n/a through 16.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:07:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53691 | Sitecore Experience Remote Code Execution through Insecure Deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53691</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Sitecore Experience Manager (XM), Sitecore Experience Platform (XP) allows Remote Code Execution (RCE).This issue affects Experience Manager (XM): from 9.0 through 9.3, from 10.0 through 10.4; Experience Platform (XP): from 9.0 through 9.3, from 10.0 through 10.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:07:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53693 | HTML Cache Poisoning through Unsafe Reflections</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53693</link><description>Use of Externally-Controlled Input to Select Classes or Code ('Unsafe Reflection') vulnerability in Sitecore Sitecore Experience Manager (XM), Sitecore Experience Platform (XP) allows Cache Poisoning.This issue affects Sitecore Experience Manager (XM): from 9.0 through 9.3, from 10.0 through 10.4; Experience Platform (XP): from 9.0 through 9.3, from 10.0 through 10.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53694 | Information Disclosure in ItemServices API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53694</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Sitecore Sitecore Experience Manager (XM), Sitecore Experience Platform (XP).This issue affects Sitecore Experience Manager (XM): from 9.2 through 10.4; Experience Platform (XP): from 9.2 through 10.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9901 | Libsoup: improper handling of http vary header in libsoup caching</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9901</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoups caching mechanism, SoupCache, where the HTTP Vary header is ignored when evaluating cached responses. This header ensures that responses vary appropriately based on request headers such as language or authentication. Without this check, cached content can be incorrectly reused across different requests, potentially exposing sensitive user information. While the issue is unlikely to affect everyday desktop use, it could result in confidentiality breaches in proxy or multi-user environments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41000 | Cross-Frame Scripting (XFS) in BoomCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41000</link><description>Cross-Frame Scripting (XFS) vulnerability in BoomCMS v9.1.4 from UXB London. XFS is a web attack technique that exploits specific browser bugs to spy on users via JavaScript. This type of attack is based on social engineering and depends entirely on the browser chosen by the user, so it is perceived as a minor threat to web application security. This vulnerability only works in older browsers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:18:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9821 | SSRF via webhook function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9821</link><description>SummaryUsers with webhook permissions can conduct SSRF via webhooks. If they have permission to view the webhook logs, the (partial) request response is also disclosed

DetailsWhen sending webhooks, the destination is not validated, causing SSRF.


ImpactBypass of firewalls to interact with internal services.
See  https://owasp.org/Top10/A10_2021-Server-Side_Request_Forgery_%28SSRF%29/ for more potential impact.

Resources https://cheatsheetseries.owasp.org/cheatsheets/Server_Side_Request_Forgery_Prevention_Cheat_Sheet.html for more information on SSRF and its fix.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 09:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43166 | Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Apache DolphinScheduler.

This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: before 3.2.2.

Users ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43166</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Apache DolphinScheduler.

This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: before 3.2.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.3.1, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 09:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2415 | OTP Bypass in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s MyRezzta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2415</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Akinsoft MyRezzta allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects MyRezzta: from s2.03.01 before v2.05.01.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13065 | Business Logic Error in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s MyRezzta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13065</link><description>Improper Enforcement of Behavioral Workflow, Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in Akinsoft MyRezzta allows Input Data Manipulation, CAPEC - 125 - Flooding.This issue affects MyRezzta: from s2.02.02 before v2.05.01.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1740 | Authentication Bypass in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s MyRezzta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1740</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Akinsoft MyRezzta allows Authentication Bypass, Password Recovery Exploitation, Brute Force.This issue affects MyRezzta: from s2.03.01 before v2.05.01.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13064 | XSS in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s MyRezzta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13064</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Akinsoft MyRezzta allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects MyRezzta: from s2.02.02 before v2.05.01.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43115 | Apache DolphinScheduler: Alert Script Attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43115</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache DolphinScheduler. An authenticated user can execute any shell script server by alert script.


This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: before 3.2.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.3.1, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2014-125127 | Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in mikecao/flight</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125127</link><description>The mikecao/flight PHP framework in versions prior to v1.2 is vulnerable to Denial of Service (DoS) attacks due to eager loading of request bodies in the Request class constructor. The framework automatically reads the entire request body on every HTTP request, regardless of whether the application needs it. An attacker can exploit this by sending requests with large payloads, causing excessive memory consumption and potentially exhausting available server memory, leading to application crashes or service unavailability. The vulnerability was fixed in v1.2 by implementing lazy loading of request bodies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13063 | IDOR in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s MyRezzta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13063</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Akinsoft MyRezzta allows Forceful Browsing.This issue affects MyRezzta: from s2.02.02 before v2.05.01.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9219 | Post SMTP &amp;lt;= 3.4.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Plugin Option Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9219</link><description>The Post SMTP  WP SMTP Plugin with Email Logs and Mobile App for Failure Notifications  Gmail SMTP, Office 365, Brevo, Mailgun, Amazon SES and more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'update_post_smtp_pro_option_callback' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to enable pro extensions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9817 | NULL Pointer Dereference in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9817</link><description>SSH dissector crash in Wireshark 4.4.0 to 4.4.8 allows denial of service</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8663 | Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in upKeeper Solutions upKeeper Manager allows Use of Known Domain Credentials...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8663</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in upKeeper Solutions upKeeper Manager allows Use of Known Domain Credentials.This issue affects upKeeper Manager: from 5.0.0 before 5.2.12.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:10:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32444 | WordPress RealHomes theme &amp;lt;= 4.3.6 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32444</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in InspiryThemes RealHomes allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects RealHomes: from n/a through 4.3.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:10:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58210 | WordPress Makeaholic Theme &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58210</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThemeMove Makeaholic allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Makeaholic: from n/a through 1.8.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:10:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9378 | Vayu Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.3.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Block Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9378</link><description>The Vayu Blocks  Website Builder for the Block Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple attributes in the Lottie block in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21025 | Improper access control in MARsExemptionManager prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to be excluded from background execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21025</link><description>Improper access control in MARsExemptionManager prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to be excluded from background execution management.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21026 | Improper handling of insufficient permission in ImsService prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to interrupt the call.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21026</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permission in ImsService prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to interrupt the call.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21027 | Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver in ImsService prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to temporarily di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21027</link><description>Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver in ImsService prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to temporarily disable the SIM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21028 | Improper privilege management in ThemeManager prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to reuse trial items.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21028</link><description>Improper privilege management in ThemeManager prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to reuse trial items.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21029 | Improper handling of insufficient permission in System UI prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to send arbitrary replies t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21029</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permission in System UI prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to send arbitrary replies to messages from the cover display.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21030 | Improper handling of insufficient permission in AppPrelaunchManagerService prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 in Chinese Android 15 allows loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21030</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permission in AppPrelaunchManagerService prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 in Chinese Android 15 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary application in the background.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21031 | Improper access control in ImsService prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to use the privileged APIs.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21031</link><description>Improper access control in ImsService prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to use the privileged APIs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21032 | Improper access control in One UI Home prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to bypass Kiosk mode under limited conditio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21032</link><description>Improper access control in One UI Home prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to bypass Kiosk mode under limited conditions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21033 | Improper access control in ContactProvider prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21033</link><description>Improper access control in ContactProvider prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21034 | Out-of-bounds write in libsavsvc.so prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21034</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in libsavsvc.so prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21035 | Improper access control in Samsung Calendar prior to version 12.5.06.5 in Android 14 and 12.6.01.12 in Android 15 allows physical attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21035</link><description>Improper access control in Samsung Calendar prior to version 12.5.06.5 in Android 14 and 12.6.01.12 in Android 15 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profiles.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21036 | Improper access control in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.30.63 allows local privileged attackers to access exported note files. User in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21036</link><description>Improper access control in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.30.63 allows local privileged attackers to access exported note files. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21037 | Improper access control in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.30.63 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profiles. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21037</link><description>Improper access control in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.30.63 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profiles. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21038 | Improper verification of intent by SamsungExceptionalBroadcastReceiver in S Assistant prior to version 9.3.2 allows local attackers to modif...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21038</link><description>Improper verification of intent by SamsungExceptionalBroadcastReceiver in S Assistant prior to version 9.3.2 allows local attackers to modify itinerary information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21039 | Improper verification of intent by SystemExceptionalBroadcastReceiver in S Assistant prior to version 9.3.2 allows local attackers to modify...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21039</link><description>Improper verification of intent by SystemExceptionalBroadcastReceiver in S Assistant prior to version 9.3.2 allows local attackers to modify itinerary information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21040 | Improper verification of intent by ExternalBroadcastReceiver in S Assistant prior to version 9.3.2 allows local attackers to modify itinerar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21040</link><description>Improper verification of intent by ExternalBroadcastReceiver in S Assistant prior to version 9.3.2 allows local attackers to modify itinerary information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21041 | Insecure Storage of Sensitive Information in Secure Folder prior to Android 16 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21041</link><description>Insecure Storage of Sensitive Information in Secure Folder prior to Android 16 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21474 | Intent redirection vulnerability in SecSettings prior to SMR Apr-2022 Release 1 allows attackers to access arbitrary file with system privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21474</link><description>Intent redirection vulnerability in SecSettings prior to SMR Apr-2022 Release 1 allows attackers to access arbitrary file with system privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3666 | Sticky Side Buttons &amp;lt; 2.0.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3666</link><description>The Sticky Side Buttons WordPress plugin before 2.0.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58272 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in Web Caster V130 versions 1.08 and earlier. If a logged-in user views a malicious page cre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58272</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in Web Caster V130 versions 1.08 and earlier. If a logged-in user views a malicious page created by an attacker, the settings of the product may be unintentionally changed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21466 | PendingIntent hijacking vulnerability in CertificatePolicy in framework prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to access con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21466</link><description>PendingIntent hijacking vulnerability in CertificatePolicy in framework prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to access contentProvider without proper permission.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21467 | Error in 3GPP specification implementation in Exynos baseband prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows incorrect handling of unencrypted messa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21467</link><description>Error in 3GPP specification implementation in Exynos baseband prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows incorrect handling of unencrypted message.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21468 | Improper access control vulnerability in Telephony prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows attackers to access files with escalated permissio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21468</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in Telephony prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows attackers to access files with escalated permission.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21469 | Improper access control vulnerability in SLocation prior to SMR Apr-2022 Release 1 allows local attackers to get device location information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21469</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in SLocation prior to SMR Apr-2022 Release 1 allows local attackers to get device location information using com.samsung.android.wifi.GEOFENCE action.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21470 | Improper access control vulnerability in SLocation prior to SMR Apr-2022 Release 1 allows local attackers to get device location information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21470</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in SLocation prior to SMR Apr-2022 Release 1 allows local attackers to get device location information using com.samsung.android.wifi.NETWORK_LOCATION action.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21471 | Improper access control vulnerability in SemClipboard prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows attackers to read arbitrary files with system p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21471</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in SemClipboard prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows attackers to read arbitrary files with system permission.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21472 | Improper input validation with Exynos Fastboot USB Interface prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows a physical attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21472</link><description>Improper input validation with Exynos Fastboot USB Interface prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows a physical attacker to execute arbitrary code in bootloader.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21473 | Improper input validation with Exynos Fastboot USB Interface prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows a physical attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21473</link><description>Improper input validation with Exynos Fastboot USB Interface prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows a physical attacker to execute arbitrary code in bootloader.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21475 | Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in libaudiosaplus_sec.so library prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21475</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in libaudiosaplus_sec.so library prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21476 | Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in libaudiosaplus_sec.so library prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21476</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in libaudiosaplus_sec.so library prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21477 | Access of Memory Location After End of Buffer vulnerability in TIGERF trustlet prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21477</link><description>Access of Memory Location After End of Buffer vulnerability in TIGERF trustlet prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to access protected data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21478 | Improper input validation vulnerability in TIGERF trustlet prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to access protected data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21478</link><description>Improper input validation vulnerability in TIGERF trustlet prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to access protected data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21479 | Improper authorization in Smart suggestions prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 in Android 13 and 4.1.01.0 in Android 12 allows remote attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21479</link><description>Improper authorization in Smart suggestions prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 in Android 13 and 4.1.01.0 in Android 12 allows remote attackers to register a schedule.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21480 | Improper input validation vulnerability in CertByte prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activities.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21480</link><description>Improper input validation vulnerability in CertByte prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21481 | Improper URL input validation vulnerability in Samsung Account application prior to version 14.1.0.0 allows remote attackers to get sensitiv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21481</link><description>Improper URL input validation vulnerability in Samsung Account application prior to version 14.1.0.0 allows remote attackers to get sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21482 | Missing authorization vulnerability in Camera prior to versions 11.1.02.18 in Android 11, 12.1.03.8 in Android 12 and 13.1.01.4 in Android 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21482</link><description>Missing authorization vulnerability in Camera prior to versions 11.1.02.18 in Android 11, 12.1.03.8 in Android 12 and 13.1.01.4 in Android 13  allows physical attackers to install package through Galaxy store before completion of Setup wizard.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21483 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.53.6 allows local attacker to access protected data using exporte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21483</link><description>Improper Access Control vulnerability in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.53.6 allows local attacker to access protected data using exported service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9785 | Misconfigured certificate validation with self-signed certificates for Print Deploy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9785</link><description>PaperCut Print Deploy is an optional component that integrates with PaperCut NG/MF which simplifies printer deployment and management. When the component is deployed to an environment, the customer has an option to configure the system to use a self-signed certificate. If the customer does not fully configure the system to leverage the trust database on the clients, it opens up the communication between clients and the server to man-in-the-middle attacks.

It was discovered that certain parts of the documentation related to the configuration of SSL in Print Deploy were lacking, which could potentially contribute to a misconfiguration of the Print Deploy client installation. PaperCut strongly recommends to use valid certificates to secure installations and to follow the updated documentation to ensure the correct SSL configuration. Those who use private CAs and/or self-signed certificates should make sure to copy their Certification Authority certificate, or their self signed certificate if using only one, to the trust store of their operating system and to the Java key store</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 04:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58176 | Dive&amp;#x27;s improper processing of custom urls can lead to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58176</link><description>Dive is an open-source MCP Host Desktop Application that enables integration with function-calling LLMs. In versions 0.9.0 through 0.9.3, there is a one-click Remote Code Execution vulnerability triggered through a custom url value, `transport` in the JSON object. An attacker can exploit the vulnerability in the following two scenarios: a victim visits a malicious website controlled by the attacker and the website redirect to the URL automatically, or a victim clicks on such a crafted link embedded on a legitimate website (e.g., in user-generated content). In both cases, the browser invokes Dive's custom URL handler (dive:), which launches the Dive app and processes the crafted URL, leading to arbitrary code execution on the victims machine. This vulnerability is caused by improper processing of custom url. This is fixed in version 0.9.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 03:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58351 | Outline&amp;#x27;s Local File Storage Feature can Cause CSP Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58351</link><description>Outline is a service that allows for collaborative documentation. In versions 0.72.0 through 0.83.0, Outline introduced a feature which facilitates local file system storage capabilities as an optional file storage strategy. This feature allowed a CSP bypass as well as a ContentType bypass that might facilitate further attacks. In the case of self-hosting and using Outline FILE_STORAGE=local on the same domain as the Outline application, a malicious payload can be uploaded as a file attachment and bypass those CSP restrictions, allowing script execution within the context of another user. This is fixed in version 0.84.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 03:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7039 | Glib: buffer under-read on glib through glib/gfileutils.c via get_tmp_file()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7039</link><description>A flaw was found in glib. An integer overflow during temporary file creation leads to an out-of-bounds memory access, allowing an attacker to potentially perform path traversal or access private temporary file content by creating symbolic links. This vulnerability allows a local attacker to manipulate file paths and access unauthorized data. The core issue stems from insufficient validation of file path lengths during temporary file operations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 02:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58163 | FreeScout&amp;#x27;s deserialization of untrusted data can lead to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58163</link><description>FreeScout is a free help desk and shared inbox built with PHP's Laravel framework. In versions 1.8.185 and below, the application performs deserialization of data that can allow authenticated attackers with knowledge of the application's APP_KEY to achieve remote code execution. The vulnerability can be exploited via endpoint: `/help/{mailbox_id}/auth/{customer_id}/{hash}/{timestamp}` where the `customer_id` and `timestamp` parameters are processed through the decrypt function in `app/Helper.php` without proper validation. The vulnerable code performs decryption using Laravel's built-in encryption functions, which subsequently deserializes the decrypted payload without sanitization. This is fixed in version 1.8.186.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 02:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9847 | ScriptAndTools Real Estate Management System register.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9847</link><description>A weakness has been identified in ScriptAndTools Real Estate Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file register.php. This manipulation of the argument uimage causes unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 02:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9848 | ScriptAndTools Real Estate Management System userlist.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9848</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in ScriptAndTools Real Estate Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/userlist.php. Such manipulation leads to execution after redirect. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 02:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57806 | Local Deep Research&amp;#x27;s API keys are stored in plain text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57806</link><description>Local Deep Research is an AI-powered research assistant for deep, iterative research. Versions 0.2.0 through 0.6.7 stored confidential information, including API keys, in a local SQLite database without encryption. This behavior was not clearly documented outside of the database architecture page. Users were not given the ability to configure the database location, allowing anyone with access to the container or host filesystem to retrieve sensitive data in plaintext by accessing the .db file. This is fixed in version 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 01:02:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9843 | Das Parking Management System  FindAll information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9843</link><description>A flaw has been found in Das Parking Management System  6.2.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /Operator/FindAll. This manipulation causes information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 01:02:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9845 | code-projects Fruit Shop Management System products.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9845</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Fruit Shop Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file products.php. Such manipulation of the argument product_code/gen_name/product_name/supplier leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 01:02:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9842 | Das Parking Management System  Search information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9842</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Das Parking Management System  6.2.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /Operator/Search. The manipulation results in information disclosure. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 01:02:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54588 | Envoy: Race condition in Dynamic Forward Proxy leads to use-after-free and segmentation faults</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54588</link><description>Envoy is an open source L7 proxy and communication bus designed for large modern service oriented architectures. Versions 1.34.0 through 1.34.4 and 1.35.0 contain a use-after-free (UAF) vulnerability in the DNS cache, causing abnormal process termination. The vulnerability is in Envoy's Dynamic Forward Proxy implementation, occurring when a completion callback for a DNS resolution triggers new DNS resolutions or removes existing pending resolutions. This condition may occur when the following conditions are met: dynamic Forwarding Filter is enabled, the `envoy.reloadable_features.dfp_cluster_resolves_hosts` runtime flag is enabled, and the Host header is modified between the Dynamic Forwarding Filter and Router filters. This issue is resolved in versions 1.34.5 and 1.35.1. To work around this issue, set the envoy.reloadable_features.dfp_cluster_resolves_hosts runtime flag to false.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 23:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9841 | code-projects Mobile Shop Management System AddNewProduct.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9841</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Mobile Shop Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file AddNewProduct.php. The manipulation of the argument ProductImage leads to unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 23:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9260 | Fluent Forms  Customizable Contact Forms, Survey, Quiz, &amp;amp; Conversational Form Builder 5.1.16 - 6.1.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) PHP Object Injection To Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9260</link><description>The Fluent Forms  Customizable Contact Forms, Survey, Quiz, &amp; Conversational Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions 5.1.16 to 6.1.1 via deserialization of untrusted input in the parseUserProperties function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. The additional presence of a POP chain allows attackers to read arbitrary files. If allow_url_include is enabled on the server, remote code execution is possible.
While the vendor patched this issue in version 6.1.0, the patch caused a fatal error in the vulnerable code, due to a missing class import, so we consider 6.1.2 to be the most complete and best patched version</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 23:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9840 | itsourcecode Sports Management System gametype.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9840</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Sports Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /Admin/gametype.php. Executing manipulation of the argument code can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 23:15:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9838 | itsourcecode Student Information Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9838</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Student Information Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/modules/subject/index.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9839 | itsourcecode Student Information Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9839</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Student Information Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/modules/course/index.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40653 | In multiple functions of ConnectionServiceWrapper.java, there is a possible way to retain a permission forever in the background due to a lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40653</link><description>In multiple functions of ConnectionServiceWrapper.java, there is a possible way to retain a permission forever in the background due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49720 | In multiple functions of Permissions.java, there is a possible way to override the state of the user's location permissions due to a logic e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49720</link><description>In multiple functions of Permissions.java, there is a possible way to override the state of the user's location permissions due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49722 | In showAvatarPicker of EditUserPhotoController.java, there is a possible cross user image leak due to a confused deputy. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49722</link><description>In showAvatarPicker of EditUserPhotoController.java, there is a possible cross user image leak due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49728 | In generateFileInfo of BluetoothOppSendFileInfo.java, there is a possible cross user media disclosure due to a confused deputy. This could l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49728</link><description>In generateFileInfo of BluetoothOppSendFileInfo.java, there is a possible cross user media disclosure due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49730 | In FuseDaemon.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to memory corruption. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49730</link><description>In FuseDaemon.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to memory corruption. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22416 | In onCreate of ChooserActivity.java , there is a possible way to view other users' images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22416</link><description>In onCreate of ChooserActivity.java , there is a possible way to view other users' images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22417 | In finishTransition of Transition.java, there is a possible way to bypass touch filtering restrictions due to a tapjacking/overlay attack. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22417</link><description>In finishTransition of Transition.java, there is a possible way to bypass touch filtering restrictions due to a tapjacking/overlay attack. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22418 | In multiple locations, there is a possible confused deputy due to Intent Redirect. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22418</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible confused deputy due to Intent Redirect. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22419 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to mislead the user into enabling malicious phone calls forwarding due to a tapjacking/overla...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22419</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to mislead the user into enabling malicious phone calls forwarding due to a tapjacking/overlay attack. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22421 | In contentDescForNotification of NotificationContentDescription.kt, there is a possible notification content leak through the lockscreen due...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22421</link><description>In contentDescForNotification of NotificationContentDescription.kt, there is a possible notification content leak through the lockscreen due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22422 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to mislead a user into approving an authentication prompt for one app when its result will be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22422</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to mislead a user into approving an authentication prompt for one app when its result will be used in another due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22423 | In ParseTag of dng_ifd.cpp, there is a possible way to crash the image renderer due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote den...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22423</link><description>In ParseTag of dng_ifd.cpp, there is a possible way to crash the image renderer due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22427 | In onCreate of NotificationAccessConfirmationActivity.java, there is a possible way to grant notification access above the lock screen due t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22427</link><description>In onCreate of NotificationAccessConfirmationActivity.java, there is a possible way to grant notification access above the lock screen due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22428 | In hasInteractAcrossUsersFullPermission of AppInfoBase.java, there is a possible way to grant permissions to an app on the secondary user fr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22428</link><description>In hasInteractAcrossUsersFullPermission of AppInfoBase.java, there is a possible way to grant permissions to an app on the secondary user from the primary user due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22429 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22429</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22430 | In isInSignificantPlace of multiple files, there is a possible way to access sensitive information due to a missing permission check. This c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22430</link><description>In isInSignificantPlace of multiple files, there is a possible way to access sensitive information due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22431 | In multiple locations, there is a possible method for a malicious app to prevent dialing emergency services under limited circumstances due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22431</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible method for a malicious app to prevent dialing emergency services under limited circumstances due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local denial of service until the phone reboots with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22433 | In canForward of IntentForwarderActivity.java, there is a possible bypass of the cross profile intent filter most commonly used in Work Prof...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22433</link><description>In canForward of IntentForwarderActivity.java, there is a possible bypass of the cross profile intent filter most commonly used in Work Profile scenarios due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22434 | In handleKeyGestureEvent of PhoneWindowManager.java, there is a possible lock screen bypass due to a logic error in the code. This could lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22434</link><description>In handleKeyGestureEvent of PhoneWindowManager.java, there is a possible lock screen bypass due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22435 | In avdt_msg_ind of avdt_msg.cc, there is a possible memory corruption due to type confusion. This could lead to paired device escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22435</link><description>In avdt_msg_ind of avdt_msg.cc, there is a possible memory corruption due to type confusion. This could lead to paired device escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22437 | In setMediaButtonReceiver of multiple files, there is a possible way to launch arbitrary activities from background due to a logic error in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22437</link><description>In setMediaButtonReceiver of multiple files, there is a possible way to launch arbitrary activities from background due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22438 | In afterKeyEventLockedInterruptable of InputDispatcher.cpp, there is a possible use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22438</link><description>In afterKeyEventLockedInterruptable of InputDispatcher.cpp, there is a possible use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22439 | In onLastAccessedStackLoaded of ActionHandler.java , there is a possible way to bypass storage restrictions across apps due to a missing per...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22439</link><description>In onLastAccessedStackLoaded of ActionHandler.java , there is a possible way to bypass storage restrictions across apps due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22442 | In multiple functions of DevicePolicyManagerService.java, there is a possible way to install unauthorized applications into a newly created ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22442</link><description>In multiple functions of DevicePolicyManagerService.java, there is a possible way to install unauthorized applications into a newly created work profile due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26416 | In initializeSwizzler of SkBmpStandardCodec.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26416</link><description>In initializeSwizzler of SkBmpStandardCodec.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9836 | macrozheng mall paySuccess authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9836</link><description>A vulnerability was found in macrozheng mall up to 1.0.3. This vulnerability affects the function paySuccess of the file /order/paySuccess. The manipulation of the argument orderId results in authorization bypass. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9837 | itsourcecode Student Information Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9837</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Student Information Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/modules/student/index.php. This manipulation of the argument studentId causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9835 | macrozheng mall cancelUserOrder cancelOrder authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9835</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in macrozheng mall up to 1.0.3. This affects the function cancelOrder of the file /order/cancelUserOrder. The manipulation of the argument orderId leads to authorization bypass. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9833 | SourceCodester Online Farm Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9833</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Online Farm Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Login/login.php. Performing manipulation of the argument uname results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 21:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9834 | PHPGurukul Small CRM registration.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9834</link><description>A flaw has been found in PHPGurukul Small CRM 4.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /registration.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Username can lead to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 21:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9831 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System edit-services.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9831</link><description>A weakness has been identified in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/edit-services.php. This manipulation of the argument sername causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9832 | SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System register-router.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9832</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /routers/register-router.php. Such manipulation of the argument phone leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9323 | Foxit PDF Reader JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9323</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-27101.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9324 | Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9324</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PRC files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26802.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9325 | Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9325</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PRC files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26785.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9326 | Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9326</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PRC files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26784.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9327 | Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9327</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PRC files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26774.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9328 | Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9328</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PRC files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26773.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9329 | Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9329</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PRC files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26772.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9330 | Foxit PDF Reader Update Service Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9330</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Update Service Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Foxit Reader Update Service. The product loads a library from an unsecured location. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-25709.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8298 | Realtek RTL8811AU rtwlanu.sys N6CQueryInformationHandleCustomized11nOids Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8298</link><description>Realtek RTL8811AU rtwlanu.sys N6CQueryInformationHandleCustomized11nOids Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Realtek RTL8811AU drivers. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the N6CQueryInformationHandleCustomized11nOids function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-25864.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8299 | Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi Driver MgntActSet_TEREDO_SET_RS_PACKET Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8299</link><description>Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi Driver MgntActSet_TEREDO_SET_RS_PACKET Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi driver. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the MgntActSet_TEREDO_SET_RS_PACKET function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-25857.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8300 | Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi Driver rtwlanu Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8300</link><description>Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi Driver rtwlanu Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi driver. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the N6CSet_DOT11_CIPHER_DEFAULT_KEY function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-26552.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8301 | Realtek RTL8811AU rtwlanu.sys N6CSet_DOT11_CIPHER_DEFAULT_KEY Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8301</link><description>Realtek RTL8811AU rtwlanu.sys N6CSet_DOT11_CIPHER_DEFAULT_KEY Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Realtek RTL8811AU drivers. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the N6CSet_DOT11_CIPHER_DEFAULT_KEY function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-24786.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8302 | Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi Driver rtwlanu Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8302</link><description>Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi Driver rtwlanu Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi driver. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the N6CSet_DOT11_CIPHER_DEFAULT_KEY function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-26553.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9273 | CData API Server MySQL Misconfiguration Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9273</link><description>CData API Server MySQL Misconfiguration Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of CData API Server. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the usage of MySQL connections. When connecting to a MySQL server, the product enables an option that gives the MySQL server permission to request local files from the MySQL client. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of NETWORK SERVICE. Was ZDI-CAN-23950.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9274 | Oxford Instruments Imaris Viewer IMS File Parsing Uninitialized Pointer Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9274</link><description>Oxford Instruments Imaris Viewer IMS File Parsing Uninitialized Pointer Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Oxford Instruments Imaris Viewer. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of IMS files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of a pointer prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21657.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9275 | Oxford Instruments Imaris Viewer IMS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9275</link><description>Oxford Instruments Imaris Viewer IMS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Oxford Instruments Imaris Viewer. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of IMS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated data structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21655.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9276 | Cockroach Labs cockroach-k8s-request-cert Empty Root Password Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9276</link><description>Cockroach Labs cockroach-k8s-request-cert Empty Root Password Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability could allow remote attackers to bypass authentication on systems that use the affected version of the Cockroach Labs cockroach-k8s-request-cert container image.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of the system shadow file. The issue results from a blank password setting for the root user. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-22195.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9830 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System add-customer-services.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9830</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/add-customer-services.php. The manipulation of the argument sids[] results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6685 | ATEN eco DC Missing Authorization Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6685</link><description>ATEN eco DC Missing Authorization Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of ATEN eco DC. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the web-based interface. The issue results from the lack of validating the assigned user role when handling requests. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the user. Was ZDI-CAN-26647.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7974 | rocket.chat Incorrect Authorization Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7974</link><description>rocket.chat Incorrect Authorization Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of rocket.chat. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the web service, which listens on TCP port 3000 by default. The issue results from incorrect authorization. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of the application. Was ZDI-CAN-26517.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7975 | Anritsu ShockLine CHX File Parsing Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7975</link><description>Anritsu ShockLine CHX File Parsing Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Anritsu ShockLine. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CHX files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-26913.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7976 | Anritsu ShockLine CHX File Parsing Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7976</link><description>Anritsu ShockLine CHX File Parsing Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Anritsu ShockLine. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CHX files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26882.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8613 | Vacron Camera ping Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8613</link><description>Vacron Camera ping Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Vacron Camera devices. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the webs.cgi endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-25892.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8614 | NoMachine Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8614</link><description>NoMachine Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of NoMachine.  An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of OpenSSL. The product loads an OpenSSL configuration file from an unsecured location. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-26766.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36162 | IBM DevOps Deploy / IBM UrbanCode Deploy information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36162</link><description>IBM DevOps Deploy / IBM UrbanCode Deploy (UCD) 8.1 before 8.1.2.2 could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive information about configuration on the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 19:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9829 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System signup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9829</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /signup.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43726 | Dell Alienware Command Center 5.x (AWCC), versions prior to 5.10.2.0, contains an Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Followi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43726</link><description>Dell Alienware Command Center 5.x (AWCC), versions prior to 5.10.2.0, contains an Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following')" vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of Privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57775 | Heap-based Buffer Overflow when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57775</link><description>There is a heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability due to improper bounds checking when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab.  This vulnerability may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted DSB file.  The vulnerability affects all versions of DASYLab.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57777 | Out Of Bounds Write in displ2.dll when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57777</link><description>There is an out of bounds write vulnerability due to improper bounds checking in displ2.dll when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab.  This vulnerability may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted DSB file.  The vulnerability affects all versions of DASYLab.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9188 | Deserialization of Untrusted Data when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9188</link><description>There is a deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability in Digilent DASYLab.  This vulnerability may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted DSB file.  The vulnerability affects all versions of DASYLab.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57774 | Out Of Bounds Write of invalid data when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57774</link><description>There is an out of bounds write vulnerability due to improper bounds checking resulting in invalid data when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab.  This vulnerability may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted DSB file.  The vulnerability affects all versions of DASYLab.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:27:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57776 | Out Of Bounds Write to invalid address when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57776</link><description>There is an out of bounds write vulnerability due to improper bounds checking resulting in an invalid address when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab.  This vulnerability may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted DSB file.  The vulnerability affects all versions of DASYLab.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57778 | Out Of Bounds Write to invalid source address when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57778</link><description>There is an out of bounds write vulnerability due to improper bounds checking resulting in an invalid source address when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab.  This vulnerability may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted DSB file.  The vulnerability affects all versions of DASYLab.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9189 | Out Of Bounds Write when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9189</link><description>There is an out of bounds write vulnerability due to improper bounds checking resulting in a large destination address when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab.  This vulnerability may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted DSB file.  The vulnerability affects all versions of DASYLab.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:27:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32100 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32100</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, 1580, 9110, W920, W930, W1000, Modem 5123, Modem 5300, and Modem 5400. A programming mistake for buffer copy leads to out-of-bounds writes via malformed ROHC packets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:27:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32098 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Magician 6.3 through 8.3 on Windows. An attacker can achieve Elevation of Privileges to SYSTEM by exploit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32098</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Magician 6.3 through 8.3 on Windows. An attacker can achieve Elevation of Privileges to SYSTEM by exploiting insecure file delete operations during the update process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50565 | Doubo ERP 1.0 has an SQL injection vulnerability due to a lack of filtering of user input, which can be remotely initiated by an attacker.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50565</link><description>Doubo ERP 1.0 has an SQL injection vulnerability due to a lack of filtering of user input, which can be remotely initiated by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51966 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the PDF preview functionality of uTools thru 7.1.1. When a user previews a specially cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51966</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the PDF preview functionality of uTools thru 7.1.1. When a user previews a specially crafted PDF file, embedded JavaScript code executes within the application's privileged context, potentially allowing attackers to steal sensitive data or perform unauthorized actions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55824 | ModStartCMS v9.5.0 has an arbitrary file write vulnerability, which allows attackers to write malicious files and execute malicious commands...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55824</link><description>ModStartCMS v9.5.0 has an arbitrary file write vulnerability, which allows attackers to write malicious files and execute malicious commands to obtain sensitive data on the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55476 | FireShare FileShare 1.2.25 contains a time-based blind SQL injection vulnerability in the sort parameter of the endpoint: GET /api/videos/pu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55476</link><description>FireShare FileShare 1.2.25 contains a time-based blind SQL injection vulnerability in the sort parameter of the endpoint: GET /api/videos/public?sort= This parameter is unsafely evaluated in a SQL ORDER BY clause without proper sanitization, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary SQL subqueries.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55474 | Many Notes 0.10.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS), which allows malicious Markdown files to execute JavaScript when viewed.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55474</link><description>Many Notes 0.10.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS), which allows malicious Markdown files to execute JavaScript when viewed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9828 | Tenda CP6 uhttp sub_2B7D04 risky encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9828</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda CP6 11.10.00.243. The affected element is the function sub_2B7D04 of the component uhttp. Executing manipulation can lead to risky cryptographic algorithm. The attack may be launched remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55472 | SQL Injection vulnerability exists in Tirreno v0.9.5, specifically in the /admin/loadUsers API endpoint. The vulnerability arises due to uns...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55472</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability exists in Tirreno v0.9.5, specifically in the /admin/loadUsers API endpoint. The vulnerability arises due to unsafe handling of user-supplied input in the columns[0][data] parameter, which is directly used in SQL queries without proper validation or parameterization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55373 | Incorrect access control in Beakon Application before v5.4.3 allows authenticated attackers with low-level privileges to escalate privileges...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55373</link><description>Incorrect access control in Beakon Application before v5.4.3 allows authenticated attackers with low-level privileges to escalate privileges and execute commands with Administrator rights.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55473 | Asian Arts Talents Foundation (AATF) Website v5.1.x and Docker version 2024.12.8.1 are vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). The vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55473</link><description>Asian Arts Talents Foundation (AATF) Website v5.1.x and Docker version 2024.12.8.1 are vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). The vulnerability exists in the /ip.php endpoint, which processes and displays the X-Forwarded-For HTTP header without proper sanitization or output encoding. This allows an attacker to inject malicious JavaScript code that will execute in visitor browsers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9696 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials in SunPower PVS6</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9696</link><description>The SunPower PVS6's BluetoothLE interface is vulnerable due to its use of hardcoded encryption parameters and publicly accessible protocol details. An attacker within Bluetooth range could exploit this vulnerability to gain full access to the device's servicing interface. This access allows the attacker to perform actions such as firmware replacement, disabling power production, modifying grid settings, creating SSH tunnels, altering firewall settings, and manipulating connected devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55372 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Beakon Application before v5.4.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55372</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Beakon Application before v5.4.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57611 | An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the dump() method allows an att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57611</link><description>An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the dump() method allows an attacker to cause a denial of service. The vulnerability exists because the method fails to check the return value of avfilter_graph_dump() for NULL, leading to a crash if the underlying memory allocation fails.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57612 | An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the name() method allows an att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57612</link><description>An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the name() method allows an attacker to cause a denial of service. The vulnerability exists because the method fails to check for a NULL return value from the av_get_sample_fmt_name() C function, which can be triggered by providing an unrecognized sample format.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57613 | An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the input() constructor funct...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57613</link><description>An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the input() constructor function allows an attacker to cause a denial of service. The vulnerability is triggered when the avio_alloc_context() call fails and returns NULL, which is then stored and later dereferenced by the Io struct's Drop implementation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57614 | An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) Integer overflow and invalid input vulnerability in the cached method all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57614</link><description>An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) Integer overflow and invalid input vulnerability in the cached method allows an attacker to cause a denial of service or potentially execute arbitrary code. The vulnerability occurs when dimension parameters are zero or exceed i32::MAX, leading to an unchecked cast that violates the underlying C function's preconditions and triggers undefined behavior.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57615 | An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) An integer overflow vulnerability in the Vector::new constructor function...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57615</link><description>An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) An integer overflow vulnerability in the Vector::new constructor function allows an attacker to cause a denial of service via a null pointer dereference. The vulnerability stems from an unchecked cast of a usize parameter to c_int, which can result in a negative value being passed to the underlying C function sws_allocVec().</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57616 | An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) A use-after-free vulnerability in the write_interleaved method allows an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57616</link><description>An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) A use-after-free vulnerability in the write_interleaved method allows an attacker to cause a denial of service or memory corruption. The method violates Rust's aliasing rules by modifying a data structure through a mutable pointer while only holding an immutable reference, which can lead to undefined behavior when the data is accessed later.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51423 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Infor Global HR GHR v.11.23.03.00.21 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51423</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Infor Global HR GHR v.11.23.03.00.21 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the class parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54599 | The Bevy Event service through 2025-07-22, as used for eBay Seller Events and other activities, allows account takeover, if SSO is used, whe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54599</link><description>The Bevy Event service through 2025-07-22, as used for eBay Seller Events and other activities, allows account takeover, if SSO is used, when a victim changes the email address that they have configured. To exploit this, an attacker would create their own account and perform an SSO login. The root cause of the issue is SSO misconfiguration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48705 | Wavlink AC1200 with firmware versions M32A3_V1410_230602 and M32A3_V1410_240222 are vulnerable to a post-authentication command injection wh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48705</link><description>Wavlink AC1200 with firmware versions M32A3_V1410_230602 and M32A3_V1410_240222 are vulnerable to a post-authentication command injection while resetting the password. This vulnerability is specifically found within the "set_sys_adm" function of the "adm.cgi" binary, and is due to improper santization of the user provided "newpass" field</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50755 | Wavlink WN535K3 20191010 was found to contain a command injection vulnerability in the set_sys_cmd function via the command parameter. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50755</link><description>Wavlink WN535K3 20191010 was found to contain a command injection vulnerability in the set_sys_cmd function via the command parameter. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 14:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50757 | Wavlink WN535K3 20191010 was found to contain a command injection vulnerability in the set_sys_adm function via the username parameter. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50757</link><description>Wavlink WN535K3 20191010 was found to contain a command injection vulnerability in the set_sys_adm function via the username parameter. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 14:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2413 | OTP Bypass in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s ProKuafor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2413</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Akinsoft ProKuafor allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects ProKuafor: from s1.02.08 before v1.02.08.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9784 | Undertow: undertow madeyoureset http/2 ddos vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9784</link><description>A flaw was found in Undertow where malformed client requests can trigger server-side stream resets without triggering abuse counters. This issue, referred to as the "MadeYouReset" attack, allows malicious clients to induce excessive server workload by repeatedly causing server-side stream aborts. While not a protocol bug, this highlights a common implementation weakness that can be exploited to cause a denial of service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12974 | XSS in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s ProKuafr</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12974</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Akinsoft ProKuafr allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects ProKuafr: from s1.02.07 before v1.02.08.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0670 | IDOR in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s ProKuafor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0670</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Akinsoft ProKuafor allows Resource Leak Exposure.This issue affects ProKuafor: from s1.02.07 before v1.02.08.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46047 | A User enumeration vulnerability in the /CredentialsServlet/ForgotPassword endpoint in Silverpeas 6.4.1 and 6.4.2 allows remote attackers to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46047</link><description>A User enumeration vulnerability in the /CredentialsServlet/ForgotPassword endpoint in Silverpeas 6.4.1 and 6.4.2 allows remote attackers to determine valid usernames via the Login parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58259 | Rancher affected by unauthenticated Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58259</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified within Rancher Manager in which it 
did not enforce request body size limits on certain public 
(unauthenticated) and authenticated API endpoints. This allows a 
malicious user to exploit this by sending excessively large payloads, 
which are fully loaded into memory during processing, leading toDenial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2414 | OTP Bypass in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s OctoCloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2414</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Akinsoft OctoCloud allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects OctoCloud: from s1.09.03 before v1.11.01.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56254 | PHPGurukul Employee Leave Management System 2.1 contains an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in leave-details.php. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56254</link><description>PHPGurukul Employee Leave Management System 2.1 contains an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in leave-details.php. An authenticated user can change the leaveid parameter in the URL to access leave application details of other users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52284 | Rancher Fleet Helm Values are stored inside BundleDeployment in plain text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52284</link><description>Unauthorized disclosure of sensitive data: Any user with `GET` or `LIST` permissions on `BundleDeployment` resources could retrieve Helm values containing credentials or other secrets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0640 | IDOR in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s OctoCloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0640</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Akinsoft OctoCloud allows Resource Leak Exposure.This issue affects OctoCloud: from s1.09.02 before v1.11.01.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:58:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57140 | rsbi-pom 4.7 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the /bi/service/model/DatasetService path.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57140</link><description>rsbi-pom 4.7 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the /bi/service/model/DatasetService path.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:58:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12973 | Host Header Injection in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s OctoCloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12973</link><description>Origin Validation Error vulnerability in Akinsoft OctoCloud allows HTTP Response Splitting, CAPEC - 87 - Forceful Browsing.This issue affects OctoCloud: from s1.09.01 before v1.11.01.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:49:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12972 | XSS in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s OctoCloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12972</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Akinsoft OctoCloud allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects OctoCloud: from s1.09.01 before v1.11.01.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46810 | A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of openSUSE Tumbleweed traefik2 allows the traefik user to escalate ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46810</link><description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of openSUSE Tumbleweed traefik2 allows the traefik user to escalate to root.This issue affects Tumbleweed: from ? before 2.11.29.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52551 | Proprietary protocol allows for unauthenticated file operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52551</link><description>E2 Facility Management Systems use a proprietary protocol that allows for unauthenticated file operations on any file in the file system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52543 | Login to the application services using only the password hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52543</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor Control (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) application services (MGW and RCI) uses client side hashing for authentication. An attacker can authenticate by obtaining only the password hash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52544 | Arbitrary read file from the filesystem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52544</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor Control (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) has a floor plan feature that allows for an unauthenticated attacker to upload floor plan files. By uploading a specially crafted floor plan file, an attacker can access any file from the E3 file system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52545 | Privilege escalation in the application services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52545</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor Control (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) RCI service contains an API call to read users info, which returns all usernames and password hashes for the application services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52546 | Stored XSS by uploading a specially crafted floor plan file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52546</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor Control (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) has a floor plan feature that allows for an unauthenticated attacker to upload floor plan files. By uploading a specially crafted floor plan file, an attacker can inject a stored XSS to the floorplan web page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52547 | DoS to the application services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52547</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor Control (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) MGW contains an API call that lacks input validation. An attacker can use this command to continuously crash the application services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52548 | Enabling SSH and Shellinabox on the vulnerable machine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52548</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor Control (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) contains a hidden API call in the application services that enables SSH and Shellinabox, which exist but are disabled by default. An attacker with admin access to the application services can utilize this API to enable remote access to the underlying OS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52549 | Predictable root linux password generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52549</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor Control (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) generates the root linux password on each boot. An attacker can generate the root linux password for a vulnerable device based on known or easy to fetch parameters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52550 | Firmware upgrade packages are unsigned</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52550</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor Control (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) firmware upgrade packages are unsigned. An attacker can forge malicious firmware upgrade packages. An attacker with admin access to the application services can install a malicious firmware upgrade.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6519 | Consistent predictable generation of the password for the default admin user &amp;quot;ONEDAY&amp;quot; to the application services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6519</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) has a default admin user "ONEDAY" with a daily generated password. An attacker can predictably generate the password for ONEDAY. The oneday user cannot be deleted or modified by any user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5662 | Deserialization Vulnerability in h2oai/h2o-3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5662</link><description>A deserialization vulnerability exists in the H2O-3 REST API (POST /99/ImportSQLTable) that affects all versions up to 3.46.0.7. This vulnerability allows remote code execution (RCE) due to improper validation of JDBC connection parameters when using a Key-Value format. The vulnerability is present in the MySQL JDBC Driver version 8.0.19 and JDK version 8u112. The issue is resolved in version 3.46.0.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9573 | Command Injection in extension Backup Plus (ns_backup)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9573</link><description>The ns_backup extension through 13.0.2 for TYPO3 allows command injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 08:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41030 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Deporsite by T-INNOVA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41030</link><description>Lack of authorisation in Deporsite by T-INNOVA. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to obtain information from other users via GET /ajax/TInnova_v2/Integrantes_Recurso_v2_1/llamadaAjax/buscarPersona using the dni parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 08:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41031 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Deporsite by T-INNOVA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41031</link><description>Lack of authorisation in Deporsite by T-INNOVA. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to change other users' profile pictures via a POST request using the parameters IdPersona and Foto in /ajax/TInnova_c/FotoUsuario/llamadaAjax/uploadImage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 08:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41690 | Endress+Hauser: Proline 10 Maintenance credentials may be exposed under certain conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41690</link><description>A low-privileged attacker in bluetooth range may be able to access the password of a higher-privilege user (Maintenance) by viewing the devices event log. This vulnerability could allow the Operator to authenticate as the Maintenance user, thereby gaining unauthorized access to sensitive configuration settings and the ability to modify device parameters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 08:23:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44017 | "Gunosy" App contains a vulnerability where sensitive information may be included in the application's outbound communication. If a user acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44017</link><description>"Gunosy" App contains a vulnerability where sensitive information may be included in the application's outbound communication. If a user accesses a crafted URL, an attacker may obtain the JWT (JSON Web Token).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9815 | alaneuler batteryKid NSXPCListener PrivilegeHelper.swift missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9815</link><description>A weakness has been identified in alaneuler batteryKid up to 2.1 on macOS. The affected element is an unknown function of the file PrivilegeHelper/PrivilegeHelper.swift of the component NSXPCListener. This manipulation causes missing authentication. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 04:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9813 | Tenda CH22 SetSambaConf formSetSambaConf buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9813</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda CH22 1.0.0.1. This issue affects the function formSetSambaConf of the file /goform/SetSambaConf. The manipulation of the argument samba_userNameSda leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 04:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9814 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System contact-us.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9814</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/contact-us.php. The manipulation of the argument mobnumber results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 04:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9811 | Campcodes Farm Management System reviewInput.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9811</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Farm Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /reviewInput.php. Performing manipulation of the argument rating results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 03:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9812 | Tenda CH22 exeCommand formexeCommand buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9812</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda CH22 1.0.0.1. This vulnerability affects the function formexeCommand of the file /goform/exeCommand. Executing manipulation of the argument cmdinput can lead to buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 03:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8662 | OpenAM (OpenAM Consortium Edition) contains a vulnerability that may cause it to malfunction as a SAML IdP due to a tampered request.This is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8662</link><description>OpenAM (OpenAM Consortium Edition) contains a vulnerability that may cause it to malfunction as a SAML IdP due to a tampered request.This issue affects OpenAM: from 14.0.0 through 14.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 02:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58161 | MobSF Path Traversal in GET /download/&amp;lt;filename&amp;gt; using absolute filenames</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58161</link><description>MobSF is a mobile application security testing tool used. In version 4.4.0, the GET /download/ route uses string path verification via os.path.commonprefix, which allows an authenticated user to download files outside the DWD_DIR download directory from "neighboring" directories whose absolute paths begin with the same prefix as DWD_DIR (e.g., .../downloads_bak, .../downloads.old). This is a Directory Traversal (escape) leading to a data leak. This issue has been patched in version 4.4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58162 | MobSF Vulnerable to Arbitrary File Write (AR-Slip) via Absolute Path in .a Extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58162</link><description>MobSF is a mobile application security testing tool used. In version 4.4.0, an authenticated user who uploaded a specially prepared one.a, can write arbitrary files to any directory writable by the user of the MobSF process. This issue has been patched in version 4.4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58178 | Command Injection via sonarqube-scan-action GitHub Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58178</link><description>SonarQube Server and Cloud is a static analysis solution for continuous code quality and security inspection. In versions 4 to 5.3.0, a command injection vulnerability was discovered in the SonarQube Scan GitHub Action that allows untrusted input arguments to be processed without proper sanitization. Arguments sent to the action are treated as shell expressions, allowing potential execution of arbitrary commands. A fix has been released in SonarQube Scan GitHub Action 5.3.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57808 | ESP-IDF web_server basic auth bypass using empty or incomplete Authorization header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57808</link><description>ESPHome is a system to control microcontrollers remotely through Home Automation systems. In version 2025.8.0 in the ESP-IDF platform, ESPHome's web_server authentication check can pass incorrectly when the client-supplied base64-encoded Authorization value is empty or is a substring of the correct value. This allows access to web_server functionality (including OTA, if enabled) without knowing any information about the correct username or password. This issue has been patched in version 2025.8.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9805 | SimStudioAI sim route.ts server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9805</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SimStudioAI sim up to 51b1e97fa22c48d144aef75f8ca31a74ad2cfed2. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file apps/sim/app/api/proxy/image/route.ts. The manipulation results in server-side request forgery. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product utilizes a rolling release system for continuous delivery, and as such, version information for affected or updated releases is not disclosed. The patch is identified as 3424a338b763115f0269b209e777608e4cd31785. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9806 | Tenda F1202 Administrative shadow hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9806</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda F1202 1.2.0.9/1.2.0.14/1.2.0.20. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /etc_ro/shadow of the component Administrative Interface. This manipulation with the input Fireitup causes hard-coded credentials. The attack can only be executed locally. A high degree of complexity is needed for the attack. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>