<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:22:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-5828 | EL Injection Vulnerability in Hitachi Tuning Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5828</link><description>Expression Language Injection vulnerability in Hitachi Tuning Manager on Windows, Linux, Solaris allows Code Injection.This issue affects Hitachi Tuning Manager: before 8.8.7-00.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5963 | An unquoted executable path exists in Hitachi Device Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5963</link><description>Unquoted Executable Path vulnerability in Hitachi Device Manager on Windows (Device Manager Server component).This issue affects Hitachi Device Manager: before 8.8.7-00.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:22:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7497 | itsourcecode Airline Reservation System index.php file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7497</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Airline Reservation System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument page leads to file inclusion. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273623.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:22:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5000 | Horizontal scrolling announcements &amp;lt;= 2.4 -  Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5000</link><description>The Horizontal scrolling announcements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's 'hsas-shortcode' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 2.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6315 | Blox Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.0.65 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6315</link><description>The Blox Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'handleUploadFile' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.65. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level and above permissions, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7484 | CRM Perks Forms &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7484</link><description>The CRM Perks Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file validation on the 'handle_uploaded_files' function in versions up to, and including, 1.1.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with administrator-level capabilities or above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7485 | Traffic Manager &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7485</link><description>The Traffic Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in the 'UserWebStat' AJAX function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7496 | itsourcecode Airline Reservation System index.php file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7496</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Airline Reservation System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument page leads to file inclusion. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273622 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:22:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7495 | itsourcecode Laravel Accounting System HomeController.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7495</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Laravel Accounting System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file app/Http/Controllers/HomeController.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273621 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 01:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7537 | oFono QMI SMS Handling Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7537</link><description>oFono QMI SMS Handling Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of oFono. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of SMS message lists. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-23157.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7538 | oFono CUSD AT Command Stack-based Buffer Overflow Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7538</link><description>oFono CUSD AT Command Stack-based Buffer Overflow Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of oFono. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of responses from AT Commands. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-23190.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7539 | oFono CUSD Stack-based Buffer Overflow Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7539</link><description>oFono CUSD Stack-based Buffer Overflow Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of oFono. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of responses from AT+CUSD commands. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-23195.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7540 | oFono AT CMGL Command Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7540</link><description>oFono AT CMGL Command Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of oFono. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of responses from AT+CMGL commands. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-23307.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7541 | oFono AT CMT Command Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7541</link><description>oFono AT CMT Command Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of oFono. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of responses from AT+CMT commands. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-23308.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7542 | oFono AT CMGR Command Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7542</link><description>oFono AT CMGR Command Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of oFono. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of responses from AT+CMGR commands. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-23309.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7543 | oFono SimToolKit Heap-based Buffer Overflow Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7543</link><description>oFono SimToolKit Heap-based Buffer Overflow Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of oFono. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of STK command PDUs. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-23456.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7544 | oFono SimToolKit Heap-based Buffer Overflow Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7544</link><description>oFono SimToolKit Heap-based Buffer Overflow Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of oFono. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of STK command PDUs. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-23457.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7545 | oFono SimToolKit Heap-based Buffer Overflow Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7545</link><description>oFono SimToolKit Heap-based Buffer Overflow Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of oFono. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of STK command PDUs. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-23458.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7546 | oFono SimToolKit Heap-based Buffer Overflow Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7546</link><description>oFono SimToolKit Heap-based Buffer Overflow Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of oFono. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of STK command PDUs. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-23459.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7547 | oFono SMS Decoder Stack-based Buffer Overflow Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7547</link><description>oFono SMS Decoder Stack-based Buffer Overflow Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of oFono. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SMS PDUs. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-23460.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7494 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System new_prescription.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7494</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /new_prescription.php. The manipulation of the argument patient leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273620.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42352 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in nuxt-icon</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42352</link><description>Nuxt is a free and open-source framework to create full-stack web applications and websites with Vue.js. `nuxt/icon` provides an API to allow client side icon lookup. This endpoint is at `/api/_nuxt_icon/[name]`. The proxied request path is improperly parsed, allowing an attacker to change the scheme and host of the request. This leads to SSRF, and could potentially lead to sensitive data exposure. The `new URL` constructor is used to parse the final path. This constructor can be passed a relative scheme or path in order to change the host the request is sent to. This constructor is also very tolerant of poorly formatted URLs. As a result we can pass a path prefixed with the string `http:`. This has the effect of changing the scheme to HTTP. We can then subsequently pass a new host, for example `http:127.0.0.1:8080`. This would allow us to send requests to a local server. This issue has been addressed in release version 1.4.5 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34343 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in navigateTo if used after SSR in nuxt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34343</link><description>Nuxt is a free and open-source framework to create full-stack web applications and websites with Vue.js. The `navigateTo` function attempts to blockthe `javascript:` protocol, but does not correctly use API's provided by `unjs/ufo`. This library also contains parsing discrepancies.  The function first tests to see if the specified URL has a protocol. This uses the unjs/ufo package for URL parsing. This function works effectively, and returns true for a javascript: protocol. After this, the URL is parsed using the parseURL function. This function will refuse to parse poorly formatted URLs. Parsing javascript:alert(1) returns null/"" for all values. Next, the protocol of the URL is then checked using the isScriptProtocol function. This function simply checks the input against a list of protocols, and does not perform any parsing. The combination of refusing to parse poorly formatted URLs, and not performing additional parsing means that script checks fail as no protocol can be found. Even if a protocol was identified, whitespace is not stripped in the parseURL implementation, bypassing the isScriptProtocol checks. Certain special protocols are identified at the top of parseURL. Inserting a newline or tab into this sequence will block the special protocol check, and bypass the latter checks. This ONLY has impact after SSR has occured, the `javascript:` protocol within a location header does not trigger XSS. This issue has been addressed in release version 3.12.4 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34344 | Remote code execution via the browser when running the test locally in nuxt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34344</link><description>Nuxt is a free and open-source framework to create full-stack web applications and websites with Vue.js. Due to the insufficient validation of the `path` parameter in the NuxtTestComponentWrapper, an attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript on the server side, which allows them to execute arbitrary commands. Users who open a malicious web page in the browser while running the test locally are affected by this vulnerability, which results in the remote code execution from the malicious web page. Since web pages can send requests to arbitrary addresses, a malicious web page can repeatedly try to exploit this vulnerability, which then triggers the exploit when the test server starts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23657 | Path Traversal: &amp;#x27;../filedir&amp;#x27; in Nuxt Devtools</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23657</link><description>Nuxt is a free and open-source framework to create full-stack web applications and websites with Vue.js. Nuxt Devtools is missing authentication on the `getTextAssetContent` RPC function which is vulnerable to path traversal.  Combined with a lack of Origin checks on the WebSocket handler,  an attacker is able to interact with a locally running devtools instance and exfiltrate data abusing this vulnerability. In certain configurations an attacker could leak the devtools authentication token and then abuse other RPC functions to achieve RCE. The `getTextAssetContent` function does not check for path traversals, this could allow an attacker to read arbitrary files over the RPC WebSocket. The WebSocket server does not check the origin of the request leading to cross-site-websocket-hijacking. This may be intentional to allow certain configurations to work correctly. Nuxt Devtools authentication tokens are placed within the home directory of the current user. The malicious webpage can connect to the Devtools WebSocket, perform a directory traversal brute force to find the authentication token, then use the *authenticated* `writeStaticAssets` function to create a new Component, Nitro Handler or `app.vue` file which will run automatically as the file is changed. This vulnerability has been addressed in release version 1.3.9. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41811 | ipl/web susceptible to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41811</link><description>ipl/web is a set of common web components for php projects. Some of the recent development by Icinga is, under certain circumstances, susceptible to cross site request forgery. (CSRF). All affected products, in any version, will be unaffected by this once `icinga-php-library` is upgraded. Version 0.10.1 includes a fix for this. It will be published as part of the `icinga-php-library` v0.14.1 release.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41816 | WordPress Cooked Plugin Persistent Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41816</link><description>Cooked is a recipe plugin for WordPress. The Cooked plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Persistent Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via the ‘[cooked-timer]’ shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This vulnerability allows authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access and above to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses a compromised page. This issue has been addressed in release version 1.8.1. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41820 | Cluster-level privilege escalation in kubean</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41820</link><description>Kubean is a cluster lifecycle management toolchain based on kubespray and other cluster LCM engine. The ClusterRole has `*` verbs of `*` resources. If a malicious user can access the worker node which has kubean's deployment, he/she can abuse these excessive permissions to do whatever he/she likes to the whole cluster, resulting in a cluster-level privilege escalation. This issue has been addressed in release version 0.18.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41958 | Two-Factor Authentication (2FA) Bypass in mailcow: dockerized</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41958</link><description>mailcow: dockerized is an open source groupware/email suite based on docker. A vulnerability has been discovered in the two-factor authentication (2FA) mechanism. This flaw allows an authenticated attacker to bypass the 2FA protection, enabling unauthorized access to other accounts that are otherwise secured with 2FA. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must first have access to an account within the system and possess the credentials of the target account that has 2FA enabled. By leveraging these credentials, the attacker can circumvent the 2FA process and gain access to the protected account. This issue has been addressed in the `2024-07` release. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:10:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41959 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via API Logs in mailcow: dockerized</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41959</link><description>mailcow: dockerized is an open source groupware/email suite based on docker. An unauthenticated attacker can inject a JavaScript payload into the API logs. This payload is executed whenever the API logs page is viewed, potentially allowing an attacker to run malicious scripts in the context of the user's browser. This could lead to unauthorized actions, data theft, or further exploitation of the affected system. This issue has been addressed in the `2024-07` release. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:10:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41960 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via Relay Hosts Configuration in mailcow: dockerized</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41960</link><description>mailcow: dockerized is an open source groupware/email suite based on docker. An authenticated admin user can inject a JavaScript payload into the Relay Hosts configuration. The injected payload is executed whenever the configuration page is viewed, enabling the attacker to execute arbitrary scripts in the context of the user's browser. This could lead to data theft, or further exploitation. This issue has been addressed in the `2024-07` release. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:10:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42350 | Public key confusion in third party block in Biscuit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42350</link><description>Biscuit is an authorization token with decentralized verification, offline attenuation and strong security policy enforcement based on a logic language. Third-party blocks can be generated without transferring the whole token to the third-party authority. Instead, a `ThirdPartyBlock` request can be sent, providing only the necessary info to generate a third-party block and to sign it: 1. the public key of the previous block (used in the signature), 2. the public keys part of the token symbol table (for public key interning in datalog expressions). A third-part block request forged by a malicious user can trick the third-party authority into generating datalog trusting the wrong keypair. Tokens with third-party blocks containing `trusted` annotations generated through a third party block request. This has been addressed in version 4 of the specification. Users are advised to update their implementations to conform. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6915 | JFrog Artifactory Cache Poisoning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6915</link><description>JFrog Artifactory versions below 7.90.6, 7.84.20, 7.77.14, 7.71.23, 7.68.22, 7.63.22, 7.59.23, 7.55.18 are vulnerable to Improper Input Validation that could potentially lead to cache poisoning.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42009 | A Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in Roundcube through 1.5.7 and 1.6.x through 1.6.7 allows a remote attacker to steal and send emails of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42009</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in Roundcube through 1.5.7 and 1.6.x through 1.6.7 allows a remote attacker to steal and send emails of a victim via a crafted e-mail message that abuses a Desanitization issue in message_body() in program/actions/mail/show.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42010 | mod_css_styles in Roundcube through 1.5.7 and 1.6.x through 1.6.7 allows a insufficiently filters Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) token sequenc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42010</link><description>mod_css_styles in Roundcube through 1.5.7 and 1.6.x through 1.6.7 allows a insufficiently filters Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) token sequences in rendered e-mail messages, allowing a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42008 | A Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in rcmail_action_mail_get-&gt;run() in Roundcube through 1.5.7 and 1.6.x through 1.6.7 allows a remote att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42008</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in rcmail_action_mail_get-&gt;run() in Roundcube through 1.5.7 and 1.6.x through 1.6.7 allows a remote attacker to steal and send emails of a victim via a malicious e-mail attachment served with a dangerous Content-Type header.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6361 | Improper Neutralization vulnerability (XSS) has been discovered in OpenText™ ALM Octane product.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6361</link><description>Improper Neutralization vulnerability (XSS) has been discovered in OpenText™ ALM Octane. The vulnerability affects all version prior to version 23.4. The vulnerability could cause remote code execution attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 18:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41381 | microweber 2.0.16 was discovered to contain a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via userfiles\modules\settings\admin.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41381</link><description>microweber 2.0.16 was discovered to contain a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via userfiles\modules\settings\admin.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40498 | SQL Injection vulnerability in PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping sysstem advanced v.1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40498</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping sysstem advanced v.1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the register.php</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41376 | dzzoffice 2.02.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via user/space/about.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41376</link><description>dzzoffice 2.02.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via user/space/about.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41380 | microweber 2.0.16 was discovered to contain a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via userfiles\modules\tags\add_tagging_tagged.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41380</link><description>microweber 2.0.16 was discovered to contain a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via userfiles\modules\tags\add_tagging_tagged.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41200 | A segmentation fault in KMPlayer v4.2.2.65 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted AVI file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41200</link><description>A segmentation fault in KMPlayer v4.2.2.65 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted AVI file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:12:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21978 | Improper input validation in SEV-SNP could allow a malicious hypervisor to read or overwrite guest memory potentially leading to data leakag...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21978</link><description>Improper input validation in SEV-SNP could allow a malicious hypervisor to read or overwrite guest memory potentially leading to data leakage or data corruption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21980 | Improper restriction of write operations in SNP firmware could allow a malicious hypervisor to potentially overwrite a guest's memory or UMC...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21980</link><description>Improper restriction of write operations in SNP firmware could allow a malicious hypervisor to potentially overwrite a guest's memory or UMC seed resulting in loss of confidentiality and integrity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31355 | Improper restriction of write operations in SNP firmware could allow a malicious hypervisor to overwrite a guest's UMC seed potentially allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31355</link><description>Improper restriction of write operations in SNP firmware could allow a malicious hypervisor to overwrite a guest's UMC seed potentially allowing reading of memory from a decommissioned guest.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40530 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in UAB Lexita PanteraCRM CMS v.401.152 and Patera CRM CMS v.402.072 allows a remote attacker to execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40530</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in UAB Lexita PanteraCRM CMS v.401.152 and Patera CRM CMS v.402.072 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via modification of the X-Forwarded-For header component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 15:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40531 | An issue in UAB Lexita PanteraCRM CMS v.401.152 and Patera CRM CMS v.402.072 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the user pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40531</link><description>An issue in UAB Lexita PanteraCRM CMS v.401.152 and Patera CRM CMS v.402.072 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the user profile management function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 15:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21459 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN HOST</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21459</link><description>Information disclosure while handling beacon or probe response frame in STA.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21467 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21467</link><description>Information disclosure while handling beacon probe frame during scan entry generation in client side.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21479 | Buffer Over-read in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21479</link><description>Transient DOS during music playback of ALAC content.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21481 | Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in Hypervisor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21481</link><description>Memory corruption when preparing a shared memory notification for a memparcel in Resource Manager.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23350 | Reachable Assertion in Multi Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23350</link><description>Permanent DOS when DL NAS transport receives multiple payloads such that one payload contains SOR container whose integrity check has failed, and the other is LPP where UE needs to send status message to network.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23352 | Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition (`Infinite Loop`) in Multi Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23352</link><description>Transient DOS when NAS receives ODAC criteria of length 1 and type 1 in registration accept OTA.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23353 | Buffer Over-read in Multi Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23353</link><description>Transient DOS while decoding attach reject message received by UE, when IEI is set to ESM_IEI.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23355 | Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in Automotive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23355</link><description>Memory corruption when keymaster operation imports a shared key.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23356 | Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23356</link><description>Memory corruption during session sign renewal request calls in HLOS.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23357 | NULL Pointer Dereference in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23357</link><description>Transient DOS while importing a PKCS#8-encoded RSA key with zero bytes modulus.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23381 | Use After Free in Graphics Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23381</link><description>Memory corruption when memory mapped in a VBO is not unmapped by the GPU SMMU.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23382 | Use After Free in Graphics Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23382</link><description>Memory corruption while processing graphics kernel driver request to create DMA fence.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23383 | Use After Free in Graphics Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23383</link><description>Memory corruption when kernel driver attempts to trigger hardware fences.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23384 | Use After Free in Graphics Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23384</link><description>Memory corruption when the mapped pages in VBO are still mapped after reclaiming by shrinker.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33010 | Use After Free in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33010</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing fragments of MBSSID IE from beacon frame.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33011 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33011</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing the MBSSID IE from the beacons, when the MBSSID IE length is zero.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33012 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33012</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing the multiple MBSSID IEs from the beacon, when the tag length is non-zero value but with end of beacon.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33013 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33013</link><description>Transient DOS when driver accesses the ML IE memory and offset value is incremented beyond ML IE length.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33014 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33014</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing ESP IE from beacon/probe response frame.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33015 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33015</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing SCAN RNR IE when bytes received from AP is such that the size of the last param of IE is less than neighbor report.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33018 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33018</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing the received TID-to-link mapping element of the TID-to-link mapping action frame.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33019 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33019</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing the received TID-to-link mapping action frame.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33020 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN HOST</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33020</link><description>Transient DOS while processing TID-to-link mapping IE elements.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33021 | Use of Uninitialized Variable in Automotive GPU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33021</link><description>Memory corruption while processing IOCTL call to set metainfo.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33022 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in Automotive GPU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33022</link><description>Memory corruption while allocating memory in HGSL driver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33023 | Use After Free in Graphics Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33023</link><description>Memory corruption while creating a fence to wait on timeline events, and simultaneously signal timeline events.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33024 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33024</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing the ML IE when a beacon with length field inside the common info of ML IE greater than the ML IE length.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33025 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33025</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing the BSS parameter change count or MLD capabilities fields of the ML IE.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33026 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33026</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing probe response and assoc response frame when received frame length is less than max size of timestamp.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33027 | Improper Access Control in Graphics Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33027</link><description>Memory corruption can occur when arbitrary user-space app gains kernel level privilege to modify DDR memory by corrupting the GPU page table.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33028 | Use After Free in Automotive Telematics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33028</link><description>Memory corruption as fence object may still be accessed in timeline destruct after isync fence is released.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33034 | Use After Free in Graphics Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33034</link><description>Memory corruption can occur if VBOs hold outdated or invalid GPU SMMU mappings, especially when the binding and reclaiming of memory buffers are performed at the same time.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7397 | Unauthenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7397</link><description>Improper filering of special characters result in a command ('command injection') vulnerability in Korenix JetPort 5601v3.This issue affects JetPort 5601v3: through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7396 | Plaintext Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7396</link><description>Missing encryption of sensitive data in Korenix JetPort 5601v3 allows Eavesdropping.This issue affects JetPort 5601v3: through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7409 | Qemu: denial of service via improper synchronization in qemu nbd server during socket closure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7409</link><description>A flaw was found in the QEMU NBD Server. This vulnerability allows a denial of service (DoS) attack via improper synchronization during socket closure when a client keeps a socket open as the server is taken offline.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7383 | Libnbd: nbd server improper certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7383</link><description>A flaw was found in libnbd. The client did not always correctly verify the NBD server's certificate when using TLS to connect to an NBD server. This issue allows a man-in-the-middle attack on NBD traffic.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7395 | Insufficient Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7395</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability in Korenix JetPort 5601v3 allows an attacker to access functionality on the device without specifying a password.This issue affects JetPort 5601v3: through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6472 | Ability to trust not validated macro signatures removed in high security mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6472</link><description>Certificate Validation user interface in LibreOffice allows potential vulnerability.




Signed macros are scripts that have been digitally signed by the 
developer using a cryptographic signature. When a document with a signed
 macro is opened a warning is displayed by LibreOffice before the macro 
is executed.

Previously if verification failed the user could fail to understand the failure and choose to enable the macros anyway.


This issue affects LibreOffice: from 24.2 before 24.2.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4607 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU memory processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4607</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user to make improper GPU memory processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r49p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r49p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r49p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 11:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2937 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU memory processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2937</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user to make improper GPU memory processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r49p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r49p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r49p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 11:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40096 | The com.cascadialabs.who (aka Who - Caller ID, Spam Block) application 15.0 for Android places sensitive information in the system log.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40096</link><description>The com.cascadialabs.who (aka Who - Caller ID, Spam Block) application 15.0 for Android places sensitive information in the system log.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 10:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36448 | Apache IoTDB Workbench: SSRF Vulnerability (EOL)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36448</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Apache IoTDB Workbench.

This issue affects Apache IoTDB Workbench: from 0.13.0.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 10:03:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38856 | Apache OFBiz: Unauthenticated endpoint could allow execution of screen rendering code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38856</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Apache OFBiz.

This issue affects Apache OFBiz: through 18.12.14.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 18.12.15, which fixes the issue.

Unauthenticated endpoints could allow execution of screen rendering code of screens if some preconditions are met (such as when the screen definitions don't explicitly check user's permissions because they rely on the configuration of their endpoints).</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 08:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42447 | Apache Airflow Providers FAB: FAB provider 1.2.1 and 1.2.0 did not let user to logout for Airflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42447</link><description>Insufficient Session Expiration vulnerability in Apache Airflow Providers FAB.

This issue affects Apache Airflow Providers FAB: 1.2.1 (when used with Apache Airflow 2.9.3) and FAB 1.2.0 for all Airflow versions. The FAB provider prevented the user from logging out.  

* FAB provider 1.2.1 only affected Airflow 2.9.3 (earlier and later versions of Airflow are not affected)

* FAB provider 1.2.0 affected all versions of Airflow.

Users who run Apache Airflow 2.9.3 are recommended to upgrade to Apache Airflow Providers FAB version 1.2.2 which fixes the issue.

Users who run Any Apache Airflow version and have FAB provider 1.2.0 are recommended to upgrade to Apache Airflow Providers FAB version 1.2.2 which fixes the issue.

Also upgrading Apache Airflow to latest version available is recommended.

Note: Early version of Airflow reference container images of Airflow 2.9.3 and constraint files contained FAB provider 1.2.1 version, but this is fixed in updated versions of the images. 

Users are advised to pull the latest Airflow images or reinstall FAB provider according to the current constraints.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 08:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2232 | Himer - Social Questions and Answers &amp;lt; 2.1.3 - CSRF While Sending the Invites</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2232</link><description>The  lacks CSRF checks allowing a user to invite any user to any group (including private groups)</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3636 | Pinpoint Booking System &amp;lt; 2.9.9.4.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3636</link><description>The Pinpoint Booking System  WordPress plugin before 2.9.9.4.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5081 | WP eMember &amp;lt;= v10.7.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5081</link><description>The wp-eMember WordPress plugin before v10.7.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6270 | Community Events &amp;lt; 1.5.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6270</link><description>The Community Events WordPress plugin before 1.5.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6498 | CollectChat &amp;lt; 2.4.4 - Admin+ XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6498</link><description>The Chatbot for WordPress by Collect.chat ⚡️ WordPress plugin before 2.4.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6710 | Ditty &amp;lt; 3.1.45 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6710</link><description>The Ditty  WordPress plugin before 3.1.45 does not sanitise and escape some parameters, which could allow users with a role as low as Contributor to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39838 | ZWX-2000CSW2-HN firmware versions prior to Ver.0.3.15 uses hard-coded credentials, which may allow a network-adjacent attacker with an admin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39838</link><description>ZWX-2000CSW2-HN firmware versions prior to Ver.0.3.15 uses hard-coded credentials, which may allow a network-adjacent attacker with an administrative privilege to alter the configuration of the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41720 | Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource issue exists in ZWX-2000CSW2-HN firmware versions prior to Ver.0.3.15, which may allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41720</link><description>Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource issue exists in ZWX-2000CSW2-HN firmware versions prior to Ver.0.3.15, which may allow a network-adjacent authenticated attacker to alter the configuration of the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41889 | Multiple Pimax products accept WebSocket connections from unintended endpoints. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary code may be ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41889</link><description>Multiple Pimax products accept WebSocket connections from unintended endpoints. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary code may be executed by a remote unauthenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39713 | A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) affects Rocket.Chat's Twilio webhook endpoint before version 6.10.1.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39713</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) affects Rocket.Chat's Twilio webhook endpoint before version 6.10.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6117 | Hamastar MeetingHub Paperless Meetings - Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6117</link><description>A Unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability in meeting management function in Hamastar MeetingHub Paperless Meetings 2021 allows remote authenticated users to perform arbitrary system commands via a crafted ASP file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6118 | Hamastar MeetingHub Paperless Meetings - Plaintext Storage of a Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6118</link><description>A Plaintext Storage of a Password vulnerability in ebooknote function in Hamastar MeetingHub Paperless Meetings 2021 allows remote attackers to obtain the other users’ credentials and gain access to the product via an XML file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7470 | Raisecom MSG1200/MSG2100E/MSG2200/MSG2300 Web Interface vpn_template_style.php sslvpn_config_mod os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7470</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Raisecom MSG1200, MSG2100E, MSG2200 and MSG2300 3.90. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function sslvpn_config_mod of the file /vpn/vpn_template_style.php of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument template/stylenum leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273563. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7469 | Raisecom MSG1200/MSG2100E/MSG2200/MSG2300 Web Interface list_vpn_web_custom.php sslvpn_config_mod os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7469</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Raisecom MSG1200, MSG2100E, MSG2200 and MSG2300 3.90. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function sslvpn_config_mod of the file /vpn/list_vpn_web_custom.php of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument template/stylenum leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273562 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 03:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7468 | Raisecom MSG1200/MSG2100E/MSG2200/MSG2300 Web Interface list_service_manage.php sslvpn_config_mod os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7468</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Raisecom MSG1200, MSG2100E, MSG2200 and MSG2300 3.90. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function sslvpn_config_mod of the file /vpn/list_service_manage.php of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument template/stylenum leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273561 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 03:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7467 | Raisecom MSG1200/MSG2100E/MSG2200/MSG2300 Web Interface list_ip_network.php sslvpn_config_mod os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7467</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Raisecom MSG1200, MSG2100E, MSG2200 and MSG2300 3.90 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function sslvpn_config_mod of the file /vpn/list_ip_network.php of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument template/stylenum leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273560. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7466 | PMWeb Web Application Firewall cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7466</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PMWeb 7.2.00 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Web Application Firewall. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273559. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7465 | TOTOLINK CP450 cstecgi.cgi loginauth buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7465</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK CP450 4.1.0cu.747_B20191224. Affected is the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273558 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7464 | TOTOLINK CP900 Telnet Service setTelnetCfg command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7464</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK CP900 6.3c.566. This issue affects the function setTelnetCfg of the component Telnet Service. The manipulation of the argument telnet_enabled leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273557 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7463 | TOTOLINK CP900 cstecgi.cgi UploadCustomModule buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7463</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK CP900 6.3c.566. This vulnerability affects the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument File leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273556. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7462 | TOTOLINK N350RT cstecgi.cgi setWizardCfg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7462</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. This affects the function setWizardCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ssid leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273555. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:08:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7461 | ForIP Tecnologia Administração PABX monitcallcenter authMonitCallcenter sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7461</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ForIP Tecnologia Administração PABX 1.x. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /authMonitCallcenter of the component monitcallcenter. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273554 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7460 | OSWAPP Warehouse Inventory System change_password.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7460</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OSWAPP Warehouse Inventory System 1.0/2.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /change_password.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273553 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7459 | OSWAPP Warehouse Inventory System edit_account.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7459</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OSWAPP Warehouse Inventory System 1.0/2.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /edit_account.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273552.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7458 | elunez eladmin Database Management/Deployment Management upload path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7458</link><description>A vulnerability was found in elunez eladmin up to 2.7 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api/deploy/upload /api/database/upload of the component Database Management/Deployment Management. The manipulation of the argument file leads to path traversal: 'dir/../../filename'. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273551.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35143 | IBM Planning Analytics Local missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35143</link><description>IBM Planning Analytics Local 2.0 and 2.1 connects to a MongoDB server. MongoDB, a document-oriented database system, is listening on the remote port, and it is configured to allow connections without password authentication. A remote attacker can gain unauthorized access to the database.  IBM X-Force ID:  292420.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 13:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7455 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System partedit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7455</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file partedit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273549 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 11:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7454 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System patients.php patient_name sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7454</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function patient_name of the file patients.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273548.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 09:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7453 | FastAdmin Attachment Management Section 4 cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7453</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FastAdmin 1.5.0.20240328. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /[admins_url].php/general/attachment/edit/ids/4?dialog=1 of the component Attachment Management Section. The manipulation of the argument row[url]/row[imagewidth]/row[imageheight] leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273544.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 04:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7452 | itsourcecode Placement Management System view_company.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7452</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file view_company.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273543.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 04:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7451 | itsourcecode Placement Management System apply_now.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7451</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file apply_now.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273542 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 03:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7450 | itsourcecode Placement Management System Image resume_upload.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7450</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /resume_upload.php of the component Image Handler. The manipulation of the argument fileToUpload leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273541 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7449 | itsourcecode Placement Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7449</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273540.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 02:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6331 | Local File Read (LFI) by Prompt Injection in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6331</link><description>stitionai/devika main branch as of commit cdfb782b0e634b773b10963c8034dc9207ba1f9f is vulnerable to Local File Read (LFI) by Prompt Injection. The integration of Google Gimini 1.0 Pro with `HarmBlockThreshold.BLOCK_NONE` for `HarmCategory.HARM_CATEGORY_HATE_SPEECH` and `HarmCategory.HARM_CATEGORY_HARASSMENT` in `safety_settings` disables content protection. This allows malicious commands to be executed, such as reading sensitive file contents like `/etc/passwd`.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 00:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>