<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 18:34:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-2526 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System rooms.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2526</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/rooms.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256963. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 18:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2525 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System receipt.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2525</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/receipt.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256962 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 18:06:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2524 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System receipt.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2524</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/receipt.php. The manipulation of the argument room_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256961 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 17:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2523 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System booktime.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2523</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/booktime.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256960. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 17:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2522 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System booktime.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2522</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/booktime.php. The manipulation of the argument room_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256959. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 16:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2521 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System bookdate.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2521</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/bookdate.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256958 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 16:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2520 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System bookdate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2520</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/bookdate.php. The manipulation of the argument room_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256957 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 15:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2519 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System navbar.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2519</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file navbar.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256956. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 14:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2518 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System book_history.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2518</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file book_history.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256955. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 13:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2517 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System book_history.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2517</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file book_history.php. The manipulation of the argument del_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256954 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 12:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2516 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2516</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file home.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256953 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 11:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2515 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System home.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2515</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file home.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256952. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 09:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1857 | The Ultimate Gift Cards for WooCommerce – Create, Redeem &amp; Manage Digital Gift Certificates with Personalized Templates plugin for WordPress...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1857</link><description>The Ultimate Gift Cards for WooCommerce – Create, Redeem &amp; Manage Digital Gift Certificates with Personalized Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.6 via the wps_wgm_preview_email_template(). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read password protected and draft posts that may contain sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 08:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22513 | djangorestframework-simplejwt version 5.3.1 and before is vulnerable to information disclosure. A user can access web application resources ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22513</link><description>djangorestframework-simplejwt version 5.3.1 and before is vulnerable to information disclosure. A user can access web application resources even after their account has been disabled due to missing user validation checks via the for_user method.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 06:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28640 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in TOTOLink X5000R V9.1.0u.6118-B20201102 and A7000R V9.1.0u.6115-B20201022 allows a remote attacker to cause ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28640</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in TOTOLink X5000R V9.1.0u.6118-B20201102 and A7000R V9.1.0u.6115-B20201022 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service (D0S) via the command field.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 06:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28639 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in TOTOLink X5000R V9.1.0u.6118-B20201102 and A7000R V9.1.0u.6115-B20201022, allow remote attackers to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28639</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in TOTOLink X5000R V9.1.0u.6118-B20201102 and A7000R V9.1.0u.6115-B20201022, allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service (DoS) via the IP field.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 06:07:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24156 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Gnuboard g6 before Github commit 58c737a263ac0c523592fd87ff71b9e3c07d7cf5, allows remote attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24156</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Gnuboard g6 before Github commit 58c737a263ac0c523592fd87ff71b9e3c07d7cf5, allows remote attackers execute arbitrary code via the wr_content parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1685 | The Social Media Share Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.0 via de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1685</link><description>The Social Media Share Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.0 via deserialization of untrusted input through the attachmentUrl parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1733 | The Word Replacer Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the word_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1733</link><description>The Word Replacer Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the word_replacer_ultra() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary content on the affected WordPress site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28070 | A vulnerability in the legacy chat component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.0.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28070</link><description>A vulnerability in the legacy chat component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.0.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to conduct a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attack due to insufficient input validation. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to access sensitive information and gain unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28069 | A vulnerability in the legacy chat component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.0.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28069</link><description>A vulnerability in the legacy chat component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.0.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to conduct an information disclosure attack due to improper configuration. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to access sensitive information and potentially conduct unauthorized actions within the vulnerable component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36483 | An authorization bypass was discovered in the Carrier MASmobile Classic application through 1.16.18 for Android, MASmobile Classic app throu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36483</link><description>An authorization bypass was discovered in the Carrier MASmobile Classic application through 1.16.18 for Android, MASmobile Classic app through 1.7.24 for iOS, and MAS ASP.Net Services through 1.9. It can be achieved via session ID prediction, allowing remote attackers to retrieve sensitive data including customer data, security system status, and event history. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. The affected products cannot simply be updated; they must be removed, but can be replaced by other Carrier software as explained in the Carrier advisory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22259 | CVE-2024-22259: Spring Framework URL Parsing with Host Validation (2nd report)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22259</link><description>Applications that use UriComponentsBuilder in Spring Framework to parse an externally provided URL (e.g. through a query parameter) AND perform validation checks on the host of the parsed URL may be vulnerable to a  open redirect https://cwe.mitre.org/data/definitions/601.html  attack or to a SSRF attack if the URL is used after passing validation checks.

This is the same as  CVE-2024-22243 https://spring.io/security/cve-2024-22243 , but with different input.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 04:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23523 | WordPress Elementor Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 3.19.2 - Contributor+ Arbitrary User Meta Data Retrieval vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23523</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Elementor Pro.This issue affects Elementor Pro: from n/a through 3.19.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 04:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24845 | WordPress Post Thumbnail Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.8 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24845</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Sewpafly Post Thumbnail Editor.This issue affects Post Thumbnail Editor: from n/a through 2.4.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 04:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6525 | The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the progress bar element attributes i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6525</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the progress bar element attributes in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This primarily affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1239 | The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the blog post read more button in all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1239</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the blog post read more button in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2042 | The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Accordion widget in all ver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2042</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Accordion widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2294 | The Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and inclu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2294</link><description>The Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.7 via the backup_name parameter in the backuply_download_backup function. This makes it possible for attackers to have an account with only activate_plugins capability to access arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information. This only impacts sites hosted on Windows servers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:02:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2308 | The ElementInvader Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the button link in the EliSlid...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2308</link><description>The ElementInvader Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the button link in the EliSlider in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:02:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51474 | WordPress TerraClassifieds plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51474</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Pixelemu TerraClassifieds.This issue affects TerraClassifieds: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51486 | WordPress WooCommerce PDF Invoice Builder, Create invoices, packing slips and more plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.101 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51486</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in RedNao WooCommerce PDF Invoice Builder.This issue affects WooCommerce PDF Invoice Builder: from n/a through 1.2.101.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51487 | WordPress ARI Stream Quiz – WordPress Quizzes Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.32 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51487</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ARI Soft ARI Stream Quiz.This issue affects ARI Stream Quiz: from n/a through 1.2.32.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27194 | WordPress Fontific plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.6 - CSRF to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27194</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Andrei Ivasiuc Fontific | Google Fonts allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Fontific | Google Fonts: from n/a through 0.1.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27195 | WordPress Watermark RELOADED plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - CSRF to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27195</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sandi Verdev Watermark RELOADED allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Watermark RELOADED: from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27197 | WordPress BeePress plugin &amp;lt;= 6.9.8 - CSRF to Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27197</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Bee BeePress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects BeePress: from n/a through 6.9.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51407 | WordPress Split Test For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51407</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rocket Elements Split Test For Elementor.This issue affects Split Test For Elementor: from n/a through 1.6.9.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51489 | WordPress Crowdsignal Polls &amp;amp; Ratings plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.11 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51489</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Automattic, Inc. Crowdsignal Dashboard – Polls, Surveys &amp; more.This issue affects Crowdsignal Dashboard – Polls, Surveys &amp; more: from n/a through 3.0.11.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51491 | WordPress Depicter Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51491</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Averta Depicter Slider.This issue affects Depicter Slider: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51510 | WordPress Export Media URLs plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51510</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Atlas Gondal Export Media URLs.This issue affects Export Media URLs: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51512 | WordPress Product Table by WBW plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51512</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WBW Product Table by WBW.This issue affects Product Table by WBW: from n/a through 1.8.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51521 | WordPress Quiz And Survey Master plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.18 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51521</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ExpressTech Quiz And Survey Master.This issue affects Quiz And Survey Master: from n/a through 8.1.18.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28862 | ROTP 6.2.2 and 6.2.1 has 0666 permissions for the .rb files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28862</link><description>The Ruby One Time Password library (ROTP) is an open source library for generating and validating one time passwords. Affected versions had overly permissive default permissions. Users should patch to version 6.3.0. Users unable to patch may correct file permissions after installation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 23:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23298 | A logic issue was addressed with improved state management.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23298</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 22:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28859 | Gadget chain in Symfony 1 due to vulnerable Swift Mailer dependency</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28859</link><description>Symfony1 is a community fork of symfony 1.4 with DIC, form enhancements, latest Swiftmailer, better performance, composer compatible and PHP 8 support. Symfony 1 has a gadget chain due to vulnerable Swift Mailer dependency that would enable an attacker to get remote code execution if a developer unserialize user input in his project. This vulnerability present no direct threat but is a vector that will enable remote code execution if a developper deserialize user untrusted data. Symfony 1 depends on Swift Mailer which is bundled by default in vendor directory in the default installation since 1.3.0. Swift Mailer classes implement some `__destruct()` methods. These methods are called when php destroys the object in memory. However, it is possible to include any object type in `$this-&gt;_keys` to make PHP access to another array/object properties than intended by the developer. In particular, it is possible to abuse the array access which is triggered on foreach($this-&gt;_keys ...) for any class implementing ArrayAccess interface. This may allow an attacker to execute any PHP command which leads to remote code execution. This issue has been addressed in version 1.5.18. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 22:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2514 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2514</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256951. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 22:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47109 | neighbour: allow NUD_NOARP entries to be forced GCed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47109</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

neighbour: allow NUD_NOARP entries to be forced GCed

IFF_POINTOPOINT interfaces use NUD_NOARP entries for IPv6. It's possible to
fill up the neighbour table with enough entries that it will overflow for
valid connections after that.

This behaviour is more prevalent after commit 58956317c8de ("neighbor:
Improve garbage collection") is applied, as it prevents removal from
entries that are not NUD_FAILED, unless they are more than 5s old.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47110 | x86/kvm: Disable kvmclock on all CPUs on shutdown</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47110</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/kvm: Disable kvmclock on all CPUs on shutdown

Currenly, we disable kvmclock from machine_shutdown() hook and this
only happens for boot CPU. We need to disable it for all CPUs to
guard against memory corruption e.g. on restore from hibernate.

Note, writing '0' to kvmclock MSR doesn't clear memory location, it
just prevents hypervisor from updating the location so for the short
while after write and while CPU is still alive, the clock remains usable
and correct so we don't need to switch to some other clocksource.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47111 | xen-netback: take a reference to the RX task thread</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47111</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

xen-netback: take a reference to the RX task thread

Do this in order to prevent the task from being freed if the thread
returns (which can be triggered by the frontend) before the call to
kthread_stop done as part of the backend tear down. Not taking the
reference will lead to a use-after-free in that scenario. Such
reference was taken before but dropped as part of the rework done in
2ac061ce97f4.

Reintroduce the reference taking and add a comment this time
explaining why it's needed.

This is XSA-374 / CVE-2021-28691.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47112 | x86/kvm: Teardown PV features on boot CPU as well</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47112</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/kvm: Teardown PV features on boot CPU as well

Various PV features (Async PF, PV EOI, steal time) work through memory
shared with hypervisor and when we restore from hibernation we must
properly teardown all these features to make sure hypervisor doesn't
write to stale locations after we jump to the previously hibernated kernel
(which can try to place anything there). For secondary CPUs the job is
already done by kvm_cpu_down_prepare(), register syscore ops to do
the same for boot CPU.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47113 | btrfs: abort in rename_exchange if we fail to insert the second ref</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47113</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: abort in rename_exchange if we fail to insert the second ref

Error injection stress uncovered a problem where we'd leave a dangling
inode ref if we failed during a rename_exchange.  This happens because
we insert the inode ref for one side of the rename, and then for the
other side.  If this second inode ref insert fails we'll leave the first
one dangling and leave a corrupt file system behind.  Fix this by
aborting if we did the insert for the first inode ref.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47114 | ocfs2: fix data corruption by fallocate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47114</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ocfs2: fix data corruption by fallocate

When fallocate punches holes out of inode size, if original isize is in
the middle of last cluster, then the part from isize to the end of the
cluster will be zeroed with buffer write, at that time isize is not yet
updated to match the new size, if writeback is kicked in, it will invoke
ocfs2_writepage()-&gt;block_write_full_page() where the pages out of inode
size will be dropped.  That will cause file corruption.  Fix this by
zero out eof blocks when extending the inode size.

Running the following command with qemu-image 4.2.1 can get a corrupted
coverted image file easily.

    qemu-img convert -p -t none -T none -f qcow2 $qcow_image \
             -O qcow2 -o compat=1.1 $qcow_image.conv

The usage of fallocate in qemu is like this, it first punches holes out
of inode size, then extend the inode size.

    fallocate(11, FALLOC_FL_KEEP_SIZE|FALLOC_FL_PUNCH_HOLE, 2276196352, 65536) = 0
    fallocate(11, 0, 2276196352, 65536) = 0

v1: https://www.spinics.net/lists/linux-fsdevel/msg193999.html
v2: https://lore.kernel.org/linux-fsdevel/20210525093034.GB4112@quack2.suse.cz/T/</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47115 | nfc: fix NULL ptr dereference in llcp_sock_getname() after failed connect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47115</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nfc: fix NULL ptr dereference in llcp_sock_getname() after failed connect

It's possible to trigger NULL pointer dereference by local unprivileged
user, when calling getsockname() after failed bind() (e.g. the bind
fails because LLCP_SAP_MAX used as SAP):

  BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000000
  CPU: 1 PID: 426 Comm: llcp_sock_getna Not tainted 5.13.0-rc2-next-20210521+ #9
  Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.14.0-1 04/01/2014
  Call Trace:
   llcp_sock_getname+0xb1/0xe0
   __sys_getpeername+0x95/0xc0
   ? lockdep_hardirqs_on_prepare+0xd5/0x180
   ? syscall_enter_from_user_mode+0x1c/0x40
   __x64_sys_getpeername+0x11/0x20
   do_syscall_64+0x36/0x70
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x44/0xae

This can be reproduced with Syzkaller C repro (bind followed by
getpeername):
https://syzkaller.appspot.com/x/repro.c?x=14def446e00000</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47116 | ext4: fix memory leak in ext4_mb_init_backend on error path.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47116</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ext4: fix memory leak in ext4_mb_init_backend on error path.

Fix a memory leak discovered by syzbot when a file system is corrupted
with an illegally large s_log_groups_per_flex.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47117 | ext4: fix bug on in ext4_es_cache_extent as ext4_split_extent_at failed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47117</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ext4: fix bug on in ext4_es_cache_extent as ext4_split_extent_at failed

We got follow bug_on when run fsstress with injecting IO fault:
[130747.323114] kernel BUG at fs/ext4/extents_status.c:762!
[130747.323117] Internal error: Oops - BUG: 0 [#1] SMP
......
[130747.334329] Call trace:
[130747.334553]  ext4_es_cache_extent+0x150/0x168 [ext4]
[130747.334975]  ext4_cache_extents+0x64/0xe8 [ext4]
[130747.335368]  ext4_find_extent+0x300/0x330 [ext4]
[130747.335759]  ext4_ext_map_blocks+0x74/0x1178 [ext4]
[130747.336179]  ext4_map_blocks+0x2f4/0x5f0 [ext4]
[130747.336567]  ext4_mpage_readpages+0x4a8/0x7a8 [ext4]
[130747.336995]  ext4_readpage+0x54/0x100 [ext4]
[130747.337359]  generic_file_buffered_read+0x410/0xae8
[130747.337767]  generic_file_read_iter+0x114/0x190
[130747.338152]  ext4_file_read_iter+0x5c/0x140 [ext4]
[130747.338556]  __vfs_read+0x11c/0x188
[130747.338851]  vfs_read+0x94/0x150
[130747.339110]  ksys_read+0x74/0xf0

This patch's modification is according to Jan Kara's suggestion in:
https://patchwork.ozlabs.org/project/linux-ext4/patch/20210428085158.3728201-1-yebin10@huawei.com/
"I see. Now I understand your patch. Honestly, seeing how fragile is trying
to fix extent tree after split has failed in the middle, I would probably
go even further and make sure we fix the tree properly in case of ENOSPC
and EDQUOT (those are easily user triggerable).  Anything else indicates a
HW problem or fs corruption so I'd rather leave the extent tree as is and
don't try to fix it (which also means we will not create overlapping
extents)."</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47118 | pid: take a reference when initializing `cad_pid`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47118</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

pid: take a reference when initializing `cad_pid`

During boot, kernel_init_freeable() initializes `cad_pid` to the init
task's struct pid.  Later on, we may change `cad_pid` via a sysctl, and
when this happens proc_do_cad_pid() will increment the refcount on the
new pid via get_pid(), and will decrement the refcount on the old pid
via put_pid().  As we never called get_pid() when we initialized
`cad_pid`, we decrement a reference we never incremented, can therefore
free the init task's struct pid early.  As there can be dangling
references to the struct pid, we can later encounter a use-after-free
(e.g.  when delivering signals).

This was spotted when fuzzing v5.13-rc3 with Syzkaller, but seems to
have been around since the conversion of `cad_pid` to struct pid in
commit 9ec52099e4b8 ("[PATCH] replace cad_pid by a struct pid") from the
pre-KASAN stone age of v2.6.19.

Fix this by getting a reference to the init task's struct pid when we
assign it to `cad_pid`.

Full KASAN splat below.

   ==================================================================
   BUG: KASAN: use-after-free in ns_of_pid include/linux/pid.h:153 [inline]
   BUG: KASAN: use-after-free in task_active_pid_ns+0xc0/0xc8 kernel/pid.c:509
   Read of size 4 at addr ffff23794dda0004 by task syz-executor.0/273

   CPU: 1 PID: 273 Comm: syz-executor.0 Not tainted 5.12.0-00001-g9aef892b2d15 #1
   Hardware name: linux,dummy-virt (DT)
   Call trace:
    ns_of_pid include/linux/pid.h:153 [inline]
    task_active_pid_ns+0xc0/0xc8 kernel/pid.c:509
    do_notify_parent+0x308/0xe60 kernel/signal.c:1950
    exit_notify kernel/exit.c:682 [inline]
    do_exit+0x2334/0x2bd0 kernel/exit.c:845
    do_group_exit+0x108/0x2c8 kernel/exit.c:922
    get_signal+0x4e4/0x2a88 kernel/signal.c:2781
    do_signal arch/arm64/kernel/signal.c:882 [inline]
    do_notify_resume+0x300/0x970 arch/arm64/kernel/signal.c:936
    work_pending+0xc/0x2dc

   Allocated by task 0:
    slab_post_alloc_hook+0x50/0x5c0 mm/slab.h:516
    slab_alloc_node mm/slub.c:2907 [inline]
    slab_alloc mm/slub.c:2915 [inline]
    kmem_cache_alloc+0x1f4/0x4c0 mm/slub.c:2920
    alloc_pid+0xdc/0xc00 kernel/pid.c:180
    copy_process+0x2794/0x5e18 kernel/fork.c:2129
    kernel_clone+0x194/0x13c8 kernel/fork.c:2500
    kernel_thread+0xd4/0x110 kernel/fork.c:2552
    rest_init+0x44/0x4a0 init/main.c:687
    arch_call_rest_init+0x1c/0x28
    start_kernel+0x520/0x554 init/main.c:1064
    0x0

   Freed by task 270:
    slab_free_hook mm/slub.c:1562 [inline]
    slab_free_freelist_hook+0x98/0x260 mm/slub.c:1600
    slab_free mm/slub.c:3161 [inline]
    kmem_cache_free+0x224/0x8e0 mm/slub.c:3177
    put_pid.part.4+0xe0/0x1a8 kernel/pid.c:114
    put_pid+0x30/0x48 kernel/pid.c:109
    proc_do_cad_pid+0x190/0x1b0 kernel/sysctl.c:1401
    proc_sys_call_handler+0x338/0x4b0 fs/proc/proc_sysctl.c:591
    proc_sys_write+0x34/0x48 fs/proc/proc_sysctl.c:617
    call_write_iter include/linux/fs.h:1977 [inline]
    new_sync_write+0x3ac/0x510 fs/read_write.c:518
    vfs_write fs/read_write.c:605 [inline]
    vfs_write+0x9c4/0x1018 fs/read_write.c:585
    ksys_write+0x124/0x240 fs/read_write.c:658
    __do_sys_write fs/read_write.c:670 [inline]
    __se_sys_write fs/read_write.c:667 [inline]
    __arm64_sys_write+0x78/0xb0 fs/read_write.c:667
    __invoke_syscall arch/arm64/kernel/syscall.c:37 [inline]
    invoke_syscall arch/arm64/kernel/syscall.c:49 [inline]
    el0_svc_common.constprop.1+0x16c/0x388 arch/arm64/kernel/syscall.c:129
    do_el0_svc+0xf8/0x150 arch/arm64/kernel/syscall.c:168
    el0_svc+0x28/0x38 arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:416
    el0_sync_handler+0x134/0x180 arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:432
    el0_sync+0x154/0x180 arch/arm64/kernel/entry.S:701

   The buggy address belongs to the object at ffff23794dda0000
    which belongs to the cache pid of size 224
   The buggy address is located 4 bytes inside of
    224-byte region [ff
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47119 | ext4: fix memory leak in ext4_fill_super</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47119</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ext4: fix memory leak in ext4_fill_super

Buffer head references must be released before calling kill_bdev();
otherwise the buffer head (and its page referenced by b_data) will not
be freed by kill_bdev, and subsequently that bh will be leaked.

If blocksizes differ, sb_set_blocksize() will kill current buffers and
page cache by using kill_bdev(). And then super block will be reread
again but using correct blocksize this time. sb_set_blocksize() didn't
fully free superblock page and buffer head, and being busy, they were
not freed and instead leaked.

This can easily be reproduced by calling an infinite loop of:

  systemctl start &lt;ext4_on_lvm&gt;.mount, and
  systemctl stop &lt;ext4_on_lvm&gt;.mount

... since systemd creates a cgroup for each slice which it mounts, and
the bh leak get amplified by a dying memory cgroup that also never
gets freed, and memory consumption is much more easily noticed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47120 | HID: magicmouse: fix NULL-deref on disconnect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47120</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

HID: magicmouse: fix NULL-deref on disconnect

Commit 9d7b18668956 ("HID: magicmouse: add support for Apple Magic
Trackpad 2") added a sanity check for an Apple trackpad but returned
success instead of -ENODEV when the check failed. This means that the
remove callback will dereference the never-initialised driver data
pointer when the driver is later unbound (e.g. on USB disconnect).</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47121 | net: caif: fix memory leak in cfusbl_device_notify</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47121</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: caif: fix memory leak in cfusbl_device_notify

In case of caif_enroll_dev() fail, allocated
link_support won't be assigned to the corresponding
structure. So simply free allocated pointer in case
of error.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47122 | net: caif: fix memory leak in caif_device_notify</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47122</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: caif: fix memory leak in caif_device_notify

In case of caif_enroll_dev() fail, allocated
link_support won't be assigned to the corresponding
structure. So simply free allocated pointer in case
of error</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47123 | io_uring: fix ltout double free on completion race</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47123</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

io_uring: fix ltout double free on completion race

Always remove linked timeout on io_link_timeout_fn() from the master
request link list, otherwise we may get use-after-free when first
io_link_timeout_fn() puts linked timeout in the fail path, and then
will be found and put on master's free.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47124 | io_uring: fix link timeout refs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47124</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

io_uring: fix link timeout refs

WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 10242 at lib/refcount.c:28 refcount_warn_saturate+0x15b/0x1a0 lib/refcount.c:28
RIP: 0010:refcount_warn_saturate+0x15b/0x1a0 lib/refcount.c:28
Call Trace:
 __refcount_sub_and_test include/linux/refcount.h:283 [inline]
 __refcount_dec_and_test include/linux/refcount.h:315 [inline]
 refcount_dec_and_test include/linux/refcount.h:333 [inline]
 io_put_req fs/io_uring.c:2140 [inline]
 io_queue_linked_timeout fs/io_uring.c:6300 [inline]
 __io_queue_sqe+0xbef/0xec0 fs/io_uring.c:6354
 io_submit_sqe fs/io_uring.c:6534 [inline]
 io_submit_sqes+0x2bbd/0x7c50 fs/io_uring.c:6660
 __do_sys_io_uring_enter fs/io_uring.c:9240 [inline]
 __se_sys_io_uring_enter+0x256/0x1d60 fs/io_uring.c:9182

io_link_timeout_fn() should put only one reference of the linked timeout
request, however in case of racing with the master request's completion
first io_req_complete() puts one and then io_put_req_deferred() is
called.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47125 | sch_htb: fix refcount leak in htb_parent_to_leaf_offload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47125</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

sch_htb: fix refcount leak in htb_parent_to_leaf_offload

The commit ae81feb7338c ("sch_htb: fix null pointer dereference
on a null new_q") fixes a NULL pointer dereference bug, but it
is not correct.

Because htb_graft_helper properly handles the case when new_q
is NULL, and after the previous patch by skipping this call
which creates an inconsistency : dev_queue-&gt;qdisc will still
point to the old qdisc, but cl-&gt;parent-&gt;leaf.q will point to
the new one (which will be noop_qdisc, because new_q was NULL).
The code is based on an assumption that these two pointers are
the same, so it can lead to refcount leaks.

The correct fix is to add a NULL pointer check to protect
qdisc_refcount_inc inside htb_parent_to_leaf_offload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47126 | ipv6: Fix KASAN: slab-out-of-bounds Read in fib6_nh_flush_exceptions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47126</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ipv6: Fix KASAN: slab-out-of-bounds Read in fib6_nh_flush_exceptions

Reported by syzbot:
HEAD commit:    90c911ad Merge tag 'fixes' of git://git.kernel.org/pub/scm..
git tree:       git://git.kernel.org/pub/scm/linux/kernel/git/torvalds/linux.git master
dashboard link: https://syzkaller.appspot.com/bug?extid=123aa35098fd3c000eb7
compiler:       Debian clang version 11.0.1-2

==================================================================
BUG: KASAN: slab-out-of-bounds in fib6_nh_get_excptn_bucket net/ipv6/route.c:1604 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: slab-out-of-bounds in fib6_nh_flush_exceptions+0xbd/0x360 net/ipv6/route.c:1732
Read of size 8 at addr ffff8880145c78f8 by task syz-executor.4/17760

CPU: 0 PID: 17760 Comm: syz-executor.4 Not tainted 5.12.0-rc8-syzkaller #0
Call Trace:
 &lt;IRQ&gt;
 __dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:79 [inline]
 dump_stack+0x202/0x31e lib/dump_stack.c:120
 print_address_description+0x5f/0x3b0 mm/kasan/report.c:232
 __kasan_report mm/kasan/report.c:399 [inline]
 kasan_report+0x15c/0x200 mm/kasan/report.c:416
 fib6_nh_get_excptn_bucket net/ipv6/route.c:1604 [inline]
 fib6_nh_flush_exceptions+0xbd/0x360 net/ipv6/route.c:1732
 fib6_nh_release+0x9a/0x430 net/ipv6/route.c:3536
 fib6_info_destroy_rcu+0xcb/0x1c0 net/ipv6/ip6_fib.c:174
 rcu_do_batch kernel/rcu/tree.c:2559 [inline]
 rcu_core+0x8f6/0x1450 kernel/rcu/tree.c:2794
 __do_softirq+0x372/0x7a6 kernel/softirq.c:345
 invoke_softirq kernel/softirq.c:221 [inline]
 __irq_exit_rcu+0x22c/0x260 kernel/softirq.c:422
 irq_exit_rcu+0x5/0x20 kernel/softirq.c:434
 sysvec_apic_timer_interrupt+0x91/0xb0 arch/x86/kernel/apic/apic.c:1100
 &lt;/IRQ&gt;
 asm_sysvec_apic_timer_interrupt+0x12/0x20 arch/x86/include/asm/idtentry.h:632
RIP: 0010:lock_acquire+0x1f6/0x720 kernel/locking/lockdep.c:5515
Code: f6 84 24 a1 00 00 00 02 0f 85 8d 02 00 00 f7 c3 00 02 00 00 49 bd 00 00 00 00 00 fc ff df 74 01 fb 48 c7 44 24 40 0e 36 e0 45 &lt;4b&gt; c7 44 3d 00 00 00 00 00 4b c7 44 3d 09 00 00 00 00 43 c7 44 3d
RSP: 0018:ffffc90009e06560 EFLAGS: 00000206
RAX: 1ffff920013c0cc0 RBX: 0000000000000246 RCX: dffffc0000000000
RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: 0000000000000000 RDI: 0000000000000000
RBP: ffffc90009e066e0 R08: dffffc0000000000 R09: fffffbfff1f992b1
R10: fffffbfff1f992b1 R11: 0000000000000000 R12: 0000000000000000
R13: dffffc0000000000 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: 1ffff920013c0cb4
 rcu_lock_acquire+0x2a/0x30 include/linux/rcupdate.h:267
 rcu_read_lock include/linux/rcupdate.h:656 [inline]
 ext4_get_group_info+0xea/0x340 fs/ext4/ext4.h:3231
 ext4_mb_prefetch+0x123/0x5d0 fs/ext4/mballoc.c:2212
 ext4_mb_regular_allocator+0x8a5/0x28f0 fs/ext4/mballoc.c:2379
 ext4_mb_new_blocks+0xc6e/0x24f0 fs/ext4/mballoc.c:4982
 ext4_ext_map_blocks+0x2be3/0x7210 fs/ext4/extents.c:4238
 ext4_map_blocks+0xab3/0x1cb0 fs/ext4/inode.c:638
 ext4_getblk+0x187/0x6c0 fs/ext4/inode.c:848
 ext4_bread+0x2a/0x1c0 fs/ext4/inode.c:900
 ext4_append+0x1a4/0x360 fs/ext4/namei.c:67
 ext4_init_new_dir+0x337/0xa10 fs/ext4/namei.c:2768
 ext4_mkdir+0x4b8/0xc00 fs/ext4/namei.c:2814
 vfs_mkdir+0x45b/0x640 fs/namei.c:3819
 ovl_do_mkdir fs/overlayfs/overlayfs.h:161 [inline]
 ovl_mkdir_real+0x53/0x1a0 fs/overlayfs/dir.c:146
 ovl_create_real+0x280/0x490 fs/overlayfs/dir.c:193
 ovl_workdir_create+0x425/0x600 fs/overlayfs/super.c:788
 ovl_make_workdir+0xed/0x1140 fs/overlayfs/super.c:1355
 ovl_get_workdir fs/overlayfs/super.c:1492 [inline]
 ovl_fill_super+0x39ee/0x5370 fs/overlayfs/super.c:2035
 mount_nodev+0x52/0xe0 fs/super.c:1413
 legacy_get_tree+0xea/0x180 fs/fs_context.c:592
 vfs_get_tree+0x86/0x270 fs/super.c:1497
 do_new_mount fs/namespace.c:2903 [inline]
 path_mount+0x196f/0x2be0 fs/namespace.c:3233
 do_mount fs/namespace.c:3246 [inline]
 __do_sys_mount fs/namespace.c:3454 [inline]
 __se_sys_mount+0x2f9/0x3b0 fs/namespace.c:3431
 do_syscall_64+0x2d/0x70 arch/x86/entry/common.c:46
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x44/0xae
RIP: 0033:0x4665f9
Code: ff ff c3 66 2e 0f 1f 84 
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47127 | ice: track AF_XDP ZC enabled queues in bitmap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47127</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ice: track AF_XDP ZC enabled queues in bitmap

Commit c7a219048e45 ("ice: Remove xsk_buff_pool from VSI structure")
silently introduced a regression and broke the Tx side of AF_XDP in copy
mode. xsk_pool on ice_ring is set only based on the existence of the XDP
prog on the VSI which in turn picks ice_clean_tx_irq_zc to be executed.
That is not something that should happen for copy mode as it should use
the regular data path ice_clean_tx_irq.

This results in a following splat when xdpsock is run in txonly or l2fwd
scenarios in copy mode:

&lt;snip&gt;
[  106.050195] BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000030
[  106.057269] #PF: supervisor read access in kernel mode
[  106.062493] #PF: error_code(0x0000) - not-present page
[  106.067709] PGD 0 P4D 0
[  106.070293] Oops: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP NOPTI
[  106.074721] CPU: 61 PID: 0 Comm: swapper/61 Not tainted 5.12.0-rc2+ #45
[  106.081436] Hardware name: Intel Corporation S2600WFT/S2600WFT, BIOS SE5C620.86B.02.01.0008.031920191559 03/19/2019
[  106.092027] RIP: 0010:xp_raw_get_dma+0x36/0x50
[  106.096551] Code: 74 14 48 b8 ff ff ff ff ff ff 00 00 48 21 f0 48 c1 ee 30 48 01 c6 48 8b 87 90 00 00 00 48 89 f2 81 e6 ff 0f 00 00 48 c1 ea 0c &lt;48&gt; 8b 04 d0 48 83 e0 fe 48 01 f0 c3 66 66 2e 0f 1f 84 00 00 00 00
[  106.115588] RSP: 0018:ffffc9000d694e50 EFLAGS: 00010206
[  106.120893] RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffff88984b8c8a00 RCX: ffff889852581800
[  106.128137] RDX: 0000000000000006 RSI: 0000000000000000 RDI: ffff88984cd8b800
[  106.135383] RBP: ffff888123b50001 R08: ffff889896800000 R09: 0000000000000800
[  106.142628] R10: 0000000000000000 R11: ffffffff826060c0 R12: 00000000000000ff
[  106.149872] R13: 0000000000000000 R14: 0000000000000040 R15: ffff888123b50018
[  106.157117] FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffff8897e0f40000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
[  106.165332] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
[  106.171163] CR2: 0000000000000030 CR3: 000000000560a004 CR4: 00000000007706e0
[  106.178408] DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
[  106.185653] DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
[  106.192898] PKRU: 55555554
[  106.195653] Call Trace:
[  106.198143]  &lt;IRQ&gt;
[  106.200196]  ice_clean_tx_irq_zc+0x183/0x2a0 [ice]
[  106.205087]  ice_napi_poll+0x3e/0x590 [ice]
[  106.209356]  __napi_poll+0x2a/0x160
[  106.212911]  net_rx_action+0xd6/0x200
[  106.216634]  __do_softirq+0xbf/0x29b
[  106.220274]  irq_exit_rcu+0x88/0xc0
[  106.223819]  common_interrupt+0x7b/0xa0
[  106.227719]  &lt;/IRQ&gt;
[  106.229857]  asm_common_interrupt+0x1e/0x40
&lt;/snip&gt;

Fix this by introducing the bitmap of queues that are zero-copy enabled,
where each bit, corresponding to a queue id that xsk pool is being
configured on, will be set/cleared within ice_xsk_pool_{en,dis}able and
checked within ice_xsk_pool(). The latter is a function used for
deciding which napi poll routine is executed.
Idea is being taken from our other drivers such as i40e and ixgbe.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47128 | bpf, lockdown, audit: Fix buggy SELinux lockdown permission checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47128</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf, lockdown, audit: Fix buggy SELinux lockdown permission checks

Commit 59438b46471a ("security,lockdown,selinux: implement SELinux lockdown")
added an implementation of the locked_down LSM hook to SELinux, with the aim
to restrict which domains are allowed to perform operations that would breach
lockdown. This is indirectly also getting audit subsystem involved to report
events. The latter is problematic, as reported by Ondrej and Serhei, since it
can bring down the whole system via audit:

  1) The audit events that are triggered due to calls to security_locked_down()
     can OOM kill a machine, see below details [0].

  2) It also seems to be causing a deadlock via avc_has_perm()/slow_avc_audit()
     when trying to wake up kauditd, for example, when using trace_sched_switch()
     tracepoint, see details in [1]. Triggering this was not via some hypothetical
     corner case, but with existing tools like runqlat &amp; runqslower from bcc, for
     example, which make use of this tracepoint. Rough call sequence goes like:

     rq_lock(rq) -&gt; -------------------------+
       trace_sched_switch() -&gt;               |
         bpf_prog_xyz() -&gt;                   +-&gt; deadlock
           selinux_lockdown() -&gt;             |
             audit_log_end() -&gt;              |
               wake_up_interruptible() -&gt;    |
                 try_to_wake_up() -&gt;         |
                   rq_lock(rq) --------------+

What's worse is that the intention of 59438b46471a to further restrict lockdown
settings for specific applications in respect to the global lockdown policy is
completely broken for BPF. The SELinux policy rule for the current lockdown check
looks something like this:

  allow &lt;who&gt; &lt;who&gt; : lockdown { &lt;reason&gt; };

However, this doesn't match with the 'current' task where the security_locked_down()
is executed, example: httpd does a syscall. There is a tracing program attached
to the syscall which triggers a BPF program to run, which ends up doing a
bpf_probe_read_kernel{,_str}() helper call. The selinux_lockdown() hook does
the permission check against 'current', that is, httpd in this example. httpd
has literally zero relation to this tracing program, and it would be nonsensical
having to write an SELinux policy rule against httpd to let the tracing helper
pass. The policy in this case needs to be against the entity that is installing
the BPF program. For example, if bpftrace would generate a histogram of syscall
counts by user space application:

  bpftrace -e 'tracepoint:raw_syscalls:sys_enter { @[comm] = count(); }'

bpftrace would then go and generate a BPF program from this internally. One way
of doing it [for the sake of the example] could be to call bpf_get_current_task()
helper and then access current-&gt;comm via one of bpf_probe_read_kernel{,_str}()
helpers. So the program itself has nothing to do with httpd or any other random
app doing a syscall here. The BPF program _explicitly initiated_ the lockdown
check. The allow/deny policy belongs in the context of bpftrace: meaning, you
want to grant bpftrace access to use these helpers, but other tracers on the
system like my_random_tracer _not_.

Therefore fix all three issues at the same time by taking a completely different
approach for the security_locked_down() hook, that is, move the check into the
program verification phase where we actually retrieve the BPF func proto. This
also reliably gets the task (current) that is trying to install the BPF tracing
program, e.g. bpftrace/bcc/perf/systemtap/etc, and it also fixes the OOM since
we're moving this out of the BPF helper's fast-path which can be called several
millions of times per second.

The check is then also in line with other security_locked_down() hooks in the
system where the enforcement is performed at open/load time, for example,
open_kcore() for /proc/kcore access or module_sig_check() for module signatures
just to pick f
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47129 | netfilter: nft_ct: skip expectations for confirmed conntrack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47129</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nft_ct: skip expectations for confirmed conntrack

nft_ct_expect_obj_eval() calls nf_ct_ext_add() for a confirmed
conntrack entry. However, nf_ct_ext_add() can only be called for
!nf_ct_is_confirmed().

[ 1825.349056] WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 1279 at net/netfilter/nf_conntrack_extend.c:48 nf_ct_xt_add+0x18e/0x1a0 [nf_conntrack]
[ 1825.351391] RIP: 0010:nf_ct_ext_add+0x18e/0x1a0 [nf_conntrack]
[ 1825.351493] Code: 41 5c 41 5d 41 5e 41 5f c3 41 bc 0a 00 00 00 e9 15 ff ff ff ba 09 00 00 00 31 f6 4c 89 ff e8 69 6c 3d e9 eb 96 45 31 ed eb cd &lt;0f&gt; 0b e9 b1 fe ff ff e8 86 79 14 e9 eb bf 0f 1f 40 00 0f 1f 44 00
[ 1825.351721] RSP: 0018:ffffc90002e1f1e8 EFLAGS: 00010202
[ 1825.351790] RAX: 000000000000000e RBX: ffff88814f5783c0 RCX: ffffffffc0e4f887
[ 1825.351881] RDX: dffffc0000000000 RSI: 0000000000000008 RDI: ffff88814f578440
[ 1825.351971] RBP: 0000000000000000 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: ffff88814f578447
[ 1825.352060] R10: ffffed1029eaf088 R11: 0000000000000001 R12: ffff88814f578440
[ 1825.352150] R13: ffff8882053f3a00 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: 0000000000000a20
[ 1825.352240] FS:  00007f992261c900(0000) GS:ffff889faec00000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
[ 1825.352343] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
[ 1825.352417] CR2: 000056070a4d1158 CR3: 000000015efe0000 CR4: 0000000000350ee0
[ 1825.352508] Call Trace:
[ 1825.352544]  nf_ct_helper_ext_add+0x10/0x60 [nf_conntrack]
[ 1825.352641]  nft_ct_expect_obj_eval+0x1b8/0x1e0 [nft_ct]
[ 1825.352716]  nft_do_chain+0x232/0x850 [nf_tables]

Add the ct helper extension only for unconfirmed conntrack. Skip rule
evaluation if the ct helper extension does not exist. Thus, you can
only create expectations from the first packet.

It should be possible to remove this limitation by adding a new action
to attach a generic ct helper to the first packet. Then, use this ct
helper extension from follow up packets to create the ct expectation.

While at it, add a missing check to skip the template conntrack too
and remove check for IPCT_UNTRACK which is implicit to !ct.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47130 | nvmet: fix freeing unallocated p2pmem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47130</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nvmet: fix freeing unallocated p2pmem

In case p2p device was found but the p2p pool is empty, the nvme target
is still trying to free the sgl from the p2p pool instead of the
regular sgl pool and causing a crash (BUG() is called). Instead, assign
the p2p_dev for the request only if it was allocated from p2p pool.

This is the crash that was caused:

[Sun May 30 19:13:53 2021] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[Sun May 30 19:13:53 2021] kernel BUG at lib/genalloc.c:518!
[Sun May 30 19:13:53 2021] invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] SMP PTI
...
[Sun May 30 19:13:53 2021] kernel BUG at lib/genalloc.c:518!
...
[Sun May 30 19:13:53 2021] RIP: 0010:gen_pool_free_owner+0xa8/0xb0
...
[Sun May 30 19:13:53 2021] Call Trace:
[Sun May 30 19:13:53 2021] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[Sun May 30 19:13:53 2021]  pci_free_p2pmem+0x2b/0x70
[Sun May 30 19:13:53 2021]  pci_p2pmem_free_sgl+0x4f/0x80
[Sun May 30 19:13:53 2021]  nvmet_req_free_sgls+0x1e/0x80 [nvmet]
[Sun May 30 19:13:53 2021] kernel BUG at lib/genalloc.c:518!
[Sun May 30 19:13:53 2021]  nvmet_rdma_release_rsp+0x4e/0x1f0 [nvmet_rdma]
[Sun May 30 19:13:53 2021]  nvmet_rdma_send_done+0x1c/0x60 [nvmet_rdma]</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47131 | net/tls: Fix use-after-free after the TLS device goes down and up</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47131</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/tls: Fix use-after-free after the TLS device goes down and up

When a netdev with active TLS offload goes down, tls_device_down is
called to stop the offload and tear down the TLS context. However, the
socket stays alive, and it still points to the TLS context, which is now
deallocated. If a netdev goes up, while the connection is still active,
and the data flow resumes after a number of TCP retransmissions, it will
lead to a use-after-free of the TLS context.

This commit addresses this bug by keeping the context alive until its
normal destruction, and implements the necessary fallbacks, so that the
connection can resume in software (non-offloaded) kTLS mode.

On the TX side tls_sw_fallback is used to encrypt all packets. The RX
side already has all the necessary fallbacks, because receiving
non-decrypted packets is supported. The thing needed on the RX side is
to block resync requests, which are normally produced after receiving
non-decrypted packets.

The necessary synchronization is implemented for a graceful teardown:
first the fallbacks are deployed, then the driver resources are released
(it used to be possible to have a tls_dev_resync after tls_dev_del).

A new flag called TLS_RX_DEV_DEGRADED is added to indicate the fallback
mode. It's used to skip the RX resync logic completely, as it becomes
useless, and some objects may be released (for example, resync_async,
which is allocated and freed by the driver).</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47132 | mptcp: fix sk_forward_memory corruption on retransmission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47132</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mptcp: fix sk_forward_memory corruption on retransmission

MPTCP sk_forward_memory handling is a bit special, as such field
is protected by the msk socket spin_lock, instead of the plain
socket lock.

Currently we have a code path updating such field without handling
the relevant lock:

__mptcp_retrans() -&gt; __mptcp_clean_una_wakeup()

Several helpers in __mptcp_clean_una_wakeup() will update
sk_forward_alloc, possibly causing such field corruption, as reported
by Matthieu.

Address the issue providing and using a new variant of blamed function
which explicitly acquires the msk spin lock.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47133 | HID: amd_sfh: Fix memory leak in amd_sfh_work</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47133</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

HID: amd_sfh: Fix memory leak in amd_sfh_work

Kmemleak tool detected a memory leak in the amd_sfh driver.

====================
unreferenced object 0xffff88810228ada0 (size 32):
  comm "insmod", pid 3968, jiffies 4295056001 (age 775.792s)
  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
    00 20 73 1f 81 88 ff ff 00 01 00 00 00 00 ad de  . s.............
    22 01 00 00 00 00 ad de 01 00 02 00 00 00 00 00  "...............
  backtrace:
    [&lt;000000007b4c8799&gt;] kmem_cache_alloc_trace+0x163/0x4f0
    [&lt;0000000005326893&gt;] amd_sfh_get_report+0xa4/0x1d0 [amd_sfh]
    [&lt;000000002a9e5ec4&gt;] amdtp_hid_request+0x62/0x80 [amd_sfh]
    [&lt;00000000b8a95807&gt;] sensor_hub_get_feature+0x145/0x270 [hid_sensor_hub]
    [&lt;00000000fda054ee&gt;] hid_sensor_parse_common_attributes+0x215/0x460 [hid_sensor_iio_common]
    [&lt;0000000021279ecf&gt;] hid_accel_3d_probe+0xff/0x4a0 [hid_sensor_accel_3d]
    [&lt;00000000915760ce&gt;] platform_probe+0x6a/0xd0
    [&lt;0000000060258a1f&gt;] really_probe+0x192/0x620
    [&lt;00000000fa812f2d&gt;] driver_probe_device+0x14a/0x1d0
    [&lt;000000005e79f7fd&gt;] __device_attach_driver+0xbd/0x110
    [&lt;0000000070d15018&gt;] bus_for_each_drv+0xfd/0x160
    [&lt;0000000013a3c312&gt;] __device_attach+0x18b/0x220
    [&lt;000000008c7b4afc&gt;] device_initial_probe+0x13/0x20
    [&lt;00000000e6e99665&gt;] bus_probe_device+0xfe/0x120
    [&lt;00000000833fa90b&gt;] device_add+0x6a6/0xe00
    [&lt;00000000fa901078&gt;] platform_device_add+0x180/0x380
====================

The fix is to freeing request_list entry once the processed entry is
removed from the request_list.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47134 | efi/fdt: fix panic when no valid fdt found</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47134</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

efi/fdt: fix panic when no valid fdt found

setup_arch() would invoke efi_init()-&gt;efi_get_fdt_params(). If no
valid fdt found then initial_boot_params will be null. So we
should stop further fdt processing here. I encountered this
issue on risc-v.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47135 | mt76: mt7921: fix possible AOOB issue in mt7921_mcu_tx_rate_report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47135</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mt76: mt7921: fix possible AOOB issue in mt7921_mcu_tx_rate_report

Fix possible array out of bound access in mt7921_mcu_tx_rate_report.
Remove unnecessary varibable in mt7921_mcu_tx_rate_report</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28253 | SpEL Injection in `PUT /api/v1/policies` in OpenMetadata</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28253</link><description>OpenMetadata is a unified platform for discovery, observability, and governance powered by a central metadata repository, in-depth lineage, and seamless team collaboration. `CompiledRule::validateExpression` is also called from `PolicyRepository.prepare`. `prepare()` is called from `EntityRepository.prepareInternal()` which, in turn, gets called from `EntityResource.createOrUpdate()`. Note that even though there is an authorization check (`authorizer.authorize()`), it gets called after `prepareInternal()` gets called and therefore after the SpEL expression has been evaluated. In order to reach this method, an attacker can send a PUT request to `/api/v1/policies` which gets handled by `PolicyResource.createOrUpdate()`. This vulnerability was discovered with the help of CodeQL's Expression language injection (Spring) query and is also tracked as `GHSL-2023-252`. This issue may lead to Remote Code Execution and has been addressed in version 1.3.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28254 | SpEL Injection in `GET /api/v1/events/subscriptions/validation/condition/&amp;lt;expr&amp;gt;` in OpenMetadata</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28254</link><description>OpenMetadata is a unified platform for discovery, observability, and governance powered by a central metadata repository, in-depth lineage, and seamless team collaboration. The `‎AlertUtil::validateExpression` method evaluates an SpEL expression using `getValue` which by default uses the `StandardEvaluationContext`, allowing the expression to reach and interact with Java classes such as `java.lang.Runtime`, leading to Remote Code Execution. The `/api/v1/events/subscriptions/validation/condition/&lt;expression&gt;` endpoint passes user-controlled data `AlertUtil::validateExpession` allowing authenticated (non-admin) users to execute arbitrary system commands on the underlaying operating system. In addition, there is a missing authorization check since `Authorizer.authorize()` is never called in the affected path and, therefore, any authenticated non-admin user is able to trigger this endpoint and evaluate arbitrary SpEL expressions leading to arbitrary command execution. This vulnerability was discovered with the help of CodeQL's Expression language injection (Spring) query and is also tracked as `GHSL-2023-235`. This issue may lead to Remote Code Execution and has been addressed in version 1.2.4. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28255 | Authentication Bypass in OpenMetadata</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28255</link><description>OpenMetadata is a unified platform for discovery, observability, and governance powered by a central metadata repository, in-depth lineage, and seamless team collaboration. The `JwtFilter` handles the API authentication by requiring and verifying JWT tokens. When a new request comes in, the request's path is checked against this list. When the request's path contains any of the excluded endpoints the filter returns without validating the JWT. Unfortunately, an attacker may use Path Parameters to make any path contain any arbitrary strings. For example, a request to `GET /api/v1;v1%2fusers%2flogin/events/subscriptions/validation/condition/111` will match the excluded endpoint condition and therefore will be processed with no JWT validation allowing an attacker to bypass the authentication mechanism and reach any arbitrary endpoint, including the ones listed above that lead to arbitrary SpEL expression injection. This bypass will not work when the endpoint uses the `SecurityContext.getUserPrincipal()` since it will return `null` and will throw an NPE. This issue may lead to authentication bypass and has been addressed in version 1.2.4. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability. This issue is also tracked as `GHSL-2023-237`.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28847 | SpEL Injection in `PUT /api/v1/events/subscriptions` in OpenMetadata</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28847</link><description>OpenMetadata is a unified platform for discovery, observability, and governance powered by a central metadata repository, in-depth lineage, and seamless team collaboration. Similarly to the GHSL-2023-250 issue, `AlertUtil::validateExpression` is also called from `EventSubscriptionRepository.prepare()`, which can lead to Remote Code Execution. `prepare()` is called from `EntityRepository.prepareInternal()` which, in turn, gets called from `EntityResource.createOrUpdate()`. Note that, even though there is an authorization check (`authorizer.authorize()`), it gets called after `prepareInternal()` gets called and, therefore, after the SpEL expression has been evaluated. In order to reach this method, an attacker can send a PUT request to `/api/v1/events/subscriptions` which gets handled by `EventSubscriptionResource.createOrUpdateEventSubscription()`. This vulnerability was discovered with the help of CodeQL's Expression language injection (Spring) query. This issue may lead to Remote Code Execution and has been addressed in version 1.2.4. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability. This issue is also tracked as `GHSL-2023-251`.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28848 | SpEL Injection in `GET /api/v1/policies/validation/condition/&amp;lt;expr&amp;gt;` in OpenMetadata</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28848</link><description>OpenMetadata is a unified platform for discovery, observability, and governance powered by a central metadata repository, in-depth lineage, and seamless team collaboration. The `‎CompiledRule::validateExpression` method evaluates an SpEL expression using an `StandardEvaluationContext`, allowing the expression to reach and interact with Java classes such as `java.lang.Runtime`, leading to Remote Code Execution. The `/api/v1/policies/validation/condition/&lt;expression&gt;` endpoint passes user-controlled data `CompiledRule::validateExpession` allowing authenticated (non-admin) users to execute arbitrary system commands on the underlaying operating system. In addition, there is a missing authorization check since `Authorizer.authorize()` is never called in the affected path and therefore any authenticated non-admin user is able to trigger this endpoint and evaluate arbitrary SpEL expressions leading to arbitrary command execution. This vulnerability was discovered with the help of CodeQL's Expression language injection (Spring) query and is also tracked as `GHSL-2023-236`. This issue may lead to Remote Code Execution and has been resolved in version 1.2.4. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27351 | In Django 3.2 before 3.2.25, 4.2 before 4.2.11, and 5.0 before 5.0.3, the django.utils.text.Truncator.words() method (with html=True) and th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27351</link><description>In Django 3.2 before 3.2.25, 4.2 before 4.2.11, and 5.0 before 5.0.3, the django.utils.text.Truncator.words() method (with html=True) and the truncatewords_html template filter are subject to a potential regular expression denial-of-service attack via a crafted string. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2019-14232 and CVE-2023-43665.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:19:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7248 | OpenText Vertica Management console might be prone to bypass via crafted requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7248</link><description>Certain functionality in OpenText Vertica Management console might be prone to bypass via crafted requests. 

The vulnerability would affect one of Vertica’s authentication functionalities by allowing specially crafted requests and sequences. 
This issue impacts the following Vertica Management Console versions:
10.x
11.1.1-24 or lower
12.0.4-18 or lower

Please upgrade to one of the following Vertica Management Console versions:
10.x to upgrade to latest versions from below.
11.1.1-25
12.0.4-19
23.x
24.x</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27085 | Denial of service through invites in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27085</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions users that are allowed to invite others can inject arbitrarily large data in parameters used in the invite route. The problem has been patched in the latest version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should disable invites or restrict access to them using the `invite allowed groups` site setting.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27920 | Unsigned code template execution through workflows in projectdiscovery/nuclei</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27920</link><description>projectdiscovery/nuclei is a fast and customisable vulnerability scanner based on simple YAML based DSL. A significant security oversight was identified in Nuclei v3, involving the execution of unsigned code templates through workflows. This vulnerability specifically affects users utilizing custom workflows, potentially allowing the execution of malicious code on the user's system. This advisory outlines the impacted users, provides details on the security patch, and suggests mitigation strategies. The vulnerability is addressed in Nuclei v3.2.0. Users are strongly recommended to update to this version to mitigate the security risk. Users should refrain from using custom workflows if unable to upgrade immediately. Only trusted, verified workflows should be executed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27100 | Denial of service via Staff Actions in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27100</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions the endpoints for suspending users, silencing users and exporting CSV files weren't enforcing limits on the sizes of the parameters that they accept. This could lead to excessive resource consumption which could render an instance inoperable. A site could be disrupted by either a malicious moderator on the same site or a malicious staff member on another site in the same multisite cluster. This issue is patched in the latest stable, beta and tests-passed versions of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:25:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28242 | Disclosure of the existence of secret categories with custom backgrounds in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28242</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions an attacker can learn that secret categories exist when they have backgrounds set. The issue is patched in the latest stable, beta and tests-passed version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should temporarily remove category backgrounds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:25:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24748 | Disclosure of the existence of secret subcategories in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24748</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions an attacker can learn that a secret subcategory exists under a public category which has no public subcategories. The issue is patched in the latest stable, beta and tests-passed version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24827 | No rate limits on POST /uploads endpoint in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24827</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. Without a rate limit on the POST /uploads endpoint, it makes it easier for an attacker to carry out a DoS attack on the server since creating an upload can be a resource intensive process. Do note that the impact varies from site to site as various site settings like `max_image_size_kb`, `max_attachment_size_kb` and `max_image_megapixels` will determine the amount of resources used when creating an upload. The issue is patched in the latest stable, beta and tests-passed version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should reduce `max_image_size_kb`, `max_attachment_size_kb` and `max_image_megapixels` as smaller uploads require less resources to process. Alternatively, `client_max_body_size` can be reduced in Nginx to prevent large uploads from reaching the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51699 | OS Command Injection for Fluid Users with JuicefsRuntime</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51699</link><description>Fluid is an open source Kubernetes-native Distributed Dataset Orchestrator and Accelerator for data-intensive applications. An OS command injection vulnerability within the Fluid project's JuicefsRuntime can potentially allow an authenticated user, who has the authority to create or update the K8s CRD Dataset/JuicefsRuntime, to execute arbitrary OS commands within the juicefs related containers. This could lead to unauthorized access, modification or deletion of data. Users who're using versions &lt; 0.9.3 with JuicefsRuntime should upgrade to v0.9.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28252 | CoreWCF NetFraming based services can leave connections open when they should be closed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28252</link><description>CoreWCF is a port of the service side of Windows Communication Foundation (WCF) to .NET Core. If you have a NetFraming based CoreWCF service, extra system resources could be consumed by connections being left established instead of closing or aborting them. There are two scenarios when this can happen. When a client established a connection to the service and sends no data, the service will wait indefinitely for the client to initiate the NetFraming session handshake. Additionally, once a client has established a session, if the client doesn't send any requests for the period of time configured in the binding ReceiveTimeout, the connection is not properly closed as part of the session being aborted. The bindings affected by this behavior are NetTcpBinding, NetNamedPipeBinding, and UnixDomainSocketBinding. Only NetTcpBinding has the ability to accept non local connections. The currently supported versions of CoreWCF are v1.4.x and v1.5.x. The fix can be found in v1.4.2 and v1.5.3 of the CoreWCF packages. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28851 | Elevation of privilege in Snowflake Hive MetaStore Connector Helper script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28851</link><description>The Snowflake Hive metastore connector provides an easy way to query Hive-managed data via Snowflake. Snowflake Hive MetaStore Connector has addressed a potential elevation of privilege vulnerability in a `helper script` for the Hive MetaStore Connector. A malicious insider without admin privileges could, in theory, use the script to download content from a Microsoft domain to the local system and replace the valid content with malicious code. If the attacker then also had local access to the same system where the maliciously modified script is run, they could attempt to manipulate users into executing the attacker-controlled helper script, potentially gaining elevated privileges to the local system. The vulnerability in the script was patched on February 09, 2024, without a version bump to the Connector. User who use the helper script are strongly advised to use the latest version as soon as possible. Users unable to upgrade should avoid using the helper script.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28854 | Slow loris vulnerability with default configuration in tls-listener</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28854</link><description>tls-listener is a rust lang wrapper around a connection listener to support TLS. With the default configuration of tls-listener, a malicious user can open 6.4 `TcpStream`s a second, sending 0 bytes, and can trigger a DoS. The default configuration options make any public service using `TlsListener::new()` vulnerable to a slow-loris DoS attack. This impacts any publicly accessible service using the default configuration of tls-listener in versions prior to 0.10.0. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may mitigate this by passing a large value, such as `usize::MAX` as the parameter to `Builder::max_handshakes`.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 18:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7060 | Missing Security Control in Zephyr OS IP Packet Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7060</link><description>Zephyr OS IP packet handling does not properly drop IP packets arriving on an external interface with a source address equal to 127.0.01 or the destination address.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 18:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2193 | Speculative Race Condition impacts modern CPU architectures that support speculative execution, also known as GhostRace.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2193</link><description>A Speculative Race Condition (SRC) vulnerability that impacts modern CPU architectures supporting speculative execution (related to Spectre V1) has been disclosed. An unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to disclose arbitrary data from the CPU using race conditions to access the speculative executable code paths.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 18:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2537 | Electron Code Injection in Logi Tune macOS Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2537</link><description>Improper Control of Dynamically-Managed Code Resources vulnerability in Logitech Logi Tune on MacOS allows Local Code Inclusion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 17:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6960 | CVE-2023-6960</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6960</link><description>TTLock App virtual keys and settings are only deleted client side, and if preserved, can access the lock after intended deletion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 17:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7003 | CVE-2023-7003</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7003</link><description>The AES key utilized in the pairing process between a lock using Sciener firmware and a wireless keypad is not unique, and can be reused to compromise other locks using the Sciener firmware.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 17:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7004 | CVE-2023-7004</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7004</link><description>The TTLock App does not employ proper verification procedures to ensure that it is communicating with the expected device, allowing for connection to a device that spoofs the MAC address of a lock, which compromises the legitimate locks integrity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 17:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7006 | CVE-2023-7006</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7006</link><description>The unlockKey character in a lock using Sciener firmware can be brute forced through repeated challenge requests, compromising the locks integrity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 17:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7007 | CVE-2023-7007</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7007</link><description>Sciener server does not validate connection requests from the GatewayG2, allowing an impersonation attack that provides the attacker the unlockKey field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 17:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7009 | CVE-2023-7009</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7009</link><description>Some Sciener-based locks support plaintext message processing over Bluetooth Low Energy, allowing unencrypted malicious commands to be passed to the lock. These malicious commands, less then 16 bytes in length, will be processed by the lock as if they were encrypted communications. This can be further exploited by an attacker to compromise the lock's integrity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 17:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7017 | CVE-2023-7017</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7017</link><description>Sciener locks' firmware update mechanism do not authenticate or validate firmware updates if passed to the lock through the Bluetooth Low Energy service. A challenge request can be sent to the lock with a command to prepare for an update, rather than an unlock request, allowing an attacker to compromise the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 17:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2497 | RaspAP raspap-webgui HTTP POST Request provider.php code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2497</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RaspAP raspap-webgui 3.0.9 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file includes/provider.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument country leads to code injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256919. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 17:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28401 | TOTOLINK X2000R before v1.0.0-B20231213.1013 contains a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Root Access Control under the Wire...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28401</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R before v1.0.0-B20231213.1013 contains a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Root Access Control under the Wireless Page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 16:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28404 | TOTOLINK X2000R before V1.0.0-B20231213.1013 contains a Stored Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MAC Filtering under the Firewall ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28404</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R before V1.0.0-B20231213.1013 contains a Stored Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MAC Filtering under the Firewall Page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 16:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28403 | TOTOLINK X2000R before V1.0.0-B20231213.1013 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the VPN Page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28403</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R before V1.0.0-B20231213.1013 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the VPN Page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 16:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-38938 | IBM Host Access Transformation Services information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38938</link><description>IBM Host Access Transformation Services (HATS) 9.6 through 9.6.1.4 and 9.7 through 9.7.0.3 stores user credentials in plain clear text which can be read by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  210989.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 15:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46181 | IBM Secure Proxy information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46181</link><description>IBM Sterling Secure Proxy 6.0.3 and 6.1.0 allows web pages to be stored locally which can be read by another user on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  269686.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 15:22:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47147 | IBM Secure Proxy file manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47147</link><description>IBM Sterling Secure Proxy 6.0.3 and 6.1.0 could allow an attacker to overwrite a log message under specific conditions.  IBM X-Force ID:  270598.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 15:22:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47699 | IBM Secure Proxy cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47699</link><description>IBM Sterling Secure Proxy 6.0.3 and 6.1.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  270974.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 15:22:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46179 | IBM Secure Proxy information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46179</link><description>IBM Sterling Secure Proxy 6.0.3 and 6.1.0 does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may be able to get the cookie values by sending a http:// link to a user or by planting this link in a site the user goes to. The cookie will be sent to the insecure link and the attacker can then obtain the cookie value by snooping the traffic.  IBM X-Force ID:  269683.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 15:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47162 | IBM Secure Proxy cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47162</link><description>IBM Sterling Secure Proxy 6.0.3 and 6.1.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  270973.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 15:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28318 | gpac 2.3-DEV-rev921-g422b78ecf-master was discovered to contain a out of boundary write vulnerability via swf_get_string at scene_manager/sw...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28318</link><description>gpac 2.3-DEV-rev921-g422b78ecf-master was discovered to contain a out of boundary write vulnerability via swf_get_string at scene_manager/swf_parse.c:325</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 14:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28319 | gpac 2.3-DEV-rev921-g422b78ecf-master was discovered to contain an out of boundary read vulnerability via gf_dash_setup_period media_tools/d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28319</link><description>gpac 2.3-DEV-rev921-g422b78ecf-master was discovered to contain an out of boundary read vulnerability via gf_dash_setup_period media_tools/dash_client.c:6374</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 14:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46182 | IBM Secure Proxy cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46182</link><description>IBM Sterling Secure Proxy 6.0.3 and 6.1.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  269692.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 14:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51369 | WordPress Customize My Account for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51369</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SysBasics Customize My Account for WooCommerce.This issue affects Customize My Account for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.8.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 14:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51522 | WordPress Paid Membership Subscriptions plugin &amp;lt;= 2.10.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51522</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Cozmoslabs Paid Member Subscriptions.This issue affects Paid Member Subscriptions: from n/a through 2.10.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 14:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50886 | WordPress Legal Pages plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 - CSRF + Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50886</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF), Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in wpWax Legal Pages.This issue affects Legal Pages: from n/a through 1.3.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 14:23:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50898 | WordPress Image Optimizer, Resizer and CDN – Sirv plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50898</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in sirv.Com Sirv.This issue affects Sirv: from n/a through 7.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 14:23:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50861 | WordPress HUSKY plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.4.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50861</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in realmag777 HUSKY – Products Filter for WooCommerce (formerly WOOF).This issue affects HUSKY – Products Filter for WooCommerce (formerly WOOF): from n/a through 1.3.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 14:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51525 | WordPress WP Simple Booking Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.8.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51525</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Veribo, Roland Murg WP Simple Booking Calendar.This issue affects WP Simple Booking Calendar: from n/a through 2.0.8.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 14:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25593 | WordPress NEX-Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 8.5.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25593</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Basix NEX-Forms – Ultimate Form Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects NEX-Forms – Ultimate Form Builder: from n/a through 8.5.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 14:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25596 | WordPress Doofinder for WooCommerce  plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25596</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Doofinder Doofinder for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Doofinder for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 14:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25597 | WordPress Ultimate Reviews plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.8 - Unauthenticated Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25597</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Etoile Web Design Ultimate Reviews allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ultimate Reviews: from n/a through 3.2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 14:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25592 | WordPress Broken Link Checker plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25592</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPMU DEV Broken Link Checker allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Broken Link Checker: from n/a through 2.2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 14:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25598 | WordPress Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin &amp;lt;= 8.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25598</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Livemesh Livemesh Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Livemesh Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 8.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 13:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2495 | Cryptographic key in plain text vulnerability in FriendlyElec&amp;#x27;s FriendlyWrt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2495</link><description>Cryptographic key vulnerability encoded in the FriendlyWrt firmware affecting version 2022-11-16.51b3d35. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to compromise the confidentiality and integrity of encrypted data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 13:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25916 | WordPress My Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.23 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25916</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Joseph C Dolson My Calendar allows Stored XSS.This issue affects My Calendar: from n/a through 3.4.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 13:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25919 | WordPress Custom Field Template plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25919</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Hiroaki Miyashita Custom Field Template allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Custom Field Template: from n/a through 2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 13:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25921 | WordPress Action Network plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25921</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Concerted Action Action Network allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Action Network: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 13:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25934 | WordPress FormFacade plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25934</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FormFacade allows Stored XSS.This issue affects FormFacade: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 13:02:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25936 | WordPress SoundCloud Shortcode plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25936</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SoundCloud Inc., Lawrie Malen SoundCloud Shortcode allows Stored XSS.This issue affects SoundCloud Shortcode: from n/a through 4.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 13:02:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27189 | WordPress WP Social Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27189</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in catchsquare WP Social Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Social Widget: from n/a through 2.2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 13:02:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27192 | WordPress Configure SMTP Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27192</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Scott Reilly Configure SMTP allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Configure SMTP: from n/a through 3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 12:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27193 | WordPress PayU India plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27193</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PayU PayU India allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects PayU India: from n/a through 3.8.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 12:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27196 | WordPress postMash – custom post order plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27196</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Joel Starnes postMash – custom post order allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects postMash – custom post order: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 12:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6725 | Openstack-designate: bind keys are world readable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6725</link><description>An access-control flaw was found in the OpenStack Designate component where private configuration information including access keys to BIND were improperly made world readable. A malicious attacker with access to any container could exploit this flaw to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 12:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23944 | Apache ZooKeeper: Information disclosure in persistent watcher handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23944</link><description>Information disclosure in persistent watchers handling in Apache ZooKeeper due to missing ACL check. It allows an attacker to monitor child znodes by attaching a persistent watcher (addWatch command) to a parent which the attacker has already access to. ZooKeeper server doesn't do ACL check when the persistent watcher is triggered and as a consequence, the full path of znodes that a watch event gets triggered upon is exposed to the owner of the watcher. It's important to note that only the path is exposed by this vulnerability, not the data of znode, but since znode path can contain sensitive information like user name or login ID, this issue is potentially critical.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.9.2, 3.8.4 which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 10:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27987 | WordPress Give plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27987</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GiveWP Give allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Give: from n/a through 3.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 10:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28752 | Apache CXF SSRF Vulnerability using the Aegis databinding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28752</link><description>A SSRF vulnerability using the Aegis DataBinding in versions of Apache CXF before 4.0.4, 3.6.3 and 3.5.8 allows an attacker to perform SSRF style attacks on webservices that take at least one parameter of any type. Users of other data bindings (including the default databinding) are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 10:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2490 | Tenda AC18 openSchedWifi setSchedWifi stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2490</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setSchedWifi of the file /goform/openSchedWifi. The manipulation of the argument schedStartTime/schedEndTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256897 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2445 | Reflected XSS in Mattermost Jira plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2445</link><description>Mattermost Jira plugin versions shipped with Mattermost versions 8.1.x before 8.1.10, 9.2.x before 9.2.6, 9.3.x before 9.3.2, and 9.4.x before 9.4.3 fail to escape user-controlled outputs when generating HTML pages, which allows an attacker to perform reflected cross-site scripting attacks against the users of the Mattermost server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2446 | Mattermost versions 8.1.x before 8.1.10, 9.2.x before 9.2.6, 9.3.x before 9.3.2, and 9.4.x before 9.4.3 fail to limit the number of @-mentio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2446</link><description>Mattermost versions 8.1.x before 8.1.10, 9.2.x before 9.2.6, 9.3.x before 9.3.2, and 9.4.x before 9.4.3 fail to limit the number of @-mentions processed per message, allowing an authenticated attacker to crash the client applications of other users via large, crafted messages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:22:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2450 | Mattermost versions 8.1.x before 8.1.10, 9.2.x before 9.2.6, 9.3.x before 9.3.2, and 9.4.x before 9.4.3 fail to correctly verify account own...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2450</link><description>Mattermost versions 8.1.x before 8.1.10, 9.2.x before 9.2.6, 9.3.x before 9.3.2, and 9.4.x before 9.4.3 fail to correctly verify account ownership when switching from email to SAML authentication, allowing an authenticated attacker to take over other user accounts via a crafted switch request under specific conditions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:22:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24975 |  Denial of Service for mobile app users due to automatic code highlighting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24975</link><description>Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in Mattermost Mobile versions before 2.13.0 fails to limit the size of the code block that will be processed by the syntax highlighter, allowing an attacker to send a very large code block and crash the mobile app.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28053 | Resource Exhaustion via the Invitation Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28053</link><description>Resource Exhaustion in Mattermost Server versions 8.1.x before 8.1.10 fails to limit the size of the payload that can be read and parsed allowing an attacker to send a very large email payload and crash the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2488 | Tenda AC18 SetPptpServerCfg formSetPPTPServer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2488</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function formSetPPTPServer of the file /goform/SetPptpServerCfg. The manipulation of the argument startIP leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256895. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2489 | Tenda AC18 SetNetControlList formSetQosBand stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2489</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. Affected is the function formSetQosBand of the file /goform/SetNetControlList. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256896. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2487 | Tenda AC18 SetOnlineDevName formSetDeviceName stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2487</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formSetDeviceName of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName. The manipulation of the argument devName/mac leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256894 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 08:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2486 | Tenda AC18 QuickIndex formQuickIndex stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2486</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function formQuickIndex of the file /goform/QuickIndex. The manipulation of the argument PPPOEPassword leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256893 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 08:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28353 | There is a command injection vulnerability in the TRENDnet TEW-827DRU router with firmware version 2.10B01. An attacker can inject commands ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28353</link><description>There is a command injection vulnerability in the TRENDnet TEW-827DRU router with firmware version 2.10B01. An attacker can inject commands into the post request parameters usapps.config.smb_admin_name in the apply.cgi interface, thereby gaining root shell privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28354 | There is a command injection vulnerability in the TRENDnet TEW-827DRU router with firmware version 2.10B01. An attacker can inject commands ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28354</link><description>There is a command injection vulnerability in the TRENDnet TEW-827DRU router with firmware version 2.10B01. An attacker can inject commands into the post request parameters usapps.@smb[%d].username in the apply.cgi interface, thereby gaining root shell privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27756 | An issue in GLPI v.10.0.12 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive informat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27756</link><description>An issue in GLPI v.10.0.12 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the title field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:04:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2483 | Surya2Developer Hostel Management Service Password Change change-password.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2483</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Surya2Developer Hostel Management Service 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /change-password.php of the component Password Change Handler. The manipulation of the argument oldpassword leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256889 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:04:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2485 | Tenda AC18 SetSpeedWan formSetSpeedWan stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2485</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formSetSpeedWan of the file /goform/SetSpeedWan. The manipulation of the argument speed_dir leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256892. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:04:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1795 | The HUSKY – Products Filter for WooCommerce Professional plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'name' parameter in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1795</link><description>The HUSKY – Products Filter for WooCommerce Professional plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'name' parameter in the woof shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.5.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1796 | The HUSKY – Products Filter for WooCommerce Professional plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1796</link><description>The HUSKY – Products Filter for WooCommerce Professional plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'woof' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as 'swoof_slug'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2399 | The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2399</link><description>The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.23 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2482 | Surya2Developer Hostel Management Service HTTP POST Request check_availability.php observable response discrepancy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2482</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Surya2Developer Hostel Management Service 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /check_availability.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument oldpassword leads to observable response discrepancy. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256891.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2480 | MHA Sistemas arMHAzena Executa Page sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2480</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in MHA Sistemas arMHAzena 9.6.0.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Executa Page. The manipulation of the argument Companhia/Planta/Agente de/Agente até leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256888. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2481 | Surya2Developer Hostel Management System manage-students.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2481</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Surya2Developer Hostel Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/manage-students.php. The manipulation of the argument del leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256890 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25227 | SQL Injection vulnerability in ABO.CMS version 5.8, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial of service (DoS), esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25227</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in ABO.CMS version 5.8, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial of service (DoS), escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information via the tb_login parameter in admin login page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 05:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2478 | BradWenqiang HR Background Management register selectAll sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2478</link><description>A vulnerability was found in BradWenqiang HR 2.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function selectAll of the file /bishe/register of the component Background Management. The manipulation of the argument userName leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256886 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 05:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2479 | MHA Sistemas arMHAzena Cadastro Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2479</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in MHA Sistemas arMHAzena 9.6.0.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Cadastro Page. The manipulation of the argument Query leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256887. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 05:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2180 | Zemana AntiLogger v2.74.204.664 - Kernel Memory Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2180</link><description>Zemana AntiLogger v2.74.204.664 is vulnerable to a Memory Information Leak vulnerability by triggering the 0x80002020 IOCTL code of the zam64.sys and zamguard64.sys drivers</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 04:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2204 | Zemana AntiLogger v2.74.204.664 - Denial of Service (DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2204</link><description>Zemana AntiLogger v2.74.204.664 is vulnerable to a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability by triggering the 0x80002004 and 0x80002010 IOCTL codes of the zam64.sys and zamguard64.sys drivers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 04:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26454 | A Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Healthcare-Chatbot through 9b7058a can occur via a crafted payload to the email1 or pwd1 parameter i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26454</link><description>A Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Healthcare-Chatbot through 9b7058a can occur via a crafted payload to the email1 or pwd1 parameter in login.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26540 | A heap-based buffer overflow in Clmg before 3.3.3 can occur via a crafted file to cimg_library::CImg&lt;unsigned char&gt;::_load_analyze.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26540</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow in Clmg before 3.3.3 can occur via a crafted file to cimg_library::CImg&lt;unsigned char&gt;::_load_analyze.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0803 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0803</link><description>Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute malicious code on a target product by sending a specially crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1915 | Incorrect Pointer Scaling vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a remote u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1915</link><description>Incorrect Pointer Scaling vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute malicious code on a target product by sending a specially crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1916 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1916</link><description>Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute malicious code on a target product by sending a specially crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1917 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1917</link><description>Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute malicious code on a target product by sending a specially crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0802 | Incorrect Pointer Scaling vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a remote u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0802</link><description>Incorrect Pointer Scaling vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to read arbitrary information from a target product or execute malicious code on a target product by sending a specially crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1853 | Zemana AntiLogger v2.74.204.664 - Arbitrary Process Termination</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1853</link><description>Zemana AntiLogger v2.74.204.664 is vulnerable to an Arbitrary Process Termination vulnerability by triggering the 0x80002048 IOCTL code of the zam64.sys and zamguard64.sys drivers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 22:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26163 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26163</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 22:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26246 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26246</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 22:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26475 | An issue in radareorg radare2 v.0.9.7 through v.5.8.6 and fixed in v.5.8.8 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the grub...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26475</link><description>An issue in radareorg radare2 v.0.9.7 through v.5.8.6 and fixed in v.5.8.8 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the grub_sfs_read_extent function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 21:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42286 | There is a PHP file inclusion vulnerability in the template configuration of eyoucms v1.6.4, allowing attackers to execute code or system co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42286</link><description>There is a PHP file inclusion vulnerability in the template configuration of eyoucms v1.6.4, allowing attackers to execute code or system commands through a carefully crafted malicious payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 21:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2249 | The LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the LinkWrapper attribute foun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2249</link><description>The LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the LinkWrapper attribute found in several widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping the user supplied attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 21:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50677 | An issue in NETGEAR-DGND4000 v.1.1.00.15_1.00.15 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the next_file parameter to the /setup.c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50677</link><description>An issue in NETGEAR-DGND4000 v.1.1.00.15_1.00.15 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the next_file parameter to the /setup.cgi component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 21:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26503 | Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability in Greek Universities Network Open eClass v.3.15 and earlier allows attackers to run arbitrary code v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26503</link><description>Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability in Greek Universities Network Open eClass v.3.15 and earlier allows attackers to run arbitrary code via upload of crafted file to certbadge.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 21:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0860 | Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information in Softing edgeConnector and edgeAggregator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0860</link><description>The affected product is vulnerable to a cleartext transmission of sensitive information vulnerability, which may allow an attacker to capture packets to craft their own requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 21:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2256 | The oik plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes such as bw_contact_button and bw_butto...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2256</link><description>The oik plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes such as bw_contact_button and bw_button shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 20:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1713 | Plv8 Deferred Trigger Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1713</link><description>A user who can create objects in a database with plv8 3.2.1 installed is able to cause deferred triggers to execute as the Superuser during autovacuum.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 20:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24562 | Security headers not set in vantage6-UI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24562</link><description>vantage6-UI is the official user interface for the vantage6 server. In affected versions a number of security headers are not set. This issue has been addressed in commit `68dfa6614` which is expected to be included in future releases. Users are advised to upgrade when a new release is made. While an upgrade path is not available users may modify the docker image build to insert the headers into nginx.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28423 | Airflow-Diagrams v2.1.0 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the unsafe_load function at cli.py. This vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28423</link><description>Airflow-Diagrams v2.1.0 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the unsafe_load function at cli.py. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted YML file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28424 | zenml v0.55.4 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the load function at /materializers/cloudpickle_materializ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28424</link><description>zenml v0.55.4 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the load function at /materializers/cloudpickle_materializer.py. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28425 | greykite v1.0.0 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the load_obj function at /templates/pickle_utils.py. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28425</link><description>greykite v1.0.0 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the load_obj function at /templates/pickle_utils.py. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23823 | CORS settings overly permissive in vantage6</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23823</link><description>vantage6 is an open source framework built to enable, manage and deploy privacy enhancing technologies like Federated Learning and Multi-Party Computation. The vantage6 server has no restrictions on CORS settings. It should be possible for people to set the allowed origins of the server.  The impact is limited because v6 does not use session cookies. This issue has been addressed in commit `70bb4e1d8` and is expected to ship in subsequent releases. Users are advised to upgrade as soon as a new release is available. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24770 | Username timing attack on recover password/MFA token in vantage6</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24770</link><description>vantage6 is an open source framework built to enable, manage and deploy privacy enhancing technologies like Federated Learning and Multi-Party Computation. Much like GHSA-45gq-q4xh-cp53, it is possible to find which usernames exist in vantage6 by calling the API routes `/recover/lost` and `/2fa/lost`. These routes send emails to users if they have lost their password or MFA token. This issue has been addressed in commit `aecfd6d0e` and is expected to ship in subsequent releases. Users are advised to upgrade as soon as a new release is available. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22346 | IBM i privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22346</link><description>Db2 for IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 infrastructure could allow a local user to gain elevated privileges due to an unqualified library call. A malicious actor could cause user-controlled code to run with administrator privilege.  IBM X-Force ID:  280203.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27265 | IBM Integration Bus for z/OS cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27265</link><description>IBM Integration Bus for z/OS 10.1 through 10.1.0.3 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.  IBM X-Force ID:  284564.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27266 | IBM Maximo Application Suite XML external entity injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27266</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite 7.6.1.3 is vulnerable to an XML External Entity Injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.  IBM X-Force ID:  284566.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27301 | Privilege Escalation Abusing installer in SupportApp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27301</link><description>Support App is an opensource application specialized in managing Apple devices. It's possible to abuse a vulnerability inside the postinstall installer script to make the installer execute arbitrary code as root. The cause of the vulnerability is the fact that the shebang `#!/bin/zsh` is being used. When the installer is executed it asks for the users password to be executed as root. However, it'll still be using the $HOME of the user and therefore loading the file  `$HOME/.zshenv` when the `postinstall` script is executed.
An attacker could add malicious code to `$HOME/.zshenv` and it will be executed when the app is installed. An attacker may leverage this vulnerability to escalate privilege on the system. This issue has been addressed in version 2.5.1 Rev 2. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42938 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iTunes 12.13.1 for Windows. A local attacker may be able to elevate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42938</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iTunes 12.13.1 for Windows. A local attacker may be able to elevate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28181 | Arbitrary method invocation turbo_boost-commands </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28181</link><description>turbo_boost-commands is a set of commands to help you build robust reactive applications with Rails &amp; Hotwire. TurboBoost Commands has existing protections in place to guarantee that only public methods on Command classes can be invoked; however, the existing checks aren't as robust as they should be. It's possible for a sophisticated attacker to invoke more methods than should be permitted depending on the the strictness of authorization checks that individual applications enforce. Being able to call some of these methods can have security implications. Commands verify that the class must be a `Command` and that the method requested is defined as a public method; however, this isn't robust enough to guard against all unwanted code execution. The library should more strictly enforce which methods are considered safe before allowing them to be executed. This issue has been addressed in versions 0.1.3, and 0.2.2. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should see the repository GHSA for workaround advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 17:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28849 | Proxy-Authorization header kept across hosts in follow-redirects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28849</link><description>follow-redirects is an open source, drop-in replacement for Node's `http` and `https` modules that automatically follows redirects. In affected versions follow-redirects only clears authorization header during cross-domain redirect, but keep the proxy-authentication header which contains credentials too. This vulnerability may lead to credentials leak, but has been addressed in version 1.15.6. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 17:11:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22655 | Protection mechanism failure in some 3rd and 4th Generation Intel(R) Xeon(R) Processors when using Intel(R) SGX or Intel(R) TDX may allow a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22655</link><description>Protection mechanism failure in some 3rd and 4th Generation Intel(R) Xeon(R) Processors when using Intel(R) SGX or Intel(R) TDX may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27502 | Insertion of sensitive information into log file for some Intel(R) Local Manageability Service software before version 2316.5.1.2 may allow ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27502</link><description>Insertion of sensitive information into log file for some Intel(R) Local Manageability Service software before version 2316.5.1.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28389 | Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) CSME installer software before version 2328.5.5.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28389</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) CSME installer software before version 2328.5.5.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28746 | Information exposure through microarchitectural state after transient execution from some register files for some Intel(R) Atom(R) Processor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28746</link><description>Information exposure through microarchitectural state after transient execution from some register files for some Intel(R) Atom(R) Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32282 | Race condition in BIOS firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32282</link><description>Race condition in BIOS firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32633 | Improper input validation in the Intel(R) CSME installer software before version 2328.5.5.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32633</link><description>Improper input validation in the Intel(R) CSME installer software before version 2328.5.5.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32666 | On-chip debug and test interface with improper access control in some 4th Generation Intel(R) Xeon(R) Processors when using Intel(R) SGX or ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32666</link><description>On-chip debug and test interface with improper access control in some 4th Generation Intel(R) Xeon(R) Processors when using Intel(R) SGX or Intel(R) TDX may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35191 | Uncontrolled resource consumption for some Intel(R) SPS firmware versions may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35191</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption for some Intel(R) SPS firmware versions may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38575 | Non-transparent sharing of return predictor targets between contexts in some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authorized user to potentially...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38575</link><description>Non-transparent sharing of return predictor targets between contexts in some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authorized user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39368 | Protection mechanism failure of bus lock regulator for some Intel(R) Processors may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable deni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39368</link><description>Protection mechanism failure of bus lock regulator for some Intel(R) Processors may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43490 | Incorrect calculation in microcode keying mechanism for some Intel(R) Xeon(R) D Processors with Intel(R) SGX may allow a privileged user to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43490</link><description>Incorrect calculation in microcode keying mechanism for some Intel(R) Xeon(R) D Processors with Intel(R) SGX may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50168 | Pega Platform from 6.x to 8.8.4 is affected by an XXE issue with PDF Generation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50168</link><description>Pega Platform from 6.x to 8.8.4 is affected by an XXE issue with PDF Generation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 15:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25139 | In TP-Link Omada er605 1.0.1 through (v2.6) 2.2.3, a cloud-brd binary is susceptible to an integer overflow that leads to a heap-based buffe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25139</link><description>In TP-Link Omada er605 1.0.1 through (v2.6) 2.2.3, a cloud-brd binary is susceptible to an integer overflow that leads to a heap-based buffer overflow. After heap shaping, an attacker can achieve code execution in the context of the cloud-brd binary that runs at the root level. This is fixed in ER605(UN)_v2_2.2.4 Build 020240119.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 15:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25156 | Path traversal in GoAnywhere MFT 7.4.1 and Earlier</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25156</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in GoAnywhere MFT prior to 7.4.2 which allows attackers to circumvent endpoint-specific permission checks in the GoAnywhere Admin and Web Clients.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 14:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28323 | The bwdates-report-result.php file in Phpgurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System 3.1 contains a potential security vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28323</link><description>The bwdates-report-result.php file in Phpgurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System 3.1 contains a potential security vulnerability related to user input validation. The script retrieves user-provided date inputs without proper validation, making it susceptible to SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 13:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28417 | Webedition CMS 9.2.2.0 has a Stored XSS vulnerability via /webEdition/we_cmd.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28417</link><description>Webedition CMS 9.2.2.0 has a Stored XSS vulnerability via /webEdition/we_cmd.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 13:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28418 | Webedition CMS 9.2.2.0 has a File upload vulnerability via /webEdition/we_cmd.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28418</link><description>Webedition CMS 9.2.2.0 has a File upload vulnerability via /webEdition/we_cmd.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 13:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1623 | Insufficient session timeout vulnerability in Sagemcom router</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1623</link><description>Insufficient session timeout vulnerability in the FAST3686 V2 Vodafone router from Sagemcom. This vulnerability could allow a local attacker to access the administration panel without requiring login credentials. This vulnerability is possible because the 'Login.asp and logout.asp' files do not handle session details correctly.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 12:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28383 | Tenda AX12 v1.0 v22.03.01.16 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid parameter in the sub_431CF0 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28383</link><description>Tenda AX12 v1.0 v22.03.01.16 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid parameter in the sub_431CF0 function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 12:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0311 | A malicious insider can bypass the existing policy of Skyhigh Client Proxy without a valid release code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0311</link><description>A malicious insider can bypass the existing policy of Skyhigh Client Proxy without a valid release code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 09:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0312 | A malicious insider can uninstall Skyhigh Client Proxy without a valid uninstall password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0312</link><description>A malicious insider can uninstall Skyhigh Client Proxy without a valid uninstall password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 09:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0313 | A malicious insider exploiting this vulnerability can circumvent existing security controls put in place by the organization. On the contrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0313</link><description>A malicious insider exploiting this vulnerability can circumvent existing security controls put in place by the organization. On the contrary, if the victim is legitimately using the temporary bypass to reach out to the Internet for retrieving application and system updates, a remote device could target it and undo the bypass, thereby denying the victim access to the update service, causing it to fail.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 09:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28746 | Apache Airflow: Ignored Airflow Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28746</link><description>Apache Airflow, versions 2.8.0 through 2.8.2, has a vulnerability that allows an authenticated user with limited permissions to access resources such as variables, connections, etc from the UI which they do not have permission to access. 

Users of Apache Airflow are recommended to upgrade to version 2.8.3 or newer to mitigate the risk associated with this vulnerability</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 08:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27986 | WordPress Livemesh Addons for Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 8.3.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27986</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Livemesh Elementor Addons by Livemesh allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Elementor Addons by Livemesh: from n/a through 8.3.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 08:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22397 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') in the SonicOS SSLVPN portal allows a remote authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22397</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') in the SonicOS SSLVPN portal allows a remote authenticated attacker as a firewall 'admin' user to store and execute arbitrary JavaScript code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22398 | An improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (Path Traversal) vulnerability in SonicWall Email Security Appliance could al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22398</link><description>An improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (Path Traversal) vulnerability in SonicWall Email Security Appliance could allow a remote attacker with administrative privileges to conduct a directory traversal attack and delete arbitrary files from the appliance file system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28391 | SQL injection vulnerability in FME Modules quickproducttable module for PrestaShop v.1.2.1 and before, allows a remote attacker to escalate ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28391</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in FME Modules quickproducttable module for PrestaShop v.1.2.1 and before, allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges and obtain information via the readCsv(), displayAjaxProductChangeAttr, displayAjaxProductAddToCart, getSearchProducts, and displayAjaxProductSku methods.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:24:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1882 | Server-side resource injection in PaperCut NG/MF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1882</link><description>This vulnerability allows an already authenticated admin user to create a malicious payload that could be leveraged for remote code execution on the server hosting the PaperCut NG/MF application server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1883 | Reflected XSS in PaperCut NG/MF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1883</link><description>This is a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in the PaperCut NG/MF application server. An attacker can exploit this weakness by crafting a malicious URL that contains a script. When an unsuspecting user clicks on this malicious link, it could potentially lead to limited loss of confidentiality, integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1884 | Server Side Request Forgery in PaperCut NG/MF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1884</link><description>This is a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the PaperCut NG/MF server-side module that  allows an attacker to induce the server-side application to make HTTP requests to an arbitrary domain of the attacker's choosing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22396 | An Integer-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SonicOS via IPSec allows a remote attacker in specific conditions to cause Denial of S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22396</link><description>An Integer-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SonicOS via IPSec allows a remote attacker in specific conditions to cause Denial of Service (DoS) and potentially execute arbitrary code by sending a specially crafted IKEv2 payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28390 | An issue in Advanced Plugins ultimateimagetool module for PrestaShop before v.2.2.01, allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges and ob...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28390</link><description>An issue in Advanced Plugins ultimateimagetool module for PrestaShop before v.2.2.01, allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via Improper Access Control.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1221 | Improper access controls on APIs on Linux and macOS in PaperCut NG/MF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1221</link><description>This vulnerability potentially allows files on a PaperCut NG/MF server to be exposed using a specifically formed payload against the impacted API endpoint. The attacker must carry out some reconnaissance to gain knowledge of a system token. This CVE only affects Linux and macOS PaperCut NG/MF servers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1222 | Incorrect authorization controls in PaperCut NG/MF APIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1222</link><description>This allows attackers to use a maliciously formed API request to gain access to an API authorization level with elevated privileges. This applies to a small subset of PaperCut NG/MF API calls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1223 |  Improper authorization controls in PaperCut NG/MF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1223</link><description>This vulnerability potentially allows unauthorized enumeration of information from the embedded device APIs. An attacker must already have existing knowledge of some combination of valid usernames, device names and an internal system key. For such an attack to be successful the system must be in a specific runtime state.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1654 | Unauthorized write operations in PaperCut NG/MF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1654</link><description>This vulnerability potentially allows unauthorized write operations which may lead to remote code execution. An attacker must already have authenticated admin access and knowledge of both an internal system identifier and details of another valid user to exploit this.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28388 | SQL injection vulnerability in SunnyToo stproductcomments module for PrestaShop v.1.0.5 and before, allows a remote attacker to escalate pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28388</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in SunnyToo stproductcomments module for PrestaShop v.1.0.5 and before, allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the StProductCommentClass::getListcomments method.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25653 | Broken Access Control in the Report functionality of Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4 allows unprivileged users, when Unlimited Admin Mode is ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25653</link><description>Broken Access Control in the Report functionality of Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4 allows unprivileged users, when Unlimited Admin Mode is enabled, to view system reports and modify custom reports via the Report functionality in the Web UI.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25652 | In Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4, it is possible for a user (with access to the Report functionality) to gain unauthorized access to remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25652</link><description>In Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4, it is possible for a user (with access to the Report functionality) to gain unauthorized access to remote sessions created by legitimate users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25649 | In Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4, it is possible for an attacker (with Administrator access to the Secret Server machine) to read the follo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25649</link><description>In Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4, it is possible for an attacker (with Administrator access to the Secret Server machine) to read the following data from a memory dump: the decrypted master key, database credentials (when SQL Server Authentication is enabled), the encryption key of RabbitMQ queue messages, and session cookies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25651 | User enumeration can occur in the Authentication REST API in Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4. This allows a remote attacker to determine whet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25651</link><description>User enumeration can occur in the Authentication REST API in Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4. This allows a remote attacker to determine whether a user is valid because of a difference in responses from the /oauth2/token endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25650 | Insecure key exchange between Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4 and the Distributed Engine 8.4.3 allows a PAM administrator to obtain the Symme...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25650</link><description>Insecure key exchange between Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4 and the Distributed Engine 8.4.3 allows a PAM administrator to obtain the Symmetric Key (used to encrypt RabbitMQ messages) via crafted payloads to the /pre-authenticate, /authenticate, and /execute-and-respond REST API endpoints. This makes it possible for a PAM administrator to impersonate the Engine and exfiltrate sensitive information from the messages published in the RabbitMQ exchanges, without being audited in the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25228 | Vinchin Backup and Recovery 7.2 and Earlier is vulnerable to Authenticated Remote Code Execution (RCE) via the getVerifydiyResult function i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25228</link><description>Vinchin Backup and Recovery 7.2 and Earlier is vulnerable to Authenticated Remote Code Execution (RCE) via the getVerifydiyResult function in ManoeuvreHandler.class.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>