<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:14:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-6852 | WP MultiTasking &amp;lt;= 0.1.12 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6852</link><description>The WP MultiTasking  WordPress plugin through 0.1.12 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6853 | WP MultiTasking &amp;lt;= 0.1.12 - Welcome Popup Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6853</link><description>The WP MultiTasking  WordPress plugin through 0.1.12 does not have CSRF check when updating welcome popups, which could allow attackers to make logged admins perform such action via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6855 | WP MultiTasking &amp;lt;= 0.1.12 - Exit Popup Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6855</link><description>The WP MultiTasking  WordPress plugin through 0.1.12 does not have CSRF check when updating exit popups, which could allow attackers to make logged admins perform such action via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6856 | WP MultiTasking &amp;lt;= 0.1.12 - SMTP Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6856</link><description>The WP MultiTasking  WordPress plugin through 0.1.12 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6859 | WP MultiTasking &amp;lt;= 0.1.12 - Reflected XSS via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6859</link><description>The WP MultiTasking  WordPress plugin through 0.1.12 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6924 | TrueBooker &amp;lt; 1.0.3 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6924</link><description>The TrueBooker  WordPress plugin before 1.0.3 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement via an AJAX action available to unauthenticated users, leading to a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6925 | TrueBooker &amp;lt; 1.0.3 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6925</link><description>The TrueBooker  WordPress plugin before 1.0.3 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6928 | Opti Marketing &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Unauthenticated SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6928</link><description>The Opti Marketing WordPress plugin through 2.0.9 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement via an AJAX action available to unauthenticated users, leading to a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8569 | code-projects Hospital Management System user-login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8569</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Hospital Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file user-login.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 05:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8568 | Mini-Tmall 1 rewardMapper.select sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8568</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Mini-Tmall up to 20240901. Affected is the function rewardMapper.select of the file tmall/admin/order/1/1. The manipulation of the argument orderBy leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 03:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8567 | itsourcecode Payroll Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8567</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in itsourcecode Payroll Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_deductions. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 02:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8566 | code-projects Online Shop Store settings.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8566</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in code-projects Online Shop Store 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /settings.php. The manipulation of the argument error leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 23:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8565 | SourceCodesters Clinics Patient Management System print_diseases.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8565</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodesters Clinics Patient Management System 2.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /print_diseases.php. The manipulation of the argument disease/from/to leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 22:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8564 | SourceCodester PHP CRUD update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8564</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester PHP CRUD 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /endpoint/update.php. The manipulation of the argument tbl_person_id/first_name/middle_name/last_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 20:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8563 | SourceCodester PHP CRUD update.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8563</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester PHP CRUD 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /endpoint/update.php. The manipulation of the argument first_name/middle_name/last_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 20:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8562 | SourceCodester PHP CRUD Add.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8562</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester PHP CRUD 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /endpoint/Add.php. The manipulation of the argument first_name/middle_name/last_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 19:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8561 | SourceCodester PHP CRUD Delete Person delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8561</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester PHP CRUD 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /endpoint/delete.php of the component Delete Person Handler. The manipulation of the argument person leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 18:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8560 | SourceCodester Simple Invoice Generator System save_invoice.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8560</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Simple Invoice Generator System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /save_invoice.php. The manipulation of the argument invoice_code/customer/cashier/total_amount/discount_percentage/discount_amount/tendered_amount leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 18:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8559 | SourceCodester Online Food Menu delete-menu.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8559</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Online Food Menu 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /endpoint/delete-menu.php. The manipulation of the argument menu leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 17:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38650 | An authentication bypass vulnerability can allow a low privileged attacker to access the NTLM hash of service account on the VSPC server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38650</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability can allow a low privileged attacker to access the NTLM hash of service account on the VSPC server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38651 | A code injection vulnerability can allow a low-privileged user to overwrite files on that VSPC server, which can lead to remote code executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38651</link><description>A code injection vulnerability can allow a low-privileged user to overwrite files on that VSPC server, which can lead to remote code execution on VSPC server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39714 | A code injection vulnerability that permits a low-privileged user to upload arbitrary files to the server, leading to remote code execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39714</link><description>A code injection vulnerability that permits a low-privileged user to upload arbitrary files to the server, leading to remote code execution on VSPC server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39715 | A code injection vulnerability that allows a low-privileged user with REST API access granted to remotely upload arbitrary files to the VSPC...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39715</link><description>A code injection vulnerability that allows a low-privileged user with REST API access granted to remotely upload arbitrary files to the VSPC server using REST API, leading to remote code execution on VSPC server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39718 | An improper input validation vulnerability that allows a low-privileged user to remotely remove files on the system with permissions equival...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39718</link><description>An improper input validation vulnerability that allows a low-privileged user to remotely remove files on the system with permissions equivalent to those of the service account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40709 | A missing authorization vulnerability allows a local low-privileged user on the machine to escalate their privileges to root level.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40709</link><description>A missing authorization vulnerability allows a local low-privileged user on the machine to escalate their privileges to root level.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40710 | A series of related high-severity vulnerabilities, the most notable enabling remote code execution (RCE) as the service account and extracti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40710</link><description>A series of related high-severity vulnerabilities, the most notable enabling remote code execution (RCE) as the service account and extraction of sensitive information (savedcredentials and passwords). Exploiting these vulnerabilities requires a user who has been assigned a low-privileged role within Veeam Backup &amp; Replication.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40711 | A deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability with a malicious payload can allow an unauthenticated remote code execution (RCE).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40711</link><description>A deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability with a malicious payload can allow an unauthenticated remote code execution (RCE).</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40712 | A path traversal vulnerability allows an attacker with a low-privileged account and local access to the system to perform local privilege es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40712</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability allows an attacker with a low-privileged account and local access to the system to perform local privilege escalation (LPE).</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40713 | A vulnerability that allows a user who has been assigned a low-privileged role within Veeam Backup &amp; Replication to alter Multi-Factor Authe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40713</link><description>A vulnerability that allows a user who has been assigned a low-privileged role within Veeam Backup &amp; Replication to alter Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) settings and bypass MFA.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40714 | An improper certificate validation vulnerability in TLS certificate validation allows an attacker on the same network to intercept sensitive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40714</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability in TLS certificate validation allows an attacker on the same network to intercept sensitive credentials during restore operations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40718 | A server side request forgery vulnerability allows a low-privileged user to perform local privilege escalation through exploiting an SSRF vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40718</link><description>A server side request forgery vulnerability allows a low-privileged user to perform local privilege escalation through exploiting an SSRF vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42019 | A vulnerability that allows an attacker to access the NTLM hash of the Veeam Reporter Service service account. This attack requires user int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42019</link><description>A vulnerability that allows an attacker to access the NTLM hash of the Veeam Reporter Service service account. This attack requires user interaction and data collected from Veeam Backup &amp; Replication.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42020 | A Cross-site-scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Reporter Widgets that allows HTML injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42020</link><description>A Cross-site-scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Reporter Widgets that allows HTML injection.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42021 | An improper access control vulnerability allows an attacker with valid access tokens to access saved credentials.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42021</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability allows an attacker with valid access tokens to access saved credentials.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42022 | An incorrect permission assignment vulnerability allows an attacker to modify product configuration files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42022</link><description>An incorrect permission assignment vulnerability allows an attacker to modify product configuration files.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42023 | An improper access control vulnerability allows low-privileged users to execute code with Administrator privileges remotely.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42023</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability allows low-privileged users to execute code with Administrator privileges remotely.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42024 | A vulnerability that allows an attacker in possession of the Veeam ONE Agent service account credentials to perform remote code execution on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42024</link><description>A vulnerability that allows an attacker in possession of the Veeam ONE Agent service account credentials to perform remote code execution on the machine where the Veeam ONE Agent is installed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30582 | A vulnerability has been identified in Node.js version 20, affecting users of the experimental permission model when the --allow-fs-read fla...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30582</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Node.js version 20, affecting users of the experimental permission model when the --allow-fs-read flag is used with a non-* argument. This flaw arises from an inadequate permission model that fails to restrict file watching through the fs.watchFile API. As a result, malicious actors can monitor files that they do not have explicit read access to.

Please note that at the time this CVE was issued, the permission model is an experimental feature of Node.js.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30583 | fs.openAsBlob() can bypass the experimental permission model when using the file system read restriction with the `--allow-fs-read` flag in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30583</link><description>fs.openAsBlob() can bypass the experimental permission model when using the file system read restriction with the `--allow-fs-read` flag in Node.js 20. This flaw arises from a missing check in the `fs.openAsBlob()` API.

Please note that at the time this CVE was issued, the permission model is an experimental feature of Node.js.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30584 | A vulnerability has been discovered in Node.js version 20, specifically within the experimental permission model. This flaw relates to impro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30584</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in Node.js version 20, specifically within the experimental permission model. This flaw relates to improper handling of path traversal bypass when verifying file permissions.

Please note that at the time this CVE was issued, the permission model is an experimental feature of Node.js.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30587 | A vulnerability in Node.js version 20 allows for bypassing restrictions set by the --experimental-permission flag using the built-in inspect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30587</link><description>A vulnerability in Node.js version 20 allows for bypassing restrictions set by the --experimental-permission flag using the built-in inspector module (node:inspector).

By exploiting the Worker class's ability to create an "internal worker" with the kIsInternal Symbol, attackers can modify the isInternal value when an inspector is attached within the Worker constructor before initializing a new WorkerImpl. This vulnerability exclusively affects Node.js users employing the permission model mechanism.

Please note that at the time this CVE was issued, the permission model is an experimental feature of Node.js.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39333 | Maliciously crafted export names in an imported WebAssembly module can inject JavaScript code. The injected code may be able to access data ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39333</link><description>Maliciously crafted export names in an imported WebAssembly module can inject JavaScript code. The injected code may be able to access data and functions that the WebAssembly module itself does not have access to, similar to as if the WebAssembly module was a JavaScript module.

This vulnerability affects users of any active release line of Node.js. The vulnerable feature is only available if Node.js is started with the `--experimental-wasm-modules` command line option.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46809 | Node.js versions which bundle an unpatched version of OpenSSL or run against a dynamically linked version of OpenSSL which are unpatched are...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46809</link><description>Node.js versions which bundle an unpatched version of OpenSSL or run against a dynamically linked version of OpenSSL which are unpatched are vulnerable to the Marvin Attack - https://people.redhat.com/~hkario/marvin/, if PCKS #1 v1.5 padding is allowed when performing RSA descryption using a private key.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:21:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36137 | A vulnerability has been identified in Node.js, affecting users of the experimental permission model when the --allow-fs-write flag is used....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36137</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Node.js, affecting users of the experimental permission model when the --allow-fs-write flag is used.

Node.js Permission Model do not operate on file descriptors, however, operations such as fs.fchown or fs.fchmod can use a "read-only" file descriptor to change the owner and permissions of a file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:21:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36138 | Bypass incomplete fix of CVE-2024-27980, that arises from improper handling of batch files with all possible extensions on Windows via child...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36138</link><description>Bypass incomplete fix of CVE-2024-27980, that arises from improper handling of batch files with all possible extensions on Windows via child_process.spawn / child_process.spawnSync. A malicious command line argument can inject arbitrary commands and achieve code execution even if the shell option is not enabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:21:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8558 | SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System Price place-order.php improper validation of specified quantity in input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8558</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /foms/routers/place-order.php of the component Price Handler. The manipulation of the argument total leads to improper validation of specified quantity in input. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 15:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8557 | SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System cancel-order.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8557</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /foms/routers/cancel-order.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 15:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8555 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System congratulations.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8555</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 2.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file congratulations.php. The manipulation of the argument goto_page leads to open redirect. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 14:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40681 | IBM MQ Operator security bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40681</link><description>IBM MQ Operator 2.0.26 and 3.2.4 could allow an authenticated user in a specifically defined role, to bypass security restrictions and execute actions against the queue manager.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 14:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40680 | IBM MQ Operator denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40680</link><description>IBM MQ Operator 2.0.26 and 3.2.4 could allow a local user to cause a denial of service due to improper memory allocation causing a segmentation fault.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 14:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37068 | IBM Maximo Application Suite information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37068</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite - Manage Component 8.10, 8.11, and 9.0 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 13:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8554 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System users.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8554</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 2.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /users.php. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 13:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1596 | Ninja Forms File Uploads &amp;lt;= 3.3.16 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1596</link><description>The Ninja Forms - File Uploads plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via an uploaded file (e.g. RTX file) in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.16 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 11:25:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6010 | Cost Calculator Builder PRO &amp;lt;= 3.1.96 -  Unauthenticated Price Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6010</link><description>The Cost Calculator Builder PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to price manipulation in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.96. This is due to the plugin allowing the price field to be manipulated prior to processing via the 'create_cc_order' function, called from the Cost Calculator Builder plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to manipulate the price of orders submitted via the calculator. Note: this vulnerability was partially patched with the release of Cost Calculator Builder version 3.2.17.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 11:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7112 | Pinpoint Booking System &amp;lt;= 2.9.9.5.0- Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7112</link><description>The Pinpoint Booking System – #1 WordPress Booking Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘schedule’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.9.5.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 11:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7620 | Customizer Export/Import &amp;lt;= 0.9.7 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Upload via Customization Settings Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7620</link><description>The Customizer Export/Import plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the '_import' function in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. NOTE: This vulnerability is only exploitable when used in conjunction with a race condition as the uploaded file is deleted shortly after it is created.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 11:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8523 | lmxcms SQL Command Execution Module admin.php formatData code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8523</link><description>A vulnerability was found in lmxcms up to 1.4 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formatData of the file /admin.php?m=Acquisi&amp;amp;a=testcj&amp;amp;lid=1 of the component SQL Command Execution Module. The manipulation of the argument data leads to code injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6849 | Preloader Plus – WordPress Loading Screen Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6849</link><description>The Preloader Plus – WordPress Loading Screen Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 08:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8538 | Big File Uploads &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8538</link><description>The Big File Uploads – Increase Maximum File Upload Size plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.2. This is due the plugin not sanitizing a file path in an error message. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 08:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8521 | Wavelog Live QSO qso index cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8521</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Wavelog up to 1.8.0. Affected is the function index of the file /qso of the component Live QSO. The manipulation of the argument manual leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.8.1 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as b31002cec6b71ab5f738881806bb546430ec692e. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45034 | Apache Airflow: Authenticated DAG authors could execute code on scheduler nodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45034</link><description>Apache Airflow versions before 2.10.1 have a vulnerability that allows DAG authors to add local settings to the DAG folder and get it executed by the scheduler, where the scheduler is not supposed to execute code submitted by the DAG author. 
Users are advised to upgrade to version 2.10.1 or later, which has fixed the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 07:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45498 | Apache Airflow: Command Injection in an example DAG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45498</link><description>Example DAG: example_inlet_event_extra.py shipped with Apache Airflow version 2.10.0 has a vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker with only DAG trigger permission to execute arbitrary commands. If you used that example as the base of your DAGs - please review if you have not copied the dangerous example; see  https://github.com/apache/airflow/pull/41873  for more information. We recommend against exposing the example DAGs in your deployment. If you must expose the example DAGs, upgrade Airflow to version 2.10.1 or later.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 07:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44838 | RapidCMS v1.3.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the username parameter at /resource/runlogin.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44838</link><description>RapidCMS v1.3.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the username parameter at /resource/runlogin.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 21:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44839 | RapidCMS v1.3.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the articleid parameter at /default/article.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44839</link><description>RapidCMS v1.3.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the articleid parameter at /default/article.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 21:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45771 | RapidCMS v1.3.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the password parameter at /resource/runlogin.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45771</link><description>RapidCMS v1.3.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the password parameter at /resource/runlogin.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 21:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44844 | DrayTek Vigor3900 v1.5.1.6 was discovered to contain an authenticated command injection vulnerability via the name parameter in the run_comm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44844</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 v1.5.1.6 was discovered to contain an authenticated command injection vulnerability via the name parameter in the run_command function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 21:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44845 | DrayTek Vigor3900 v1.5.1.6 was discovered to contain an authenticated command injection vulnerability via the value parameter in the filter_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44845</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 v1.5.1.6 was discovered to contain an authenticated command injection vulnerability via the value parameter in the filter_string function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 21:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34155 | Stack exhaustion in all Parse functions in go/parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34155</link><description>Calling any of the Parse functions on Go source code which contains deeply nested literals can cause a panic due to stack exhaustion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34156 | Stack exhaustion in Decoder.Decode in encoding/gob</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34156</link><description>Calling Decoder.Decode on a message which contains deeply nested structures can cause a panic due to stack exhaustion. This is a follow-up to CVE-2022-30635.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34158 | Stack exhaustion in Parse in go/build/constraint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34158</link><description>Calling Parse on a "// +build" build tag line with deeply nested expressions can cause a panic due to stack exhaustion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7652 | An error in the ECMA-262 specification relating to Async Generators could have resulted in a type confusion, potentially leading to memory c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7652</link><description>An error in the ECMA-262 specification relating to Async Generators could have resulted in a type confusion, potentially leading to memory corruption and an exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-27592 | QVR Smart Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27592</link><description>An unquoted search path or element vulnerability has been reported to affect QVR Smart Client. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow local authenticated administrators to execute unauthorized code or commands via unspecified vectors.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Windows 10 SP1, Windows 11, Mac OS, and Mac M1: QVR Smart Client 2.4.0.0570 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34974 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud, QVR, QES</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34974</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to execute commands via a network.
QuTScloud, QVR, QES are not affected.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 4.5.4.2790 build 20240605 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34979 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34979</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 4.5.4.2790 build 20240605 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2790 build 20240606 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39298 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39298</link><description>A missing authorization vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow local authenticated users to access data or perform actions that they should not be allowed to perform via unspecified vectors.
QuTScloud, is not affected.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.0.2737 build 20240417 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.0.2782 build 20240601 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39300 | QTS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39300</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect legacy QTS. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 4.3.6.2805 build 20240619 and later
QTS 4.3.4.2814 build 20240618 and later
QTS 4.3.3.2784 build 20240619 and later
QTS 4.2.6 build 20240618 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45038 | Music Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45038</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability has been reported to affect Music Station. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to compromise the security of the system via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Music Station 5.4.0 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47563 | Video Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47563</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect Video Station. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Video Station 5.8.2 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50360 | Video Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50360</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been reported to affect Video Station. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Video Station 5.8.1 ( 2024/02/26 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50366 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50366</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.6.2722 build 20240402 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.6.2734 build 20240414 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51366 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51366</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to read the contents of unexpected files and expose sensitive data via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.6.2722 build 20240402 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.6.2734 build 20240414 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51367 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51367</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.6.2722 build 20240402 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.6.2734 build 20240414 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51368 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51368</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.6.2722 build 20240402 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.6.2734 build 20240414 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21897 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21897</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.6.2722 build 20240402 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.6.2734 build 20240414 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21898 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21898</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to execute commands via a network.
We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.6.2722 build 20240402 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.6.2734 build 20240414 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21903 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21903</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.6.2722 build 20240402 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.6.2734 build 20240414 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21904 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21904</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to read the contents of unexpected files and expose sensitive data via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.7.2770 build 20240520 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.7.2770 build 20240520 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21906 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21906</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.8.2823 build 20240712 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.8.2823 build 20240712 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27122 | Notes Station 3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27122</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect Notes Station 3. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
Notes Station 3 3.9.6 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27125 | Helpdesk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27125</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect Helpdesk. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Helpdesk 3.3.1 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27126 | Notes Station 3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27126</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect Notes Station 3. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
Notes Station 3 3.9.6 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32762 | QuLog Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32762</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect QuLog Center. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QuLog Center 1.8.0.872 ( 2024/06/17 ) and later
QuLog Center 1.7.0.827 ( 2024/06/17 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32763 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32763</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.8.2823 build 20240712 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.8.2823 build 20240712 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32771 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32771</link><description>An improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow local network authenticated administrators to perform an arbitrary number of authentication attempts via unspecified vectors.
QuTScloud is not affected.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.0.2782 build 20240601 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.0.2782 build 20240601 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38640 | Download Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38640</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect Download Station. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Download Station 5.8.6.283 ( 2024/06/21 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38641 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38641</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow local network users to execute commands via unspecified vectors.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.8.2823 build 20240712 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.8.2823 build 20240712 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38642 | QuMagie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38642</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability has been reported to affect QuMagie. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow local network users to compromise the security of the system via unspecified vectors.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuMagie 2.3.1 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8394 | When aborting the verification of an OTR chat session, an attacker could have caused a use-after-free bug leading to a potentially exploitab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8394</link><description>When aborting the verification of an OTR chat session, an attacker could have caused a use-after-free bug leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 128.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44402 | D-Link DI-8100G 17.12.20A1 is vulnerable to Command Injection via msp_info.htm.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44402</link><description>D-Link DI-8100G 17.12.20A1 is vulnerable to Command Injection via msp_info.htm.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44408 | D-Link DIR-823G v1.0.2B05_20181207 is vulnerable to Information Disclosure. The device allows unauthorized configuration file downloads, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44408</link><description>D-Link DIR-823G v1.0.2B05_20181207 is vulnerable to Information Disclosure. The device allows unauthorized configuration file downloads, and the downloaded configuration files contain plaintext user passwords.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44401 | D-Link DI-8100G 17.12.20A1 is vulnerable to Command Injection via sub47A60C function in the upgrade_filter.asp file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44401</link><description>D-Link DI-8100G 17.12.20A1 is vulnerable to Command Injection via sub47A60C function in the upgrade_filter.asp file</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8517 | SPIP Bigup Multipart File Upload OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8517</link><description>SPIP before 4.3.2, 4.2.16, and 
4.1.18 is vulnerable to a command injection issue. A 
remote and unauthenticated attacker can execute arbitrary operating system commands by sending a crafted multipart file upload HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45294 | `org.hl7.fhir.core` XXE vulnerability in XSLT transforms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45294</link><description>The HL7 FHIR Core Artifacts repository provides the java core object handling code, with utilities (including validator), for the Fast Healthcare Interoperability Resources (FHIR) specification. Prior to version 6.3.23, XSLT transforms performed by various components are vulnerable to XML external entity injections. A processed XML file with a malicious DTD tag could produce XML containing data from the host system. This impacts use cases where org.hl7.fhir.core is being used to within a host where external clients can submit XML. This issue has been patched in release 6.3.23. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 15:57:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45758 | H2O.ai H2O through 3.46.0.4 allows attackers to arbitrarily set the JDBC URL, leading to deserialization attacks, file reads, and command ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45758</link><description>H2O.ai H2O through 3.46.0.4 allows attackers to arbitrarily set the JDBC URL, leading to deserialization attacks, file reads, and command execution. Exploitation can occur when an attacker has access to post to the ImportSQLTable URI with a JSON document containing a connection_url property with any typical JDBC Connection URL attack payload such as one that uses queryInterceptors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 15:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8509 | Migration toolkit for virtualization: forklift-controller: empty bearer token may perform authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8509</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Forklift Controller.  There is no verification against the authorization header except to ensure it uses bearer authentication. Without an Authorization header and some form of a Bearer token, a 401 error occurs. The presence of a token value provides a 200 response with the requested information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 15:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25584 | Dovecot accepts dot LF DOT LF symbol as end of DATA command. RFC requires that it should always be CR LF DOT CR LF. This causes Dovecot to c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25584</link><description>Dovecot accepts dot LF DOT LF symbol as end of DATA command. RFC requires that it should always be CR LF DOT CR LF. This causes Dovecot to convert single mail with LF DOT LF in middle, into two emails when relaying to SMTP. Dovecot will split mail with LF DOT LF into two mails. Upgrade to latest released version. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 15:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7493 | WPCOM Member &amp;lt;= 1.5.2.1 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via User Meta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7493</link><description>The WPCOM Member plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2.1. This is due to the plugin allowing arbitrary data to be passed to wp_insert_user() during registration. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update their role to that of an administrator during registration.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 14:07:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7599 | Advanced Sermons &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7599</link><description>The Advanced Sermons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘sermon_video_embed’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 14:07:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7611 | Enter Addons – Ultimate Template Builder for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Events Card Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7611</link><description>The Enter Addons – Ultimate Template Builder for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tag' attribute of the Events Card widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 14:07:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7622 | Revision Manager TMC &amp;lt;= 2.8.19 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Email Sending</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7622</link><description>The Revision Manager TMC plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary email sending due to a missing capability check on the _a_ajaxQuickEmailTestCallback() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.19. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to send emails with arbitrary content to any individual through the vulnerable web server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 14:07:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8428 | ForumWP – Forum &amp;amp; Discussion Board Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8428</link><description>The ForumWP – Forum &amp; Discussion Board Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation via Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.2 via the submit_form_handler due to missing validation on the 'user_id' user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to change the email address of administrative user accounts which can then be leveraged to reset the administrative users password and gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 14:07:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6445 | Authenticated Local File Inclusion (LFI) in DataFlowX&amp;#x27;s DataDiodeX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6445</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in DataFlowX Technology DataDiodeX allows Path Traversal.This issue affects DataDiodeX: before v3.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 13:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44837 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component \bean\Manager.java of Drug v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web script...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44837</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component \bean\Manager.java of Drug v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the user parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 13:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44739 | Sourcecodester Simple Forum Website v1.0 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /php-sqlite-forum/?page=manage_user&amp;id=.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44739</link><description>Sourcecodester Simple Forum Website v1.0 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /php-sqlite-forum/?page=manage_user&amp;amp;id=.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 13:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45299 | alf.io&amp;#x27;s preloaded data as json is not escaped correctly</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45299</link><description>alf.io is an open source ticket reservation system for conferences, trade shows, workshops, and meetups. Prior to version 2.0-M5, the preloaded data as json is not escaped correctly, the administrator / event admin could break their own install by inserting non correctly escaped text. The Content-Security-Policy directive blocks any potential script execution. The administrator or event administrator can override the texts for customization purpose. The texts are not properly escaped. Version 2.0-M5 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 13:28:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45300 | Bypassing promo code limitations with race conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45300</link><description>alf.io is an open source ticket reservation system for conferences, trade shows, workshops, and meetups. Prior to version 2.0-M5, a race condition allows the user to bypass the limit on the number of promo codes and use the discount coupon multiple times. In "alf.io", an event organizer can apply price discounts by using promo codes to your events. The organizer can limit the number of promo codes that will be used for this, but the time-gap between checking the number of codes and restricting the use of the codes allows a threat actor to bypass the promo code limit. Version 2.0-M5 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 13:28:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45405 | gix-path improperly resolves configuration path reported by Git</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45405</link><description>`gix-path` is a crate of the `gitoxide` project (an implementation of `git` written in Rust) dealing paths and their conversions. Prior to version 0.10.11, `gix-path` runs `git` to find the path of a configuration file associated with the `git` installation, but improperly resolves paths containing unusual or non-ASCII characters, in rare cases enabling a local attacker to inject configuration leading to code execution. Version 0.10.11 contains a patch for the issue.

In `gix_path::env`, the underlying implementation of the `installation_config` and `installation_config_prefix` functions calls `git config -l --show-origin` to find the path of a file to treat as belonging to the `git` installation. Affected versions of `gix-path` do not pass `-z`/`--null` to cause `git` to report literal paths. Instead, to cover the occasional case that `git` outputs a quoted path, they attempt to parse the path by stripping the quotation marks. The problem is that, when a path is quoted, it may change in substantial ways beyond the concatenation of quotation marks. If not reversed, these changes can result in another valid path that is not equivalent to the original.

On a single-user system, it is not possible to exploit this, unless `GIT_CONFIG_SYSTEM` and `GIT_CONFIG_GLOBAL` have been set to unusual values or Git has been installed in an unusual way. Such a scenario is not expected. Exploitation is unlikely even on a multi-user system, though it is plausible in some uncommon configurations or use cases. In general, exploitation is more likely to succeed if users are expected to install `git` themselves, and are likely to do so in predictable locations; locations where `git` is installed, whether due to usernames in their paths or otherwise, contain characters that `git` quotes by default in paths, such as non-English letters and accented letters; a custom `system`-scope configuration file is specified with the `GIT_CONFIG_SYSTEM` environment variable, and its path is in an unusual location or has strangely named components; or a `system`-scope configuration file is absent, empty, or suppressed by means other than `GIT_CONFIG_NOSYSTEM`. Currently, `gix-path` can treat a `global`-scope configuration file as belonging to the installation if no higher scope configuration file is available. This increases the likelihood of exploitation even on a system where `git` is installed system-wide in an ordinary way. However, exploitation is expected to be very difficult even under any combination of those factors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 13:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45039 | gnark&amp;#x27;s Groth16 commitment extension unsound for more than one commitment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45039</link><description>gnark is a fast zk-SNARK library that offers a high-level API to design circuits. Versions prior to 0.11.0 have a soundness issue - in case of multiple commitments used inside the circuit the prover is able to choose all but the last commitment. As gnark uses the commitments for optimized non-native multiplication, lookup checks etc. as random challenges, then it could impact the soundness of the whole circuit. However, using multiple commitments has been discouraged due to the additional cost to the verifier and it has not been supported in the recursive in-circuit Groth16 verifier and Solidity verifier. gnark's maintainers expect the impact of the issue be very small - only for the users who have implemented the native Groth16 verifier or are using it with multiple commitments. We do not have information of such users. The issue has been patched in version 0.11.0. As a workaround, users should follow gnark maintainers' recommendation to use only a single commitment and then derive in-circuit commitments as needed using the `std/multicommit` package.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 13:03:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45040 | gnark&amp;#x27;s commitments to private witnesses in Groth16 as implemented break zero-knowledge property</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45040</link><description>gnark is a fast zk-SNARK library that offers a high-level API to design circuits. Prior to version 0.11.0, commitments to private witnesses in Groth16 as implemented break the zero-knowledge property. The vulnerability affects only Groth16 proofs with commitments. Notably, PLONK proofs are not affected. The vulnerability affects the zero-knowledge property of the proofs - in case the witness (secret or internal) values are small, then the attacker may be able to enumerate all possible choices to deduce the actual value. If the possible choices for the variables to be committed is large or there are many values committed, then it would be computationally infeasible to enumerate all valid choices. It doesn't affect the completeness/soundness of the proofs. The vulnerability has been fixed in version 0.11.0. The patch to fix the issue is to add additional randomized value to the list of committed value at proving time to mask the rest of the values which were committed. As a workaround, the user can manually commit to a randomized value.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 13:03:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1744 | Information Disclosure in Ariva Computer&amp;#x27;s Accord ORS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1744</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Ariva Computer Accord ORS allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Accord ORS: before 7.3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 12:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52915 | media: dvb-usb-v2: af9035: Fix null-ptr-deref in af9035_i2c_master_xfer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52915</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: dvb-usb-v2: af9035: Fix null-ptr-deref in af9035_i2c_master_xfer

In af9035_i2c_master_xfer, msg is controlled by user. When msg[i].buf
is null and msg[i].len is zero, former checks on msg[i].buf would be
passed. Malicious data finally reach af9035_i2c_master_xfer. If accessing
msg[i].buf[0] without sanity check, null ptr deref would happen.
We add check on msg[i].len to prevent crash.

Similar commit:
commit 0ed554fd769a
("media: dvb-usb: az6027: fix null-ptr-deref in az6027_i2c_xfer()")</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 09:10:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52916 | media: aspeed: Fix memory overwrite if timing is 1600x900</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52916</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: aspeed: Fix memory overwrite if timing is 1600x900

When capturing 1600x900, system could crash when system memory usage is
tight.

The way to reproduce this issue:
1. Use 1600x900 to display on host
2. Mount ISO through 'Virtual media' on OpenBMC's web
3. Run script as below on host to do sha continuously
  #!/bin/bash
  while [ [1] ];
  do
	find /media -type f -printf '"%h/%f"\n' | xargs sha256sum
  done
4. Open KVM on OpenBMC's web

The size of macro block captured is 8x8. Therefore, we should make sure
the height of src-buf is 8 aligned to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 09:10:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7349 | LifterLMS &amp;lt;= 7.7.5 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7349</link><description>The LifterLMS – WP LMS for eLearning, Online Courses, &amp; Quizzes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to blind SQL Injection via the 'order' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 7.7.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 06:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8292 | WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp;amp; More &amp;lt;= 16.26.8 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Password Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8292</link><description>The WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation/account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 16.26.8. This is due to to plugin not properly verifying a user's identity during new order creation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to supply any email through the user_email field and update the password for that user during new order creation. This requires the commerce addon to be enabled in order to exploit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 06:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8317 | WP AdCenter – Ad Manager &amp;amp; Adsense Ads &amp;lt;= 2.5.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via ad_alignment Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8317</link><description>The WP AdCenter – Ad Manager &amp; Adsense Ads plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘ad_alignment’ attribute in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 06:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8427 | Frontend Post Submission Manager Lite – Frontend Posting WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8427</link><description>The Frontend Post Submission Manager Lite – Frontend Posting WordPress Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the save_global_settings and process_form_edit functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugin's settings and forms.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 06:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6792 | WP ULike &amp;lt; 4.7.2.1 - Subscriber+ Stored-XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6792</link><description>The WP ULike  WordPress plugin before 4.7.2.1 does not properly sanitize user display names when rendering on a public page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 06:16:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39585 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.5.4 through 10.5.5.10 and 10.5.6.x, contain(s) an Use of Hard-coded Password vulnerability. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39585</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.5.4 through 10.5.5.10 and 10.5.6.x, contain(s) an Use of Hard-coded Password vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Client-side request forgery and Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 04:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45751 | tgt (aka Linux target framework) before 1.0.93 attempts to achieve entropy by calling rand without srand. The PRNG seed is always 1, and thu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45751</link><description>tgt (aka Linux target framework) before 1.0.93 attempts to achieve entropy by calling rand without srand. The PRNG seed is always 1, and thus the sequence of challenges is always identical.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 04:35:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38486 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.5.4 through 10.5.5.10 and 10.5.6.x , contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elemen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38486</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, version(s) 10.5.5.4 through 10.5.5.10 and 10.5.6.x , contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 04:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7415 | Remember Me Controls &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7415</link><description>The Remember Me Controls plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1. This is due to the plugin allowing direct access to the bootstrap.php file which has display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 03:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8247 | Newsletters &amp;lt;= 4.9.9.2 - Authenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8247</link><description>The Newsletters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.9.2. This is due to the plugin not restricting what user meta can be updated as screen options. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to escalate their privileges to that of an administrator. Please note that this only affects users with access to edit/update screen options, which means an administrator would need to grant lower privilege users with access to the Sent &amp; Draft Emails page of the plugin in order for this to be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 03:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8480 | Image Optimizer, Resizer and CDN – Sirv &amp;lt;= 7.2.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8480</link><description>The Image Optimizer, Resizer and CDN – Sirv plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'sirv_save_prevented_sizes' function in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to exploit the 'sirv_upload_file_by_chunks_callback' function, which lacks proper file type validation, allowing attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 03:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40865 | The issue was addressed by suspending Persona when the virtual keyboard is active. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.3. Inputs to the virtua...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40865</link><description>The issue was addressed by suspending Persona when the virtual keyboard is active. This issue is fixed in visionOS 1.3. Inputs to the virtual keyboard may be inferred from Persona.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 01:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44082 | In OpenStack Ironic before 26.0.1 and ironic-python-agent before 9.13.1, there is a vulnerability in image processing, in which a crafted im...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44082</link><description>In OpenStack Ironic before 26.0.1 and ironic-python-agent before 9.13.1, there is a vulnerability in image processing, in which a crafted image could be used by an authenticated user to exploit undesired behaviors in qemu-img, including possible unauthorized access to potentially sensitive data. The affected/fixed version details are: Ironic: &lt;21.4.3, &gt;=22.0.0 &lt;23.0.2, &gt;=23.1.0 &lt;24.1.2, &gt;=25.0.0 &lt;26.0.1; Ironic-python-agent: &lt;9.4.2, &gt;=9.5.0 &lt;9.7.1, &gt;=9.8.0 &lt;9.11.1, &gt;=9.12.0 &lt;9.13.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 01:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>