<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 02:53:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-10340 | Shortcodes Blocks Creator Ultimate &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10340</link><description>The Shortcodes Blocks Creator Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'scu' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 2.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 02:53:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10810 | code-projects E-Health Care System app_request.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10810</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects E-Health Care System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file Doctor/app_request.php. The manipulation of the argument app_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 02:53:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10807 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System search.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10807</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file hms/doctor/search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 02:04:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10808 | code-projects E-Health Care System req_detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10808</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects E-Health Care System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file Admin/req_detail.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 02:04:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10809 | code-projects E-Health Care System chat.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10809</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects E-Health Care System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Doctor/chat.php. The manipulation of the argument name/message leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "name" to be affected. But it must be assumed that the parameter "message" is affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 02:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10806 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System betweendates-detailsreports.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10806</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file betweendates-detailsreports.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 02:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31998 | CSRF security issue on CSV import in Combodo iTop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31998</link><description>Combodo iTop is a simple, web based IT Service Management tool. A CSRF can be performed on CSV import simulation. This issue has been fixed in versions 3.1.2 and 3.2.0. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 23:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32870 | iTop hub connector Information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32870</link><description>Combodo iTop is a simple, web based IT Service Management tool. Server, OS, DBMS, PHP, and iTop info (name, version and parameters) can be read by anyone having access to iTop URI. This issue has been patched in versions 2.7.11, 3.0.5, 3.1.2, and 3.2.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 23:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34443 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in the run_query.php page in Combodo iTop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34443</link><description>Combodo iTop is a simple, web based IT Service Management tool. When displaying page Run queries Cross-site Scripting (XSS) are possible for scripts outside of script tags. This has been fixed in versions 2.7.9, 3.0.4, 3.1.0. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 23:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34444 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability on pages/ajax.searchform.php in Combodo iTop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34444</link><description>Combodo iTop is a simple, web based IT Service Management tool. When displaying pages/ajax.searchform.php XSS are possible for scripts outside of script tags. This issue has been fixed in versions 2.7.9, 3.0.4, 3.1.0. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 23:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34445 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability on pages/ajax.render.php in Combodo iTop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34445</link><description>Combodo iTop is a simple, web based IT Service Management tool. When displaying pages/ajax.render.php XSS are possible for scripts outside of script tags. This issue has been fixed in versions 2.7.9, 3.0.4, 3.1.0. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 23:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31448 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in link CSV import in Combodo iTop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31448</link><description>Combodo iTop is a simple, web based IT Service Management tool. By filling malicious code in a CSV content, an Cross-site Scripting (XSS) attack can be performed when importing this content. This issue has been fixed in versions 3.1.2 and 3.2.0. All users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should validate CSV content before importing it.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 23:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50346 | WebFeed HTML injection vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50346</link><description>WebFeed is a lightweight web feed reader extension for Firefox/Chrome. Multiple HTML injection vulnerabilities in WebFeed can lead to CSRF and UI spoofing attacks. A remote attacker can provide malicious RSS feeds and attract the victim user to visit it using WebFeed. The attacker can then inject malicious HTML into the extension page and fool the victim into sending out HTTP requests to arbitrary sites with the victim's credentials. Users are vulnerable to CSRF attacks when visiting malicious RSS feeds via WebFeed. Unwanted actions could be executed on the user's behalf on arbitrary websites. This issue has been addressed in release version 0.9.2. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 23:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51498 | [@imput/cobalt-web] Cross-site Scripting when downloading picker image from malicious instance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51498</link><description>cobalt is a media downloader that doesn't piss you off. A malicious cobalt instance could serve links with the `javascript:` protocol, resulting in Cross-site Scripting (XSS) when the user tries to download an item from a picker. This issue has been present since commit `66bac03e`, was mitigated in commit `97977efa` (correctly configured web instances were no longer vulnerable) and fully fixed in commit `c4be1d3a` (included in release version 10.2.1). Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should enable a content-security-policy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 23:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51500 | Failure to check for packets from the broadcast address allows potential DDoS amplification attack in Meshtastic firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51500</link><description>Meshtastic firmware is a device firmware for the Meshtastic project. The Meshtastic firmware does not check for packets claiming to be from the special broadcast address (0xFFFFFFFF) which could result in unexpected behavior and potential for DDoS attacks on the network. A malicious actor could craft a packet to be from that address which would result in an amplification of this one message into every node on the network sending multiple messages. Such an attack could result in degraded network performance for all users as the available bandwidth is consumed. This issue has been addressed in release version 2.5.6. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 23:10:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51501 | CRLF injection in Refit&amp;#x27;s [Header], [HeaderCollection] and [Authorize] attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51501</link><description>Refit is an automatic type-safe REST library for .NET Core, Xamarin and .NET The various header-related Refit attributes (Header, HeaderCollection and Authorize) are vulnerable to CRLF injection. The way HTTP headers are added to a request is via the `HttpHeaders.TryAddWithoutValidation` method. This method does not check for CRLF characters in the header value. This means that any headers added to a refit request are vulnerable to CRLF-injection. In general, CRLF-injection into a HTTP header (when using HTTP/1.1) means that one can inject additional HTTP headers or smuggle whole HTTP requests. If an application using the Refit library passes a user-controllable value through to a header, then that application becomes vulnerable to CRLF-injection. This is not necessarily a security issue for a command line application like the one above, but if such code were present in a web application then it becomes vulnerable to request splitting (as shown in the PoC) and thus Server Side Request Forgery. Strictly speaking this is a potential vulnerability in applications using Refit and not in Refit itself. This issue has been addressed in release version 8.0.0 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 23:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51502 | Panic Vulnerability in loona-hpack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51502</link><description>loona is an experimental, HTTP/1.1 and HTTP/2 implementation in Rust on top of io-uring. `loona-hpack` suffers from the same vulnerability as the original `hpack` as documented in issue #11. All users who try to decode untrusted input using the Decoder are vulnerable to this exploit. This issue has been addressed in release version 0.4.3. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 22:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48052 | In gradio &lt;=4.42.0, the gr.DownloadButton function has a hidden server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability. The reason is that within ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48052</link><description>In gradio &lt;=4.42.0, the gr.DownloadButton function has a hidden server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability. The reason is that within the save_url_to_cache function, there are no restrictions on the URL, which allows access to local target resources. This can lead to the download of local resources and sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 22:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48057 | localai &lt;=2.20.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). When calling the delete model API and passing inappropriate parameters, it can...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48057</link><description>localai &lt;=2.20.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). When calling the delete model API and passing inappropriate parameters, it can cause a one-time storage XSS, which will trigger the payload when a user accesses the homepage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 22:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10805 | code-projects University Event Management System doedit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10805</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects University Event Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file doedit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions a confusing product name to be affected. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 22:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48050 | In agentscope &lt;=v0.0.4, the file agentscope\web\workstation\workflow_utils.py has the function is_callable_expression. Within this function,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48050</link><description>In agentscope &lt;=v0.0.4, the file agentscope\web\workstation\workflow_utils.py has the function is_callable_expression. Within this function, the line result = eval(s) poses a security risk as it can directly execute user-provided commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 22:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48059 | gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt project, version &lt;=20240802 is vulnerable to stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in WebSocket session transmission....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48059</link><description>gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt project, version &lt;=20240802 is vulnerable to stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in WebSocket session transmission. An attacker can inject malicious content into a WebSocket message. When a victim accesses this session, the malicious JavaScript is executed in the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 22:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48061 | langflow &lt;=1.0.18 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) as any component provided the code functionality and the components run on th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48061</link><description>langflow &lt;=1.0.18 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) as any component provided the code functionality and the components run on the local machine rather than in a sandbox.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 22:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51734 | User data deletion by anoynmous users in Zope</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51734</link><description>Zope AccessControl provides a general security framework for use in Zope. In affected versions anonymous users can delete the user data maintained by an `AccessControl.userfolder.UserFolder` which may prevent any privileged access. This problem has been fixed in version 7.2. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may address the issue by adding `data__roles__ = ()` to `AccessControl.userfolder.UserFolder`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 22:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51744 | Bad documentation of error handling in ParseWithClaims can lead to potentially dangerous situations in golang-jwt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51744</link><description>golang-jwt is a Go implementation of JSON Web Tokens. Unclear documentation of the error behavior in `ParseWithClaims` can lead to situation where users are potentially not checking errors in the way they should be. Especially, if a token is both expired and invalid, the errors returned by `ParseWithClaims` return both error codes. If users only check for the `jwt.ErrTokenExpired ` using `error.Is`, they will ignore the embedded `jwt.ErrTokenSignatureInvalid` and thus potentially accept invalid tokens. A fix has been back-ported with the error handling logic from the `v5` branch to the `v4` branch. In this logic, the `ParseWithClaims` function will immediately return in "dangerous" situations (e.g., an invalid signature), limiting the combined errors only to situations where the signature is valid, but further validation failed (e.g., if the signature is valid, but is expired AND has the wrong audience). This fix is part of the 4.5.1 release. We are aware that this changes the behaviour of an established function and is not 100 % backwards compatible, so updating to 4.5.1 might break your code. In case you cannot update to 4.5.0, please make sure that you are properly checking for all errors ("dangerous" ones first), so that you are not running in the case detailed above.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 21:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48463 | Bruno before 1.29.1 uses Electron shell.openExternal without validation (of http or https) for opening windows within the Markdown docs view...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48463</link><description>Bruno before 1.29.1 uses Electron shell.openExternal without validation (of http or https) for opening windows within the Markdown docs viewer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 21:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10791 | Codezips Hospital Appointment System doctorAction.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10791</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Codezips Hospital Appointment System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /doctorAction.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions contradicting file and parameter names to be affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 19:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45086 | IBM WebSphere Application Server XML external entity injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45086</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 8.5 and 9.0 is vulnerable to an XML external entity injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A privileged user could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 19:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45185 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45185</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, 9110, W920, W930, Modem 5123, Modem 5300. There is an out-of-bounds write due to a heap overflow in the GPRS protocol.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 19:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30617 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Chamilo LMS 1.11.26 "/main/social/home.php," allows attackers to initiate a request tha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30617</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Chamilo LMS 1.11.26 "/main/social/home.php," allows attackers to initiate a request that posts a fake post onto the user's social wall without their consent or knowledge.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 19:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30619 | Chamilo LMS Version 1.11.26 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. A non-authenticated attacker can request the number of messages and t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30619</link><description>Chamilo LMS Version 1.11.26 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. A non-authenticated attacker can request the number of messages and the number of online users via "/main/inc/ajax/message.ajax.php?a=get_count_message" AND "/main/inc/ajax/online.ajax.php?a=get_users_online."</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 19:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30616 | Chamilo LMS 1.11.26 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control via main/auth/profile. Non-admin users can manipulate sensitive profiles infor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30616</link><description>Chamilo LMS 1.11.26 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control via main/auth/profile. Non-admin users can manipulate sensitive profiles information, posing a significant risk to data integrity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 19:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30618 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Chamilo LMS 1.11.26 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in a web b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30618</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Chamilo LMS 1.11.26 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in a web browser by including a malicious payload in the 'content' parameter of 'group_topics.php'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 19:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10768 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal two_tables.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10768</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/assets/plugins/DataTables/media/unit_testing/templates/two_tables.php. The manipulation of the argument scripts leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 18:46:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34885 | Insufficiently protected credentials in SMTP server settings in 1C-Bitrix Bitrix24 23.300.100 allows remote administrators to read SMTP acco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34885</link><description>Insufficiently protected credentials in SMTP server settings in 1C-Bitrix Bitrix24 23.300.100 allows remote administrators to read SMTP accounts passwords via HTTP GET request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 18:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34891 | Insufficiently protected credentials in DAV server settings in 1C-Bitrix Bitrix24 23.300.100 allows remote administrators to read Exchange a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34891</link><description>Insufficiently protected credentials in DAV server settings in 1C-Bitrix Bitrix24 23.300.100 allows remote administrators to read Exchange account passwords via HTTP GET request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 18:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34882 | Insufficiently protected credentials in SMTP server settings in 1C-Bitrix Bitrix24 23.300.100 allows remote administrators to send SMTP acco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34882</link><description>Insufficiently protected credentials in SMTP server settings in 1C-Bitrix Bitrix24 23.300.100 allows remote administrators to send SMTP account passwords to an arbitrary server via HTTP POST request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 18:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34883 | Insufficiently protected credentials in DAV server settings in 1C-Bitrix Bitrix24 23.300.100 allow remote administrators to read proxy-serve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34883</link><description>Insufficiently protected credentials in DAV server settings in 1C-Bitrix Bitrix24 23.300.100 allow remote administrators to read proxy-server accounts passwords via HTTP GET request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 18:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34887 | Insufficiently protected credentials in AD/LDAP server settings in 1C-Bitrix Bitrix24 23.300.100 allows remote administrators to send AD/LDA...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34887</link><description>Insufficiently protected credentials in AD/LDAP server settings in 1C-Bitrix Bitrix24 23.300.100 allows remote administrators to send AD/LDAP administrators account passwords to an arbitrary server via HTTP POST request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 18:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51329 | A Host header injection vulnerability in Agile-Board 1.0 allows attackers to obtain the password reset token via user interaction with a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51329</link><description>A Host header injection vulnerability in Agile-Board 1.0 allows attackers to obtain the password reset token via user interaction with a crafted password reset link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 18:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51326 | SQL Injection vulnerability in projectworlds Travel management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the 't2' ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51326</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in projectworlds Travel management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the 't2' parameter in deletesubcategory.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 17:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51327 | SQL Injection in loginform.php in ProjectWorld's Travel Management System v1.0 allows remote attackers to bypass authentication via SQL Inje...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51327</link><description>SQL Injection in loginform.php in ProjectWorld's Travel Management System v1.0 allows remote attackers to bypass authentication via SQL Injection in the 'username' and 'password' fields.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 17:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10766 | Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System save_user.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10766</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /pages/save_user.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher disclosure contains confusing vulnerability classes and file names.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 17:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48336 | The install() function of ProviderInstaller.java in Magisk App before canary version 27007 does not verify the GMS app before loading it, wh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48336</link><description>The install() function of ProviderInstaller.java in Magisk App before canary version 27007 does not verify the GMS app before loading it, which allows a local untrusted app with no additional privileges to silently execute arbitrary code in the Magisk app and escalate privileges to root via a crafted package, aka Bug #8279. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 17:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51328 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in addcategory.php in projectworld's Travel Management System v1.0 allows remote attacker to inject arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51328</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in addcategory.php in projectworld's Travel Management System v1.0 allows remote attacker to inject arbitrary code via the t2 parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 17:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51127 | An issue in the createTempFile method of hornetq v2.4.9 allows attackers to arbitrarily overwrite files or access sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51127</link><description>An issue in the createTempFile method of hornetq v2.4.9 allows attackers to arbitrarily overwrite files or access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 17:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51136 | An XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in Dmoz2CSV in openimaj v1.3.10 allows attackers to access sensitive information or execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51136</link><description>An XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in Dmoz2CSV in openimaj v1.3.10 allows attackers to access sensitive information or execute arbitrary code via supplying a crafted XML file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 17:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48809 | An issue in Open Networking Foundations sdran-in-a-box v.1.4.3 and onos-a1t v.0.2.3 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48809</link><description>An issue in Open Networking Foundations sdran-in-a-box v.1.4.3 and onos-a1t v.0.2.3 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the onos-a1t component of the sdran-in-a-box, specifically the DeleteWatcher function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 17:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10764 | Codezips Online Institute Management System save_user.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10764</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Codezips Online Institute Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /pages/save_user.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10765 | Codezips Online Institute Management System profile.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10765</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Codezips Online Institute Management System up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /profile.php. The manipulation of the argument old_image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45888 | DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a command injection vulnerability. This vulnerability occurs when the `action` parameter in `cgi-bin/main...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45888</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a command injection vulnerability. This vulnerability occurs when the `action` parameter in `cgi-bin/mainfunction.cgi` is set to `set_ap_map_config.'</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45893 | DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a post-authentication command injection vulnerability. This vulnerability occurs when the `action` parame...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45893</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a post-authentication command injection vulnerability. This vulnerability occurs when the `action` parameter in `cgi-bin/mainfunction.cgi` is set to `setSWMOption.`</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45882 | DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a command injection vulnerability. This vulnerability occurs when the `action` parameter in `cgi-bin/main...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45882</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a command injection vulnerability. This vulnerability occurs when the `action` parameter in `cgi-bin/mainfunction.cgi` is set to `delete_map_profile.`</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45884 | DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a post-authentication command injection vulnerability. This vulnerability occurs when the `action` parame...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45884</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a post-authentication command injection vulnerability. This vulnerability occurs when the `action` parameter in `cgi-bin/mainfunction.cgi` is set to `setSWMGroup.`</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45885 | DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a post-authentication command injection vulnerability. This vulnerability occurs when the `action` parame...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45885</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a post-authentication command injection vulnerability. This vulnerability occurs when the `action` parameter in `cgi-bin/mainfunction.cgi` is set to `autodiscovery_clear.`</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45891 | DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a post-authentication command injection vulnerability. This vulnerability occurs when the `action` parame...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45891</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a post-authentication command injection vulnerability. This vulnerability occurs when the `action` parameter in `cgi-bin/mainfunction.cgi` is set to `delete_wlan_profile.`</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45887 | DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a post-authentication command injection vulnerability. This vulnerability occurs when the `action` parame...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45887</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a post-authentication command injection vulnerability. This vulnerability occurs when the `action` parameter in `cgi-bin/mainfunction.cgi` is set to `doOpenVPN.`</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45889 | DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a post-authentication command injection vulnerability. This vulnerability occurs when the `action` parame...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45889</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a post-authentication command injection vulnerability. This vulnerability occurs when the `action` parameter in `cgi-bin/mainfunction.cgi` is set to `commandTable.`</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45890 | DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a post-authentication command injection vulnerability This vulnerability occurs when the `action` paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45890</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 contains a post-authentication command injection vulnerability This vulnerability occurs when the `action` parameter in `cgi-bin/mainfunction.cgi` is set to `download_ovpn.`</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51626 | WordPress Woocommerce Quote Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51626</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Mansur Ahamed Woocommerce Quote Calculator allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Woocommerce Quote Calculator: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51677 | WordPress Knowledge Base plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51677</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WebberZone Knowledge Base allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Knowledge Base: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51678 | WordPress Elo Rating Shortcode plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51678</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Marcel Pol Elo Rating Shortcode allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Elo Rating Shortcode: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51680 | WordPress Cresta Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51680</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CrestaProject – Rizzo Andrea Cresta Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Cresta Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51681 | WordPress WP Pocket URLs plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51681</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodeRevolution WP Pocket URLs allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Pocket URLs: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51682 | WordPress HT Builder – WordPress Theme Builder for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51682</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HasThemes HT Builder – WordPress Theme Builder for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects HT Builder – WordPress Theme Builder for Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51683 | WordPress Custom post type templates for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10.1 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51683</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Michael Gangolf Custom post type templates for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Custom post type templates for Elementor: from n/a through 1.10.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51685 | WordPress Accordion title for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51685</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Michael Gangolf Accordion title for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Accordion title for Elementor: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50528 | WordPress Stacks Mobile App Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.3 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50528</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Stacks Stacks Mobile App Builder allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Stacks Mobile App Builder: from n/a through 5.2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51672 | WordPress BetterLinks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.7 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51672</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WPDeveloper BetterLinks allows SQL Injection.This issue affects BetterLinks: from n/a through 2.1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50523 | WordPress All Post Contact Form plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50523</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in RainbowLink Inc. All Post Contact Form allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects All Post Contact Form: from n/a through 1.7.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50525 | WordPress Helloprint plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50525</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Helloprint Plug your WooCommerce into the largest catalog of customized print products from Helloprint allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Plug your WooCommerce into the largest catalog of customized print products from Helloprint: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:58:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50526 | WordPress Multi Purpose Mail Form plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50526</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in mahlamusa Multi Purpose Mail Form allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Multi Purpose Mail Form: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:58:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50527 | WordPress Stacks Mobile App Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.3 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50527</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Stacks Stacks Mobile App Builder allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Stacks Mobile App Builder: from n/a through 5.2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50529 | WordPress Training – Courses plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50529</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Rudra Innnovative Software Training – Courses allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Training – Courses: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50530 | WordPress Stars SMTP Mailer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50530</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Myriad Solutionz Stars SMTP Mailer allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Stars SMTP Mailer: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50531 | WordPress RSVPMaker for Toastmasters plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2.4 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50531</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in David F. Carr RSVPMaker for Toastmasters allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects RSVPMaker for Toastmasters: from n/a through 6.2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51408 | AppSmith Community 1.8.3 before 1.46 allows SSRF via New DataSource for application/json requests to 169.254.169.254 to retrieve AWS metadat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51408</link><description>AppSmith Community 1.8.3 before 1.46 allows SSRF via New DataSource for application/json requests to 169.254.169.254 to retrieve AWS metadata credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51582 | WordPress WP Hotel Booking plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51582</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in ThimPress WP Hotel Booking allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects WP Hotel Booking: from n/a through 2.1.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51665 | WordPress Magical Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51665</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Noor alam Magical Addons For Elementor allows Server Side Request Forgery.This issue affects Magical Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45164 | Akamai SIA (Secure Internet Access Enterprise) ThreatAvert, in SPS (Security and Personalization Services) before the latest 19.2.0 patch an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45164</link><description>Akamai SIA (Secure Internet Access Enterprise) ThreatAvert, in SPS (Security and Personalization Services) before the latest 19.2.0 patch and Apps Portal before 19.2.0.3 or 19.2.0.20240814, has incorrect authorization controls for the Admin functionality on the ThreatAvert Policy page. An authenticated user can navigate directly to the /#app/intelligence/threatAvertPolicies URI and disable policy enforcement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51249 | In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51249</link><description>In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the reboot function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51251 | In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the ba...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51251</link><description>In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the backup function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51246 | In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the do...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51246</link><description>In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the doPPTP function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51253 | In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the do...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51253</link><description>In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the doL2TP function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10035 | Code Injection in BG-TEK&amp;#x27;s CoslatV3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10035</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in BG-TEK Informatics Security Technologies CoslatV3 allows Command Injection.This issue affects CoslatV3: through 3.1069. 



NOTE: The vendor was contacted and it was learned that the product is not supported.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 12:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36485 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36485</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions 8121 and prior are vulnerable to SQL Injection in Technician reports option.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 11:28:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51661 | WordPress Media Library Assistant plugin &amp;lt;= 3.19 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51661</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in David Lingren Media Library Assistant allows Command Injection.This issue affects Media Library Assistant: from n/a through 3.19.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 11:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48878 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48878</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADManager Plus versions 7241 and prior are vulnerable to SQL Injection in Archived Audit Report.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 11:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10389 | Path Traversal in Safearchive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10389</link><description>There exists a Path Traversal vulnerability in Safearchive on Platforms with Case-Insensitive Filesystems (e.g., NTFS). This allows Attackers to Write Arbitrary Files via Archive Extraction containing symbolic links. We recommend upgrading past commit f7ce9d7b6f9c6ecd72d0b0f16216b046e55e44dc</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23377 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in ComputerVision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23377</link><description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTL command from user-space, when a user modifies the original packet size of the command after system properties have been already sent to the EVA driver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23385 | Reachable Assertion in Modem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23385</link><description>Transient DOS as modem reset occurs when an unexpected MAC RAR (with invalid PDU length) is seen at UE.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23386 | Improper Input Validation in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23386</link><description>memory corruption when WiFi display APIs are invoked with large random inputs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33029 | Use After Free in DSP Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33029</link><description>Memory corruption while handling the PDR in driver for getting the remote heap maps.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33030 | Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in Performance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33030</link><description>Memory corruption while parsing IPC frequency table parameters for LPLH that has size greater than expected size.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33031 | Improper Input Validation in RIL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33031</link><description>Memory corruption while processing the update SIM PB records request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33032 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Camera_Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33032</link><description>Memory corruption when the user application modifies the same shared memory asynchronously when kernel is accessing it.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33033 | Use After Free in ComputerVision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33033</link><description>Memory corruption while processing IOCTL calls to unmap the buffers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33068 | Use After Free in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33068</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing fragments of MBSSID IE from beacon frame.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38403 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38403</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing BTM ML IE when per STA profile is not included.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38405 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38405</link><description>Transient DOS while processing the CU information from RNR IE.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38406 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38406</link><description>Memory corruption while handling IOCTL calls in JPEG Encoder driver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38407 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38407</link><description>Memory corruption while processing input parameters for any IOCTL call in the JPEG Encoder driver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38408 | Cryptographic Issues in BT Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38408</link><description>Cryptographic issue when a controller receives an LMP start encryption command under unexpected conditions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38409 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in WLAN Windows Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38409</link><description>Memory corruption while station LL statistic handling.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38410 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow in WLAN Windows Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38410</link><description>Memory corruption while IOCLT is called when device is in invalid state and the WMI command buffer may be freed twice.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38415 | Use After Free in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38415</link><description>Memory corruption while handling session errors from firmware.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38419 | Use After Free in Automotive GPU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38419</link><description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTL calls from the use-space for HGSL memory node.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38421 | Use After Free in Graphics Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38421</link><description>Memory corruption while processing GPU commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38422 | Integer Overflow to Buffer Overflow in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38422</link><description>Memory corruption while processing voice packet with arbitrary data received from ADSP.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38423 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Graphics Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38423</link><description>Memory corruption while processing GPU page table switch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38424 | Use After Free in GPS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38424</link><description>Memory corruption during GNSS HAL process initialization.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23590 | Apache Kylin: Session fixation in web interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23590</link><description>Session Fixation vulnerability in Apache Kylin.

This issue affects Apache Kylin: from 2.0.0 through 4.x.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 5.0.0 or above, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 09:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48342 | Redis 2.60 through 7.41 allows a denial of service (memory consumption) when authentication is enabled because "client-output-buffer-limit n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48342</link><description>Redis 2.60 through 7.41 allows a denial of service (memory consumption) when authentication is enabled because "client-output-buffer-limit normal" has no limit, and an attacker can send requests without a password (which results in a "NOAUTH Authentication required" response). NOTE: this is disputed by third parties because Redis is not intended for use with untrusted clients.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 06:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10761 | Umbraco CMS Dashboard frame cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10761</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Umbraco CMS 12.3.6. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /Umbraco/preview/frame?id{} of the component Dashboard. The manipulation of the argument culture leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 05:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10760 | code-projects University Event Management System dodelete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10760</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects University Event Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /dodelete.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 04:47:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10759 | itsourcecode Farm Management System edit-pig.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10759</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Farm Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /edit-pig.php. The manipulation of the argument pigno/weight/arrived/breed/remark/status leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "pigno" to be affected. But it must be assumed that other parameters are affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 04:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10758 | code-projects/anirbandutta9 Content Management System/News-Buzz index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10758</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects/anirbandutta9 Content Management System and News-Buzz 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument user_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is distributed under two entirely different names.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 03:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10756 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal html_table.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10756</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/assets/plugins/DataTables/media/unit_testing/templates/html_table.php. The manipulation of the argument scripts leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 03:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10757 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal js_data.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10757</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/assets/plugins/DataTables/media/unit_testing/templates/js_data.php. The manipulation of the argument scripts leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 03:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10754 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal dymanic_table.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10754</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/assets/plugins/DataTables/media/unit_testing/templates/dymanic_table.php. The manipulation of the argument scripts leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10755 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal empty_table.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10755</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/assets/plugins/DataTables/media/unit_testing/templates/empty_table.php. The manipulation of the argument scripts leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10753 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal dom_data_two_headers.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10753</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file admin/assets/plugins/DataTables/media/unit_testing/templates/dom_data_two_headers.php. The manipulation of the argument scripts leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20104 | In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no addit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20104</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09073261; Issue ID: MSV-1772.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20106 | In m4u, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20106</link><description>In m4u, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08960505; Issue ID: MSV-1590.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20107 | In da, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20107</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09124360; Issue ID: MSV-1823.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20108 | In atci, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20108</link><description>In atci, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09082988; Issue ID: MSV-1774.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20109 | In ccu, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20109</link><description>In ccu, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09065928; Issue ID: MSV-1763.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20110 | In ccu, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20110</link><description>In ccu, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09065887; Issue ID: MSV-1762.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20111 | In ccu, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20111</link><description>In ccu, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09065033; Issue ID: MSV-1754.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20112 | In isp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20112</link><description>In isp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09071481; Issue ID: MSV-1730.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20113 | In ccu, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20113</link><description>In ccu, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09036814; Issue ID: MSV-1715.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20114 | In ccu, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20114</link><description>In ccu, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09037038; Issue ID: MSV-1714.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20115 | In ccu, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20115</link><description>In ccu, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09036695; Issue ID: MSV-1713.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20117 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper structure design. This could lead to local information disclosure with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20117</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper structure design. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09008925; Issue ID: MSV-1681.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20118 | In mms, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Syst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20118</link><description>In mms, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09062392; Issue ID: MSV-1621.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20119 | In mms, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Syst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20119</link><description>In mms, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09062301; Issue ID: MSV-1620.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20120 | In KeyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20120</link><description>In KeyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08956986; Issue ID: MSV-1575.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20121 | In KeyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20121</link><description>In KeyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08956986; Issue ID: MSV-1574.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20122 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper structure design. This could lead to local information disclosure with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20122</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper structure design. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09008925; Issue ID: MSV-1572.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20123 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper structure design. This could lead to local information disclosure with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20123</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper structure design. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09008925; Issue ID: MSV-1569.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20124 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper structure design. This could lead to local information disclosure with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20124</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper structure design. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09008925; Issue ID: MSV-1568.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 02:50:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10750 | Tenda i22 SysToo websReadEvent null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10750</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda i22 1.0.0.3(4687) and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function websReadEvent of the file /goform/GetIPTV?fgHPOST/goform/SysToo. The manipulation of the argument Content-Length leads to null pointer dereference. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 01:53:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10751 | Codezips ISP Management System pay.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10751</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips ISP Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file pay.php. The manipulation of the argument customer leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 01:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10752 | Codezips Pet Shop Management System productsadd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10752</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Pet Shop Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /productsadd.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions contradicting file names to be affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 01:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10748 | Cosmote Greece What&amp;#x27;s Up App Realm Database RealmDB.java default key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10748</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Cosmote Greece What's Up App 4.47.3 on Android. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file gr/desquared/kmmsharedmodule/db/RealmDB.java of the component Realm Database Handler. The manipulation of the argument defaultRealmKey leads to use of default cryptographic key. Local access is required to approach this attack. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 01:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10749 | ThinkAdmin Plugs.php script deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10749</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in ThinkAdmin up to 6.1.67. Affected is the function script of the file /app/admin/controller/api/Plugs.php. The manipulation of the argument uptoken leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 01:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10747 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal dom_data_th.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10747</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/assets/plugins/DataTables/media/unit_testing/templates/dom_data_th.php. The manipulation of the argument scripts leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 01:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10746 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal dom_data.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10746</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/assets/plugins/DataTables/media/unit_testing/templates/dom_data.php. The manipulation of the argument scripts leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 23:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10745 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal deferred_table.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10745</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/assets/plugins/DataTables/media/unit_testing/templates/deferred_table.php. The manipulation of the argument scripts leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 23:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10744 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal complex_header_2.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10744</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/assets/plugins/DataTables/media/unit_testing/templates/complex_header_2.php. The manipulation of the argument scripts leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 22:32:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10743 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal editable_ajax.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10743</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /shopping/admin/assets/plugins/DataTables/examples/examples_support/editable_ajax.php. The manipulation of the argument value leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 21:43:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10742 | code-projects Wazifa System control.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10742</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Wazifa System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /controllers/control.php. The manipulation of the argument to leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 21:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10741 | code-projects E-Health Care System registration.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10741</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects E-Health Care System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Users/registration.php. The manipulation of the argument f_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 20:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10740 | code-projects E-Health Care System consulting_detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10740</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects E-Health Care System up to 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /Admin/consulting_detail.php. The manipulation of the argument consulting_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 19:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10739 | code-projects E-Health Care System adminlogin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10739</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects E-Health Care System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Admin/adminlogin.php. The manipulation of the argument email/admin_pswd as part of String leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "email" to be affected. But it must be assumed that parameter "admin_pswd" is affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 17:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10738 | itsourcecode Farm Management System manage-breed.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10738</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Farm Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file manage-breed.php. The manipulation of the argument breed leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 17:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10737 | Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System teacher.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10737</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /teacher.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 15:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10736 | Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10736</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /student.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 14:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10735 | Project Worlds Life Insurance Management System editNominee.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10735</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Project Worlds Life Insurance Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /editNominee.php. The manipulation of the argument nominee_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 14:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10734 | Project Worlds Life Insurance Management System editPayment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10734</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Project Worlds Life Insurance Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /editPayment.php. The manipulation of the argument recipt_no leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 13:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10733 | code-projects Restaurant Order System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10733</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Restaurant Order System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument uid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 12:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10732 | Tongda OA 2017 index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10732</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.10 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /module/word_model/view/index.php. The manipulation of the argument query_str leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 11:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10731 | Tongda OA check_seal.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10731</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tongda OA up to 11.10. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pda/appcenter/check_seal.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 10:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10730 | Tongda OA web_show.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10730</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tongda OA up to 11.6. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /pda/appcenter/web_show.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 08:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>