<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:30:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-39926 | An issue was discovered in Vaultwarden (formerly Bitwarden_RS) 1.30.3. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) or, due to the default CSP, HTML ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39926</link><description>An issue was discovered in Vaultwarden (formerly Bitwarden_RS) 1.30.3. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) or, due to the default CSP, HTML injection vulnerability has been discovered in the admin dashboard. This potentially allows an authenticated attacker to inject malicious code into the dashboard, which is then executed or rendered in the context of an administrator's browser when viewing the injected content. However, it is important to note that the default Content Security Policy (CSP) of the application blocks most exploitation paths, significantly mitigating the potential impact.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3100 | A potential buffer overflow vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Notebook products that could allow a local attacker with elevated priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3100</link><description>A potential buffer overflow vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Notebook products that could allow a local attacker with elevated privileges to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45101 | A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered when Single Sign On (SSO) is enabled that could allow an attacker to intercept a valid, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45101</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered when Single Sign On (SSO) is enabled that could allow an attacker to intercept a valid, authenticated LXCA user’s XCC session if they can convince the user to click on a specially crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45103 | A valid, authenticated LXCA user may be able to unmanage an LXCA managed device in through the LXCA web interface without sufficient privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45103</link><description>A valid, authenticated LXCA user may be able to unmanage an LXCA managed device in through the LXCA web interface without sufficient privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45104 | A valid, authenticated LXCA user without sufficient privileges may be able to use the device identifier to modify an LXCA managed device thr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45104</link><description>A valid, authenticated LXCA user without sufficient privileges may be able to use the device identifier to modify an LXCA managed device through a specially crafted web API call.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45105 | An internal product security audit discovered a UEFI SMM (System Management Mode) callout vulnerability in some ThinkSystem servers that cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45105</link><description>An internal product security audit discovered a UEFI SMM (System Management Mode) callout vulnerability in some ThinkSystem servers that could allow a local attacker with elevated privileges to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4550 | A potential buffer overflow vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo ThinkSystem and ThinkStation products that could allow a local attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4550</link><description>A potential buffer overflow vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo ThinkSystem and ThinkStation products that could allow a local attacker with elevated privileges to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7756 | A potential vulnerability was reported in the ThinkPad L390 Yoga and 10w Notebook that could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7756</link><description>A potential vulnerability was reported in the ThinkPad L390 Yoga and 10w Notebook that could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges by accessing an embedded UEFI shell.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8059 | IPMI credentials may be captured in XCC audit log entries when the account username length is 16 characters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8059</link><description>IPMI credentials may be captured in XCC audit log entries when the account username length is 16 characters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8278 | A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in XCC that could allow a valid, authenticated XCC user with elevated privileges to perf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8278</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in XCC that could allow a valid, authenticated XCC user with elevated privileges to perform command injection via specially crafted IPMI commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8279 | A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in XCC that could allow a valid, authenticated XCC user with elevated privileges to perf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8279</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in XCC that could allow a valid, authenticated XCC user with elevated privileges to perform command injection via specially crafted file uploads.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8280 | An input validation weakness was discovered in XCC that could allow a valid, authenticated XCC user with elevated privileges to perform comm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8280</link><description>An input validation weakness was discovered in XCC that could allow a valid, authenticated XCC user with elevated privileges to perform command injection or cause a recoverable denial of service using a specially crafted file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8281 | An input validation weakness was discovered in XCC that could allow a valid, authenticated XCC user with elevated privileges to perform comm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8281</link><description>An input validation weakness was discovered in XCC that could allow a valid, authenticated XCC user with elevated privileges to perform command injection through specially crafted command line input in the XCC SSH captive shell.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39924 | An issue was discovered in Vaultwarden (formerly Bitwarden_RS) 1.30.3. A vulnerability has been identified in the authentication and authori...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39924</link><description>An issue was discovered in Vaultwarden (formerly Bitwarden_RS) 1.30.3. A vulnerability has been identified in the authentication and authorization process of the endpoint responsible for altering the metadata of an emergency access. It permits an attacker with granted emergency access to escalate their privileges by changing the access level and modifying the wait time. Consequently, the attacker can gain full control over the vault (when only intended to have read access) while bypassing the necessary wait period.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39925 | An issue was discovered in Vaultwarden (formerly Bitwarden_RS) 1.30.3. It lacks an offboarding process for members who leave an organization...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39925</link><description>An issue was discovered in Vaultwarden (formerly Bitwarden_RS) 1.30.3. It lacks an offboarding process for members who leave an organization. As a result, the shared organization key is not rotated when a member departs. Consequently, the departing member, whose access should be revoked, retains a copy of the organization key. Additionally, the application fails to adequately protect some encrypted data stored on the server. Consequently, an authenticated user could gain unauthorized access to encrypted data of any organization, even if the user is not a member of the targeted organization. However, the user would need to know the corresponding organizationId. Hence, if a user (whose access to an organization has been revoked) already possesses the organization key, that user could use the key to decrypt the leaked data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 17:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31414 | The Eaton Foreseer software provides users the capability to customize the dashboard in WebView pages. However, the input fields for this fe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31414</link><description>The Eaton Foreseer software provides users the capability to customize the dashboard in WebView pages. However, the input fields for this feature in the Eaton Foreseer software lacked proper input sanitization on the server-side, which could lead to injection and execution of malicious scripts when abused by bad actors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31415 | The Eaton Foreseer software provides the feasibility for the user to configure external servers for multiple purposes such as network manage...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31415</link><description>The Eaton Foreseer software provides the feasibility for the user to configure external servers for multiple purposes such as network management, user management, etc. The software uses encryption to store these configurations securely on the host machine. However, the keys used for this encryption were insecurely stored, which could be abused to possibly change or remove the server configuration.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31416 | The Eaton Foreseer software provides multiple customizable input fields for the users to configure parameters in the tool like alarms, repor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31416</link><description>The Eaton Foreseer software provides multiple customizable input fields for the users to configure parameters in the tool like alarms, reports, etc. Some of these input fields were not checking the length and bounds of the entered value. The exploit of this security flaw by a bad actor may result in excessive memory consumption or integer overflow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45368 | AutomationDirect DirectLogic H2-DM1E Session Fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45368</link><description>The H2-DM1E PLC's authentication protocol appears to utilize either a custom encoding scheme or a challenge-response protocol. However, there's an observed anomaly in the H2-DM1E PLC's protocol execution, namely its acceptance of multiple distinct packets as valid authentication responses. This behavior deviates from standard security practices where a single, specific response or encoding pattern is expected for successful authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43099 | AutomationDirect DirectLogic H2-DM1E Authentication Bypass by Capture-replay</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43099</link><description>The session hijacking attack targets the application layer's control mechanism, which manages authenticated sessions between a host PC and a PLC. During such sessions, a session key is utilized to maintain security. However, if an attacker captures this session key, they can inject traffic into an ongoing authenticated session. To successfully achieve this, the attacker also needs to spoof both the IP address and MAC address of the originating host which is typical of a session-based attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6087 | Improper Access Control in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6087</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability exists in lunary-ai/lunary at the latest commit (a761d83) on the main branch. The vulnerability allows an attacker to use the auth tokens issued by the 'invite user' functionality to obtain valid JWT tokens. These tokens can be used to compromise target users upon registration for their own arbitrary organizations. The attacker can invite a target email, obtain a one-time use token, retract the invite, and later use the token to reset the password of the target user, leading to full account takeover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6582 | Broken Access Control in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6582</link><description>A broken access control vulnerability exists in the latest version of lunary-ai/lunary. The `saml.ts` file allows a user from one organization to update the Identity Provider (IDP) settings and view the SSO metadata of another organization. This vulnerability can lead to unauthorized access and potential account takeover if the email of a user in the target organization is known.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6862 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6862</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in lunary-ai/lunary version 1.2.34 due to overly permissive CORS settings. This vulnerability allows an attacker to sign up for and create projects or use the instance as if they were a user with local access. The main attack vector is for instances hosted locally on personal machines, which are not publicly accessible. The CORS settings in the backend permit all origins, exposing unauthenticated endpoints to CSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6867 | Information Disclosure in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6867</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in the lunary-ai/lunary, specifically in the `runs/{run_id}/related` endpoint. This endpoint does not verify that the user has the necessary access rights to the run(s) they are accessing. As a result, it returns not only the specified run but also all runs that have the `run_id` listed as their parent run. This issue affects the main branch, commit a761d833. The vulnerability allows unauthorized users to obtain information about non-public runs and their related runs, given the `run_id` of a public or non-public run.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44798 | phpgurukul Bus Pass Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-site scripting (XSS) in /admin/pass-bwdates-reports-details.php via fromdat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44798</link><description>phpgurukul Bus Pass Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-site scripting (XSS) in /admin/pass-bwdates-reports-details.php via fromdate and todate parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6587 | SSRF in berriai/litellm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6587</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in berriai/litellm version 1.38.10. This vulnerability allows users to specify the `api_base` parameter when making requests to `POST /chat/completions`, causing the application to send the request to the domain specified by `api_base`. This request includes the OpenAI API key. A malicious user can set the `api_base` to their own domain and intercept the OpenAI API key, leading to unauthorized access and potential misuse of the API key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42025 | A Command Injection vulnerability found in a Self-Hosted UniFi Network Servers (Linux) with UniFi Network Application (Version 8.3.32 and ea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42025</link><description>A Command Injection vulnerability found in a Self-Hosted UniFi Network Servers (Linux) with UniFi Network Application (Version 8.3.32 and earlier) allows a malicious actor with unifi user shell access to escalate privileges to root on the host device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44685 | Titan SFTP and Titan MFT Server 2.0.25.2426 and earlier have a vulnerability a vulnerability where sensitive information, including password...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44685</link><description>Titan SFTP and Titan MFT Server 2.0.25.2426 and earlier have a vulnerability a vulnerability where sensitive information, including passwords, is exposed in clear text within the JSON response when configuring SMTP settings via the Web UI.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-2446 | WP Editor &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Authenticated (Admin+) PHAR Deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2446</link><description>The WP Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to deserialization of untrusted input via the 'current_theme_root' parameter in versions up to, and including 1.2.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with administrative privileges to call files using a PHAR wrapper that will deserialize and call arbitrary PHP Objects that can be used to perform a variety of malicious actions granted a POP chain is also present. It also requires that the attacker is successful in uploading a file with the serialized payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5789 | Triton Lite &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5789</link><description>The Triton Lite theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'url' attribute within the theme's Button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5867 | Delicate &amp;lt;= 3.5.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5867</link><description>The Delicate theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'link' parameter within the theme's Button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5869 | Neighborly &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5869</link><description>The Neighborly theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter within the theme's Button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5870 | Tweaker5 &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5870</link><description>The Tweaker5 theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter within the theme's Button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5884 | Beauty &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via tpl_featured_cat_id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5884</link><description>The Beauty theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘tpl_featured_cat_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6544 | Custom Post Limits &amp;lt;= 4.4.1 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6544</link><description>The Custom Post Limits plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to full path disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.1. This is due to the plugin utilizing bootstrap and leaving test files with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7423 | Stream &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7423</link><description>The Stream plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the network_options_action() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary options that can lead to DoS or privilege escalation via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8242 | MStore API – Create Native Android &amp;amp; iOS Apps On The Cloud &amp;lt;= 4.15.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8242</link><description>The MStore API – Create Native Android &amp; iOS Apps On The Cloud plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the update_user_profile() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.15.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files (not including PHP files) on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. This can be paired with a registration endpoint for unauthenticated users to exploit the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8269 | MStore API – Create Native Android &amp;amp; iOS Apps On The Cloud &amp;lt;= 4.15.3 - Unauthorized User Registration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8269</link><description>The MStore API – Create Native Android &amp; iOS Apps On The Cloud plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized user registration in all versions up to, and including, 4.15.3. This is due to the plugin not checking that user registration is enabled prior to creating a user account through the register() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create user accounts on sites, even when user registration is disabled and plugin functionality is not activated.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8714 | WordPress Affiliates Plugin — SliceWP Affiliates &amp;lt;= 1.1.20 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8714</link><description>The WordPress Affiliates Plugin — SliceWP Affiliates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.20. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8730 | Exit Notifier &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8730</link><description>The Exit Notifier plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8731 | Cron Jobs &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8731</link><description>The Cron Jobs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8732 | Roles &amp;amp; Capabilities &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8732</link><description>The Roles &amp; Capabilities plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8734 | Lucas String Replace &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8734</link><description>The Lucas String Replace plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8737 | PDF Thumbnail Generator &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8737</link><description>The PDF Thumbnail Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8747 | Email Obfuscate Shortcode &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8747</link><description>The Email Obfuscate Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'email-obfuscate' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46713 | perf/aux: Fix AUX buffer serialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46713</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

perf/aux: Fix AUX buffer serialization

Ole reported that event-&gt;mmap_mutex is strictly insufficient to
serialize the AUX buffer, add a per RB mutex to fully serialize it.

Note that in the lock order comment the perf_event::mmap_mutex order
was already wrong, that is, it nesting under mmap_lock is not new with
this patch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46046 | Tenda FH451 v1.0.0.9 has a stack overflow vulnerability located in the RouteStatic function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46046</link><description>Tenda FH451 v1.0.0.9 has a stack overflow vulnerability located in the RouteStatic function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 14:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46047 | Tenda FH451 v1.0.0.9 has a stack overflow vulnerability in the fromDhcpListClient function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46047</link><description>Tenda FH451 v1.0.0.9 has a stack overflow vulnerability in the fromDhcpListClient function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 14:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46048 | Tenda FH451 v1.0.0.9 has a command injection vulnerability in the formexeCommand function i</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46048</link><description>Tenda FH451 v1.0.0.9 has a command injection vulnerability in the formexeCommand function i</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 14:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46049 | Tenda O6 V3.0 firmware V1.0.0.7(2054) contains a stack overflow vulnerability in the formexeCommand function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46049</link><description>Tenda O6 V3.0 firmware V1.0.0.7(2054) contains a stack overflow vulnerability in the formexeCommand function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 13:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46044 | CH22 V1.0.0.6(468) has a stack overflow vulnerability located in the fromqossetting function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46044</link><description>CH22 V1.0.0.6(468) has a stack overflow vulnerability located in the fromqossetting function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 13:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46045 | Tenda CH22 V1.0.0.6(468) has a stack overflow vulnerability located in the frmL7PlotForm function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46045</link><description>Tenda CH22 V1.0.0.6(468) has a stack overflow vulnerability located in the frmL7PlotForm function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 13:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43756 | Photoshop Desktop | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43756</link><description>Photoshop Desktop versions 24.7.4, 25.11 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 09:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43760 | Photoshop Desktop | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43760</link><description>Photoshop Desktop versions 24.7.4, 25.11 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 09:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45108 | Photoshop Desktop | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45108</link><description>Photoshop Desktop versions 24.7.4, 25.11 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 09:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45109 | Photoshop Desktop | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45109</link><description>Photoshop Desktop versions 24.7.4, 25.11 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 09:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41874 | ColdFusion | Deserialization of Untrusted Data (CWE-502)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41874</link><description>ColdFusion versions 2023.9, 2021.15 and earlier are affected by a Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by providing crafted input to the application, which when deserialized, leads to execution of malicious code. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 09:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45113 | ColdFusion | Improper Authentication (CWE-287)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45113</link><description>ColdFusion versions 2023.6, 2021.12 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authentication vulnerability that could result in privilege escalation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to gain unauthorized access and affect the integrity of the application. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 09:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41869 | Acrobat Reader | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41869</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.002.21005, 24.001.30159, 20.005.30655, 24.003.20054 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 09:17:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45112 | Acrobat Reader | Access of Resource Using Incompatible Type (&amp;#x27;Type Confusion&amp;#x27;) (CWE-843)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45112</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.002.21005, 24.001.30159, 20.005.30655, 24.003.20054 and earlier are affected by a Type Confusion vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. This issue occurs when a resource is accessed using a type that is not compatible with the actual object type, leading to a logic error that an attacker could exploit. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 09:17:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6656 | Hardcoded Credentals in TNB Mobile Solutions&amp;#x27; Cockpit Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6656</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in TNB Mobile Solutions Cockpit Software allows Read Sensitive Strings Within an Executable.This issue affects Cockpit Software: before v2.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 08:56:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34121 | Illustrator | Integer Overflow or Wraparound (CWE-190)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34121</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.6, 27.9.5 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 08:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41857 | Illustrator | Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) (CWE-191)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41857</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.6, 27.9.5 and earlier are affected by an Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 08:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43758 | Illustrator | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43758</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.6, 27.9.5 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 08:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43759 | Illustrator | NULL Pointer Dereference (CWE-476)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43759</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.6, 27.9.5 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service (DoS). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, resulting in a DoS condition. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 08:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45111 | Illustrator | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45111</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.6, 27.9.5 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 08:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39380 | After Effects | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39380</link><description>After Effects versions 23.6.6, 24.5 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 08:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39381 | After Effects | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39381</link><description>After Effects versions 23.6.6, 24.5 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 08:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39382 | After Effects | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39382</link><description>After Effects versions 23.6.6, 24.5 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 08:34:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39384 | Premiere Pro | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39384</link><description>Premiere Pro versions 24.5, 23.6.8 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 08:34:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39385 | Premiere Pro | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39385</link><description>Premiere Pro versions 24.5, 23.6.8 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 08:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41859 | After Effects | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41859</link><description>After Effects versions 23.6.6, 24.5 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 08:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41867 | After Effects | Stack-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-121)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41867</link><description>After Effects versions 23.6.6, 24.5 and earlier are affected by a Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary file system write operations. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to modify or corrupt files, potentially leading to a compromise of system integrity. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 08:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39377 | Media Encoder | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39377</link><description>Media Encoder versions 24.5, 23.6.8 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 07:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41870 | Media Encoder | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41870</link><description>Media Encoder versions 24.5, 23.6.8 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 07:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41871 | Media Encoder | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41871</link><description>Media Encoder versions 24.5, 23.6.8 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 07:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41872 | Media Encoder | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41872</link><description>Media Encoder versions 24.5, 23.6.8 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 07:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41873 | Media Encoder | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41873</link><description>Media Encoder versions 24.5, 23.6.8 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 07:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46712 | drm/vmwgfx: Disable coherent dumb buffers without 3d</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46712</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/vmwgfx: Disable coherent dumb buffers without 3d

Coherent surfaces make only sense if the host renders to them using
accelerated apis. Without 3d the entire content of dumb buffers stays
in the guest making all of the extra work they're doing to synchronize
between guest and host useless.

Configurations without 3d also tend to run with very low graphics
memory limits. The pinned console fb, mob cursors and graphical login
manager tend to run out of 16MB graphics memory that those guests use.

Fix it by making sure the coherent dumb buffers are only used on
configs with 3d enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5567 | Betheme | Responsive Multipurpose WordPress &amp;amp; WooCommerce Theme &amp;lt;= 27.5.5 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5567</link><description>The Betheme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 27.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7888 | Classified Listing – Classified ads &amp;amp; Business Directory Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.7 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7888</link><description>The Classified Listing – Classified ads &amp; Business Directory Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on several functions like export_forms(), import_forms(), update_fb_options(), and many more in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to modify forms and various other settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8663 | WP Simple Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 2.0.10 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8663</link><description>The WP Simple Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.10. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8664 | WP Test Email &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8664</link><description>The WP Test Email plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8665 | YITH Custom Login &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8665</link><description>The YITH Custom Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8742 | Essential Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 6.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Filterable Gallery Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8742</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Addon, Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Filterable Gallery widget in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46708 | pinctrl: qcom: x1e80100: Fix special pin offsets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46708</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

pinctrl: qcom: x1e80100: Fix special pin offsets

Remove the erroneus 0x100000 offset to prevent the boards from crashing
on pin state setting, as well as for the intended state changes to take
effect.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:41:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46709 | drm/vmwgfx: Fix prime with external buffers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46709</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/vmwgfx: Fix prime with external buffers

Make sure that for external buffers mapping goes through the dma_buf
interface instead of trying to access pages directly.

External buffers might not provide direct access to readable/writable
pages so to make sure the bo's created from external dma_bufs can be
read dma_buf interface has to be used.

Fixes crashes in IGT's kms_prime with vgem. Regular desktop usage won't
trigger this due to the fact that virtual machines will not have
multiple GPUs but it enables better test coverage in IGT.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:41:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46710 | drm/vmwgfx: Prevent unmapping active read buffers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46710</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/vmwgfx: Prevent unmapping active read buffers

The kms paths keep a persistent map active to read and compare the cursor
buffer. These maps can race with each other in simple scenario where:
a) buffer "a" mapped for update
b) buffer "a" mapped for compare
c) do the compare
d) unmap "a" for compare
e) update the cursor
f) unmap "a" for update
At step "e" the buffer has been unmapped and the read contents is bogus.

Prevent unmapping of active read buffers by simply keeping a count of
how many paths have currently active maps and unmap only when the count
reaches 0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46711 | mptcp: pm: fix ID 0 endp usage after multiple re-creations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46711</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mptcp: pm: fix ID 0 endp usage after multiple re-creations

'local_addr_used' and 'add_addr_accepted' are decremented for addresses
not related to the initial subflow (ID0), because the source and
destination addresses of the initial subflows are known from the
beginning: they don't count as "additional local address being used" or
"ADD_ADDR being accepted".

It is then required not to increment them when the entrypoint used by
the initial subflow is removed and re-added during a connection. Without
this modification, this entrypoint cannot be removed and re-added more
than once.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46701 | libfs: fix infinite directory reads for offset dir</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46701</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

libfs: fix infinite directory reads for offset dir

After we switch tmpfs dir operations from simple_dir_operations to
simple_offset_dir_operations, every rename happened will fill new dentry
to dest dir's maple tree(&amp;amp;SHMEM_I(inode)-&gt;dir_offsets-&gt;mt) with a free
key starting with octx-&gt;newx_offset, and then set newx_offset equals to
free key + 1. This will lead to infinite readdir combine with rename
happened at the same time, which fail generic/736 in xfstests(detail show
as below).

1. create 5000 files(1 2 3...) under one dir
2. call readdir(man 3 readdir) once, and get one entry
3. rename(entry, "TEMPFILE"), then rename("TEMPFILE", entry)
4. loop 2~3, until readdir return nothing or we loop too many
   times(tmpfs break test with the second condition)

We choose the same logic what commit 9b378f6ad48cf ("btrfs: fix infinite
directory reads") to fix it, record the last_index when we open dir, and
do not emit the entry which index &gt;= last_index. The file-&gt;private_data
now used in offset dir can use directly to do this, and we also update
the last_index when we llseek the dir file.

[brauner: only update last_index after seek when offset is zero like Jan suggested]</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46702 | thunderbolt: Mark XDomain as unplugged when router is removed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46702</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

thunderbolt: Mark XDomain as unplugged when router is removed

I noticed that when we do discrete host router NVM upgrade and it gets
hot-removed from the PCIe side as a result of NVM firmware authentication,
if there is another host connected with enabled paths we hang in tearing
them down. This is due to fact that the Thunderbolt networking driver
also tries to cleanup the paths and ends up blocking in
tb_disconnect_xdomain_paths() waiting for the domain lock.

However, at this point we already cleaned the paths in tb_stop() so
there is really no need for tb_disconnect_xdomain_paths() to do that
anymore. Furthermore it already checks if the XDomain is unplugged and
bails out early so take advantage of that and mark the XDomain as
unplugged when we remove the parent router.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46703 | Revert &amp;quot;serial: 8250_omap: Set the console genpd always on if no console suspend&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46703</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Revert "serial: 8250_omap: Set the console genpd always on if no console suspend"

This reverts commit 68e6939ea9ec3d6579eadeab16060339cdeaf940.

Kevin reported that this causes a crash during suspend on platforms that
dont use PM domains.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46704 | workqueue: Fix spruious data race in __flush_work()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46704</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

workqueue: Fix spruious data race in __flush_work()

When flushing a work item for cancellation, __flush_work() knows that it
exclusively owns the work item through its PENDING bit. 134874e2eee9
("workqueue: Allow cancel_work_sync() and disable_work() from atomic
contexts on BH work items") added a read of @work-&gt;data to determine whether
to use busy wait for BH work items that are being canceled. While the read
is safe when @from_cancel, @work-&gt;data was read before testing @from_cancel
to simplify code structure:

	data = *work_data_bits(work);
	if (from_cancel &amp;&amp;
	    !WARN_ON_ONCE(data &amp; WORK_STRUCT_PWQ) &amp;&amp; (data &amp; WORK_OFFQ_BH)) {

While the read data was never used if !@from_cancel, this could trigger
KCSAN data race detection spuriously:

  ==================================================================
  BUG: KCSAN: data-race in __flush_work / __flush_work

  write to 0xffff8881223aa3e8 of 8 bytes by task 3998 on cpu 0:
   instrument_write include/linux/instrumented.h:41 [inline]
   ___set_bit include/asm-generic/bitops/instrumented-non-atomic.h:28 [inline]
   insert_wq_barrier kernel/workqueue.c:3790 [inline]
   start_flush_work kernel/workqueue.c:4142 [inline]
   __flush_work+0x30b/0x570 kernel/workqueue.c:4178
   flush_work kernel/workqueue.c:4229 [inline]
   ...

  read to 0xffff8881223aa3e8 of 8 bytes by task 50 on cpu 1:
   __flush_work+0x42a/0x570 kernel/workqueue.c:4188
   flush_work kernel/workqueue.c:4229 [inline]
   flush_delayed_work+0x66/0x70 kernel/workqueue.c:4251
   ...

  value changed: 0x0000000000400000 -&gt; 0xffff88810006c00d

Reorganize the code so that @from_cancel is tested before @work-&gt;data is
accessed. The only problem is triggering KCSAN detection spuriously. This
shouldn't need READ_ONCE() or other access qualifiers.

No functional changes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46705 | drm/xe: reset mmio mappings with devm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46705</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/xe: reset mmio mappings with devm

Set our various mmio mappings to NULL. This should make it easier to
catch something rogue trying to mess with mmio after device removal. For
example, we might unmap everything and then start hitting some mmio
address which has already been unmamped by us and then remapped by
something else, causing all kinds of carnage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46706 | tty: serial: fsl_lpuart: mark last busy before uart_add_one_port</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46706</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tty: serial: fsl_lpuart: mark last busy before uart_add_one_port

With "earlycon initcall_debug=1 loglevel=8" in bootargs, kernel
sometimes boot hang. It is because normal console still is not ready,
but runtime suspend is called, so early console putchar will hang
in waiting TRDE set in UARTSTAT.

The lpuart driver has auto suspend delay set to 3000ms, but during
uart_add_one_port, a child device serial ctrl will added and probed with
its pm runtime enabled(see serial_ctrl.c).
The runtime suspend call path is:
device_add
     |-&gt; bus_probe_device
           |-&gt;device_initial_probe
	           |-&gt;__device_attach
                         |-&gt; pm_runtime_get_sync(dev-&gt;parent);
			 |-&gt; pm_request_idle(dev);
			 |-&gt; pm_runtime_put(dev-&gt;parent);

So in the end, before normal console ready, the lpuart get runtime
suspended. And earlycon putchar will hang.

To address the issue, mark last busy just after pm_runtime_enable,
three seconds is long enough to switch from bootconsole to normal
console.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:41:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46707 | KVM: arm64: Make ICC_*SGI*_EL1 undef in the absence of a vGICv3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46707</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

KVM: arm64: Make ICC_*SGI*_EL1 undef in the absence of a vGICv3

On a system with a GICv3, if a guest hasn't been configured with
GICv3 and that the host is not capable of GICv2 emulation,
a write to any of the ICC_*SGI*_EL1 registers is trapped to EL2.

We therefore try to emulate the SGI access, only to hit a NULL
pointer as no private interrupt is allocated (no GIC, remember?).

The obvious fix is to give the guest what it deserves, in the
shape of a UNDEF exception.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:41:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38816 | CVE-2024-38816: Path traversal vulnerability in functional web frameworks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38816</link><description>Applications serving static resources through the functional web frameworks WebMvc.fn or WebFlux.fn are vulnerable to path traversal attacks. An attacker can craft malicious HTTP requests and obtain any file on the file system that is also accessible to the process in which the Spring application is running.

Specifically, an application is vulnerable when both of the following are true:

  *  the web application uses RouterFunctions to serve static resources
  *  resource handling is explicitly configured with a FileSystemResource location


However, malicious requests are blocked and rejected when any of the following is true:

  *  the  Spring Security HTTP Firewall https://docs.spring.io/spring-security/reference/servlet/exploits/firewall.html  is in use
  *  the application runs on Tomcat or Jetty</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6493 | NinjaTeam Header Footer Custom Code &amp;lt; 1.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6493</link><description>The NinjaTeam Header Footer Custom Code WordPress plugin before 1.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6617 | NinjaTeam Header Footer Custom Code &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS via CSS Styles</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6617</link><description>The NinjaTeam Header Footer Custom Code WordPress plugin before 1.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6723 | AI Engine &amp;lt; 2.4.8 - Admin+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6723</link><description>The AI Engine WordPress plugin before 2.4.8 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, leading to a SQL injection exploitable by admin users when viewing chatbot discussions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6850 | Carousel Slider &amp;lt; 2.2.14 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6850</link><description>The Carousel Slider WordPress plugin before 2.2.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as editors to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7129 | Appointment Booking Calendar &amp;lt; 1.6.7.43 - Admin+ Template Injection to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7129</link><description>The Appointment Booking Calendar — Simply Schedule Appointments Booking Plugin WordPress plugin before 1.6.7.43 does not escape template syntax provided via user input, leading to Twig Template Injection which further exploited can result to remote code Execution by high privilege such as admins</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7133 | My Sticky Bar &amp;lt; 2.7.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7133</link><description>The Floating Notification Bar, Sticky Menu on Scroll, Announcement Banner, and Sticky Header for Any   WordPress plugin before 2.7.3 does not validate and escape some of its settings before outputting them back in the page, which could allow users with a high role to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7863 | Favicon Generator &amp;lt; 2.1 - Arbitrary File Upload via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7863</link><description>The Favicon Generator (CLOSED) WordPress plugin before 2.1 does not validate files to be uploaded and does not have CSRF checks, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin upload arbitrary files such as PHP on the server</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7864 | Favicon Generator &amp;lt; 2.1 - Arbitrary File Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7864</link><description>The Favicon Generator (CLOSED) WordPress plugin before 2.1 does not have CSRF and path validation in the output_sub_admin_page_0() function, allowing attackers to make logged in admins delete arbitrary files on the server</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5628 | Avada | Website Builder For WordPress &amp;amp; eCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.11.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via fusion_button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5628</link><description>The Avada | Website Builder For WordPress &amp; eCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's fusion_button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.11.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. NOTE: This vulnerability was partially fixed in 3.11.9. Additional hardening for alternate attack vectors was added to version 3.11.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46673 | scsi: aacraid: Fix double-free on probe failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46673</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

scsi: aacraid: Fix double-free on probe failure

aac_probe_one() calls hardware-specific init functions through the
aac_driver_ident::init pointer, all of which eventually call down to
aac_init_adapter().

If aac_init_adapter() fails after allocating memory for aac_dev::queues,
it frees the memory but does not clear that member.

After the hardware-specific init function returns an error,
aac_probe_one() goes down an error path that frees the memory pointed to
by aac_dev::queues, resulting.in a double-free.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46674 | usb: dwc3: st: fix probed platform device ref count on probe error path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46674</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: dwc3: st: fix probed platform device ref count on probe error path

The probe function never performs any paltform device allocation, thus
error path "undo_platform_dev_alloc" is entirely bogus.  It drops the
reference count from the platform device being probed.  If error path is
triggered, this will lead to unbalanced device reference counts and
premature release of device resources, thus possible use-after-free when
releasing remaining devm-managed resources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46675 | usb: dwc3: core: Prevent USB core invalid event buffer address access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46675</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: dwc3: core: Prevent USB core invalid event buffer address access

This commit addresses an issue where the USB core could access an
invalid event buffer address during runtime suspend, potentially causing
SMMU faults and other memory issues in Exynos platforms. The problem
arises from the following sequence.
        1. In dwc3_gadget_suspend, there is a chance of a timeout when
        moving the USB core to the halt state after clearing the
        run/stop bit by software.
        2. In dwc3_core_exit, the event buffer is cleared regardless of
        the USB core's status, which may lead to an SMMU faults and
        other memory issues. if the USB core tries to access the event
        buffer address.

To prevent this hardware quirk on Exynos platforms, this commit ensures
that the event buffer address is not cleared by software  when the USB
core is active during runtime suspend by checking its status before
clearing the buffer address.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46676 | nfc: pn533: Add poll mod list filling check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46676</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nfc: pn533: Add poll mod list filling check

In case of im_protocols value is 1 and tm_protocols value is 0 this
combination successfully passes the check
'if (!im_protocols &amp;&amp; !tm_protocols)' in the nfc_start_poll().
But then after pn533_poll_create_mod_list() call in pn533_start_poll()
poll mod list will remain empty and dev-&gt;poll_mod_count will remain 0
which lead to division by zero.

Normally no im protocol has value 1 in the mask, so this combination is
not expected by driver. But these protocol values actually come from
userspace via Netlink interface (NFC_CMD_START_POLL operation). So a
broken or malicious program may pass a message containing a "bad"
combination of protocol parameter values so that dev-&gt;poll_mod_count
is not incremented inside pn533_poll_create_mod_list(), thus leading
to division by zero.
Call trace looks like:
nfc_genl_start_poll()
  nfc_start_poll()
    -&gt;start_poll()
    pn533_start_poll()

Add poll mod list filling check.

Found by Linux Verification Center (linuxtesting.org) with SVACE.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46677 | gtp: fix a potential NULL pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46677</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

gtp: fix a potential NULL pointer dereference

When sockfd_lookup() fails, gtp_encap_enable_socket() returns a
NULL pointer, but its callers only check for error pointers thus miss
the NULL pointer case.

Fix it by returning an error pointer with the error code carried from
sockfd_lookup().

(I found this bug during code inspection.)</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46678 | bonding: change ipsec_lock from spin lock to mutex</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46678</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bonding: change ipsec_lock from spin lock to mutex

In the cited commit, bond-&gt;ipsec_lock is added to protect ipsec_list,
hence xdo_dev_state_add and xdo_dev_state_delete are called inside
this lock. As ipsec_lock is a spin lock and such xfrmdev ops may sleep,
"scheduling while atomic" will be triggered when changing bond's
active slave.

[  101.055189] BUG: scheduling while atomic: bash/902/0x00000200
[  101.055726] Modules linked in:
[  101.058211] CPU: 3 PID: 902 Comm: bash Not tainted 6.9.0-rc4+ #1
[  101.058760] Hardware name:
[  101.059434] Call Trace:
[  101.059436]  
[  101.060873]  dump_stack_lvl+0x51/0x60
[  101.061275]  __schedule_bug+0x4e/0x60
[  101.061682]  __schedule+0x612/0x7c0
[  101.062078]  ? __mod_timer+0x25c/0x370
[  101.062486]  schedule+0x25/0xd0
[  101.062845]  schedule_timeout+0x77/0xf0
[  101.063265]  ? asm_common_interrupt+0x22/0x40
[  101.063724]  ? __bpf_trace_itimer_state+0x10/0x10
[  101.064215]  __wait_for_common+0x87/0x190
[  101.064648]  ? usleep_range_state+0x90/0x90
[  101.065091]  cmd_exec+0x437/0xb20 [mlx5_core]
[  101.065569]  mlx5_cmd_do+0x1e/0x40 [mlx5_core]
[  101.066051]  mlx5_cmd_exec+0x18/0x30 [mlx5_core]
[  101.066552]  mlx5_crypto_create_dek_key+0xea/0x120 [mlx5_core]
[  101.067163]  ? bonding_sysfs_store_option+0x4d/0x80 [bonding]
[  101.067738]  ? kmalloc_trace+0x4d/0x350
[  101.068156]  mlx5_ipsec_create_sa_ctx+0x33/0x100 [mlx5_core]
[  101.068747]  mlx5e_xfrm_add_state+0x47b/0xaa0 [mlx5_core]
[  101.069312]  bond_change_active_slave+0x392/0x900 [bonding]
[  101.069868]  bond_option_active_slave_set+0x1c2/0x240 [bonding]
[  101.070454]  __bond_opt_set+0xa6/0x430 [bonding]
[  101.070935]  __bond_opt_set_notify+0x2f/0x90 [bonding]
[  101.071453]  bond_opt_tryset_rtnl+0x72/0xb0 [bonding]
[  101.071965]  bonding_sysfs_store_option+0x4d/0x80 [bonding]
[  101.072567]  kernfs_fop_write_iter+0x10c/0x1a0
[  101.073033]  vfs_write+0x2d8/0x400
[  101.073416]  ? alloc_fd+0x48/0x180
[  101.073798]  ksys_write+0x5f/0xe0
[  101.074175]  do_syscall_64+0x52/0x110
[  101.074576]  entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x4b/0x53

As bond_ipsec_add_sa_all and bond_ipsec_del_sa_all are only called
from bond_change_active_slave, which requires holding the RTNL lock.
And bond_ipsec_add_sa and bond_ipsec_del_sa are xfrm state
xdo_dev_state_add and xdo_dev_state_delete APIs, which are in user
context. So ipsec_lock doesn't have to be spin lock, change it to
mutex, and thus the above issue can be resolved.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46679 | ethtool: check device is present when getting link settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46679</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ethtool: check device is present when getting link settings

A sysfs reader can race with a device reset or removal, attempting to
read device state when the device is not actually present. eg:

     [exception RIP: qed_get_current_link+17]
  #8 [ffffb9e4f2907c48] qede_get_link_ksettings at ffffffffc07a994a [qede]
  #9 [ffffb9e4f2907cd8] __rh_call_get_link_ksettings at ffffffff992b01a3
 #10 [ffffb9e4f2907d38] __ethtool_get_link_ksettings at ffffffff992b04e4
 #11 [ffffb9e4f2907d90] duplex_show at ffffffff99260300
 #12 [ffffb9e4f2907e38] dev_attr_show at ffffffff9905a01c
 #13 [ffffb9e4f2907e50] sysfs_kf_seq_show at ffffffff98e0145b
 #14 [ffffb9e4f2907e68] seq_read at ffffffff98d902e3
 #15 [ffffb9e4f2907ec8] vfs_read at ffffffff98d657d1
 #16 [ffffb9e4f2907f00] ksys_read at ffffffff98d65c3f
 #17 [ffffb9e4f2907f38] do_syscall_64 at ffffffff98a052fb

 crash&gt; struct net_device.state ffff9a9d21336000
    state = 5,

state 5 is __LINK_STATE_START (0b1) and __LINK_STATE_NOCARRIER (0b100).
The device is not present, note lack of __LINK_STATE_PRESENT (0b10).

This is the same sort of panic as observed in commit 4224cfd7fb65
("net-sysfs: add check for netdevice being present to speed_show").

There are many other callers of __ethtool_get_link_ksettings() which
don't have a device presence check.

Move this check into ethtool to protect all callers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46680 | Bluetooth: btnxpuart: Fix random crash seen while removing driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46680</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: btnxpuart: Fix random crash seen while removing driver

This fixes the random kernel crash seen while removing the driver, when
running the load/unload test over multiple iterations.

1) modprobe btnxpuart
2) hciconfig hci0 reset
3) hciconfig (check hci0 interface up with valid BD address)
4) modprobe -r btnxpuart
Repeat steps 1 to 4

The ps_wakeup() call in btnxpuart_close() schedules the psdata-&gt;work(),
which gets scheduled after module is removed, causing a kernel crash.

This hidden issue got highlighted after enabling Power Save by default
in 4183a7be7700 (Bluetooth: btnxpuart: Enable Power Save feature on
startup)

The new ps_cleanup() deasserts UART break immediately while closing
serdev device, cancels any scheduled ps_work and destroys the ps_lock
mutex.

[   85.884604] Unable to handle kernel paging request at virtual address ffffd4a61638f258
[   85.884624] Mem abort info:
[   85.884625]   ESR = 0x0000000086000007
[   85.884628]   EC = 0x21: IABT (current EL), IL = 32 bits
[   85.884633]   SET = 0, FnV = 0
[   85.884636]   EA = 0, S1PTW = 0
[   85.884638]   FSC = 0x07: level 3 translation fault
[   85.884642] swapper pgtable: 4k pages, 48-bit VAs, pgdp=0000000041dd0000
[   85.884646] [ffffd4a61638f258] pgd=1000000095fff003, p4d=1000000095fff003, pud=100000004823d003, pmd=100000004823e003, pte=0000000000000000
[   85.884662] Internal error: Oops: 0000000086000007 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
[   85.890932] Modules linked in: algif_hash algif_skcipher af_alg overlay fsl_jr_uio caam_jr caamkeyblob_desc caamhash_desc caamalg_desc crypto_engine authenc libdes crct10dif_ce polyval_ce polyval_generic snd_soc_imx_spdif snd_soc_imx_card snd_soc_ak5558 snd_soc_ak4458 caam secvio error snd_soc_fsl_spdif snd_soc_fsl_micfil snd_soc_fsl_sai snd_soc_fsl_utils gpio_ir_recv rc_core fuse [last unloaded: btnxpuart(O)]
[   85.927297] CPU: 1 PID: 67 Comm: kworker/1:3 Tainted: G           O       6.1.36+g937b1be4345a #1
[   85.936176] Hardware name: FSL i.MX8MM EVK board (DT)
[   85.936182] Workqueue: events 0xffffd4a61638f380
[   85.936198] pstate: 60000005 (nZCv daif -PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
[   85.952817] pc : 0xffffd4a61638f258
[   85.952823] lr : 0xffffd4a61638f258
[   85.952827] sp : ffff8000084fbd70
[   85.952829] x29: ffff8000084fbd70 x28: 0000000000000000 x27: 0000000000000000
[   85.963112] x26: ffffd4a69133f000 x25: ffff4bf1c8540990 x24: ffff4bf215b87305
[   85.963119] x23: ffff4bf215b87300 x22: ffff4bf1c85409d0 x21: ffff4bf1c8540970
[   85.977382] x20: 0000000000000000 x19: ffff4bf1c8540880 x18: 0000000000000000
[   85.977391] x17: 0000000000000000 x16: 0000000000000133 x15: 0000ffffe2217090
[   85.977399] x14: 0000000000000001 x13: 0000000000000133 x12: 0000000000000139
[   85.977407] x11: 0000000000000001 x10: 0000000000000a60 x9 : ffff8000084fbc50
[   85.977417] x8 : ffff4bf215b7d000 x7 : ffff4bf215b83b40 x6 : 00000000000003e8
[   85.977424] x5 : 00000000410fd030 x4 : 0000000000000000 x3 : 0000000000000000
[   85.977432] x2 : 0000000000000000 x1 : ffff4bf1c4265880 x0 : 0000000000000000
[   85.977443] Call trace:
[   85.977446]  0xffffd4a61638f258
[   85.977451]  0xffffd4a61638f3e8
[   85.977455]  process_one_work+0x1d4/0x330
[   85.977464]  worker_thread+0x6c/0x430
[   85.977471]  kthread+0x108/0x10c
[   85.977476]  ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
[   85.977488] Code: bad PC value
[   85.977491] ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---

Preset since v6.9.11</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46681 | pktgen: use cpus_read_lock() in pg_net_init()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46681</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

pktgen: use cpus_read_lock() in pg_net_init()

I have seen the WARN_ON(smp_processor_id() != cpu) firing
in pktgen_thread_worker() during tests.

We must use cpus_read_lock()/cpus_read_unlock()
around the for_each_online_cpu(cpu) loop.

While we are at it use WARN_ON_ONCE() to avoid a possible syslog flood.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46682 | nfsd: prevent panic for nfsv4.0 closed files in nfs4_show_open</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46682</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nfsd: prevent panic for nfsv4.0 closed files in nfs4_show_open

Prior to commit 3f29cc82a84c ("nfsd: split sc_status out of
sc_type") states_show() relied on sc_type field to be of valid
type before calling into a subfunction to show content of a
particular stateid. From that commit, we split the validity of
the stateid into sc_status and no longer changed sc_type to 0
while unhashing the stateid. This resulted in kernel oopsing
for nfsv4.0 opens that stay around and in nfs4_show_open()
would derefence sc_file which was NULL.

Instead, for closed open stateids forgo displaying information
that relies of having a valid sc_file.

To reproduce: mount the server with 4.0, read and close
a file and then on the server cat /proc/fs/nfsd/clients/2/states

[  513.590804] Call trace:
[  513.590925]  _raw_spin_lock+0xcc/0x160
[  513.591119]  nfs4_show_open+0x78/0x2c0 [nfsd]
[  513.591412]  states_show+0x44c/0x488 [nfsd]
[  513.591681]  seq_read_iter+0x5d8/0x760
[  513.591896]  seq_read+0x188/0x208
[  513.592075]  vfs_read+0x148/0x470
[  513.592241]  ksys_read+0xcc/0x178</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46683 | drm/xe: prevent UAF around preempt fence</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46683</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/xe: prevent UAF around preempt fence

The fence lock is part of the queue, therefore in the current design
anything locking the fence should then also hold a ref to the queue to
prevent the queue from being freed.

However, currently it looks like we signal the fence and then drop the
queue ref, but if something is waiting on the fence, the waiter is
kicked to wake up at some later point, where upon waking up it first
grabs the lock before checking the fence state. But if we have already
dropped the queue ref, then the lock might already be freed as part of
the queue, leading to uaf.

To prevent this, move the fence lock into the fence itself so we don't
run into lifetime issues. Alternative might be to have device level
lock, or only release the queue in the fence release callback, however
that might require pushing to another worker to avoid locking issues.

References: https://gitlab.freedesktop.org/drm/xe/kernel/-/issues/2454
References: https://gitlab.freedesktop.org/drm/xe/kernel/-/issues/2342
References: https://gitlab.freedesktop.org/drm/xe/kernel/-/issues/2020
(cherry picked from commit 7116c35aacedc38be6d15bd21b2fc936eed0008b)</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46684 | binfmt_elf_fdpic: fix AUXV size calculation when ELF_HWCAP2 is defined</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46684</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

binfmt_elf_fdpic: fix AUXV size calculation when ELF_HWCAP2 is defined

create_elf_fdpic_tables() does not correctly account the space for the
AUX vector when an architecture has ELF_HWCAP2 defined. Prior to the
commit 10e29251be0e ("binfmt_elf_fdpic: fix /proc//auxv") it
resulted in the last entry of the AUX vector being set to zero, but with
that change it results in a kernel BUG.

Fix that by adding one to the number of AUXV entries (nitems) when
ELF_HWCAP2 is defined.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46685 | pinctrl: single: fix potential NULL dereference in pcs_get_function()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46685</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

pinctrl: single: fix potential NULL dereference in pcs_get_function()

pinmux_generic_get_function() can return NULL and the pointer 'function'
was dereferenced without checking against NULL. Add checking of pointer
'function' in pcs_get_function().

Found by code review.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46686 | smb/client: avoid dereferencing rdata=NULL in smb2_new_read_req()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46686</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

smb/client: avoid dereferencing rdata=NULL in smb2_new_read_req()

This happens when called from SMB2_read() while using rdma
and reaching the rdma_readwrite_threshold.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46687 | btrfs: fix a use-after-free when hitting errors inside btrfs_submit_chunk()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46687</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: fix a use-after-free when hitting errors inside btrfs_submit_chunk()

[BUG]
There is an internal report that KASAN is reporting use-after-free, with
the following backtrace:

  BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in btrfs_check_read_bio+0xa68/0xb70 [btrfs]
  Read of size 4 at addr ffff8881117cec28 by task kworker/u16:2/45
  CPU: 1 UID: 0 PID: 45 Comm: kworker/u16:2 Not tainted 6.11.0-rc2-next-20240805-default+ #76
  Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS rel-1.16.2-3-gd478f380-rebuilt.opensuse.org 04/01/2014
  Workqueue: btrfs-endio btrfs_end_bio_work [btrfs]
  Call Trace:
   dump_stack_lvl+0x61/0x80
   print_address_description.constprop.0+0x5e/0x2f0
   print_report+0x118/0x216
   kasan_report+0x11d/0x1f0
   btrfs_check_read_bio+0xa68/0xb70 [btrfs]
   process_one_work+0xce0/0x12a0
   worker_thread+0x717/0x1250
   kthread+0x2e3/0x3c0
   ret_from_fork+0x2d/0x70
   ret_from_fork_asm+0x11/0x20

  Allocated by task 20917:
   kasan_save_stack+0x37/0x60
   kasan_save_track+0x10/0x30
   __kasan_slab_alloc+0x7d/0x80
   kmem_cache_alloc_noprof+0x16e/0x3e0
   mempool_alloc_noprof+0x12e/0x310
   bio_alloc_bioset+0x3f0/0x7a0
   btrfs_bio_alloc+0x2e/0x50 [btrfs]
   submit_extent_page+0x4d1/0xdb0 [btrfs]
   btrfs_do_readpage+0x8b4/0x12a0 [btrfs]
   btrfs_readahead+0x29a/0x430 [btrfs]
   read_pages+0x1a7/0xc60
   page_cache_ra_unbounded+0x2ad/0x560
   filemap_get_pages+0x629/0xa20
   filemap_read+0x335/0xbf0
   vfs_read+0x790/0xcb0
   ksys_read+0xfd/0x1d0
   do_syscall_64+0x6d/0x140
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x4b/0x53

  Freed by task 20917:
   kasan_save_stack+0x37/0x60
   kasan_save_track+0x10/0x30
   kasan_save_free_info+0x37/0x50
   __kasan_slab_free+0x4b/0x60
   kmem_cache_free+0x214/0x5d0
   bio_free+0xed/0x180
   end_bbio_data_read+0x1cc/0x580 [btrfs]
   btrfs_submit_chunk+0x98d/0x1880 [btrfs]
   btrfs_submit_bio+0x33/0x70 [btrfs]
   submit_one_bio+0xd4/0x130 [btrfs]
   submit_extent_page+0x3ea/0xdb0 [btrfs]
   btrfs_do_readpage+0x8b4/0x12a0 [btrfs]
   btrfs_readahead+0x29a/0x430 [btrfs]
   read_pages+0x1a7/0xc60
   page_cache_ra_unbounded+0x2ad/0x560
   filemap_get_pages+0x629/0xa20
   filemap_read+0x335/0xbf0
   vfs_read+0x790/0xcb0
   ksys_read+0xfd/0x1d0
   do_syscall_64+0x6d/0x140
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x4b/0x53

[CAUSE]
Although I cannot reproduce the error, the report itself is good enough
to pin down the cause.

The call trace is the regular endio workqueue context, but the
free-by-task trace is showing that during btrfs_submit_chunk() we
already hit a critical error, and is calling btrfs_bio_end_io() to error
out.  And the original endio function called bio_put() to free the whole
bio.

This means a double freeing thus causing use-after-free, e.g.:

1. Enter btrfs_submit_bio() with a read bio
   The read bio length is 128K, crossing two 64K stripes.

2. The first run of btrfs_submit_chunk()

2.1 Call btrfs_map_block(), which returns 64K
2.2 Call btrfs_split_bio()
    Now there are two bios, one referring to the first 64K, the other
    referring to the second 64K.
2.3 The first half is submitted.

3. The second run of btrfs_submit_chunk()

3.1 Call btrfs_map_block(), which by somehow failed
    Now we call btrfs_bio_end_io() to handle the error

3.2 btrfs_bio_end_io() calls the original endio function
    Which is end_bbio_data_read(), and it calls bio_put() for the
    original bio.

    Now the original bio is freed.

4. The submitted first 64K bio finished
   Now we call into btrfs_check_read_bio() and tries to advance the bio
   iter.
   But since the original bio (thus its iter) is already freed, we
   trigger the above use-after free.

   And even if the memory is not poisoned/corrupted, we will later call
   the original endio function, causing a double freeing.

[FIX]
Instead of calling btrfs_bio_end_io(), call btrfs_orig_bbio_end_io(),
which has the extra check on split bios and do the pr
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46688 | erofs: fix out-of-bound access when z_erofs_gbuf_growsize() partially fails</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46688</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

erofs: fix out-of-bound access when z_erofs_gbuf_growsize() partially fails

If z_erofs_gbuf_growsize() partially fails on a global buffer due to
memory allocation failure or fault injection (as reported by syzbot [1]),
new pages need to be freed by comparing to the existing pages to avoid
memory leaks.

However, the old gbuf-&gt;pages[] array may not be large enough, which can
lead to null-ptr-deref or out-of-bound access.

Fix this by checking against gbuf-&gt;nrpages in advance.

[1] https://lore.kernel.org/r/000000000000f7b96e062018c6e3@google.com</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46689 | soc: qcom: cmd-db: Map shared memory as WC, not WB</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46689</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

soc: qcom: cmd-db: Map shared memory as WC, not WB

Linux does not write into cmd-db region. This region of memory is write
protected by XPU. XPU may sometime falsely detect clean cache eviction
as "write" into the write protected region leading to secure interrupt
which causes an endless loop somewhere in Trust Zone.

The only reason it is working right now is because Qualcomm Hypervisor
maps the same region as Non-Cacheable memory in Stage 2 translation
tables. The issue manifests if we want to use another hypervisor (like
Xen or KVM), which does not know anything about those specific mappings.

Changing the mapping of cmd-db memory from MEMREMAP_WB to MEMREMAP_WT/WC
removes dependency on correct mappings in Stage 2 tables. This patch
fixes the issue by updating the mapping to MEMREMAP_WC.

I tested this on SA8155P with Xen.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46690 | nfsd: fix nfsd4_deleg_getattr_conflict in presence of third party lease</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46690</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nfsd: fix nfsd4_deleg_getattr_conflict in presence of third party lease

It is not safe to dereference fl-&gt;c.flc_owner without first confirming
fl-&gt;fl_lmops is the expected manager.  nfsd4_deleg_getattr_conflict()
tests fl_lmops but largely ignores the result and assumes that flc_owner
is an nfs4_delegation anyway.  This is wrong.

With this patch we restore the "!= &amp;amp;nfsd_lease_mng_ops" case to behave
as it did before the change mentioned below.  This is the same as the
current code, but without any reference to a possible delegation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46691 | usb: typec: ucsi: Move unregister out of atomic section</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46691</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: typec: ucsi: Move unregister out of atomic section

Commit '9329933699b3 ("soc: qcom: pmic_glink: Make client-lock
non-sleeping")' moved the pmic_glink client list under a spinlock, as it
is accessed by the rpmsg/glink callback, which in turn is invoked from
IRQ context.

This means that ucsi_unregister() is now called from atomic context,
which isn't feasible as it's expecting a sleepable context. An effort is
under way to get GLINK to invoke its callbacks in a sleepable context,
but until then lets schedule the unregistration.

A side effect of this is that ucsi_unregister() can now happen
after the remote processor, and thereby the communication link with it, is
gone. pmic_glink_send() is amended with a check to avoid the resulting NULL
pointer dereference.
This does however result in the user being informed about this error by
the following entry in the kernel log:

  ucsi_glink.pmic_glink_ucsi pmic_glink.ucsi.0: failed to send UCSI write request: -5</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46692 | firmware: qcom: scm: Mark get_wq_ctx() as atomic call</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46692</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

firmware: qcom: scm: Mark get_wq_ctx() as atomic call

Currently get_wq_ctx() is wrongly configured as a standard call. When two
SMC calls are in sleep and one SMC wakes up, it calls get_wq_ctx() to
resume the corresponding sleeping thread. But if get_wq_ctx() is
interrupted, goes to sleep and another SMC call is waiting to be allocated
a waitq context, it leads to a deadlock.

To avoid this get_wq_ctx() must be an atomic call and can't be a standard
SMC call. Hence mark get_wq_ctx() as a fast call.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46693 | soc: qcom: pmic_glink: Fix race during initialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46693</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

soc: qcom: pmic_glink: Fix race during initialization

As pointed out by Stephen Boyd it is possible that during initialization
of the pmic_glink child drivers, the protection-domain notifiers fires,
and the associated work is scheduled, before the client registration
returns and as a result the local "client" pointer has been initialized.

The outcome of this is a NULL pointer dereference as the "client"
pointer is blindly dereferenced.

Timeline provided by Stephen:
 CPU0                               CPU1
 ----                               ----
 ucsi-&gt;client = NULL;
 devm_pmic_glink_register_client()
  client-&gt;pdr_notify(client-&gt;priv, pg-&gt;client_state)
   pmic_glink_ucsi_pdr_notify()
    schedule_work(&amp;amp;ucsi-&gt;register_work)
    
                                    pmic_glink_ucsi_register()
                                     ucsi_register()
                                      pmic_glink_ucsi_read_version()
                                       pmic_glink_ucsi_read()
                                        pmic_glink_ucsi_read()
                                         pmic_glink_send(ucsi-&gt;client)
                                         
 ucsi-&gt;client = client // Too late!

This code is identical across the altmode, battery manager and usci
child drivers.

Resolve this by splitting the allocation of the "client" object and the
registration thereof into two operations.

This only happens if the protection domain registry is populated at the
time of registration, which by the introduction of commit '1ebcde047c54
("soc: qcom: add pd-mapper implementation")' became much more likely.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46694 | drm/amd/display: avoid using null object of framebuffer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46694</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: avoid using null object of framebuffer

Instead of using state-&gt;fb-&gt;obj[0] directly, get object from framebuffer
by calling drm_gem_fb_get_obj() and return error code when object is
null to avoid using null object of framebuffer.

(cherry picked from commit 73dd0ad9e5dad53766ea3e631303430116f834b3)</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46695 | selinux,smack: don&amp;#x27;t bypass permissions check in inode_setsecctx hook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46695</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

selinux,smack: don't bypass permissions check in inode_setsecctx hook

Marek Gresko reports that the root user on an NFS client is able to
change the security labels on files on an NFS filesystem that is
exported with root squashing enabled.

The end of the kerneldoc comment for __vfs_setxattr_noperm() states:

 *  This function requires the caller to lock the inode's i_mutex before it
 *  is executed. It also assumes that the caller will make the appropriate
 *  permission checks.

nfsd_setattr() does do permissions checking via fh_verify() and
nfsd_permission(), but those don't do all the same permissions checks
that are done by security_inode_setxattr() and its related LSM hooks do.

Since nfsd_setattr() is the only consumer of security_inode_setsecctx(),
simplest solution appears to be to replace the call to
__vfs_setxattr_noperm() with a call to __vfs_setxattr_locked().  This
fixes the above issue and has the added benefit of causing nfsd to
recall conflicting delegations on a file when a client tries to change
its security label.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46696 | nfsd: fix potential UAF in nfsd4_cb_getattr_release</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46696</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nfsd: fix potential UAF in nfsd4_cb_getattr_release

Once we drop the delegation reference, the fields embedded in it are no
longer safe to access. Do that last.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46697 | nfsd: ensure that nfsd4_fattr_args.context is zeroed out</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46697</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nfsd: ensure that nfsd4_fattr_args.context is zeroed out

If nfsd4_encode_fattr4 ends up doing a "goto out" before we get to
checking for the security label, then args.context will be set to
uninitialized junk on the stack, which we'll then try to free.
Initialize it early.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46698 | video/aperture: optionally match the device in sysfb_disable()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46698</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

video/aperture: optionally match the device in sysfb_disable()

In aperture_remove_conflicting_pci_devices(), we currently only
call sysfb_disable() on vga class devices.  This leads to the
following problem when the pimary device is not VGA compatible:

1. A PCI device with a non-VGA class is the boot display
2. That device is probed first and it is not a VGA device so
   sysfb_disable() is not called, but the device resources
   are freed by aperture_detach_platform_device()
3. Non-primary GPU has a VGA class and it ends up calling sysfb_disable()
4. NULL pointer dereference via sysfb_disable() since the resources
   have already been freed by aperture_detach_platform_device() when
   it was called by the other device.

Fix this by passing a device pointer to sysfb_disable() and checking
the device to determine if we should execute it or not.

v2: Fix build when CONFIG_SCREEN_INFO is not set
v3: Move device check into the mutex
    Drop primary variable in aperture_remove_conflicting_pci_devices()
    Drop __init on pci sysfb_pci_dev_is_enabled()</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46699 | drm/v3d: Disable preemption while updating GPU stats</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46699</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/v3d: Disable preemption while updating GPU stats

We forgot to disable preemption around the write_seqcount_begin/end() pair
while updating GPU stats:

  [ ] WARNING: CPU: 2 PID: 12 at include/linux/seqlock.h:221 __seqprop_assert.isra.0+0x128/0x150 [v3d]
  [ ] Workqueue: v3d_bin drm_sched_run_job_work [gpu_sched]
 &lt;...snip...&gt;
  [ ] Call trace:
  [ ]  __seqprop_assert.isra.0+0x128/0x150 [v3d]
  [ ]  v3d_job_start_stats.isra.0+0x90/0x218 [v3d]
  [ ]  v3d_bin_job_run+0x23c/0x388 [v3d]
  [ ]  drm_sched_run_job_work+0x520/0x6d0 [gpu_sched]
  [ ]  process_one_work+0x62c/0xb48
  [ ]  worker_thread+0x468/0x5b0
  [ ]  kthread+0x1c4/0x1e0
  [ ]  ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20

Fix it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46700 | drm/amdgpu/mes: fix mes ring buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46700</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdgpu/mes: fix mes ring buffer overflow

wait memory room until enough before writing mes packets
to avoid ring buffer overflow.

v2: squash in sched_hw_submission fix

(cherry picked from commit 34e087e8920e635c62e2ed6a758b0cd27f836d13)</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8656 | WPFactory Helper &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 -  Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8656</link><description>The WPFactory Helper plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 03:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43180 | IBM Concert information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43180</link><description>IBM Concert 1.0 does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may be able to get the cookie values by sending a http:// link to a user or by planting this link in a site the user goes to. The cookie will be sent to the insecure link and the attacker can then obtain the cookie value by snooping the traffic.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 01:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8762 | code-projects Crud Operation System updatedata.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8762</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Crud Operation System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /updatedata.php. The manipulation of the argument sid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 01:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8751 | Vulnerability in SICK MSC800</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8751</link><description>A vulnerability in the MSC800 allows an unauthenticated attacker to modify the product’s IP
address over Sopas ET. 
This can lead to Denial of Service. 
Users are recommended to upgrade both
MSC800 and MSC800 LFT to version V4.26 and S2.93.20 respectively which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 21:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7961 | Rockwell Automation Path Traversal Vulnerability in Pavilion8®</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7961</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation affected product.  If exploited, the threat actor could upload arbitrary files to the server that could result in a remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 20:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7960 | Rockwell Automation Incorrect Privileges and Path Traversal Vulnerability in Pavilion8®</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7960</link><description>The Rockwell Automation affected product contains a vulnerability that allows a threat actor to view sensitive information and change settings. The vulnerability exists due to having an incorrect privilege matrix that allows users to have access to functions they should not.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 20:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44459 | A memory allocation issue in vernemq v2.0.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via excessive memory consumption.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44459</link><description>A memory allocation issue in vernemq v2.0.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via excessive memory consumption.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 20:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44460 | An invalid read size in Nanomq v0.21.9 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44460</link><description>An invalid read size in Nanomq v0.21.9 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 20:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6077 | Rockwell Automation ControlLogix/GuardLogix 5580 and CompactLogix/Compact GuardLogix® 5380 Vulnerable to DoS vulnerability via CIP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6077</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation affected products when specially crafted packets are sent to the CIP Security Object. If exploited the device will become unavailable and require a factory reset to recover.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 20:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8533 | Rockwell Automation OptixPanel™ Privilege Escalation Vulnerability via File Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8533</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation affected products. The vulnerability occurs due to improper default file permissions allowing users to exfiltrate credentials and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 20:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45607 | whatsapp-api-js fails to validate message&amp;#x27;s signature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45607</link><description>whatsapp-api-js is a TypeScript server agnostic Whatsapp's Official API framework. It's possible to check the payload validation using the WhatsAppAPI.verifyRequestSignature and expect false when the signature is valid. Incorrect Access Control, anyone using the post or verifyRequestSignature methods to handle messages is impacted. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 20:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20430 | Cisco Meraki Systems Manager Agent for Windows Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20430</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Meraki Systems Manager (SM) Agent for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges.&amp;nbsp;

This vulnerability is due to incorrect handling of directory search paths at runtime. A low-privileged attacker could exploit this vulnerability by placing both malicious configuration files and malicious DLL files on an affected system, which would read and execute the files when Cisco Meraki SM launches on startup. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected system with SYSTEM privileges.&amp;nbsp;</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 19:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25270 | An issue in Mirapolis LMS 4.6.XX allows authenticated users to exploit an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability by manipulat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25270</link><description>An issue in Mirapolis LMS 4.6.XX allows authenticated users to exploit an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability by manipulating the ID parameter and increment STEP parameter, leading to the exposure of sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36066 | The CMP CLI client in KeyFactor EJBCA before 8.3.1 has only 6 octets of salt, and is thus not compliant with the security requirements of RF...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36066</link><description>The CMP CLI client in KeyFactor EJBCA before 8.3.1 has only 6 octets of salt, and is thus not compliant with the security requirements of RFC 4211, and might make man-in-the-middle attacks easier. CMP includes password-based MAC as one of the options for message integrity and authentication (the other option is certificate-based). RFC 4211 section 4.4 requires that password-based MAC parameters use a salt with a random value of at least 8 octets. This helps to inhibit dictionary attacks. Because the standalone CMP client originally was developed as test code, the salt was instead hardcoded and only 6 octets long.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45181 | An issue was discovered in WibuKey64.sys in WIBU-SYSTEMS WibuKey before v6.70 and fixed in v.6.70. An improper bounds check allows crafted p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45181</link><description>An issue was discovered in WibuKey64.sys in WIBU-SYSTEMS WibuKey before v6.70 and fixed in v.6.70. An improper bounds check allows crafted packets to cause an arbitrary address write, resulting in kernel memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45182 | An issue was discovered in WibuKey64.sys in WIBU-SYSTEMS WibuKey before v6.70 and fixed in v.6.70 An improper bounds check allows specially ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45182</link><description>An issue was discovered in WibuKey64.sys in WIBU-SYSTEMS WibuKey before v6.70 and fixed in v.6.70 An improper bounds check allows specially crafted packets to cause an arbitrary address read, resulting in Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4472 | Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4472</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 prior to 17.1.7, starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.5, and starting from 17.3 prior to 17.3.2, where dependency proxy credentials are retained in graphql Logs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6678 | Authentication Bypass by Spoofing in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6678</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 8.14 prior to 17.1.7, starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.5, and starting from 17.3 prior to 17.3.2, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as an arbitrary user under certain circumstances.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8311 | Improper Protection of Alternate Path in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8311</link><description>An issue was discovered with pipeline execution policies in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 17.2 prior to 17.2.5, 17.3 prior to 17.3.2 which allows authenticated users to bypass variable overwrite protection via inclusion of a CI/CD template.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8641 | Privilege Context Switching Error in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8641</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 13.7 prior to 17.1.7, from 17.2 prior to 17.2.5, and from 17.3 prior to 17.3.2. It may have been possible for an attacker with a victim's CI_JOB_TOKEN to obtain a GitLab session token belonging to the victim.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34334 | ORDAT FOSS-Online before v2.24.01 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the forgot password function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34334</link><description>ORDAT FOSS-Online before v2.24.01 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the forgot password function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34335 | ORDAT FOSS-Online before version 2.24.01 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the login page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34335</link><description>ORDAT FOSS-Online before version 2.24.01 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the login page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34336 | User enumeration vulnerability in ORDAT FOSS-Online before v2.24.01 allows attackers to determine if an account exists in the application by...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34336</link><description>User enumeration vulnerability in ORDAT FOSS-Online before v2.24.01 allows attackers to determine if an account exists in the application by comparing the server responses of the forgot password functionality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45303 | Discourse Calendar plugin event names susceptible to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45303</link><description>Discourse Calendar plugin adds the ability to create a dynamic calendar in the first post of a topic to Discourse. Rendering event names can be susceptible to XSS attacks. This vulnerability only affects sites which have modified or disabled Discourse’s default Content Security Policy. The issue is patched in version 0.5 of the Discourse Calendar plugin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45383 | A mishandling of IRP requests vulnerability exists in the HDAudBus_DMA interface of Microsoft High Definition Audio Bus Driver 10.0.19041.36...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45383</link><description>A mishandling of IRP requests vulnerability exists in the HDAudBus_DMA interface of Microsoft High Definition Audio Bus Driver 10.0.19041.3636 (WinBuild.160101.0800). A specially crafted application can issue multiple IRP Complete requests which leads to a local denial-of-service. An attacker can execute malicious script/application to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41629 | An issue in Texas Instruments Fusion Digital Power Designer v.7.10.1 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the plainte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41629</link><description>An issue in Texas Instruments Fusion Digital Power Designer v.7.10.1 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the plaintext storage of credentials</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8695 | A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via crafted extension description/changelog could be abused by a malicious extension in Docker Desktop before 4.34.2.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8695</link><description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via crafted extension description/changelog could be abused by a malicious extension in Docker Desktop before 4.34.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8696 | A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via crafted extension publisher-url/additional-urls could be abused by a malicious extension in Docker Desktop before 4.34.2.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8696</link><description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via crafted extension publisher-url/additional-urls could be abused by a malicious extension in Docker Desktop before 4.34.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:00:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-24061 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Firewall menu in Control Panel in KASDA KW5515 version 4.3.1.0, allows attackers to execute arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-24061</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Firewall menu in Control Panel in KASDA KW5515 version 4.3.1.0, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code and steal cookies via a crafted script</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 17:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8631 | Privilege Defined With Unsafe Actions in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8631</link><description>A privilege escalation issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.6 prior to 17.1.7, from 17.2 prior to 17.2.5, and from 17.3 prior to 17.3.2. A user assigned the Admin Group Member custom role could have escalated their privileges to include other custom roles.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 17:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2743 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2743</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab-EE starting with version 13.3 before 17.1.7, 17.2 before 17.2.5, and 17.3 before 17.3.2 that would allow an attacker to modify an on-demand DAST scan without permissions and leak variables.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 17:09:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4612 | URL Redirection to Untrusted Site (&amp;#x27;Open Redirect&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4612</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 12.9 before 17.1.7, 17.2 before 17.2.5, and 17.3 before 17.3.2. Under certain conditions an open redirect vulnerability could allow for an account takeover by breaking the OAuth flow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 17:09:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4660 | Missing Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4660</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 11.2 before 17.1.7, all versions starting from 17.2 before 17.2.5, all versions starting from 17.3 before 17.3.2. It was possible for a guest to read the source code of a private project by using group templates.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 17:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5435 | Generation of Error Message Containing Sensitive Information in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5435</link><description>An issue has been discovered discovered in GitLab EE/CE affecting all versions starting from 15.10 before 17.1.7, all versions starting from 17.2 before 17.2.5, all versions starting from 17.3 before 17.3.2 will disclose user password from repository mirror configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 17:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6389 | Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6389</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab-CE/EE affecting all versions starting with 17.0 before 17.1.7, 17.2 before 17.2.5, and 17.3 before 17.3.2. An attacker as a guest user was able to access commit information via the release Atom endpoint, contrary to permissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 17:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6446 | Business Logic Errors in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6446</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 17.1 to 17.1.7, 17.2 prior to 17.2.5 and 17.3 prior to 17.3.2. A crafted URL could be used to trick a victim to trust an attacker controlled application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 17:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8124 | Inefficient Regular Expression Complexity in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8124</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.4 prior to 17.1.7, starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.5, starting from 17.3 prior to 17.3.2  which could cause Denial of Service via sending a large `glm_source` parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 17:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8635 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8635</link><description>A server-side request forgery issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.8 prior to 17.1.7, from 17.2 prior to 17.2.5, and from 17.3 prior to 17.3.2. It was possible for an attacker to make requests to internal resources using a custom Maven Dependency Proxy URL</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 17:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8640 | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command (&amp;#x27;Command Injection&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8640</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.11 prior to 17.1.7, from 17.2 prior to 17.2.5, and from 17.3 prior to 17.3.2. Due to incomplete input filtering, it was possible to inject commands into a connected Cube server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 17:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8754 | External Control of Critical State Data in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8754</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE/CE affecting all versions from 16.9.7 prior to 17.1.7, 17.2 prior to 17.2.5, and 17.3 prior to 17.3.2. An improper input validation error allows attacker to squat on accounts via linking arbitrary unclaimed provider identities when JWT authentication is configured.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 17:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6840 | Automation-controller: gain access to the k8s api server via job execution with container group</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6840</link><description>An improper authorization flaw exists in the Ansible Automation Controller. This flaw allows an attacker using the k8S API server to send an HTTP request with a service account token mounted via `automountServiceAccountToken: true`, resulting in privilege escalation to a service account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 16:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45826 | ThinManager® Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45826</link><description>CVE-2024-45826 IMPACT
Due to improper input validation, a path traversal and remote code execution vulnerability exists when the ThinManager® processes a crafted POST request. If exploited, a user can install an executable file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6658 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability of Authenticated User in Progress LoadMaster allows OS Command Injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6658</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability of Authenticated User in Progress LoadMaster allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects:



 Product 





Affected Versions 





LoadMaster 





From 7.2.55.0 to 7.2.60.0 (inclusive) 





  





From 7.2.49.0 to 7.2.54.11 (inclusive) 





  





7.2.48.12 and all prior versions 








Multi-Tenant Hypervisor 





7.1.35.11 and all prior versions 










ECS





All prior versions to 7.2.60.0 (inclusive)</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45825 | 5015-U8IHFT Denial-of-Service Vulnerability via CIP Message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45825</link><description>CVE-2024-45825 IMPACT
A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the affected products. The vulnerability occurs when a malformed CIP packet is sent over the network to the device and results in a major nonrecoverable fault causing a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6700 | Pega Platform versions 8.1 to Infinity 24.1.2 are affected by an XSS issue with App name.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6700</link><description>Pega Platform versions 8.1 to Infinity 24.1.2 are affected by an XSS issue with App name.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6701 | Pega Platform versions 8.1 to Infinity 24.1.2 are affected by an XSS issue with case type.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6701</link><description>Pega Platform versions 8.1 to Infinity 24.1.2 are affected by an XSS issue with case type.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6702 | Pega Platform versions 8.1 to Infinity 24.1.2 are affected by an HTML Injection issue with Stage.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6702</link><description>Pega Platform versions 8.1 to Infinity 24.1.2 are affected by an HTML Injection issue with Stage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42483 | ESP-NOW Replay Attacks Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42483</link><description>ESP-NOW Component provides a connectionless Wi-Fi communication protocol. An replay attacks vulnerability was discovered in the implementation of the ESP-NOW because the caches is not differentiated by message types, it is a single, shared resource for all kinds of messages, whether they are broadcast or unicast, and regardless of whether they are ciphertext or plaintext. This can result an attacker to clear the cache of its legitimate entries, there by creating an opportunity to re-inject previously captured packets. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.5.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42484 | ESP-NOW OOB Vulnerability In Group Type Message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42484</link><description>ESP-NOW Component provides a connectionless Wi-Fi communication protocol. An Out-of-Bound (OOB) vulnerability was discovered in the implementation of the ESP-NOW group type message because there is no check for the addrs_num field of the group type message. This can result in memory corruption related attacks. Normally there are two fields in the group information that need to be checked, i.e., the addrs_num field and the addrs_list fileld. Since we only checked the addrs_list field, an attacker can send a group type message with an invalid addrs_num field, which will cause the message handled by the firmware to be much larger than the current buffer, thus causing a memory corruption issue that goes beyond the payload length.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45823 | FactoryTalk® Batch View™ Authentication Bypass Vulnerability via shared secrets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45823</link><description>CVE-2024-45823 IMPACT



An
authentication bypass vulnerability exists in the affected product. The
vulnerability exists due to shared secrets across accounts and could allow a threat
actor to impersonate a user if the threat actor is able to enumerate additional
information required during authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6510 | Local privilege escalation vulnerability in AVG Internet Security</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6510</link><description>Local Privilege Escalation in AVG Internet Security v24 on Windows allows a local unprivileged user to escalate privileges to SYSTEM via COM-Hijacking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45824 | FactoryTalk® View Site Edition Remote Code Execution Vulnerability via Lack of Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45824</link><description>CVE-2024-45824 IMPACT



A remote
code vulnerability exists in the affected products. The vulnerability occurs
when chained with Path Traversal, Command Injection, and XSS Vulnerabilities
and allows for full unauthenticated remote code execution. The link in the
mitigations section below contains patches to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28990 | SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) Hardcoded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28990</link><description>SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) was found to contain a hard-coded credential authentication bypass vulnerability. If exploited, this vulnerability would allow access to the RabbitMQ management console.

We thank Trend Micro Zero Day Initiative (ZDI) for its ongoing partnership in coordinating with SolarWinds on responsible disclosure of this and other potential vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28991 | SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28991</link><description>SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) was found to be susceptible to a remote code execution vulnerability. If exploited, this vulnerability would allow an authenticated user to abuse the service, resulting in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40457 | No-IP Dynamic Update Client (DUC) v3.x uses cleartext credentials that may occur on a command line or in a file. NOTE: the vendor's position...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40457</link><description>No-IP Dynamic Update Client (DUC) v3.x uses cleartext credentials that may occur on a command line or in a file. NOTE: the vendor's position is that cleartext in /etc/default/noip-duc is recommended and is the intentional behavior.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3305 | Information Disclosure in Utarit Information&amp;#x27;s SoliClub</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3305</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Utarit Information SoliClub allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects SoliClub: before 4.4.0 for iOS, before 5.2.1 for Android.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3306 | IDOR in Utarit Information&amp;#x27;s SoliClub</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3306</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Utarit Information SoliClub allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects SoliClub: before 4.4.0 for iOS, before 5.2.1 for Android.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45850 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.10.5.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the Microsoft SharePoint...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45850</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.10.5.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the Microsoft SharePoint integration is installed on the server. For databases created with the SharePoint engine, an ‘INSERT’ query can be used for site column creation. If such a query is specially crafted to contain Python code and is run against the database, the code will be passed to an eval function and executed on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45851 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.10.5.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the Microsoft SharePoint...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45851</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.10.5.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the Microsoft SharePoint integration is installed on the server. For databases created with the SharePoint engine, an ‘INSERT’ query can be used for list item creation. If such a query is specially crafted to contain Python code and is run against the database, the code will be passed to an eval function and executed on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45852 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 23.3.2.0 and newer of the MindsDB platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded model to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45852</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 23.3.2.0 and newer of the MindsDB platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded model to run arbitrary code on the server when interacted with.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45853 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 23.10.2.0 and newer of the MindsDB platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded ‘inhous...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45853</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 23.10.2.0 and newer of the MindsDB platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded ‘inhouse’ model to run arbitrary code on the server when used for a prediction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45854 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 23.10.3.0 and newer of the MindsDB platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded ‘inhous...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45854</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 23.10.3.0 and newer of the MindsDB platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded ‘inhouse’ model to run arbitrary code on the server when a ‘describe’ query is run on it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45855 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 23.10.2.0 and newer of the MindsDB platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded ‘inhous...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45855</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 23.10.2.0 and newer of the MindsDB platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded ‘inhouse’ model to run arbitrary code on the server when using ‘finetune’ on it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45856 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in all versions of the MindsDB platform, enabling the execution of a JavaScript payload wh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45856</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in all versions of the MindsDB platform, enabling the execution of a JavaScript payload whenever a user enumerates an ML Engine, database, project, or dataset containing arbitrary JavaScript code within the web UI.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27320 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 0.0.8 and newer of the Refuel Autolabel library because of the way its classifi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27320</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 0.0.8 and newer of the Refuel Autolabel library because of the way its classification tasks handle provided CSV files. If a victim user creates a classification task using a maliciously crafted CSV file containing Python code, the code will be passed to an eval function which executes it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27321 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 0.0.8 and newer of the Refuel Autolabel library because of the way its multilab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27321</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 0.0.8 and newer of the Refuel Autolabel library because of the way its multilabel classification tasks handle provided CSV files. If a user creates a multilabel classification task using a maliciously crafted CSV file containing Python code, the code will be passed to an eval function which executes it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45846 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.10.3.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the Weaviate integration...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45846</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.10.3.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the Weaviate integration is installed on the server. If a specially crafted ‘SELECT WHERE’ clause containing Python code is run against a database created with the Weaviate engine, the code will be passed to an eval function and executed on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45847 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.11.4.2 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when one of several integrati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45847</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.11.4.2 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when one of several integrations is installed on the server. If a specially crafted ‘UPDATE’ query containing Python code is run against a database created with the specified integration engine, the code will be passed to an eval function and executed on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45848 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.12.4.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the ChromaDB integration...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45848</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.12.4.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the ChromaDB integration is installed on the server. If a specially crafted ‘INSERT’ query containing Python code is run against a database created with the ChromaDB engine, the code will be passed to an eval function and executed on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45849 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.10.5.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the Microsoft SharePoint...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45849</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.10.5.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the Microsoft SharePoint integration is installed on the server. For databases created with the SharePoint engine, an ‘INSERT’ query can be used for list creation. If such a query is specially crafted to contain Python code and is run against the database, the code will be passed to an eval function and executed on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45857 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 2.4.0 or newer of the Cleanlab project, enabling a maliciously crafted datalab.pkl f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45857</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 2.4.0 or newer of the Cleanlab project, enabling a maliciously crafted datalab.pkl file to run arbitrary code on an end user’s system when the data directory is loaded.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22503 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22503</link><description>Possible 
Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation Vulnerability

in eDirectory has been discovered in
OpenText™ eDirectory 9.2.3.0000.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22518 | Sensitive Information logging in NetIQ Identity Manager Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22518</link><description>A vulnerability identified in OpenText™ 
Identity Manager AzureAD Driver that allows logging of sensitive information into log file. This impacts all versions before 5.1.4.0</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22532 | Possible NLDAP Denial of Service attack Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22532</link><description>Possible NLDAP Denial of Service attack Vulnerability

in eDirectory has been discovered in
OpenText™ 
eDirectory before 9.2.4.0000.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22533 | Possible Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22533</link><description>Possible Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File Vulnerability

in eDirectory has been discovered in
OpenText™ eDirectory 9.2.4.0000.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-38131 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38131</link><description>Possible Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability

in eDirectory has been discovered in
OpenText™ eDirectory 9.2.5.0000.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-38132 | Possible External service interaction Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38132</link><description>Possible 
External Service Interaction attack

in eDirectory has been discovered in
OpenText™ eDirectory. This impact all version before 9.2.6.0000.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-38133 | Possible Improper authentication Vulnerability in OpenText eDirectory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38133</link><description>Possible 
External Service Interaction attack

in eDirectory has been discovered in
OpenText™ eDirectory. This impact all version before 9.2.6.0000.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-26322 | Possible Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File Vulnerability in Identity Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26322</link><description>Possible Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File Vulnerability

in Identity Manager has been discovered in
OpenText™ 
Identity Manager REST Driver. This impact version before 1.1.2.0200.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8749 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Idoit pro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8749</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in idoit pro version 28. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to send a specially crafted query to the ID parameter in /var/www/html/src/classes/modules/api/model/cmdb/isys_api_model_cmdb_objects_by_relation.class.php and retrieve all the information stored in the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 11:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8750 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Idoit pro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8750</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in idoit pro version 28. This vulnerability allows an attacker to retrieve session details of an authenticated user due to lack of proper sanitization of the following parameters (id,lang,mNavID,name,pID,treeNode,type,view).</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 11:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2010 | Reflected XSS in TE Informatics&amp;#x27; V5 Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2010</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in TE Informatics V5 allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects V5: before 6.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 08:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8522 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.7 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;c_only_fields&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8522</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'c_only_fields' parameter of the /wp-json/learnpress/v1/courses REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 08:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8529 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.7 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;c_fields&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8529</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'c_fields' parameter of the /wp-json/lp/v1/courses/archive-course REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 08:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8622 | amCharts: Charts and Maps &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8622</link><description>The amCharts: Charts and Maps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'amcharts_javascript' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 due to the ability to supply arbitrary JavaScript a lack of nonce validation on the preview functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 08:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3163 | Easy Property Listings &amp;lt; 3.5.4 - Arbitrary Contact Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3163</link><description>The Easy Property Listings WordPress plugin before 3.5.4 does not have CSRF check when deleting contacts in bulk, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin delete them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5799 | CM Pop-Up Banners for WordPress &amp;lt; 1.7.3 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5799</link><description>The CM Pop-Up Banners for WordPress plugin before 1.7.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its popup fields, which could allow high privilege users such as Contributors to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6017 | Music Request Manager &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6017</link><description>The Music Request Manager WordPress plugin through 1.3 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6018 | Music Request Manager &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6018</link><description>The Music Request Manager WordPress plugin through 1.3 does not escape the $_SERVER['REQUEST_URI'] parameter before outputting it back in an attribute, which could lead to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in old web browsers</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6019 | Music Request Manager &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6019</link><description>The Music Request Manager WordPress plugin through 1.3 does not sanitise and escape incoming music requests, which could allow unauthenticated users to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks against administrators</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6887 | Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress &amp;lt; 1.12.16 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6887</link><description>The Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress  WordPress plugin before 1.12.16 does not sanitise and escape some of its Giveaways settings, which could allow high privilege users such as editor and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7766 | Adicon Server &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7766</link><description>The Adicon Server WordPress plugin through 1.2 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7816 | Gixaw Chat &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7816</link><description>The Gixaw Chat WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7817 | Misiek Photo Album &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Album Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7817</link><description>The Misiek Photo Album WordPress plugin through 1.4.3 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users delete arbitrary albums via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7818 | Misiek Photo Album &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7818</link><description>The Misiek Photo Album WordPress plugin through 1.4.3 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7820 | ILC Thickbox &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Settings update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7820</link><description>The ILC Thickbox WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7822 | Quick Code &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7822</link><description>The Quick Code WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7859 | Visual Sound &amp;lt;= 1.03 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7859</link><description>The Visual Sound WordPress plugin through 1.03 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7860 | Simple Headline Rotator &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7860</link><description>The Simple Headline Rotator WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7861 | Misiek Paypal &amp;lt;= 1.1.20090324 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7861</link><description>The Misiek Paypal WordPress plugin through 1.1.20090324 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7862 | Blog Introduction &amp;lt;= 0.3.0 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7862</link><description>The blogintroduction-wordpress-plugin WordPress plugin through 0.3.0 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8054 | MM-Breaking News &amp;lt;= 0.7.9 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8054</link><description>The MM-Breaking News WordPress plugin through 0.7.9 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8056 | MM-Breaking News &amp;lt;= 0.7.9 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8056</link><description>The MM-Breaking News WordPress plugin through 0.7.9 does not escape the $_SERVER['REQUEST_URI'] parameter before outputting it back in an attribute, which could lead to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in old web browsers</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45624 | Exposure of sensitive information due to incompatible policies issue exists in Pgpool-II. If a database user accesses a query cache, table d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45624</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information due to incompatible policies issue exists in Pgpool-II. If a database user accesses a query cache, table data unauthorized for the user may be retrieved.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 04:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8711 | SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System includes exposure of information through directory listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8711</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /includes/. The manipulation leads to exposure of information through directory listing. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 03:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38222 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38222</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 03:22:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8710 | code-projects Inventory Management Products Table Page viewProduct.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8710</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Inventory Management 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /model/viewProduct.php of the component Products Table Page. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 03:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8709 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System admin_class.php save_user sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8709</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. Affected is the function delete_user/save_user of the file /admin_class.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 02:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8708 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System categories.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8708</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file categories.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 02:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29847 | Deserialization of untrusted data in the agent portal of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote unauthenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29847</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data in the agent portal of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32840 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32840</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32842 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32842</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32843 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32843</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32845 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32845</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32846 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32846</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32848 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32848</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34779 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34779</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34783 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34783</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34785 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34785</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37397 | An External XML Entity (XXE) vulnerability in the provisioning web service of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37397</link><description>An External XML Entity (XXE) vulnerability in the provisioning web service of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to leak API secrets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8707 | 云课网络科技有限公司 Yunke Online School System Appadmin.php downfile path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8707</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 云课网络科技有限公司 Yunke Online School System up to 3.0.6. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function downfile of the file application/admin/controller/Appadmin.php. The manipulation of the argument url leads to path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8706 | JFinalCMS com.cms.util.TemplateUtils update path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8706</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JFinalCMS up to 20240903. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function update of the file /admin/template/update of the component com.cms.util.TemplateUtils. The manipulation of the argument fileName leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 23:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28981 | Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Data Integration &amp;amp; Analytics - Insufficiently Protected Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28981</link><description>Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Data Integration &amp; Analytics versions before 10.1.0.0 and 9.3.0.8, including 8.3.x, discloses database passwords when searching metadata injectable fields.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 23:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7890 | Local privilege escalation allows a low-privileged user to gain SYSTEM privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7890</link><description>Local privilege escalation allows a low-privileged user to gain SYSTEM privileges in Citrix Workspace app for Windows</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 22:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8705 | Shandong Star Measurement and Control Equipment Heating Network Wireless Monitoring System UCCGSrv.asmx GetDataKindByType sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8705</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shandong Star Measurement and Control Equipment Heating Network Wireless Monitoring System 5.6.2 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function GetDataKindByType of the file /DataSrvs/UCCGSrv.asmx. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 22:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7889 | Local privilege escalation allows a low-privileged user to gain SYSTEM privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7889</link><description>Local privilege escalation allows a low-privileged user to gain SYSTEM privileges in Citrix Workspace app for Windows</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 22:22:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8694 | JFinalCMS com.cms.controller.admin.TemplateController update path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8694</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in JFinalCMS up to 20240903. This affects the function update of the file /admin/template/update of the component com.cms.controller.admin.TemplateController. The manipulation of the argument fileName leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 21:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8693 | Kaon CG3000 dhcpcd Command cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8693</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Kaon CG3000 1.01.43. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component dhcpcd Command Handler. The manipulation of the argument -h with the input  leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 19:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44541 | evilnapsis Inventio Lite Versions v4 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "username" parameter in "/?action=processlogin."</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44541</link><description>evilnapsis Inventio Lite Versions v4 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "username" parameter in "/?action=processlogin."</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 19:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8692 | TDuckCloud TDuckPro password recovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8692</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TDuckCloud TDuckPro up to 6.3. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to weak password recovery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 18:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42760 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Ellevo v.6.2.0.38160 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /api/mob/instrucao/cont...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42760</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Ellevo v.6.2.0.38160 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /api/mob/instrucao/conta/destinatarios component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 18:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44574 | RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the sys_conf function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44574</link><description>RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the sys_conf function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 17:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44575 | RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 does not set the Secure attribute for sensitive cookies in HTTPS sessions, which could cause the user agent to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44575</link><description>RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 does not set the Secure attribute for sensitive cookies in HTTPS sessions, which could cause the user agent to send those cookies in cleartext over an HTTP session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 17:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44577 | RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the time_date function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44577</link><description>RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the time_date function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 17:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44570 | RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain a code injection vulnerability via the getParams function in phpinf.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44570</link><description>RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain a code injection vulnerability via the getParams function in phpinf.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 17:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44571 | RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain incorrect access control in the mService function at phpinf.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44571</link><description>RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain incorrect access control in the mService function at phpinf.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 17:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44572 | RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the sys_mgmt function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44572</link><description>RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the sys_mgmt function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 17:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44573 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the VLAN configuration of RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44573</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the VLAN configuration of RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 17:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20304 | Cisco IOS XR Software Packet Memory Exhaustion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20304</link><description>A vulnerability in the multicast traceroute version 2 (Mtrace2) feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to exhaust the UDP packet memory of an affected device.

This vulnerability exists because the Mtrace2 code does not properly handle packet memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust the incoming UDP packet memory. The affected device would not be able to process higher-level UDP-based protocols packets, possibly causing a denial of service (DoS) condition.
Note: This vulnerability can be exploited using IPv4 or IPv6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20317 | Cisco IOS XR Software Layer 2 Services Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20317</link><description>A vulnerability in the handling of specific Ethernet frames by Cisco IOS XR Software for various Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) platforms could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause critical priority packets to be dropped, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.

This vulnerability is due to incorrect classification of certain types of Ethernet frames that are received on an interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific types of Ethernet frames to or through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause control plane protocol relationships to fail, resulting in a DoS condition. For more information, see the  section of this advisory.
Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20343 | Cisco IOS XR Software CLI Arbitrary File Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20343</link><description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read any file in the file system of the underlying Linux operating system. The attacker must have valid credentials on the affected device.

This vulnerability is due to incorrect validation of the arguments that are passed to a specific CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to an affected device with low-privileged credentials and using the affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker access files in read-only mode on the Linux file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20381 | Cisco Network Services Orchestrator Configuration Update Authorization Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20381</link><description>A vulnerability in the JSON-RPC API feature in ConfD that is used by the web-based management interfaces of Cisco Crosswork Network Services Orchestrator (NSO), Cisco Optical Site Manager, and Cisco RV340 Dual WAN Gigabit VPN Routers could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to modify the configuration of an affected application or device.

This vulnerability is due to improper authorization checks on the API. An attacker with privileges sufficient to access the affected application or device could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to the JSON-RPC API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to make unauthorized modifications to the configuration of the affected application or device, including creating new user accounts or elevating their own privileges on an affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20390 | Cisco IOS XR Software Dedicated XML Agent TCP Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20390</link><description>A vulnerability in the Dedicated XML Agent feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) on XML TCP listen port 38751.

This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper error validation of ingress XML packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a sustained, crafted stream of XML traffic to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause XML TCP port 38751 to become unreachable while the attack traffic persists.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20398 | Cisco IOS XR Software Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20398</link><description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to obtain read/write file system access on the underlying operating system of an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user arguments that are passed to specific CLI commands. An attacker with a low-privileged account could exploit this vulnerability by using crafted commands at the prompt. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20406 | Cisco IOS XR Software Intermediate System-to-Intermediate System Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20406</link><description>A vulnerability in the segment routing feature for the Intermediate System-to-Intermediate System (IS-IS) protocol of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of ingress IS-IS packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific IS-IS packets to an affected device after forming an adjacency. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the IS-IS process on all affected devices that are participating in the Flexible Algorithm to crash and restart, resulting in a DoS condition.
Note: The IS-IS protocol is a routing protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must be Layer 2-adjacent to the affected device and must have formed an adjacency. This vulnerability affects segment routing for IS-IS over IPv4 and IPv6 control planes as well as devices that are configured as level 1, level 2, or multi-level routing IS-IS type.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20483 | Cisco IOS XR PON Controller Command Injection Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20483</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Routed PON Controller Software, which runs as a docker container on hardware that is supported by Cisco IOS XR Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with Administrator-level privileges on the PON Manager or direct access to the PON Manager MongoDB instance to perform command injection attacks on the PON Controller container and execute arbitrary commands as root.

These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration commands. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the PON controller.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20489 | Cisco Routed Passive Optical Network Cleartext Password Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20489</link><description>A vulnerability in the storage method of the PON Controller configuration file could allow an authenticated, local attacker with low privileges to obtain the MongoDB credentials.

This vulnerability is due to improper storage of the unencrypted database credentials on the device that is running Cisco IOS XR Software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the configuration files on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view MongoDB credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8687 | PAN-OS: Cleartext Exposure of GlobalProtect Portal Passcodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8687</link><description>An information exposure vulnerability exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables a GlobalProtect end user to learn both the configured GlobalProtect uninstall password and the configured disable or disconnect passcode. After the password or passcode is known, end users can uninstall, disable, or disconnect GlobalProtect even if the GlobalProtect app configuration would not normally permit them to do so.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8688 | PAN-OS: Arbitrary File Read Vulnerability in the Command Line Interface (CLI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8688</link><description>An improper neutralization of matching symbols vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS command line interface (CLI) enables authenticated administrators (including read-only administrators) with access to the CLI to to read arbitrary files on the firewall.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8689 | ActiveMQ Content Pack: Cleartext Exposure of Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8689</link><description>A problem with the ActiveMQ integration for both Cortex XSOAR and Cortex XSIAM can result in the cleartext exposure of the configured ActiveMQ credentials in log bundles.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8690 | Cortex XDR Agent: Local Windows Administrator Can Disable the Agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8690</link><description>A problem with a detection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices enables a user with Windows administrator privileges to disable the agent. This issue may be leveraged by malware to disable the Cortex XDR agent and then to perform malicious activity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8691 | PAN-OS: User Impersonation in GlobalProtect Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8691</link><description>A vulnerability in the GlobalProtect portal in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious authenticated GlobalProtect user to impersonate another GlobalProtect user. Active GlobalProtect users impersonated by an attacker who is exploiting this vulnerability are disconnected from GlobalProtect. Upon exploitation, PAN-OS logs indicate that the impersonated user authenticated to GlobalProtect, which hides the identity of the attacker.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8097 | Sensitive information exposure when the org.glassfish.admingui LOGGER is set to FINEST level</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8097</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Payara Platform Payara Server (Logging modules) allows Sensitive credentials posted in plain-text on the server log.This issue affects Payara Server: from 6.0.0 before 6.18.0, from 6.2022.1 before 6.2024.9, from 5.20.0 before 5.67.0, from 5.2020.2 before 5.2022.5, from 4.1.2.191.0 before 4.1.2.191.50.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8686 | PAN-OS: Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8686</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated administrator to bypass system restrictions and run arbitrary commands as root on the firewall.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39378 | Audition | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39378</link><description>Audition versions 24.4.1, 23.6.6 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:16:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41868 | Audition | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41868</link><description>Audition versions 24.4.1, 23.6.6 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44851 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Discussion section of Perfex CRM v1.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44851</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Discussion section of Perfex CRM v1.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Content parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44466 | COMFAST CF-XR11 V2.7.2 has a command injection vulnerability in function sub_424CB4. Attackers can send POST request messages to /usr/bin/we...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44466</link><description>COMFAST CF-XR11 V2.7.2 has a command injection vulnerability in function sub_424CB4. Attackers can send POST request messages to /usr/bin/webmgnt and inject commands into parameter iface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5760 | The Samsung Universal Print Driver for Windows is potentially vulnerable to escalation of privilege allowing the creation of a reverse shell...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5760</link><description>The Samsung Universal Print Driver for Windows is potentially vulnerable to escalation of privilege allowing the creation of a reverse shell in the tool. This is only applicable for products in the application released or manufactured before 2018.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:35:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7312 | REST Interface Link Redirection via Host parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7312</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Payara Platform Payara Server (REST Management Interface modules) allows Session Hijacking.This issue affects Payara Server: from 6.0.0 before 6.18.0, from 6.2022.1 before 6.2024.9, from 5.2020.2 before 5.2022.5, from 5.20.0 before 5.67.0, from 4.1.2.191.0 before 4.1.2.191.50.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:35:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45009 | mptcp: pm: only decrement add_addr_accepted for MPJ req</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45009</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mptcp: pm: only decrement add_addr_accepted for MPJ req

Adding the following warning ...

  WARN_ON_ONCE(msk-&gt;pm.add_addr_accepted == 0)

... before decrementing the add_addr_accepted counter helped to find a
bug when running the "remove single subflow" subtest from the
mptcp_join.sh selftest.

Removing a 'subflow' endpoint will first trigger a RM_ADDR, then the
subflow closure. Before this patch, and upon the reception of the
RM_ADDR, the other peer will then try to decrement this
add_addr_accepted. That's not correct because the attached subflows have
not been created upon the reception of an ADD_ADDR.

A way to solve that is to decrement the counter only if the attached
subflow was an MP_JOIN to a remote id that was not 0, and initiated by
the host receiving the RM_ADDR.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45010 | mptcp: pm: only mark &amp;#x27;subflow&amp;#x27; endp as available</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45010</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mptcp: pm: only mark 'subflow' endp as available

Adding the following warning ...

  WARN_ON_ONCE(msk-&gt;pm.local_addr_used == 0)

... before decrementing the local_addr_used counter helped to find a bug
when running the "remove single address" subtest from the mptcp_join.sh
selftests.

Removing a 'signal' endpoint will trigger the removal of all subflows
linked to this endpoint via mptcp_pm_nl_rm_addr_or_subflow() with
rm_type == MPTCP_MIB_RMSUBFLOW. This will decrement the local_addr_used
counter, which is wrong in this case because this counter is linked to
'subflow' endpoints, and here it is a 'signal' endpoint that is being
removed.

Now, the counter is decremented, only if the ID is being used outside
of mptcp_pm_nl_rm_addr_or_subflow(), only for 'subflow' endpoints, and
if the ID is not 0 -- local_addr_used is not taking into account these
ones. This marking of the ID as being available, and the decrement is
done no matter if a subflow using this ID is currently available,
because the subflow could have been closed before.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45011 | char: xillybus: Check USB endpoints when probing device</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45011</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

char: xillybus: Check USB endpoints when probing device

Ensure, as the driver probes the device, that all endpoints that the
driver may attempt to access exist and are of the correct type.

All XillyUSB devices must have a Bulk IN and Bulk OUT endpoint at
address 1. This is verified in xillyusb_setup_base_eps().

On top of that, a XillyUSB device may have additional Bulk OUT
endpoints. The information about these endpoints' addresses is deduced
from a data structure (the IDT) that the driver fetches from the device
while probing it. These endpoints are checked in setup_channels().

A XillyUSB device never has more than one IN endpoint, as all data
towards the host is multiplexed in this single Bulk IN endpoint. This is
why setup_channels() only checks OUT endpoints.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45012 | nouveau/firmware: use dma non-coherent allocator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45012</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nouveau/firmware: use dma non-coherent allocator

Currently, enabling SG_DEBUG in the kernel will cause nouveau to hit a
BUG() on startup, when the iommu is enabled:

kernel BUG at include/linux/scatterlist.h:187!
invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP NOPTI
CPU: 7 PID: 930 Comm: (udev-worker) Not tainted 6.9.0-rc3Lyude-Test+ #30
Hardware name: MSI MS-7A39/A320M GAMING PRO (MS-7A39), BIOS 1.I0 01/22/2019
RIP: 0010:sg_init_one+0x85/0xa0
Code: 69 88 32 01 83 e1 03 f6 c3 03 75 20 a8 01 75 1e 48 09 cb 41 89 54
24 08 49 89 1c 24 41 89 6c 24 0c 5b 5d 41 5c e9 7b b9 88 00 &lt;0f&gt; 0b 0f 0b
0f 0b 48 8b 05 5e 46 9a 01 eb b2 66 66 2e 0f 1f 84 00
RSP: 0018:ffffa776017bf6a0 EFLAGS: 00010246
RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffffa77600d87000 RCX: 000000000000002b
RDX: 0000000000000001 RSI: 0000000000000000 RDI: ffffa77680d87000
RBP: 000000000000e000 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: 0000000000000000
R10: ffff98f4c46aa508 R11: 0000000000000000 R12: ffff98f4c46aa508
R13: ffff98f4c46aa008 R14: ffffa77600d4a000 R15: ffffa77600d4a018
FS:  00007feeb5aae980(0000) GS:ffff98f5c4dc0000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 00007f22cb9a4520 CR3: 00000001043ba000 CR4: 00000000003506f0
Call Trace:
 
 ? die+0x36/0x90
 ? do_trap+0xdd/0x100
 ? sg_init_one+0x85/0xa0
 ? do_error_trap+0x65/0x80
 ? sg_init_one+0x85/0xa0
 ? exc_invalid_op+0x50/0x70
 ? sg_init_one+0x85/0xa0
 ? asm_exc_invalid_op+0x1a/0x20
 ? sg_init_one+0x85/0xa0
 nvkm_firmware_ctor+0x14a/0x250 [nouveau]
 nvkm_falcon_fw_ctor+0x42/0x70 [nouveau]
 ga102_gsp_booter_ctor+0xb4/0x1a0 [nouveau]
 r535_gsp_oneinit+0xb3/0x15f0 [nouveau]
 ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
 ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
 ? nvkm_udevice_new+0x95/0x140 [nouveau]
 ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
 ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
 ? ktime_get+0x47/0xb0

Fix this by using the non-coherent allocator instead, I think there
might be a better answer to this, but it involve ripping up some of
APIs using sg lists.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45013 | nvme: move stopping keep-alive into nvme_uninit_ctrl()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45013</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nvme: move stopping keep-alive into nvme_uninit_ctrl()

Commit 4733b65d82bd ("nvme: start keep-alive after admin queue setup")
moves starting keep-alive from nvme_start_ctrl() into
nvme_init_ctrl_finish(), but don't move stopping keep-alive into
nvme_uninit_ctrl(), so keep-alive work can be started and keep pending
after failing to start controller, finally use-after-free is triggered if
nvme host driver is unloaded.

This patch fixes kernel panic when running nvme/004 in case that connection
failure is triggered, by moving stopping keep-alive into nvme_uninit_ctrl().

This way is reasonable because keep-alive is now started in
nvme_init_ctrl_finish().</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45014 | s390/boot: Avoid possible physmem_info segment corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45014</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

s390/boot: Avoid possible physmem_info segment corruption

When physical memory for the kernel image is allocated it does not
consider extra memory required for offsetting the image start to
match it with the lower 20 bits of KASLR virtual base address. That
might lead to kernel access beyond its memory range.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45015 | drm/msm/dpu: move dpu_encoder&amp;#x27;s connector assignment to atomic_enable()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45015</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/msm/dpu: move dpu_encoder's connector assignment to atomic_enable()

For cases where the crtc's connectors_changed was set without enable/active
getting toggled , there is an atomic_enable() call followed by an
atomic_disable() but without an atomic_mode_set().

This results in a NULL ptr access for the dpu_encoder_get_drm_fmt() call in
the atomic_enable() as the dpu_encoder's connector was cleared in the
atomic_disable() but not re-assigned as there was no atomic_mode_set() call.

Fix the NULL ptr access by moving the assignment for atomic_enable() and also
use drm_atomic_get_new_connector_for_encoder() to get the connector from
the atomic_state.

Patchwork: https://patchwork.freedesktop.org/patch/606729/</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45016 | netem: fix return value if duplicate enqueue fails</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45016</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netem: fix return value if duplicate enqueue fails

There is a bug in netem_enqueue() introduced by
commit 5845f706388a ("net: netem: fix skb length BUG_ON in __skb_to_sgvec")
that can lead to a use-after-free.

This commit made netem_enqueue() always return NET_XMIT_SUCCESS
when a packet is duplicated, which can cause the parent qdisc's q.qlen
to be mistakenly incremented. When this happens qlen_notify() may be
skipped on the parent during destruction, leaving a dangling pointer
for some classful qdiscs like DRR.

There are two ways for the bug happen:

- If the duplicated packet is dropped by rootq-&gt;enqueue() and then
  the original packet is also dropped.
- If rootq-&gt;enqueue() sends the duplicated packet to a different qdisc
  and the original packet is dropped.

In both cases NET_XMIT_SUCCESS is returned even though no packets
are enqueued at the netem qdisc.

The fix is to defer the enqueue of the duplicate packet until after
the original packet has been guaranteed to return NET_XMIT_SUCCESS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45017 | net/mlx5: Fix IPsec RoCE MPV trace call</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45017</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/mlx5: Fix IPsec RoCE MPV trace call

Prevent the call trace below from happening, by not allowing IPsec
creation over a slave, if master device doesn't support IPsec.

WARNING: CPU: 44 PID: 16136 at kernel/locking/rwsem.c:240 down_read+0x75/0x94
Modules linked in: esp4_offload esp4 act_mirred act_vlan cls_flower sch_ingress mlx5_vdpa vringh vhost_iotlb vdpa mst_pciconf(OE) nfsv3 nfs_acl nfs lockd grace fscache netfs xt_CHECKSUM xt_MASQUERADE xt_conntrack ipt_REJECT nf_reject_ipv4 nft_compat nft_counter nft_chain_nat nf_nat nf_conntrack nf_defrag_ipv6 nf_defrag_ipv4 rfkill cuse fuse rpcrdma sunrpc rdma_ucm ib_srpt ib_isert iscsi_target_mod target_core_mod ib_umad ib_iser libiscsi scsi_transport_iscsi rdma_cm ib_ipoib iw_cm ib_cm ipmi_ssif intel_rapl_msr intel_rapl_common amd64_edac edac_mce_amd kvm_amd kvm irqbypass crct10dif_pclmul crc32_pclmul mlx5_ib ghash_clmulni_intel sha1_ssse3 dell_smbios ib_uverbs aesni_intel crypto_simd dcdbas wmi_bmof dell_wmi_descriptor cryptd pcspkr ib_core acpi_ipmi sp5100_tco ccp i2c_piix4 ipmi_si ptdma k10temp ipmi_devintf ipmi_msghandler acpi_power_meter acpi_cpufreq ext4 mbcache jbd2 sd_mod t10_pi sg mgag200 drm_kms_helper syscopyarea sysfillrect mlx5_core sysimgblt fb_sys_fops cec
 ahci libahci mlxfw drm pci_hyperv_intf libata tg3 sha256_ssse3 tls megaraid_sas i2c_algo_bit psample wmi dm_mirror dm_region_hash dm_log dm_mod [last unloaded: mst_pci]
CPU: 44 PID: 16136 Comm: kworker/44:3 Kdump: loaded Tainted: GOE 5.15.0-20240509.el8uek.uek7_u3_update_v6.6_ipsec_bf.x86_64 #2
Hardware name: Dell Inc. PowerEdge R7525/074H08, BIOS 2.0.3 01/15/2021
Workqueue: events xfrm_state_gc_task
RIP: 0010:down_read+0x75/0x94
Code: 00 48 8b 45 08 65 48 8b 14 25 80 fc 01 00 83 e0 02 48 09 d0 48 83 c8 01 48 89 45 08 5d 31 c0 89 c2 89 c6 89 c7 e9 cb 88 3b 00 &lt;0f&gt; 0b 48 8b 45 08 a8 01 74 b2 a8 02 75 ae 48 89 c2 48 83 ca 02 f0
RSP: 0018:ffffb26387773da8 EFLAGS: 00010282
RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffffa08b658af900 RCX: 0000000000000001
RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: ff886bc5e1366f2f RDI: 0000000000000000
RBP: ffffa08b658af940 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: 0000000000000000
R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000000 R12: ffffa0a9bfb31540
R13: ffffa0a9bfb37900 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: ffffa0a9bfb37905
FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffffa0a9bfb00000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 000055a45ed814e8 CR3: 000000109038a000 CR4: 0000000000350ee0
Call Trace:
 
 ? show_trace_log_lvl+0x1d6/0x2f9
 ? show_trace_log_lvl+0x1d6/0x2f9
 ? mlx5_devcom_for_each_peer_begin+0x29/0x60 [mlx5_core]
 ? down_read+0x75/0x94
 ? __warn+0x80/0x113
 ? down_read+0x75/0x94
 ? report_bug+0xa4/0x11d
 ? handle_bug+0x35/0x8b
 ? exc_invalid_op+0x14/0x75
 ? asm_exc_invalid_op+0x16/0x1b
 ? down_read+0x75/0x94
 ? down_read+0xe/0x94
 mlx5_devcom_for_each_peer_begin+0x29/0x60 [mlx5_core]
 mlx5_ipsec_fs_roce_tx_destroy+0xb1/0x130 [mlx5_core]
 tx_destroy+0x1b/0xc0 [mlx5_core]
 tx_ft_put+0x53/0xc0 [mlx5_core]
 mlx5e_xfrm_free_state+0x45/0x90 [mlx5_core]
 ___xfrm_state_destroy+0x10f/0x1a2
 xfrm_state_gc_task+0x81/0xa9
 process_one_work+0x1f1/0x3c6
 worker_thread+0x53/0x3e4
 ? process_one_work.cold+0x46/0x3c
 kthread+0x127/0x144
 ? set_kthread_struct+0x60/0x52
 ret_from_fork+0x22/0x2d
 
---[ end trace 5ef7896144d398e1 ]---</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45018 | netfilter: flowtable: initialise extack before use</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45018</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: flowtable: initialise extack before use

Fix missing initialisation of extack in flow offload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45019 | net/mlx5e: Take state lock during tx timeout reporter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45019</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/mlx5e: Take state lock during tx timeout reporter

mlx5e_safe_reopen_channels() requires the state lock taken. The
referenced changed in the Fixes tag removed the lock to fix another
issue. This patch adds it back but at a later point (when calling
mlx5e_safe_reopen_channels()) to avoid the deadlock referenced in the
Fixes tag.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45020 | bpf: Fix a kernel verifier crash in stacksafe()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45020</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: Fix a kernel verifier crash in stacksafe()

Daniel Hodges reported a kernel verifier crash when playing with sched-ext.
Further investigation shows that the crash is due to invalid memory access
in stacksafe(). More specifically, it is the following code:

    if (exact != NOT_EXACT &amp;&amp;
        old-&gt;stack[spi].slot_type[i % BPF_REG_SIZE] !=
        cur-&gt;stack[spi].slot_type[i % BPF_REG_SIZE])
            return false;

The 'i' iterates old-&gt;allocated_stack.
If cur-&gt;allocated_stack &lt; old-&gt;allocated_stack the out-of-bound
access will happen.

To fix the issue add 'i &gt;= cur-&gt;allocated_stack' check such that if
the condition is true, stacksafe() should fail. Otherwise,
cur-&gt;stack[spi].slot_type[i % BPF_REG_SIZE] memory access is legal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45021 | memcg_write_event_control(): fix a user-triggerable oops</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45021</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

memcg_write_event_control(): fix a user-triggerable oops

we are *not* guaranteed that anything past the terminating NUL
is mapped (let alone initialized with anything sane).</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45022 | mm/vmalloc: fix page mapping if vm_area_alloc_pages() with high order fallback to order 0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45022</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/vmalloc: fix page mapping if vm_area_alloc_pages() with high order fallback to order 0

The __vmap_pages_range_noflush() assumes its argument pages** contains
pages with the same page shift.  However, since commit e9c3cda4d86e ("mm,
vmalloc: fix high order __GFP_NOFAIL allocations"), if gfp_flags includes
__GFP_NOFAIL with high order in vm_area_alloc_pages() and page allocation
failed for high order, the pages** may contain two different page shifts
(high order and order-0).  This could lead __vmap_pages_range_noflush() to
perform incorrect mappings, potentially resulting in memory corruption.

Users might encounter this as follows (vmap_allow_huge = true, 2M is for
PMD_SIZE):

kvmalloc(2M, __GFP_NOFAIL|GFP_X)
    __vmalloc_node_range_noprof(vm_flags=VM_ALLOW_HUGE_VMAP)
        vm_area_alloc_pages(order=9) ---&gt; order-9 allocation failed and fallback to order-0
            vmap_pages_range()
                vmap_pages_range_noflush()
                    __vmap_pages_range_noflush(page_shift = 21) ----&gt; wrong mapping happens

We can remove the fallback code because if a high-order allocation fails,
__vmalloc_node_range_noprof() will retry with order-0.  Therefore, it is
unnecessary to fallback to order-0 here.  Therefore, fix this by removing
the fallback code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45023 | md/raid1: Fix data corruption for degraded array with slow disk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45023</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

md/raid1: Fix data corruption for degraded array with slow disk

read_balance() will avoid reading from slow disks as much as possible,
however, if valid data only lands in slow disks, and a new normal disk
is still in recovery, unrecovered data can be read:

raid1_read_request
 read_balance
  raid1_should_read_first
  -&gt; return false
  choose_best_rdev
  -&gt; normal disk is not recovered, return -1
  choose_bb_rdev
  -&gt; missing the checking of recovery, return the normal disk
 -&gt; read unrecovered data

Root cause is that the checking of recovery is missing in
choose_bb_rdev(). Hence add such checking to fix the problem.

Also fix similar problem in choose_slow_rdev().</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45024 | mm/hugetlb: fix hugetlb vs. core-mm PT locking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45024</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/hugetlb: fix hugetlb vs. core-mm PT locking

We recently made GUP's common page table walking code to also walk hugetlb
VMAs without most hugetlb special-casing, preparing for the future of
having less hugetlb-specific page table walking code in the codebase. 
Turns out that we missed one page table locking detail: page table locking
for hugetlb folios that are not mapped using a single PMD/PUD.

Assume we have hugetlb folio that spans multiple PTEs (e.g., 64 KiB
hugetlb folios on arm64 with 4 KiB base page size).  GUP, as it walks the
page tables, will perform a pte_offset_map_lock() to grab the PTE table
lock.

However, hugetlb that concurrently modifies these page tables would
actually grab the mm-&gt;page_table_lock: with USE_SPLIT_PTE_PTLOCKS, the
locks would differ.  Something similar can happen right now with hugetlb
folios that span multiple PMDs when USE_SPLIT_PMD_PTLOCKS.

This issue can be reproduced [1], for example triggering:

[ 3105.936100] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[ 3105.939323] WARNING: CPU: 31 PID: 2732 at mm/gup.c:142 try_grab_folio+0x11c/0x188
[ 3105.944634] Modules linked in: [...]
[ 3105.974841] CPU: 31 PID: 2732 Comm: reproducer Not tainted 6.10.0-64.eln141.aarch64 #1
[ 3105.980406] Hardware name: QEMU KVM Virtual Machine, BIOS edk2-20240524-4.fc40 05/24/2024
[ 3105.986185] pstate: 60000005 (nZCv daif -PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
[ 3105.991108] pc : try_grab_folio+0x11c/0x188
[ 3105.994013] lr : follow_page_pte+0xd8/0x430
[ 3105.996986] sp : ffff80008eafb8f0
[ 3105.999346] x29: ffff80008eafb900 x28: ffffffe8d481f380 x27: 00f80001207cff43
[ 3106.004414] x26: 0000000000000001 x25: 0000000000000000 x24: ffff80008eafba48
[ 3106.009520] x23: 0000ffff9372f000 x22: ffff7a54459e2000 x21: ffff7a546c1aa978
[ 3106.014529] x20: ffffffe8d481f3c0 x19: 0000000000610041 x18: 0000000000000001
[ 3106.019506] x17: 0000000000000001 x16: ffffffffffffffff x15: 0000000000000000
[ 3106.024494] x14: ffffb85477fdfe08 x13: 0000ffff9372ffff x12: 0000000000000000
[ 3106.029469] x11: 1fffef4a88a96be1 x10: ffff7a54454b5f0c x9 : ffffb854771b12f0
[ 3106.034324] x8 : 0008000000000000 x7 : ffff7a546c1aa980 x6 : 0008000000000080
[ 3106.038902] x5 : 00000000001207cf x4 : 0000ffff9372f000 x3 : ffffffe8d481f000
[ 3106.043420] x2 : 0000000000610041 x1 : 0000000000000001 x0 : 0000000000000000
[ 3106.047957] Call trace:
[ 3106.049522]  try_grab_folio+0x11c/0x188
[ 3106.051996]  follow_pmd_mask.constprop.0.isra.0+0x150/0x2e0
[ 3106.055527]  follow_page_mask+0x1a0/0x2b8
[ 3106.058118]  __get_user_pages+0xf0/0x348
[ 3106.060647]  faultin_page_range+0xb0/0x360
[ 3106.063651]  do_madvise+0x340/0x598

Let's make huge_pte_lockptr() effectively use the same PT locks as any
core-mm page table walker would.  Add ptep_lockptr() to obtain the PTE
page table lock using a pte pointer -- unfortunately we cannot convert
pte_lockptr() because virt_to_page() doesn't work with kmap'ed page tables
we can have with CONFIG_HIGHPTE.

Handle CONFIG_PGTABLE_LEVELS correctly by checking in reverse order, such
that when e.g., CONFIG_PGTABLE_LEVELS==2 with
PGDIR_SIZE==P4D_SIZE==PUD_SIZE==PMD_SIZE will work as expected.  Document
why that works.

There is one ugly case: powerpc 8xx, whereby we have an 8 MiB hugetlb
folio being mapped using two PTE page tables.  While hugetlb wants to take
the PMD table lock, core-mm would grab the PTE table lock of one of both
PTE page tables.  In such corner cases, we have to make sure that both
locks match, which is (fortunately!) currently guaranteed for 8xx as it
does not support SMP and consequently doesn't use split PT locks.

[1] https://lore.kernel.org/all/1bbfcc7f-f222-45a5-ac44-c5a1381c596d@redhat.com/</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45025 | fix bitmap corruption on close_range() with CLOSE_RANGE_UNSHARE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45025</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fix bitmap corruption on close_range() with CLOSE_RANGE_UNSHARE

copy_fd_bitmaps(new, old, count) is expected to copy the first
count/BITS_PER_LONG bits from old-&gt;full_fds_bits[] and fill
the rest with zeroes.  What it does is copying enough words
(BITS_TO_LONGS(count/BITS_PER_LONG)), then memsets the rest.
That works fine, *if* all bits past the cutoff point are
clear.  Otherwise we are risking garbage from the last word
we'd copied.

For most of the callers that is true - expand_fdtable() has
count equal to old-&gt;max_fds, so there's no open descriptors
past count, let alone fully occupied words in -&gt;open_fds[],
which is what bits in -&gt;full_fds_bits[] correspond to.

The other caller (dup_fd()) passes sane_fdtable_size(old_fdt, max_fds),
which is the smallest multiple of BITS_PER_LONG that covers all
opened descriptors below max_fds.  In the common case (copying on
fork()) max_fds is ~0U, so all opened descriptors will be below
it and we are fine, by the same reasons why the call in expand_fdtable()
is safe.

Unfortunately, there is a case where max_fds is less than that
and where we might, indeed, end up with junk in -&gt;full_fds_bits[] -
close_range(from, to, CLOSE_RANGE_UNSHARE) with
	* descriptor table being currently shared
	* 'to' being above the current capacity of descriptor table
	* 'from' being just under some chunk of opened descriptors.
In that case we end up with observably wrong behaviour - e.g. spawn
a child with CLONE_FILES, get all descriptors in range 0..127 open,
then close_range(64, ~0U, CLOSE_RANGE_UNSHARE) and watch dup(0) ending
up with descriptor #128, despite #64 being observably not open.

The minimally invasive fix would be to deal with that in dup_fd().
If this proves to add measurable overhead, we can go that way, but
let's try to fix copy_fd_bitmaps() first.

* new helper: bitmap_copy_and_expand(to, from, bits_to_copy, size).
* make copy_fd_bitmaps() take the bitmap size in words, rather than
bits; it's 'count' argument is always a multiple of BITS_PER_LONG,
so we are not losing any information, and that way we can use the
same helper for all three bitmaps - compiler will see that count
is a multiple of BITS_PER_LONG for the large ones, so it'll generate
plain memcpy()+memset().

Reproducer added to tools/testing/selftests/core/close_range_test.c</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45026 | s390/dasd: fix error recovery leading to data corruption on ESE devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45026</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

s390/dasd: fix error recovery leading to data corruption on ESE devices

Extent Space Efficient (ESE) or thin provisioned volumes need to be
formatted on demand during usual IO processing.

The dasd_ese_needs_format function checks for error codes that signal
the non existence of a proper track format.

The check for incorrect length is to imprecise since other error cases
leading to transport of insufficient data also have this flag set.
This might lead to data corruption in certain error cases for example
during a storage server warmstart.

Fix by removing the check for incorrect length and replacing by
explicitly checking for invalid track format in transport mode.

Also remove the check for file protected since this is not a valid
ESE handling case.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45027 | usb: xhci: Check for xhci-&amp;gt;interrupters being allocated in xhci_mem_clearup()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45027</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: xhci: Check for xhci-&gt;interrupters being allocated in xhci_mem_clearup()

If xhci_mem_init() fails, it calls into xhci_mem_cleanup() to mop
up the damage. If it fails early enough, before xhci-&gt;interrupters
is allocated but after xhci-&gt;max_interrupters has been set, which
happens in most (all?) cases, things get uglier, as xhci_mem_cleanup()
unconditionally derefences xhci-&gt;interrupters. With prejudice.

Gate the interrupt freeing loop with a check on xhci-&gt;interrupters
being non-NULL.

Found while debugging a DMA allocation issue that led the XHCI driver
on this exact path.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45028 | mmc: mmc_test: Fix NULL dereference on allocation failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45028</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mmc: mmc_test: Fix NULL dereference on allocation failure

If the "test-&gt;highmem = alloc_pages()" allocation fails then calling
__free_pages(test-&gt;highmem) will result in a NULL dereference.  Also
change the error code to -ENOMEM instead of returning success.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45029 | i2c: tegra: Do not mark ACPI devices as irq safe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45029</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

i2c: tegra: Do not mark ACPI devices as irq safe

On ACPI machines, the tegra i2c module encounters an issue due to a
mutex being called inside a spinlock. This leads to the following bug:

	BUG: sleeping function called from invalid context at kernel/locking/mutex.c:585
	...

	Call trace:
	__might_sleep
	__mutex_lock_common
	mutex_lock_nested
	acpi_subsys_runtime_resume
	rpm_resume
	tegra_i2c_xfer

The problem arises because during __pm_runtime_resume(), the spinlock
&amp;amp;dev-&gt;power.lock is acquired before rpm_resume() is called. Later,
rpm_resume() invokes acpi_subsys_runtime_resume(), which relies on
mutexes, triggering the error.

To address this issue, devices on ACPI are now marked as not IRQ-safe,
considering the dependency of acpi_subsys_runtime_resume() on mutexes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45030 | igb: cope with large MAX_SKB_FRAGS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45030</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

igb: cope with large MAX_SKB_FRAGS

Sabrina reports that the igb driver does not cope well with large
MAX_SKB_FRAG values: setting MAX_SKB_FRAG to 45 causes payload
corruption on TX.

An easy reproducer is to run ssh to connect to the machine.  With
MAX_SKB_FRAGS=17 it works, with MAX_SKB_FRAGS=45 it fails.  This has
been reported originally in
https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=2265320

The root cause of the issue is that the driver does not take into
account properly the (possibly large) shared info size when selecting
the ring layout, and will try to fit two packets inside the same 4K
page even when the 1st fraglist will trump over the 2nd head.

Address the issue by checking if 2K buffers are insufficient.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46672 | wifi: brcmfmac: cfg80211: Handle SSID based pmksa deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46672</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: brcmfmac: cfg80211: Handle SSID based pmksa deletion

wpa_supplicant 2.11 sends since 1efdba5fdc2c ("Handle PMKSA flush in the
driver for SAE/OWE offload cases") SSID based PMKSA del commands.
brcmfmac is not prepared and tries to dereference the NULL bssid and
pmkid pointers in cfg80211_pmksa. PMKID_V3 operations support SSID based
updates so copy the SSID.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8306 | CWE-269: Improper Privilege Management vulnerability exists that could cause unauthorized
access, loss of confidentiality, integrity and ava...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8306</link><description>CWE-269: Improper Privilege Management vulnerability exists that could cause unauthorized
access, loss of confidentiality, integrity and availability of the workstation when non-admin
authenticated user tries to perform privilege escalation by tampering with the binaries.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4465 | Incorrect authorization for Reports configuration in Guardian/CMC before 24.2.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4465</link><description>An access control vulnerability was discovered in the Reports section due to a specific access restriction not being properly enforced for users with limited privileges.



If a logged-in user with reporting privileges learns how to create a specific application request, they might be able to make limited changes to the reporting configuration. This could result in a partial loss of data integrity. In Guardian/CMC instances with a reporting configuration, there could be limited Denial of Service (DoS) impacts, as the reports may not reach their intended destination, and there could also be limited information disclosure impacts. Furthermore, modifying the destination SMTP server for the reports could lead to the compromise of external credentials, as they might be sent to an unauthorized server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 14:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43793 | Halo&amp;#x27;s editor has a stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43793</link><description>Halo is an open source website building tool. A security vulnerability has been identified in versions prior to 2.19.0 of the Halo project. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute malicious scripts in the user's browser through specific HTML and JavaScript code, potentially leading to a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.19.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 14:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8636 | Heap buffer overflow in Skia in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6613.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8636</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in Skia in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6613.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 14:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8637 | Use after free in Media Router in Google Chrome on Android prior to 128.0.6613.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap cor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8637</link><description>Use after free in Media Router in Google Chrome on Android prior to 128.0.6613.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 14:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8638 | Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6613.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit object corruption via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8638</link><description>Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6613.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit object corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 14:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8639 | Use after free in Autofill in Google Chrome on Android prior to 128.0.6613.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corrupt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8639</link><description>Use after free in Autofill in Google Chrome on Android prior to 128.0.6613.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 14:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27112 | SQL Injection in SOPlanning before 1.52.02</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27112</link><description>A unauthenticated SQL Injection has been found in the SO Planning tool that occurs when the public view setting is enabled. An attacker could use this vulnerability to gain access to the underlying database. The vulnerability has been remediated in version 1.52.02.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27113 | Insecure Direct Object Reference to export Database in SOPlanning before 1.52.02</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27113</link><description>An unauthenticated Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) to the database has been found in the SO Planning tool that occurs when the public view setting is enabled. An attacker could use this vulnerability to gain access to the underlying database by exporting it as a CSV file. The vulnerability has been remediated in version 1.52.02.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27114 | Remote Code Execution through File Upload in SOPlanning before 1.52.02</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27114</link><description>A unauthenticated Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability is found in the SO Planning online planning tool. If the public view setting is enabled, a attacker can upload a PHP-file that will be available for execution for a few milliseconds before it is removed, leading to execution of code on the underlying system. The vulnerability has been remediated in version 1.52.02.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27115 | Remote Code Execution through File Upload in SOPlanning before 1.52.02</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27115</link><description>A unauthenticated Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability is found in the SO Planning online planning tool. With this vulnerability, an attacker can upload executable files that are moved to a publicly accessible folder before verifying any requirements. This leads to the possibility of execution of code on the underlying system when the file is triggered. The vulnerability has been remediated in version 1.52.02.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8642 | Eclipse EDC: Consumer pull transfer token validation checks not applied</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8642</link><description>In Eclipse Dataspace Components, from version 0.5.0 and before version 0.9.0, the ConsumerPullTransferTokenValidationApiController does not check for token validity (expiry, not-before, issuance date), which can allow an attacker to bypass the check for token expiration. The issue requires to have a dataplane configured to support http proxy consumer pull AND include the module "transfer-data-plane". The affected code was marked deprecated from the version 0.6.0 in favour of Dataplane Signaling. In 0.9.0 the vulnerable code has been removed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8646 | Eclipse Glassfish: URL redirection vulnerability to untrusted sites</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8646</link><description>In Eclipse Glassfish versions prior to 7.0.10, a URL redirection vulnerability to untrusted sites existed.
This vulnerability is caused by the vulnerability (CVE-2023-41080) in the Apache code included in GlassFish.
This vulnerability only affects applications that are explicitly deployed to the root context ('/').</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6091 | Shell Command Denylist Bypass in significant-gravitas/autogpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6091</link><description>A vulnerability in significant-gravitas/autogpt version 0.5.1 allows an attacker to bypass the shell commands denylist settings. The issue arises when the denylist is configured to block specific commands, such as 'whoami' and '/bin/whoami'. An attacker can circumvent this restriction by executing commands with a modified path, such as '/bin/./whoami', which is not recognized by the denylist.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:01:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45790 | User Enumeration vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45790</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Reedos aiM-Star version 2.0.1 due to missing restrictions for excessive failed authentication attempts on its API based login. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by conducting a brute force attack against legitimate user passwords, which could lead to gain unauthorized access and compromise other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 12:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45788 | No Rate Limiting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45788</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Reedos aiM-Star version 2.0.1 due to missing rate limiting on OTP requests in certain API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending multiple OTP request through vulnerable API endpoints which could lead to the OTP bombing/flooding on the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 12:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45789 | Parameter Tampering Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45789</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Reedos aiM-Star version 2.0.1 due to improper validation of the ‘mode’ parameter in the API endpoint used during the registration process. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating parameter in the API request body on the vulnerable application.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to bypass certain constraints in the registration process leading to creation of multiple accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 12:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45786 | Improper Authorization Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45786</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Reedos aiM-Star version 2.0.1 due to improper access controls on its certain API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating a parameter through API request URL which could lead to gain unauthorized access to sensitive information belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 11:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45787 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45787</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Reedos aiM-Star version 2.0.1 due to transmission of sensitive information in plain text in certain API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating a parameter through API request URL and intercepting response of the API request leading to exposure of sensitive information belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 11:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5416 | Elementor Website Builder – More than Just a Page Builder &amp;lt;= 3.23.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting in the URL Parameter in Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5416</link><description>The Elementor Website Builder – More than Just a Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the url parameter of multiple widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.23.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in Elementor Editor pages. This was partially patched in version 3.23.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7609 | Directory Traversal in Vidco Software&amp;#x27;s VOC TESTER</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7609</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Vidco Software VOC TESTER allows Path Traversal.This issue affects VOC TESTER: before 12.34.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 11:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8096 | OCSP stapling bypass with GnuTLS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8096</link><description>When curl is told to use the Certificate Status Request TLS extension, often referred to as OCSP stapling, to verify that the server certificate is valid, it might fail to detect some OCSP problems and instead wrongly consider the response as fine.  If the returned status reports another error than 'revoked' (like for example 'unauthorized') it is not treated as a bad certficate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 10:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45327 | An improper authorization vulnerability [CWE-285] in FortiSOAR version 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.3.0 through 7.3.2, 7.2.0 through 7.2.2, 7.0.0 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45327</link><description>An improper authorization vulnerability [CWE-285] in FortiSOAR version 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.3.0 through 7.3.2, 7.2.0 through 7.2.2, 7.0.0 through 7.0.3 change password endpoint may allow an authenticated attacker to perform a brute force attack on users and administrators password via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 10:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25212 | video carousel slider with lightbox &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25212</link><description>The video carousel slider with lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 08:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8277 | WooCommerce Photo Reviews Premium &amp;lt;= 1.3.13.2 - Authentication Bypass to Account Takeover and Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8277</link><description>The WooCommerce Photo Reviews Premium plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.13.2. This is due to the plugin not properly validating what user transient is being used in the login() function and not properly verifying the user's identity. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as user that has dismissed an admin notice in the past 30 days, which is often an administrator. Alternatively, a user can log in as any user with any transient that has a valid user_id as the value, though it would be more difficult to exploit this successfully.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 08:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7626 | WP Delicious – Recipe Plugin for Food Bloggers (formerly Delicious Recipes) &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 - Improper Path Validation to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Move and Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7626</link><description>The WP Delicious – Recipe Plugin for Food Bloggers (formerly Delicious Recipes) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file movement and reading due to insufficient file path validation in the save_edit_profile_details() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to move arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is moved (such as wp-config.php). This can also lead to the reading of arbitrary files that may contain sensitive information like wp-config.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 07:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8045 | Advanced WordPress Backgrounds &amp;lt;= 1.12.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via imageTag Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8045</link><description>The Advanced WordPress Backgrounds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘imageTag’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 07:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8440 | Essential Addons for Elementor -- Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp;amp; WooCommerce Builders &amp;lt;= 6.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Fancy Text Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8440</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Fancy Text widget in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 06:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3899 | Envira Gallery &amp;lt; 1.8.15 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3899</link><description>The Gallery Plugin for WordPress  WordPress plugin before 1.8.15 does not sanitise and escape some of its image settings, which could allow users with post-writing privilege such as Author to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 06:14:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7716 | GS Logo Slider Lite &amp;lt; 3.6.9 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7716</link><description>The Logo Slider  WordPress plugin before 3.6.9 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 06:14:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21529 | Versions of the package dset before 3.1.4 are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution via the dset function due improper user input sanitization. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21529</link><description>Versions of the package dset before 3.1.4 are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution via the dset function due improper user input sanitization. This vulnerability allows the attacker to inject malicious object property using the built-in Object property __proto__, which is recursively assigned to all the objects in the program.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 05:10:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7721 | HTML5 Video Player – mp4 Video Player Plugin and Block &amp;lt;= 2.5.34 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7721</link><description>The HTML5 Video Player – mp4 Video Player Plugin and Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'save_password' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.34. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to set any options that are not explicitly checked as false to an array, including enabling user registration if it has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 04:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7727 | HTML5 Video Player – mp4 Video Player Plugin and Block &amp;lt;= 2.5.32 - Missing Authorization in multiple functions via h5vp_ajax_handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7727</link><description>The HTML5 Video Player – mp4 Video Player Plugin and Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on multiple functions called via the 'h5vp_ajax_handler' ajax action in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.32. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to call these functions to manipulate data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 04:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1656 | Affected versions of Octopus Server had a weak content security policy.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1656</link><description>Affected versions of Octopus Server had a weak content security policy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 04:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43690 | Inclusion of Functionality from Untrusted Control Sphere(CWE-829) in the Command Centre Server and Workstations may allow an attacker to per...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43690</link><description>Inclusion of Functionality from Untrusted Control Sphere(CWE-829) in the Command Centre Server and Workstations may allow an attacker to perform Remote Code Execution (RCE).

This issue affects: Command Centre Server and Command Centre Workstations 9.10 prior to vEL9.10.1530 (MR2), 9.00 prior to vEL9.00.2168 (MR4), 8.90 prior to vEL8.90.2155 (MR5), 8.80 prior to vEL8.80.1938 (MR6), all versions of 8.70 and prior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 04:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23906 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (CWE-79) in the Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 diagnostic webpage allows an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23906</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (CWE-79) in the Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 diagnostic webpage allows an attacker to modify Controller configuration during an authenticated Operator's session.

 



This issue affects: Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 9.10 prior to vCR9.10.240816a (distributed in 9.10.1530 (MR2)), 9.00 prior to vCR9.00.240816a (distributed in 9.00.2168 (MR4)), 8.90 prior to vCR8.90.240816a (distributed in 8.90.2155 (MR5)), 8.80 prior to vCR8.80.240816b (distributed in 8.80.1938 (MR6)), all versions of 8.70 and prior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 04:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24972 | Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input (CWE-120) in the Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 diagnostic web interface allows an authorise...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24972</link><description>Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input (CWE-120) in the Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 diagnostic web interface allows an authorised and authenticated operator to reboot the Controller, causing a Denial of Service. Gallagher recommend the diagnostic web page is not enabled (default is off) unless advised by Gallagher Technical support. This interface is intended only for diagnostic purposes.

This issue affects: Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 9.10 prior to vCR9.10.240816a (distributed in 9.10.1530 (MR2)), 9.00 prior to vCR9.00.240816a (distributed in 9.00.2168 (MR4)), 8.90 prior to vCR8.90.240816a (distributed in 8.90.2155 (MR5)), 8.80 prior to vCR8.80.240816b (distributed in 8.80.1938 (MR6)), all versions of 8.70 and prior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 04:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39808 | Incorrect Calculation of Buffer Size (CWE-131) in the Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 OSDP message handling, allows an attacker with phy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39808</link><description>Incorrect Calculation of Buffer Size (CWE-131) in the Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 OSDP message handling, allows an attacker with physical access to Controller wiring to instigate a reboot leading to a denial of service. 



This issue affects: Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 9.10 prior to vCR9.10.240816a (distributed in 9.10.1530 (MR2)), 9.00 prior to vCR9.00.240816a (distributed in 9.00.2168 (MR4)), 8.90 prior to vCR8.90.240816a (distributed in 8.90.2155 (MR5)), 8.80 prior to vCR8.80.240816b (distributed in 8.80.1938 (MR6)), all versions of 8.70 and prior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 04:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8253 | Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks 2.2.87 - 2.2.90 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8253</link><description>The Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions 2.2.87 to 2.2.90. This is due to the plugin not properly restricting what user meta values can be updated and ensuring a form is active. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update their user meta to become an administrator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 03:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23716 | In DevmemIntPFNotify of devicemem_server.c, there is a possible use-after-free due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23716</link><description>In DevmemIntPFNotify of devicemem_server.c, there is a possible use-after-free due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege in the kernel with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31336 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31336</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40650 | In wifi_item_edit_content of styles.xml , there is a possible FRP bypass due to Missing check for FRP state. This could lead to local escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40650</link><description>In wifi_item_edit_content of styles.xml , there is a possible FRP bypass due to Missing check for FRP state. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40652 | In onCreate of SettingsHomepageActivity.java, there is a possible way to access the Settings app while the device is provisioning due to a m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40652</link><description>In onCreate of SettingsHomepageActivity.java, there is a possible way to access the Settings app while the device is provisioning due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40654 | In multiple locations, there is a possible permission bypass due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40654</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible permission bypass due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40655 | In bindAndGetCallIdentification of CallScreeningServiceHelper.java, there is a possible way to maintain a while-in-use permission in the bac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40655</link><description>In bindAndGetCallIdentification of CallScreeningServiceHelper.java, there is a possible way to maintain a while-in-use permission in the background due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40656 | In handleCreateConferenceComplete of ConnectionServiceWrapper.java, there is a possible way to reveal images across users due to a confused ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40656</link><description>In handleCreateConferenceComplete of ConnectionServiceWrapper.java, there is a possible way to reveal images across users due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40657 | In addPreferencesForType of AccountTypePreferenceLoader.java, there is a possible way to disable apps for other users due to a confused depu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40657</link><description>In addPreferencesForType of AccountTypePreferenceLoader.java, there is a possible way to disable apps for other users due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40658 | In getConfig of SoftVideoDecoderOMXComponent.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40658</link><description>In getConfig of SoftVideoDecoderOMXComponent.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40659 | In getRegistration of RemoteProvisioningService.java, there is a possible way to permanently disable the AndroidKeyStore key generation feat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40659</link><description>In getRegistration of RemoteProvisioningService.java, there is a possible way to permanently disable the AndroidKeyStore key generation feature by updating the attestation keys of all installed apps due to improper input validation. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40662 | In scheme of Uri.java, there is a possible way to craft a malformed Uri object due to improper input validation. This could lead to local es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40662</link><description>In scheme of Uri.java, there is a possible way to craft a malformed Uri object due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>