<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:26:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-11251 | SQLi in Dayneks Software&amp;#x27;s E-Commerce Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11251</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Dayneks Software Industry and Trade Inc. E-Commerce Platform allows SQL Injection.This issue affects E-Commerce Platform: through 27022026.

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24350 | Stored XSS in PluXml CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24350</link><description>PluXml CMS is vulnerable to Stored XSS in file uploading functionality. An authenticated attacker can upload an SVG file containing a malicious payload, which will be executed when a victim clicks the link associated with the uploaded image.
In version 5.9.0-rc7 clicking the link associated with the uploaded image doesn't execute malicious code but directly accessing the file will still execute the embedded payload.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only versions 5.8.21 and 5.9.0-rc7 were tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24351 | Stored XSS in PluXml CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24351</link><description>PluXml CMS is vulnerable to Stored XSS in Static Pages editing functionality. Attacker with editing privileges can inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed when visiting edited page.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only versions 5.8.21 and 5.9.0-rc7 were tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24352 | Session Fixation in PluXml CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24352</link><description>PluXml CMS allows a user's session identifier to be set before authentication. The value of this session ID stays the same after authentication. This behaviour enables an attacker to fix a session ID
for a victim and later hijack the authenticated session.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only versions 5.8.21 and 5.9.0-rc7 were tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2831 | MailArchiver &amp;lt;= 4.5.0 - Authenticated (Admininistrator+) SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;logid&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2831</link><description>The MailArchiver plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘logid’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1434 | Reflected XSS in Omega-PSIR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1434</link><description>Omega-PSIR is vulnerable to Reflected XSS via the lang parameter. An attacker can craft a malicious URL that, when opened, causes arbitrary JavaScript to execute in the victim’s browser.

This issue was fixed in 4.6.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10938 | OVRI Payment 1.7.0 - Malicious .htaccess directive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10938</link><description>The OVRI Payment plugin for WordPress contains malicious .htaccess files in version 1.7.0. The files contain directives to prevent the execution of certain scripts while allowing execution of known malicious PHP files. If moved outside of the plugin's directory, they may interfere with the proper function of a site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14142 | Electric Enquiries &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;button&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14142</link><description>The Electric Enquiries plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'button' parameter of the electric-enquiry shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1305 | Japanized for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.8.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Paidy Order Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1305</link><description>The Japanized for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Improper Authentication in versions up to, and including, 2.8.4. This is due to a flawed permission check in the `paidy_webhook_permission_check` function that unconditionally returns `true` when the webhook signature header is omitted. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass payment verification and fraudulently mark orders as "Processing" or "Completed" without actual payment via a crafted POST request to the Paidy webhook endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21659 | Johnson Controls -Frick Quantum HD-Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution and Information Disclosure due to Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21659</link><description>Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution and Information Disclosure due to Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability in Johnson Controls Frick Controls Quantum HD allow an unauthenticated attacker to
execute arbitrary code on the affected device, leading to full system compromise. 
This issue affects Frick Controls Quantum HD: Frick Controls Quantum HD version 10.22 and prior.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21660 | Johnson Controls-Frick Quantum HD-Hardcoded Email Credentials Saved as Plaintext in Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21660</link><description>Hardcoded Email Credentials Saved as Plaintext in Firmware (CWE-256: Plaintext Storage of a Password) vulnerability in Frick Controls Quantum HD version 10.22 and prior lead to unauthorized access, exposure of sensitive information, and potential misuse or system compromise
This issue affects Frick Controls Quantum HD version 10.22 and prior.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1626 | An attacker may exploit the use of weak CBC-based cipher suites in the device’s SSH service to potentially observe or manipulate parts of th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1626</link><description>An attacker may exploit the use of weak CBC-based cipher suites in the device’s SSH service to potentially observe or manipulate parts of the encrypted SSH communication, if they are able to intercept or interact with the network traffic.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1627 | An attacker may exploit the use of outdated and weak MAC algorithms in the device’s SSH service to potentially compromise the integrity of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1627</link><description>An attacker may exploit the use of outdated and weak MAC algorithms in the device’s SSH service to potentially compromise the integrity of the SSH session, allowing manipulation of transmitted data if the attacker can interact with the network traffic.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21656 | Johnson Controls -Frick Quantum HD- Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21656</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Johnson Controls Frick Controls Quantum HD allows Code Injection. Insufficient validation of input in certain parameters may permit unexpected actions, which could impact the security of the device before authentication occurs.This issue affects Frick Controls Quantum HD version 10.22 and prior.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:10:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21657 | Johnson Controls -Frick Quantum HD- Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21657</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Johnson Controls Frick Controls Quantum HD allows Code Injection. Insufficient validation of input in certain parameters may permit unexpected actions, which could impact the security of the device before authentication occurs.This issue affects Frick Controls Quantum HD version 10.22 and prior.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:10:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21658 | Johnson Controls -Frick Quantum HD- Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21658</link><description>Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution i.e Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Johnson Controls Frick Controls Quantum HD allows Code Injection.This issue affects Frick Controls Quantum HD version 10.22 and prior.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:10:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21654 | Johnson Controls -Frick Quantum HD- Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21654</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Johnson Controls Frick Controls Quantum HD allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects Frick Controls Quantum HD version 10.22 and prior.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2362 | WP Accessibility &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;alt&amp;#x27; Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2362</link><description>The WP Accessibility plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via the 'alt' attribute of images processed by the "Long Description UI" feature in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.1. This is due to the plugin's JavaScript retrieving the alt attribute using getAttribute() and unsafely concatenating it into innerHTML and insertAdjacentHTML calls without proper sanitization or escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Exploitation requires the "Long Description UI" setting to be enabled and set to "Link to description."</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:10:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2383 | Simple Download Monitor &amp;lt;= 4.0.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2383</link><description>The Simple Download Monitor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via custom field in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:10:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12150 | Org.keycloak/keycloak-services: webauthn attestation statement verification bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12150</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak’s WebAuthn registration component. This vulnerability allows an attacker to bypass the configured attestation policy and register untrusted or forged authenticators via submission of an attestation object with fmt: "none", even when the realm is configured to require direct attestation. This can lead to weakened authentication integrity and unauthorized authenticator registration.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2251 | Path Traversal leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2251</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory (Path Traversal) vulnerability in Xerox FreeFlow Core allows unauthorized path traversal leading to RCE. 
This issue affects Xerox FreeFlow Core versions up to and including 8.0.7.







Please consider upgrading to FreeFlow Core version 8.1.0 via the software available on -  https://www.support.xerox.com/en-us/product/core/downloads 

  https://www.support.xerox.com/en-us/product/core/downloads</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2252 | XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability resulting in Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2252</link><description>An XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability allows malicious user to perform Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via crafted XML input containing malicious external entity references.

This issue affects Xerox FreeFlow Core versions up to and including 8.0.7. 

Please consider upgrading to FreeFlow Core version 8.1.0 via the software available on -  https://www.support.xerox.com/en-us/product/core/downloads</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27776 | IM-LogicDesigner module of intra-mart Accel Platform contains insecure deserialization issue. This can be exploited only when IM-LogicDesign...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27776</link><description>IM-LogicDesigner module of intra-mart Accel Platform contains insecure deserialization issue. This can be exploited only when IM-LogicDesigner is deployed on the system. Arbitrary code may be executed when some crafted file is imported by a user with the administrative privilege.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13327 | Uv: uv: specially crafted zip archives lead to arbitrary code execution due to parsing differentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13327</link><description>A flaw was found in uv. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute malicious code during package resolution or installation via specially crafted ZIP (Zipped Information Package) archives that exploit parsing differentials, requiring user interaction to install an attacker-controlled package.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:53:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9572 | Foreman: satellite: graphql api permission bypass leads to information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9572</link><description>n authorization flaw in Foreman's GraphQL API allows low-privileged users to access metadata beyond their assigned permissions. Unlike the REST API, which correctly enforces access controls, the GraphQL endpoint does not apply proper filtering, leading to an authorization bypass.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:53:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9907 | Event-driven-ansible: event stream test mode exposes sensitive headers in aap eda</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9907</link><description>A flaw was found in the Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform, Event-Driven Ansible (EDA) Event Stream API. This vulnerability allows exposure of sensitive client credentials and internal infrastructure headers via the test_headers field when an event stream is in test mode. The possible outcome includes leakage of internal infrastructure details, accidental disclosure of user or system credentials, privilege escalation if high-value tokens are exposed, and persistent sensitive data exposure to all users with read access on the event stream.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9908 | Event-driven-ansible: sensitive internal headers disclosure in aap eda event streams</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9908</link><description>A flaw was found in the Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform, Event-Driven Ansible (EDA) Event Streams. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to gain access to sensitive internal infrastructure headers (such as X-Trusted-Proxy and X-Envoy-*) and event stream URLs via crafted requests and job templates. By exfiltrating these headers, an attacker could spoof trusted requests, escalate privileges, or perform malicious event injection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9909 | Aap-gateway: improper path validation in gateway allows credential exfiltration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9909</link><description>A flaw was found in the Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform Gateway route creation component. This vulnerability allows credential theft via the creation of misleading routes using a double-slash (//) prefix in the gateway_path. A malicious or socially engineered administrator can configure a honey-pot route to intercept and exfiltrate user credentials, potentially maintaining persistent access or creating a backdoor even after their permissions are revoked.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0871 | Org.keycloak/keycloak-services: keycloak: unauthorized modification of unmanaged user attributes by administrators</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0871</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. An administrator with `manage-users` permission can bypass the "Only administrators can view" setting for unmanaged attributes, allowing them to modify these attributes. This improper access control can lead to unauthorized changes to user profiles, even when the system is configured to restrict such modifications.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0980 | Rubyipmi: red hat satellite: remote code execution in rubyipmi via malicious bmc username</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0980</link><description>A flaw was found in rubyipmi, a gem used in the Baseboard Management Controller (BMC) component of Red Hat Satellite. An authenticated attacker with host creation or update permissions could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious username for the BMC interface. This could lead to remote code execution (RCE) on the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12981 | Listee &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12981</link><description>The Listee theme for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6. This is due to a broken validation check in the bundled listee-core plugin's user registration function that fails to properly sanitize the user_role parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register as Administrator by manipulating the user_role parameter during registration.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14040 | Automotive Car Dealership Business WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 13.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Call to Action Fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14040</link><description>The Automotive Car Dealership Business WordPress Theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Call to Action' custom fields in all versions up to, and including, 13.4. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied attributes in the 'action_text', 'action_button_text', 'action_link', and 'action_class' custom fields. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:07:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14149 | Xpro Addons — 140+ Widgets for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.4.24 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Image Scroller Widget box link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14149</link><description>The Xpro Addons — 140+ Widgets for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Image Scroller widget box link attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.24 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:07:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15509 | The SmartRemote module has insufficient restrictions on loading URLs, which may lead to some information leakage.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15509</link><description>The SmartRemote module has insufficient restrictions on loading URLs, which may lead to some information leakage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:07:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15567 | Insufficient protection mechanisms in the Health Module may lead to partial information disclosure.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15567</link><description>Insufficient protection mechanisms in the Health Module may lead to partial information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:07:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3302 | SourceCodester Doctor Appointment System Sign Up register.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3302</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Doctor Appointment System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /register.php of the component Sign Up Page. Executing a manipulation of the argument Email can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:07:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27653 | The installers for multiple products provided by Soliton Systems K.K. contain an issue with incorrect default permissions, which may allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27653</link><description>The installers for multiple products provided by Soliton Systems K.K. contain an issue with incorrect default permissions, which may allow arbitrary code to be executed with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:03:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28372 | telnetd in GNU inetutils through 2.7 allows privilege escalation that can be exploited by abusing systemd service credentials support added ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28372</link><description>telnetd in GNU inetutils through 2.7 allows privilege escalation that can be exploited by abusing systemd service credentials support added to the login(1) implementation of util-linux in release 2.40. This is related to client control over the CREDENTIALS_DIRECTORY environment variable, and requires an unprivileged local user to create a login.noauth file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:03:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3293 | snowflakedb snowflake-jdbc JDBC URL SdkProxyRoutePlanner.java SdkProxyRoutePlanner redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3293</link><description>A weakness has been identified in snowflakedb snowflake-jdbc up to 4.0.1. Impacted is the function SdkProxyRoutePlanner of the file src/main/java/net/snowflake/client/internal/core/SdkProxyRoutePlanner.java of the component JDBC URL Handler. Executing a manipulation of the argument nonProxyHosts can lead to inefficient regular expression complexity. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. This patch is called 5fb0a8a318a2ed87f4022a1f56e742424ba94052. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:03:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3301 | Totolink N300RH Web Management cstecgi.cgi setWebWlanIdx os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3301</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Totolink N300RH 6.1c.1353_B20190305. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setWebWlanIdx of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component Web Management Interface. Performing a manipulation of the argument webWlanIdx results in os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:03:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28370 | In the query parser in OpenStack Vitrage before 12.0.1, 13.0.0, 14.0.0, and 15.0.0, a user allowed to access the Vitrage API may trigger cod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28370</link><description>In the query parser in OpenStack Vitrage before 12.0.1, 13.0.0, 14.0.0, and 15.0.0, a user allowed to access the Vitrage API may trigger code execution on the Vitrage service host as the user the Vitrage service runs under. This may result in unauthorized access to the host and further compromise of the Vitrage service. All deployments exposing the Vitrage API are affected. This occurs in _create_query_function in vitrage/graph/query.py.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:03:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3292 | jizhiCMS Batch Model.php findAll sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3292</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in jizhiCMS up to 2.5.6. Affected is the function findAll in the library frphp/lib/Model.php of the component Batch Interface. The manipulation of the argument data leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:03:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1442 | Unitree UPK files Hard-Coded Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1442</link><description>Since the encryption algorithm used to protect firmware updates is itself encrypted using key material available to an attacker (or anyone paying attention), the firmware updates may be altered by an unauthorized user, and then trusted by a Unitree product, such as the Unitree Go2 and other models. This issue appears to affect all of Unitree’s current offerings as of February 26, 2026, and so should be considered a vulnerability in both the firmware generation and extraction processes. At the time of this release, there is no publicly-documented mechanism to subvert the update process and insert poisoned firmware packages without the equipment owner’s knowledge.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:05:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1558 | WP Recipe Maker &amp;lt;= 10.3.2 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post Metadata Modification via &amp;#x27;recipeId&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1558</link><description>The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in versions up to, and including, 10.3.2. This is due to the /wp-json/wp-recipe-maker/v1/integrations/instacart REST API endpoint's permission_callback being set to __return_true and a lack of subsequent authorization or ownership checks on the user-supplied recipeId. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to overwrite arbitrary post metadata (wprm_instacart_combinations) for any post ID on the site via the recipeId parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:05:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3287 | youlaitech youlai-mall App-side Product Pagination Endpoint SpuController.java listPagedSpuForApp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3287</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in youlaitech youlai-mall 2.0.0. This affects the function listPagedSpuForApp of the file mall-pms/pms-boot/src/main/java/com/youlai/mall/pms/controller/app/SpuController.java of the component App-side Product Pagination Endpoint. Performing a manipulation of the argument sortField/sort results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:05:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3289 | Sanluan PublicCMS Template Cache Generation TemplateCacheComponent.java saveMetadata path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3289</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Sanluan PublicCMS 6.202506.d. This impacts the function saveMetadata of the file TemplateCacheComponent.java of the component Template Cache Generation. Executing a manipulation can lead to path traversal. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:05:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28363 | In OpenClaw before 2026.2.23, tools.exec.safeBins validation for sort could be bypassed via GNU long-option abbreviations (such as --compres...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28363</link><description>In OpenClaw before 2026.2.23, tools.exec.safeBins validation for sort could be bypassed via GNU long-option abbreviations (such as --compress-prog) in allowlist mode, leading to approval-free execution paths that were intended to require approval. Only an exact string such as --compress-program was denied.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:05:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28364 | In OCaml before 4.14.3 and 5.x before 5.4.1, a buffer over-read in Marshal deserialization (runtime/intern.c) enables remote code execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28364</link><description>In OCaml before 4.14.3 and 5.x before 5.4.1, a buffer over-read in Marshal deserialization (runtime/intern.c) enables remote code execution through a multi-phase attack chain. The vulnerability stems from missing bounds validation in the readblock() function, which performs unbounded memcpy() operations using attacker-controlled lengths from crafted Marshal data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:05:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2428 | Fluent Forms Pro Add On Pack &amp;lt;= 6.1.17 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Payment Status modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2428</link><description>The Fluent Forms Pro Add On Pack plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insufficient Verification of Data Authenticity in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.17. This is due to the PayPal IPN (Instant Payment Notification) verification being disabled by default (`disable_ipn_verification` defaults to `'yes'` in `PayPalSettings.php`). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send forged PayPal IPN notifications to the publicly accessible IPN endpoint, marking unpaid form submissions as "paid" and triggering post-payment automation (emails, access grants, digital product delivery).</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:05:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3286 | itwanger paicoding Image Save Endpoint ImageRestController.java save server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3286</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itwanger paicoding 1.0.0/1.0.1/1.0.2/1.0.3. The impacted element is the function Save of the file paicoding-web/src/main/java/com/github/paicoding/forum/web/common/image/rest/ImageRestController.java of the component Image Save Endpoint. Such manipulation of the argument img leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:05:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3282 | libvips unpremultiply.c vips_unpremultiply_build out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3282</link><description>A flaw has been found in libvips 8.19.0. This vulnerability affects the function vips_unpremultiply_build of the file libvips/conversion/unpremultiply.c. Executing a manipulation of the argument alpha_band can lead to out-of-bounds read. The attack needs to be launched locally. The exploit has been published and may be used. This patch is called 7215ead1e0cd7d3703cc4f5fca06d7d0f4c22b91. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3283 | libvips extract.c vips_extract_band_build out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3283</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in libvips 8.19.0. This issue affects the function vips_extract_band_build of the file libvips/conversion/extract.c. The manipulation of the argument extract_band leads to out-of-bounds read. The attack needs to be performed locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is 24795bb3d19d84f7b6f5ed86451ad556c8f2fe70. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3284 | libvips extract.c vips_extract_area_build integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3284</link><description>A vulnerability was found in libvips 8.19.0. Impacted is the function vips_extract_area_build of the file libvips/conversion/extract.c. The manipulation of the argument extract_area results in integer overflow. The attack requires a local approach. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The patch is identified as 24795bb3d19d84f7b6f5ed86451ad556c8f2fe70. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3285 | berry-lang berry be_lexer.c scan_string out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3285</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in berry-lang berry up to 1.1.0. The affected element is the function scan_string of the file src/be_lexer.c. This manipulation causes out-of-bounds read. The attack requires local access. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Patch name: 7149c59a39ba44feca261b12f06089f265fec176. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24497 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in SimTech Systems, Inc. ThinkWise allows Remote Code Inclusion.This issue affects ThinkWise: from...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24497</link><description>Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in SimTech Systems, Inc. ThinkWise allows Remote Code Inclusion.This issue affects ThinkWise: from 7 through 23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24498 | Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in EFM-Networks, Inc. IpTIME T5008, EFM-Networks, Inc. IpTIME AX200...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24498</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in EFM-Networks, Inc. IpTIME T5008, EFM-Networks, Inc. IpTIME AX2004M, EFM-Networks, Inc. IpTIME AX3000Q, EFM-Networks, Inc. IpTIME AX6000M allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects ipTIME T5008: through 15.26.8; ipTIME AX2004M: through 15.26.8; ipTIME AX3000Q: through 15.26.8; ipTIME AX6000M: through 15.26.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3275 | Tenda F453 httpd addressNat fromAddressNat buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3275</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda F453 1.0.0.3. This affects the function fromAddressNat of the file /goform/addressNat of the component httpd. Executing a manipulation of the argument entrys can lead to buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3281 | libvips bandrank.c vips_bandrank_build heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3281</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in libvips 8.19.0. This affects the function vips_bandrank_build of the file libvips/conversion/bandrank.c. Performing a manipulation of the argument index results in heap-based buffer overflow. The attack must be initiated from a local position. The exploit is now public and may be used. The patch is named fd28c5463697712cb0ab116a2c55e4f4d92c4088. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20764 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20764</link><description>An OS command injection 
vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling an 
authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution on the system by
 providing malicious input via the device hostname configuration which 
is later processed during system setup, resulting in remote code 
execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20797 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20797</link><description>A stack based buffer overflow exists in an API route of XWEB Pro version
 1.12.1 and prior, enabling unauthenticated attackers to cause stack 
corruption and a termination of the program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22877 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22877</link><description>An arbitrary file-read vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 
and prior, enabling unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files on
 the system, and potentially causing a denial-of-service attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23702 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23702</link><description>An OS command injection 
vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling an 
authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution on the system by
 sending malicious input injected into the server username field of the 
import preconfiguration action in the API V1 route.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24452 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24452</link><description>An OS command injection 
 vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling an 
authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution on the system by
 supplying a crafted template file to the devices route.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25037 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25037</link><description>An OS command injection 

vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling an 
authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution on the system by
 configuring a maliciously crafted LCD state which is later processed 
during system setup, enabling remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25105 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25105</link><description>An OS command injection 





vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling an 
authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution on the system by
 injecting malicious input into parameters of the Modbus command tool in
 the debug route.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25196 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25196</link><description>An OS command injection 
vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling an 
authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution on the system by
 injecting malicious input into the Wi-Fi SSID and/or password fields 
can lead to remote code execution when the configuration is processed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25721 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25721</link><description>An OS command injection 
vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling an 
authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution on the system by
 injecting malicious input into the server username and/or password 
fields of the restore action in the API V1 route.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3037 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3037</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 
and prior, enabling an authenticated attacker to achieve remote code 
execution on the system by modifying malicious input injected into the 
MBird SMS service URL and/or code via the utility route which is later 
processed during system setup, leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3274 | Tenda F453 httpd L7Prot frmL7ProtForm buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3274</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda F453 1.0.0.3. Affected by this issue is the function frmL7ProtForm of the file /goform/L7Prot of the component httpd. Performing a manipulation of the argument page results in buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4456 | Net::CIDR versions before 0.24 for Perl mishandle leading zeros in IP CIDR addresses, which may have unspecified impact</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4456</link><description>Net::CIDR versions before 0.24 for Perl mishandle leading zeros in IP CIDR addresses, which may have unspecified impact.

The functions `addr2cidr` and `cidrlookup` may return leading zeros in a CIDR string, which may in turn be parsed as octal numbers by subsequent users. In some cases an attacker may be able to leverage this to bypass access controls based on IP addresses.

The documentation advises validating untrusted CIDR strings with the `cidrvalidate` function. However, this mitigation is optional and not enforced by default. In practice, users may call `addr2cidr` or `cidrlookup` with untrusted input and without validation, incorrectly assuming that this is safe.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20742 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20742</link><description>An OS command injection 

vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling an 
authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution on the system by
 injecting malicious input into requests sent to the templates route.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20902 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20902</link><description>An OS command injection 



vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling an 
authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution on the system by
 injecting malicious input into the map filename field during the map 
upload action of the parameters route.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20910 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20910</link><description>An OS command injection 
vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling an 
authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution on the system by
 injecting malicious input into the devices field of the firmware update
 update action to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21389 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21389</link><description>An OS command injection 
vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling an 
authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution on the system by
 injecting malicious input into the request body sent to the contacts 
import route.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21718 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21718</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in Copeland XWEB Pro 
version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling any attackers to bypass the 
authentication requirement and achieve pre-authenticated code execution 
on the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22878 | Mobility46 mobility46.se Insufficiently Protected Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22878</link><description>Charging station authentication identifiers are publicly accessible via web-based mapping platforms.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24445 | EV Energy ev.energy Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24445</link><description>The WebSocket Application Programming Interface lacks restrictions on 
the number of authentication requests. This absence of rate limiting may
 allow an attacker to conduct denial-of-service attacks by suppressing 
or mis-routing legitimate charger telemetry, or conduct brute-force 
attacks to gain unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24517 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24517</link><description>An OS command injection 


vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling an 
authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution on the system by
 injecting malicious input into requests sent to the firmware update 
route.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24663 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24663</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 
and prior, enabling an unauthenticated attacker to achieve remote code 
execution on the system by sending a crafted request to the libraries 
installation route and injecting malicious input into the request body.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24689 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24689</link><description>An OS command injection 

vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling an 
authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution on the system by
 injecting malicious input into the devices field of the firmware update
 apply action.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24695 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24695</link><description>An OS command injection 




vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling an 
authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution on the system by
 injecting malicious input into OpenSSL argument fields within requests 
sent to the utility route, leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25085 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro Unexpected Status Code or Return Value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25085</link><description>A vulnerability exists in Copeland XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, in
 which an unexpected return value from the authentication routine is 
later on processed as a legitimate value, resulting in an authentication
 bypass.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25109 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25109</link><description>An OS command injection 


vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling an 
authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution on the system by
 injecting malicious input into the devices field when accessing the get
 setup route, leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25111 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25111</link><description>An OS command injection 
vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling an 
authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution on the system by
 injecting malicious input into requests sent to the restore route.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25195 | Copeland XWEB and XWEB Pro OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25195</link><description>An OS command injection 



vulnerability exists in XWEB Pro version 1.12.1 and prior, enabling an 
authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution on the system by
 supplying a crafted firmware update file via the firmware update route.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25774 | EV Energy ev.energy Insufficiently Protected Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25774</link><description>Charging station authentication identifiers are publicly accessible via web-based mapping platforms.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26290 | EV Energy ev.energy Insufficient Session Expiration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26290</link><description>The WebSocket backend uses charging station identifiers to uniquely 
associate sessions but allows multiple endpoints to connect using the 
same session identifier. This implementation results in predictable 
session identifiers and enables session hijacking or shadowing, where 
the most recent connection displaces the legitimate charging station and
 receives backend commands intended for that station. This vulnerability
 may allow unauthorized users to authenticate as other users or enable a
 malicious actor to cause a denial-of-service condition by overwhelming 
the backend with valid session requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26305 | Mobility46 mobility46.se Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26305</link><description>The WebSocket Application Programming Interface lacks restrictions on 
the number of authentication requests. This absence of rate limiting may
 allow an attacker to conduct denial-of-service attacks by suppressing 
or mis-routing legitimate charger telemetry, or conduct brute-force 
attacks to gain unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27028 | Mobility46 mobility46.se Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27028</link><description>WebSocket endpoints lack proper authentication mechanisms, enabling 
attackers to perform unauthorized station impersonation and manipulate 
data sent to the backend. An unauthenticated attacker can connect to the
 OCPP WebSocket endpoint using a known or discovered charging station 
identifier, then issue or receive OCPP commands as a legitimate charger.
 Given that no authentication is required, this can lead to privilege 
escalation, unauthorized control of charging infrastructure, and 
corruption of charging network data reported to the backend.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27647 | Mobility46 mobility46.se Insufficient Session Expiration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27647</link><description>The WebSocket backend uses charging station identifiers to uniquely 
associate sessions but allows multiple endpoints to connect using the 
same session identifier. This implementation results in predictable 
session identifiers and enables session hijacking or shadowing, where 
the most recent connection displaces the legitimate charging station and
 receives backend commands intended for that station. This vulnerability
 may allow unauthorized users to authenticate as other users or enable a
 malicious actor to cause a denial-of-service condition by overwhelming 
the backend with valid session requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3273 | Tenda F453 httpd AdvSetWrlsafeset formWrlsafeset buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3273</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda F453 1.0.0.3. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formWrlsafeset of the file /goform/AdvSetWrlsafeset of the component httpd. Such manipulation of the argument mit_ssid_index leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25113 | SWITCH EV swtchenergy.com Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25113</link><description>The WebSocket Application Programming Interface lacks restrictions on 
the number of authentication requests. This absence of rate limiting may
 allow an attacker to conduct denial-of-service attacks by suppressing 
or mis-routing legitimate charger telemetry, or conduct brute-force 
attacks to gain unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25778 | SWITCH EV swtchenergy.com Insufficient Session Expiration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25778</link><description>The WebSocket backend uses charging station identifiers to uniquely 
associate sessions but allows multiple endpoints to connect using the 
same session identifier. This implementation results in predictable 
session identifiers and enables session hijacking or shadowing, where 
the most recent connection displaces the legitimate charging station and
 receives backend commands intended for that station. This vulnerability
 may allow unauthorized users to authenticate as other users or enable a
 malicious actor to cause a denial-of-service condition by overwhelming 
the backend with valid session requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27767 | SWITCH EV swtchenergy.com Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27767</link><description>WebSocket endpoints lack proper authentication mechanisms, enabling 
attackers to perform unauthorized station impersonation and manipulate 
data sent to the backend. An unauthenticated attacker can connect to the
 OCPP WebSocket endpoint using a known or discovered charging station 
identifier, then issue or receive OCPP commands as a legitimate charger.
 Given that no authentication is required, this can lead to privilege 
escalation, unauthorized control of charging infrastructure, and 
corruption of charging network data reported to the backend.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27772 | EV Energy ev.energy Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27772</link><description>WebSocket endpoints lack proper authentication mechanisms, enabling 
attackers to perform unauthorized station impersonation and manipulate 
data sent to the backend. An unauthenticated attacker can connect to the
 OCPP WebSocket endpoint using a known or discovered charging station 
identifier, then issue or receive OCPP commands as a legitimate charger.
 Given that no authentication is required, this can lead to privilege 
escalation, unauthorized control of charging infrastructure, and 
corruption of charging network data reported to the backend.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27773 | SWITCH EV swtchenergy.com Insufficiently Protected Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27773</link><description>Charging station authentication identifiers are publicly accessible via web-based mapping platforms.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3271 | Tenda F453 httpd P2pListFilterof fromP2pListFilter buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3271</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda F453 1.0.0.3. This impacts the function fromP2pListFilter of the file /goform/P2pListFilterof of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument page results in buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3272 | Tenda F453 httpd DhcpListClient fromDhcpListClient buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3272</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda F453 1.0.0.3. Affected is the function fromDhcpListClient of the file /goform/DhcpListClient of the component httpd. This manipulation of the argument page causes buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20895 | EV2GO ev2go.io Insufficient Session Expiration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20895</link><description>The WebSocket backend uses charging station identifiers to uniquely 
associate sessions but allows multiple endpoints to connect using the 
same session identifier. This implementation results in predictable 
session identifiers and enables session hijacking or shadowing, where 
the most recent connection displaces the legitimate charging station and
 receives backend commands intended for that station. This vulnerability
 may allow unauthorized users to authenticate as other users or enable a
 malicious actor to cause a denial-of-service condition by overwhelming 
the backend with valid session requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22890 | EV2GO ev2go.io Insufficiently Protected Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22890</link><description>Charging station authentication identifiers are publicly accessible via web-based mapping platforms.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25945 | EV2GO ev2go.io Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25945</link><description>The WebSocket Application Programming Interface lacks restrictions on 
the number of authentication requests. This absence of rate limiting may
 allow an attacker to conduct denial-of-service attacks by suppressing 
or mis-routing legitimate charger telemetry, or conduct brute-force 
attacks to gain unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:04:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40932 | Apache::SessionX versions through 2.01 for Perl create insecure session id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40932</link><description>Apache::SessionX versions through 2.01 for Perl create insecure session id.

Apache::SessionX generates session ids insecurely. The default session id generator in Apache::SessionX::Generate::MD5 returns a MD5 hash seeded with the built-in rand() function, the epoch time, and the PID. The PID will come from a small set of numbers, and the epoch time may be guessed, if it is not leaked from the HTTP Date header. The built-in rand function is unsuitable for cryptographic usage. Predicable session ids could allow an attacker to gain access to systems.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1585 | An unquoted Windows service executable path vulnerability in IJ Scan Utility for Windows versions 1.1.2 through 1.5.0 may allow a local atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1585</link><description>An unquoted Windows service executable path vulnerability in IJ Scan Utility for Windows versions 1.1.2 through 1.5.0 may allow a local attacker to execute a malicious file with the privileges of the affected service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20733 | CloudCharge cloudcharge.se Insufficiently Protected Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20733</link><description>Charging station authentication identifiers are publicly accessible via web-based mapping platforms.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24731 | EV2GO ev2go.io Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24731</link><description>WebSocket endpoints lack proper authentication mechanisms, enabling 
attackers to perform unauthorized station impersonation and manipulate 
data sent to the backend. An unauthenticated attacker can connect to the
 OCPP WebSocket endpoint using a known or discovered charging station 
identifier, then issue or receive OCPP commands as a legitimate charger.
 Given that no authentication is required, this can lead to privilege 
escalation, unauthorized control of charging infrastructure, and 
corruption of charging network data reported to the backend.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27652 | CloudCharge cloudcharge.se Insufficient Session Expiration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27652</link><description>The WebSocket backend uses charging station identifiers to uniquely 
associate sessions but allows multiple endpoints to connect using the 
same session identifier. This implementation results in predictable 
session identifiers and enables session hijacking or shadowing, where 
the most recent connection displaces the legitimate charging station and
 receives backend commands intended for that station. This vulnerability
 may allow unauthorized users to authenticate as other users or enable a
 malicious actor to cause a denial-of-service condition by overwhelming 
the backend with valid session requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3269 | psi-probe PSI Probe Session ExpireSessionsController.java handleRequestInternal denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3269</link><description>A flaw has been found in psi-probe PSI Probe up to 5.3.0. The impacted element is the function handleRequestInternal of the file psi-probe-core/src/main/java/psiprobe/controllers/sessions/ExpireSessionsController.java of the component Session Handler. Executing a manipulation can lead to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3270 | psi-probe PSI Probe Whois Whois.java lookup server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3270</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in psi-probe PSI Probe up to 5.3.0. This affects the function lookup of the file psi-probe-core/src/main/java/psiprobe/tools/Whois.java of the component Whois. The manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20781 | CloudCharge cloudcharge.se Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20781</link><description>WebSocket endpoints lack proper authentication mechanisms, enabling 
attackers to perform unauthorized station impersonation and manipulate 
data sent to the backend. An unauthenticated attacker can connect to the
 OCPP WebSocket endpoint using a known or discovered charging station 
identifier, then issue or receive OCPP commands as a legitimate charger.
 Given that no authentication is required, this can lead to privilege 
escalation, unauthorized control of charging infrastructure, and 
corruption of charging network data reported to the backend.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25114 | CloudCharge cloudcharge.se Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25114</link><description>The WebSocket Application Programming Interface lacks restrictions on 
the number of authentication requests. This absence of rate limiting may
 allow an attacker to conduct denial-of-service attacks by suppressing 
or mis-routing legitimate charger telemetry, or conduct brute-force 
attacks to gain unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2597 | Crypt::SysRandom::XS versions before 0.010 for Perl is vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow in the XS function random_bytes()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2597</link><description>Crypt::SysRandom::XS versions before 0.010 for Perl is vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow in the XS function random_bytes().

The function does not validate that the length parameter is non-negative. If a negative value (e.g. -1) is supplied, the expression length + 1u causes an integer wraparound, resulting in a zero-byte allocation. The subsequent call to chosen random function (e.g. getrandom) passes the original negative value, which is implicitly converted to a large unsigned value (typically SIZE_MAX). This can result in writes beyond the allocated buffer, leading to heap memory corruption and application crash (denial of service).

In common usage, the length argument is typically hardcoded by the caller, which reduces the likelihood of attacker-controlled exploitation. Applications that pass untrusted input to this parameter may be affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20791 | Chargemap chargemap.com Insufficiently Protected Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20791</link><description>Charging station authentication identifiers are publicly accessible via web-based mapping platforms.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20792 | Chargemap chargemap.com Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20792</link><description>The WebSocket Application Programming Interface lacks restrictions on 
the number of authentication requests. This absence of rate limiting may
 allow an attacker to conduct denial-of-service attacks by suppressing 
or misrouting legitimate charger telemetry, or conduct brute-force 
attacks to gain unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25711 | Chargemap chargemap.com Insufficient Session Expiration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25711</link><description>The WebSocket backend uses charging station identifiers to uniquely 
associate sessions but allows multiple endpoints to connect using the 
same session identifier. This implementation results in predictable 
session identifiers and enables session hijacking or shadowing, where 
the most recent connection displaces the legitimate charging station and
 receives backend commands intended for that station. This vulnerability
 may allow unauthorized users to authenticate as other users or enable a
 malicious actor to cause a denial-of-service condition by overwhelming 
the backend with valid session requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25851 | Chargemap chargemap.com Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25851</link><description>WebSocket endpoints lack proper authentication mechanisms, enabling 
attackers to perform unauthorized station impersonation and manipulate 
data sent to the backend. An unauthenticated attacker can connect to the
 OCPP WebSocket endpoint using a known or discovered charging station 
identifier, then issue or receive OCPP commands as a legitimate charger.
 Given that no authentication is required, this can lead to privilege 
escalation, unauthorized control of charging infrastructure, and 
corruption of charging network data reported to the backend.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28230 | In SteVe, any authenticated charger can terminate any other charger&amp;#x27;s active transaction (missing ownership verification on StopTransaction)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28230</link><description>SteVe is an open-source EV charging station management system. In versions up to and including 3.11.0, when a charger sends a StopTransaction message, SteVe looks up the transaction solely by transactionId (a sequential integer starting from 1) without verifying that the requesting charger matches the charger that originally started the transaction. Any authenticated charger can terminate any other charger’s active session across the entire network. The root cause is in OcppServerRepositoryImpl.getTransaction() which queries only by transactionId with no chargeBoxId ownership check. The validator checks that the transaction exists and is not already stopped but never verifies identity. As an attacker controlling a single registered charger I could enumerate sequential transaction IDs and send StopTransaction messages targeting active sessions on every other charger on the network simultaneously. Combined with FINDING-014 (unauthenticated SOAP endpoints), no registered charger is even required — the attack is executable with a single curl command requiring only a known chargeBoxId. Commit 7f169c6c5b36a9c458ec41ce8af581972e5c724e contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28269 | Kiteworks Core has an OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28269</link><description>Kiteworks is a private data network (PDN). Prior to version 9.2.0, avulnerability in Kiteworks command execution functionality allows authenticated users to redirect command output to arbitrary file locations. This could be exploited to overwrite critical system files and gain elevated access. Version 9.2.0 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28274 | Initiative Vulnerable to Token Theft via Stored XSS in Document Uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28274</link><description>Initiative is a self-hosted project management platform. Versions of the application prior to 0.32.4 are vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the document upload functionality. Any user with upload permissions within the "Initiatives" section can upload a malicious `.html` or `.htm` file as a document. Because the uploaded HTML file is served under the application's origin without proper sandboxing, the embedded JavaScript executes in the context of the application. As a result, authentication tokens, session cookies, or other sensitive data can be exfiltrated to an attacker-controlled server. Additionally, since the uploaded file is hosted under the application's domain, simply sharing the direct file link may result in execution of the malicious script when accessed. Version 0.32.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28275 | Initiative Vulnerable to Improper Session Invalidation (JWT Remains Valid)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28275</link><description>Initiative is a self-hosted project management platform. Versions of the application prior to 0.32.4 do not invalidate previously issued JWT access tokens after a user changes their password. As a result, older tokens remain valid until expiration and can still be used to access protected API endpoints. This behavior allows continued authenticated access even after the account password has been updated. Version 0.32.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28276 | Initiative Allows Unauthenticated Access to Uploaded Documents via Public /uploads/ Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28276</link><description>Initiative is a self-hosted project management platform. An access control vulnerability exists in Initiative versions prior to 0.32.2 where uploaded documents are served from a publicly accessible /uploads/ directory without any authentication or authorization checks. Any uploaded file can be accessed directly via its URL by unauthenticated users (e.g., in an incognito browser session), leading to potential disclosure of sensitive documents. The problem was patched in v0.32.2, and the patch was further improved on in 032.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28279 | `osctrl-admin` Vulnerable to OS Command Injection via Environment Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28279</link><description>osctrl is an osquery management solution. Prior to version 0.5.0, an OS command injection vulnerability exists in the `osctrl-admin` environment configuration. An authenticated administrator can inject arbitrary shell commands via the hostname parameter when creating or editing environments. These commands are embedded into enrollment one-liner scripts generated using Go's `text/template` package (which does not perform shell escaping) and execute on every endpoint that enrolls using the compromised environment. An attacker with administrator access can achieve remote code execution on every endpoint that enrolls using the compromised environment. Commands execute as root/SYSTEM (the privilege level used for osquery enrollment) before osquery is installed, leaving no agent-level audit trail. This enables backdoor installation, credential exfiltration, and full endpoint compromise. This is fixed in osctrl `v0.5.0`. As a workaround, restrict osctrl administrator access to trusted personnel, review existing environment configurations for suspicious hostnames, and/or monitor enrollment scripts for unexpected commands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28280 | `osctrl-admin` has Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in On-Demand Query List</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28280</link><description>osctrl is an osquery management solution. Prior to version 0.5.0, a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the `osctrl-admin` on-demand query list. A user with query-level permissions can inject arbitrary JavaScript via the query parameter when running an on-demand query. The payload is stored and executes in the browser of any user (including administrators) who visits the query list page. This can be chained with CSRF token extraction to escalate privileges and take actions as the logged in user. An attacker with query-level permissions (the lowest privilege tier) can execute arbitrary JavaScript in the browsers of all users who view the query list. Depending on their level of access, it can lead to full platform compromise if an administrator executes the payload. The issue is fixed in osctrl `v0.5.0`. As a workaround, restrict query-level permissions to trusted users, monitor query list for suspicious payloads, and/or review osctrl user accounts for unauthorized administrators.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3268 | psi-probe PSI Probe Session Attribute RemoveSessAttributeController.java access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3268</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in psi-probe PSI Probe up to 5.3.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file psi-probe-core/src/main/java/psiprobe/controllers/sessions/RemoveSessAttributeController.java of the component Session Attribute Handler. Performing a manipulation results in improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28213 | EverShop Vulnerable to Arbitrary Customer Account Takeover via Exposure of Password Reset Token in API Response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28213</link><description>EverShop is a TypeScript-first eCommerce platform. Versions prior to 2.1.1 have a vulnerability in the "Forgot Password" functionality. When specifying a target email address, the API response returns the password reset token. This allows an attacker to take over the associated account. Version 2.1.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:57:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28215 | hoppscotch Vulnerable to Unauthenticated Onboarding Config Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28215</link><description>hoppscotch is an open source API development ecosystem. Prior to version 2026.2.0, an unauthenticated attacker can overwrite the entire infrastructure configuration of a self-hosted Hoppscotch instance including OAuth provider credentials and SMTP settings  by sending a single HTTP POST request with no authentication. The endpoint POST /v1/onboarding/config has no authentication guard and performs no check on whether onboarding was already completed. A successful exploit allows the attacker to replace the instance's Google/GitHub/Microsoft OAuth application credentials with their own, causing all subsequent user logins via SSO to authenticate against the attacker's OAuth app. The attacker captures OAuth tokens and email addresses of every user who logs in after the exploit. Additionally, the endpoint returns a recovery token that can be used to read all stored secrets in plaintext, including SMTP passwords and any other configured credentials. Version 2026.2.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:57:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28216 | hoppscotch has IDOR in updateUserEnvironment / deleteUserEnvironment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28216</link><description>hoppscotch is an open source API development ecosystem. Prior to version 2026.2.0, any logged-in user can read, modify or delete another user's personal environment by ID. `user-environments.resolver.ts:82-109`, `updateUserEnvironment` mutation uses `@UseGuards(GqlAuthGuard)` but is missing the `@GqlUser()` decorator entirely. The user's identity is never extracted, so the service receives only the environment ID and performs a `prisma.userEnvironment.update({ where: { id } })` without any ownership filter. `deleteUserEnvironment` does extract the user but the service only uses the UID to check if the target is a global environment. Actual delete query uses WHERE { id } without AND userUid. hoppscotch environments store API keys, auth tokens and secrets used in API requests. An authenticated attacker who obtains another user's environment ID can read their secrets, replace them with malicious values or delete them entirely. The environment ID format is CUID, which limits mass exploitation but insider threat and combined info leak scenarios are realistic. Version 2026.2.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:57:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28217 | IDOR in GraphQL userCollection Query Exposes Other Users&amp;#x27; Private Collections</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28217</link><description>hoppscotch is an open source API development ecosystem. Prior to version 2026.2.0, the `userCollection` GraphQL query accepts an arbitrary collection ID and returns the full collection data — including title, type, and the serialized `data` field containing HTTP requests with headers and potentially secrets — to any authenticated user, without verifying that the requesting user owns the collection. This is an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) caused by a missing authorization check that exists on every other operation in the same resolver. Version 2026.2.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:57:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28225 | Manyfold has IDOR in ModelFilesController</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28225</link><description>Manyfold is an open source, self-hosted web application for managing a collection of 3d models, particularly focused on 3d printing. Prior to version 0.133.1, the `get_model` method in `ModelFilesController` (line 158-160) loads models using `Model.find_param(params[:model_id])` without `policy_scope()`, bypassing Pundit authorization. All other controllers correctly use `policy_scope(Model).find_param()` (e.g., `ModelsController` line 263). Version 0.133.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:57:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28226 | Phishing Club has Authenticated Blind SQL Injection in GetOrphaned Recipient Listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28226</link><description>Phishing Club is a phishing simulation and man-in-the-middle framework. Prior to version 1.30.2, an authenticated SQL injection vulnerability exists in the GetOrphaned recipient listing endpoint in versions prior to v1.30.2. The endpoint constructs a raw SQL query and concatenates the user-controlled sortBy value directly into the ORDER BY clause without allowlist validation. Because unknown values are silently passed through `RemapOrderBy()`, an authenticated attacker can inject SQL expressions into the `ORDER BY` clause. This issue was patched in v1.30.2 by validating the order-by column against an allowlist and clearing unknown mappings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:57:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3265 | go2ismail Free-CRM Security API improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3265</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in go2ismail Free-CRM up to b83c40a90726d5e58f0cc680ffdcaa28a03fb5d1. This affects an unknown part of the file /api/Security/ of the component Security API. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery. Therefore, version details for affected or updated releases cannot be specified. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:57:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28207 | Zen-C Vulnerable to Command Injection via Malicious Output Filename</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28207</link><description>Zen C is a systems programming language that compiles to human-readable GNU C/C11. Prior to version 0.4.2, a command injection vulnerability (CWE-78) in the Zen C compiler allows local attackers to execute arbitrary shell commands by providing a specially crafted output filename via the `-o` command-line argument. The vulnerability existed in the `main` application logic (specifically in `src/main.c`), where the compiler constructed a shell command string to invoke the backend C compiler. This command string was built by concatenating various arguments, including the user-controlled output filename, and was subsequently executed using the `system()` function. Because `system()` invokes a shell to parse and execute the command, shell metacharacters within the output filename were interpreted by the shell, leading to arbitrary command execution. An attacker who can influence the command-line arguments passed to the `zc` compiler (like through a build script or a CI/CD pipeline configuration) can execute arbitrary commands with the privileges of the user running the compiler. The vulnerability has been fixed in version 0.4.2 by removing `system()` calls, implementing `ArgList`, and internal argument handling. Users are advised to update to Zen C version v0.4.2 or later.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:57:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28208 | Junrar has arbitrary file write due to backslash path traversal bypass in LocalFolderExtractor on Linux/Unix</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28208</link><description>Junrar is an open source java RAR archive library. Prior to version 7.5.8, a backslash path traversal vulnerability in `LocalFolderExtractor` allows an attacker to write arbitrary files with attacker-controlled content anywhere on the filesystem when a crafted RAR archive is extracted on Linux/Unix. This can often lead to remote code execution (e.g., overwriting shell profiles, source code, cron jobs, etc). Version 7.5.8 has a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:57:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28211 | Arbitrary code execution in log reader via untrusted log file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28211</link><description>The NVDA Dev &amp; Test Toolbox is an NVDA add-on for gathering tools to help NVDA development and testing. A vulnerability exists in versions 2.0 through 8.0 in the Log Reader feature of this add-on. A maliciously crafted log file can lead to arbitrary code execution when a user reads it with log reader commands. The log reading command process speech log entries in an unsafe manner. Python expressions embedded in the log may be evaluated when when speech entries are read with log reading commands. An attacker can exploit this by convincing a user to open a malicious crafted log file and to analyze it using the log reading commands. When the log is read, attacker-controlled code may execute with the privileges of the current user.
This issue does not require elevated privileges and relies solely on user interaction (opening the log file). Version 9.0 contains a fix for the issue. As a workaround, avoid using log reading commands, or at least, commands to move to next/previous log message (any message or commands for each type of message). For more security, one may disable their gestures in the input gesture dialog.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:57:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27638 | ActualBudget missing authorization in sync endpoints allows cross-user budget file access in multi-user mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27638</link><description>Actual is a local-first personal finance tool. Prior to version 26.2.1, in multi-user mode (OpenID), the sync API endpoints (`/sync/*`) don't verify that the authenticated user owns or has access to the file being operated on. Any authenticated user can read, modify, and overwrite any other user's budget files by providing their file ID. Version 26.2.1 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:20:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27838 | wger: IDOR via user-unscoped cache keys on routine API actions exposes workout data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27838</link><description>wger is a free, open-source workout and fitness manager. Five routine detail action endpoints check a cache before calling `self.get_object()`. In versions up to and including 2.4, ache keys are scoped only by `pk` — no user ID is included. When a victim has previously accessed their routine via the API, an attacker can retrieve the cached response for the same PK without any ownership check. Commit e964328784e2ee2830a1991d69fadbce86ac9fbf contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:20:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27839 | wger: IDOR in nutritional_values endpoints exposes private dietary data via direct ORM lookup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27839</link><description>wger is a free, open-source workout and fitness manager. In versions up to and including 2.4, three `nutritional_values` action endpoints fetch objects via `Model.objects.get(pk=pk)` — a raw ORM call that bypasses the user-scoped queryset. Any authenticated user can read another user's private nutrition plan data, including caloric intake and full macro breakdown, by supplying an arbitrary PK. Commit 29876a1954fe959e4b58ef070170e81703dab60e contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:20:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3264 | go2ismail Free-CRM Administrative redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3264</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in go2ismail Free-CRM up to b83c40a90726d5e58f0cc680ffdcaa28a03fb5d1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Administrative Interface. Executing a manipulation can lead to execution after redirect. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This product implements a rolling release for ongoing delivery, which means version information for affected or updated releases is unavailable. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:20:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27449 | Umbraco.Engage.Forms Allows Unauthorized Access to Multiple API Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27449</link><description>Umbraco Engage is a business intelligence platform. A vulnerability has been identified in Umbraco Engage prior to versions 16.2.1 and 17.1.1 where certain API endpoints are exposed without enforcing authentication or authorization checks. The affected endpoints can be accessed directly over the network without requiring a valid session or user credentials. By supplying a user-controlled identifier parameter (e.g., ?id=), an attacker can retrieve sensitive data associated with arbitrary records. Because no access control validation is performed, the endpoints are vulnerable to enumeration attacks, allowing attackers to iterate over identifiers and extract data at scale. An unauthenticated attacker can retrieve sensitive Engage-related data by directly querying the affected API endpoints. The vulnerability allows arbitrary record access through predictable or enumerable identifiers. The confidentiality impact is considered high. No direct integrity or availability impact has been identified. The scope of exposed data depends on the deployment but may include analytics data, tracking data, customer-related information, or other Engage-managed content. The vulnerability affects both v16 and v17. Patches have already been released. Users are advised to update to 16.2.1 or 17.1.1. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27457 | Weblate: Missing access control for the AddonViewSet API exposes all addon configurations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27457</link><description>Weblate is a web based localization tool. Prior to version 5.16.1, the REST API's `AddonViewSet` (`weblate/api/views.py`, line 2831) uses `queryset = Addon.objects.all()` without overriding `get_queryset()` to scope results by user permissions. This allows any authenticated user (or anonymous users if `REQUIRE_LOGIN` is not set) to list and retrieve ALL addons across all projects and components via `GET /api/addons/` and `GET /api/addons/{id}/`. Version 5.16.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27835 | wger: IDOR in RepetitionsConfig and MaxRepetitionsConfig API leak other users&amp;#x27; workout data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27835</link><description>wger is a free, open-source workout and fitness manager. In versions up to and including 2.4, `RepetitionsConfigViewSet` and `MaxRepetitionsConfigViewSet` return all users' repetition config data because their `get_queryset()` calls `.all()` instead of filtering by the authenticated user. Any registered user can enumerate every other user's workout structure. Commit 1fda5690b35706bb137850c8a084ec6a13317b64 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25741 | Zulip Vulnerable to Modification of Payment Method (Stripe Default Card) by Non-Billing Users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25741</link><description>Zulip is an open-source team collaboration tool. Prior to commit bf28c82dc9b1f630fa8e9106358771b20a0040f7, the API endpoint for creating a card update session during an upgrade flow was accessible to users with only organization member privileges. When the associated Stripe Checkout session is completed, the Stripe webhook updates the organization’s default payment method. Because no billing-specific authorization check is enforced, a regular (non-billing) member can change the organization’s payment method. This vulnerability affected the Zulip Cloud payment processing system, and has been patched as of commit bf28c82dc9b1f630fa8e9106358771b20a0040f7. Self-hosted deploys are no longer affected and no patch or upgrade is required for them.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28219 | Privilege Escalation via Mass Assignment Allows Regular Users to Set Topics as Global Banners</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28219</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. Prior to versions 2025.12.2, 2026.1.1, and 2026.2.0, an improper authorization check in the topic management logic allows authenticated users to modify privileged attributes of their topics. By manipulating specific parameters in a PUT or POST request, a regular user can elevate a topic’s status to a site-wide notice or banner, bypassing intended administrative restrictions. Versions 2025.12.2, 2026.1.1, and 2026.2.0 patch the issue. There are no practical workarounds to prevent this behavior other than applying the security patch. Administrators concerned about unauthorized promotions should audit recent changes to site banners and global notices until the fix is deployed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28227 | Discourse Vulnerable to Unauthorized Topic Creation in Staff-Only Categories via Topic Timer publish_to_category</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28227</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. Prior to versions 2025.12.2, 2026.1.1, and 2026.2.0, TL4 users can publish topics into staff-only categories via the `publish_to_category` topic timer, bypassing authorization checks. Versions 2025.12.2, 2026.1.1, and 2026.2.0 patch the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3263 | go2ismail Asp.Net-Core-Inventory-Order-Management-System Security API improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3263</link><description>A vulnerability was found in go2ismail Asp.Net-Core-Inventory-Order-Management-System up to 9.20250118. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /api/Security/ of the component Security API. Performing a manipulation results in improper authorization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27153 | Discourse doesn&amp;#x27;t prevent moderators from exporting user Chat DMs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27153</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. Prior to versions 2025.12.2, 2026.1.1, and 2026.2.0, moderators could export user Chat DMs via the CSV export endpoint by exploiting an overly permissive allowlist in `can_export_entity?`. The method allowed moderators to export any entity not explicitly blocked instead of restricting to an explicit allowlist. Versions 2025.12.2, 2026.1.1, and 2026.2.0 patch the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27154 | Discourse has XSS when editing a malicious post</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27154</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. Prior to versions 2025.12.2, 2026.1.1, and 2026.2.0, a user full name can be evaluated as raw HTML when the following settings are set: `display_name_on_posts` =&gt; true; and `prioritize_username_in_ux` =&gt; false. Editing a post of a malicious user would trigger an XSS. Versions 2025.12.2, 2026.1.1, and 2026.2.0 patch the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28218 | Discourse&amp;#x27;s Fail-Open Access Control in Data Explorer Plugin Allows Unauthorized SQL Query Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28218</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. Prior to versions 2025.12.2, 2026.1.1, and 2026.2.0, fail-open access control in Data Explorer plugin allows any authenticated user to execute SQL queries that have no explicit group assignments, including built-in system queries. Versions 2025.12.2, 2026.1.1, and 2026.2.0 patch the issue. As a workaround, either explicitly set group permissions on each Data Explorer query that doesn't have permissions, or disable discourse-data-explorer plugin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2244 | Sensitive Data Exposure in Google Cloud Vertex AI Workbench</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2244</link><description>A vulnerability in Google Cloud Vertex AI Workbench from 7/21/2025 to 01/30/2026 allows an attacker to exfiltrate valid Google Cloud access tokens of other users via abuse of a built-in startup script.

All instances after January 30th, 2026 have been patched to protect from this vulnerability. No user action is required for this.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14343 | Reflected XSS in Dokuzsoft Technology&amp;#x27;s E-Commerce Product</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14343</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dokuzsoft Technology Ltd. E-Commerce Product allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects E-Commerce Product: through 10122025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2677 | Multiple vulnerabilities in A3factura software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2677</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) on the A3factura web platform, in parameter 'name', in 'a3factura-app.wolterskluwer.es/#/incomes/representatives-management' endpoint, which could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code in the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2678 | Multiple vulnerabilities in A3factura software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2678</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) on the A3factura web platform, in parameter 'name', parameter 'name', in 'a3factura-app.wolterskluwer.es/#/incomes/customers' endpoint, which could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code in the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2679 | Multiple vulnerabilities in A3factura software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2679</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) on the A3factura web platform, in parameter 'customerName', in 'a3factura-app.wolterskluwer.es/#/incomes/salesInvoices' endpoint, which could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code in the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2680 | Multiple vulnerabilities in A3factura software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2680</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) on the A3factura web platform, in parameter 'customerVATNumber', in 'a3factura-app.wolterskluwer.es/#/incomes/salesDeliveryNotes' endpoint, which could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code in the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 13:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1198 | SQL Injection in SIMPLE.ERP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1198</link><description>SIMPLE.ERP is vulnerable to the SQL Injection in search functionality in "Obroty na kontach" window. Lack of input validation allows an authenticated attacker to prepare a malicious query to the database that will be executed.
This issue was fixed in 6.30@A04.4_u06.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64999 | Cross-site scripting in HTML logs of Synthetic Monitoring test services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64999</link><description>Improper neutralization of input in Checkmk versions 2.4.0 before 2.4.0p22, and 2.3.0 before 2.3.0p43 allows an attacker that can manipulate a host's check output to inject malicious JavaScript into the Synthetic Monitoring HTML logs, which can then be accessed via a crafted phishing link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 10:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28083 | WordPress Flatsome theme &amp;lt;= 3.20.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28083</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in UX-themes Flatsome flatsome allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Flatsome: from n/a through &lt;= 3.20.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28131 | WordPress Elementor Addon Elements plugin &amp;lt;= 1.14.4 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28131</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in WPVibes Elementor Addon Elements addon-elements-for-elementor-page-builder allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Elementor Addon Elements: from n/a through &lt;= 1.14.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28132 | WordPress WooCommerce Photo Reviews plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28132</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in villatheme WooCommerce Photo Reviews woocommerce-photo-reviews allows Code Injection.This issue affects WooCommerce Photo Reviews: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28136 | WordPress WP SMS plugin &amp;lt;= 6.9.12 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28136</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in VeronaLabs WP SMS wp-sms allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WP SMS: from n/a through &lt;= 6.9.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28138 | WordPress uListing plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28138</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Stylemix uListing ulisting allows Object Injection.This issue affects uListing: from n/a through &lt;= 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1692 | Missing origin validation in GraphicalData web service requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1692</link><description>A missing origin validation in WebSockets vulnerability affects the GraphicalData web services used by the WebVue, WebScheduler, TouchVue and SnapVue features of PcVue in version 12.0.0 through 16.3.3 included. It might allow a remote attacker to lure a successfully authenticated user to a malicious website.

This vulnerability only affects the following two endpoints: GraphicalData/js/signalR/connect and GraphicalData/js/signalR/reconnect.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:02:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1693 | Use of vulnerable Resource Owner Password Credentials flow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1693</link><description>The OAuth grant type Resource Owner Password Credentials (ROPC) flow is still used by the werbservices used by the WebVue, WebScheduler, TouchVue and Snapvue features of PcVue in version 12.0.0 through 16.3.3 included despite being deprecated. It might allow a remote attacker to steal user credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:02:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1694 | Server configuration details in HTTP headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1694</link><description>HTTP headers are added by the default configuration of IIS and ASP.net, and are not removed at the deployment phase of the webservices used by the WebVue, WebScheduler, TouchVue and SnapVue features of PcVue in version 12.0.0 through 16.3.3 included. It unnecessarily exposes sensitive information about the server configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:02:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1695 | XSS vulnerability upon unsuccessful authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1695</link><description>An XSS vulnerability affects the OAuth web services used by the WebVue, WebScheduler, TouchVue and SnapVue features of PcVue in version 12.0.0 through 16.3.3 included. It might allow a remote attacker to trick a legitimate user into loading content from another site upon unsuccessful user authentication on an unknown application (unknown client_id).

This vulnerability only affects the error page of the OAuth server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:02:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1696 | Missing security HTTP headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1696</link><description>Some HTTP security headers are not properly set by the web server when sending responses to the client application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:02:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1697 | Use of unsecure cookies for GraphicalData web service and WebClient web app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1697</link><description>The Secure and SameSite attribute are missing in the GraphicalData web services and WebClient web app of PcVue in version 12.0.0 through 16.3.3 included.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:02:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1698 | HTTP Host header vulnerability in WebClient and WebScheduler web apps</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1698</link><description>A HTTP Host header attack vulnerability affects WebClient and the WebScheduler web apps of PcVue in version 15.0.0 through 16.3.3 included, allowing a remote attacker to inject harmful payloads that manipulate server-side behavior.

This vulnerability only affects the endpoints /Authentication/ExternalLogin, /Authentication/AuthorizationCodeCallback and /Authentication/Logout
of the WebClient and WebScheduler web apps.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:02:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23703 | The installer of FinalCode Client provided by Digital Arts Inc. contains an incorrect default permissions vulnerability. A non-administrativ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23703</link><description>The installer of FinalCode Client provided by Digital Arts Inc. contains an incorrect default permissions vulnerability. A non-administrative user may execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privilege.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25191 | The installer of FinalCode Client provided by Digital Arts Inc. contains an issue with the DLL search path. If a user is directed to place a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25191</link><description>The installer of FinalCode Client provided by Digital Arts Inc. contains an issue with the DLL search path. If a user is directed to place a malicious DLL file and the installer to the same directory and execute the installer, arbitrary code may be executed with the installer's execution privilege.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1311 | Worry Proof Backup &amp;lt;= 0.2.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Path Traversal via Backup Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1311</link><description>The Worry Proof Backup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 0.2.4 via the backup upload functionality. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload a malicious ZIP archive with path traversal sequences to write arbitrary files anywhere on the server, including executable PHP files. This can lead to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1779 | User Registration &amp;amp; Membership &amp;lt;= 5.1.2 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1779</link><description>The User Registration &amp; Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 5.1.2. This is due to incorrect authentication in the 'register_member' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in a newly registered user on the site who has the 'urm_user_just_created' user meta set.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23999 | Fleet: Device lock PIN can be predicted if lock time is known</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23999</link><description>Fleet is open source device management software. In versions prior to 4.80.1, Fleet generated device lock and wipe PINs using a predictable algorithm based solely on the current Unix timestamp. Because no secret key or additional entropy was used, the resulting PIN could potentially be derived if the approximate time the device was locked is known. Fleet’s device lock and wipe commands generate a 6-digit PIN that is displayed to administrators for unlocking a device. In affected versions, this PIN was deterministically derived from the current timestamp. An attacker with physical possession of a locked device and knowledge of the approximate time the lock command was issued could theoretically predict the correct PIN within a limited search window. However, successful exploitation is constrained by multiple factors: Physical access to the device is required, the approximate lock time must be known, the operating system enforces rate limiting on PIN entry attempts, attempts would need to be spread over, and device wipe operations would typically complete before sufficient attempts could be made. As a result, this issue does not allow remote exploitation, fleet-wide compromise, or bypass of Fleet authentication controls. Version 4.80.1 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24004 | Fleet: Unauthenticated Android device disenrollment vulnerability via Pub/Sub endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24004</link><description>Fleet is open source device management software. In versions prior to 4.80.1, a vulnerability in Fleet’s Android MDM Pub/Sub handling could allow unauthenticated requests to trigger device unenrollment events. This may result in unauthorized removal of individual Android devices from Fleet management. If Android MDM is enabled, an attacker could send a crafted request to the Android Pub/Sub endpoint to unenroll a targeted Android device from Fleet without authentication. This issue does not grant access to Fleet, allow execution of commands, or provide visibility into device data. Impact is limited to disruption of Android device management for the affected device. Version 4.80.1 fixes the issue. If an immediate upgrade is not possible, affected Fleet users should temporarily disable Android MDM.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25963 | Fleet: Authorization Bypass in certificate template batch deletion for team administrators</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25963</link><description>Fleet is open source device management software. In versions prior to 4.80.1, a broken authorization check in Fleet’s certificate template deletion API could allow a team administrator to delete certificate templates belonging to other teams within the same Fleet instance. Fleet supports certificate templates that are scoped to individual teams. In affected versions, the batch deletion endpoint validated authorization using a user-supplied team identifier but did not verify that the certificate template IDs being deleted actually belonged to that team. As a result, a team administrator could delete certificate templates associated with other teams, potentially disrupting certificate-based workflows such as device enrollment, Wi-Fi authentication, VPN access, or other certificate-dependent configurations for the affected teams. This issue does not allow privilege escalation, access to sensitive data, or compromise of Fleet’s control plane. Impact is limited to integrity and availability of certificate templates across teams. Version 4.80.1 patches the issue. If an immediate upgrade is not possible, administrators should restrict access to certificate template management to trusted users and avoid delegating team administrator permissions where not strictly required.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27465 | Fleet: Sensitive Google Calendar credentials disclosed to low-privileged users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27465</link><description>Fleet is open source device management software. In versions prior to 4.80.1, a vulnerability in Fleet’s configuration API could expose Google Calendar service account credentials to authenticated users with low-privilege roles. This may allow unauthorized access to Google Calendar resources associated with the service account. Fleet returns configuration data through an API endpoint that is accessible to authenticated users, including those with the lowest-privilege “Observer” role. In affected versions, Google Calendar service account credentials were not properly obfuscated before being returned. As a result, a low-privilege user could retrieve the service account’s private key material. Depending on how the Google Calendar integration is configured, this could allow unauthorized access to calendar data or other Google Workspace resources associated with the service account. This issue does not allow escalation of privileges within Fleet or access to device management functionality. Version 4.80.1 patches the issue. If an immediate upgrade is not possible, administrators should remove the Google Calendar integration from Fleet and rotate the affected Google service account credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27963 | Audiobookshelf has Stored XSS in Tooltip.vue via Audiobook Metadata</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27963</link><description>Audiobookshelf is a self-hosted audiobook and podcast server. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.32.0 of the Audiobookshelf web application that allows arbitrary JavaScript execution through malicious library metadata. Attackers with library modification privileges can execute code in victim users' browsers, potentially leading to session hijacking and data exfiltration. Version 2.32.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27974 | Audiobooksheld VUlnerable to Stored XSS in WrappingMarquee.js via Audiobook Metadata (Mobile App Audio Player)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27974</link><description>Audiobookshelf is a self-hosted audiobook and podcast server. A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 0.12.0-beta of the Audiobookshelf mobile application that allows arbitrary JavaScript execution through malicious library metadata. Attackers with library modification privileges (or control over a malicious podcast RSS feed) can execute code in victim users' WebViews, potentially leading to session hijacking, data exfiltration, and unauthorized access to native device APIs. audiobookshelf-app version 0.12.0-beta fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27975 | Ajenti has a potential Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27975</link><description>Ajenti is a Linux and BSD modular server admin panel. Prior to version 2.2.13, an unauthenticated user could gain access to a server to execute arbitrary code on this server. This is fixed in the version 2.2.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2356 | User Registration &amp;amp; Membership &amp;lt;= 5.1.2 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Limited User Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2356</link><description>The User Registration &amp; Membership – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.2 via the 'register_member' function, due to missing validation on the 'member_id' user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary user accounts that newly registered on the site who has the 'urm_user_just_created' user meta set.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1557 | WP Responsive Images &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Unauthenticated Path Traversal to Arbitrary File Read via src</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1557</link><description>The WP Responsive Images plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 via the 'src' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27942 | fast-xml-parser has stack overflow in XMLBuilder with preserveOrder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27942</link><description>fast-xml-parser allows users to validate XML, parse XML to JS object, or build XML from JS object without C/C++ based libraries and no callback. Prior to version 5.3.8, the application crashes with stack overflow when user use XML builder with `preserveOrder:true`. Version 5.3.8 fixes the issue. As a workaround, use XML builder with `preserveOrder:false` or check the input data before passing to builder.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27943 | OpenEMR&amp;#x27;s Eye Exam View Trusts form_id Without Verifying Patient/Encounter Ownership</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27943</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. In versions up to and including 8.0.0, the eye exam (eye_mag) view loads data by `form_id` (or equivalent) without verifying that the form belongs to the current user’s patient/encounter context. An authenticated user can access or edit any patient’s eye exam by supplying another form ID; in some flows the session’s active patient may also be switched. A fix is available on the `main` branch of the OpenEMR GitHub repository.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27948 | Copyparty vulnerable to eflected cross-site scripting via setck parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27948</link><description>Copyparty is a portable file server. In versions prior to 1.20.9, an XSS allows for reflected cross-site scripting via URL-parameter `?setck=...`. Version 1.20.9 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27952 | Agenta has Python Sandbox Escape, Leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27952</link><description>Agenta is an open-source LLMOps platform. In Agenta-API prior to version 0.48.1, a Python sandbox escape vulnerability existed in Agenta's custom code evaluator. Agenta used RestrictedPython as a sandboxing mechanism for user-supplied evaluator code, but incorrectly whitelisted the `numpy` package as safe within the sandbox. This allowed authenticated users to bypass the sandbox and achieve arbitrary code execution on the API server. The escape path was through `numpy.ma.core.inspect`, which exposes Python's introspection utilities — including `sys.modules` — thereby providing access to unfiltered system-level functionality like `os.system`. This vulnerability affects the Agenta self-hosted platform (API server), not the SDK when used as a standalone Python library. The custom code evaluator runs server-side within the API process. The issue is fixed in v0.48.1 by removing `numpy` from the sandbox allowlist. In later versions (v0.60+), the RestrictedPython sandbox was removed entirely and replaced with a different execution model.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27954 | LiveHelperChat has department-level authorization bypass in holdaction, blockuser, and transferchat endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27954</link><description>Live Helper Chat is an open-source application that enables live support websites. In versions up to and including 4.52, three chat action endpoints  (holdaction.php, blockuser.php, and transferchat.php) load chat objects by ID without calling `erLhcoreClassChat::hasAccessToRead()`, allowing operators to act on chats in departments they are not assigned to. Operators with the relevant role permissions (holduse, allowblockusers, allowtransfer) can hold, block users from, or transfer chats in departments they are not assigned to. This is a horizontal privilege escalation within one organization. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27959 | Koa has Host Header Injection via `ctx.hostname`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27959</link><description>Koa is middleware for Node.js using ES2017 async functions. Prior to versions 3.1.2 and 2.16.4, Koa's `ctx.hostname` API performs naive parsing of the HTTP Host header, extracting everything before the first colon without validating the input conforms to RFC 3986 hostname syntax. When a malformed Host header containing a `@` symbol is received, `ctx.hostname` returns `evil[.]com` - an attacker-controlled value. Applications using `ctx.hostname` for URL generation, password reset links, email verification URLs, or routing decisions are vulnerable to Host header injection attacks. Versions 3.1.2 and 2.16.4 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27961 | Agenta&amp;#x27;s Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) via custom evaluator Jinja2 templates allows RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27961</link><description>Agenta is an open-source LLMOps platform. A Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 0.86.8 in Agenta's API server evaluator template rendering. Although the vulnerable code lives in the SDK package, it is executed server-side within the API process when running evaluators. This does not affect standalone SDK usage — it only impacts self-hosted or managed Agenta platform deployments. Version 0.86.8 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27965 | Vitess users with backup storage access can gain unauthorized access to production deployment environments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27965</link><description>Vitess is a database clustering system for horizontal scaling of MySQL. Prior to versions 23.0.3 and 22.0.4, anyone with read/write access to the backup storage location (e.g. an S3 bucket) can manipulate backup manifest files so that arbitrary code is later executed when that backup is restored. This can be used to provide that attacker with unintended/unauthorized access to the production deployment environment — allowing them to access information available in that environment as well as run any additional arbitrary commands there. Versions 23.0.3 and 22.0.4 contain a patch. Some workarounds are available. Those who intended to use an external decompressor then can always specify that decompressor command in the `--external-decompressor` flag value for `vttablet` and `vtbackup`. That then overrides any value specified in the manifest file. Those who did not intend to use an external decompressor, nor an internal one, can specify a value such as `cat` or `tee` in the `--external-decompressor` flag value for `vttablet` and `vtbackup` to ensure that a harmless command is always used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27966 | Langflow has Remote Code Execution in CSV Agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27966</link><description>Langflow is a tool for building and deploying AI-powered agents and workflows. Prior to version 1.8.0, the CSV Agent node in Langflow hardcodes `allow_dangerous_code=True`, which automatically exposes LangChain’s Python REPL tool (`python_repl_ast`). As a result, an attacker can execute arbitrary Python and OS commands on the server via prompt injection, leading to full Remote Code Execution (RCE). Version 1.8.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27968 | Packistry accepts expired access tokens</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27968</link><description>Packistry is a self-hosted Composer repository designed to handle PHP package distribution. Prior to version 0.13.0, RepositoryAwareController::authorize() verified token presence and ability, but did not enforce token expiration. As a result, an expired deploy token with the correct ability could still access repository endpoints (e.g., Composer metadata/download APIs). The fix in version 0.13.0 adds an explicit expiration check, and tests now test expired deploy tokens to ensure they are rejected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27969 | Vitess users with backup storage access can write to arbitrary file paths on restore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27969</link><description>Vitess is a database clustering system for horizontal scaling of MySQL. Prior to versions 23.0.3 and 22.0.4, anyone with read/write access to the backup storage location (e.g. an S3 bucket) can manipulate backup manifest files so that files in the manifest — which may be files that they have also added to the manifest and backup contents — are written to any accessible location on restore. This is a common path traversal security issue. This can be used to provide that attacker with unintended/unauthorized access to the production deployment environment — allowing them to access information available in that environment as well as run any additional arbitrary commands there. Versions 23.0.3 and 22.0.4 contain a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27970 | Angular i18n vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27970</link><description>Angular is a development platform for building mobile and desktop web applications using TypeScript/JavaScript and other languages. Versions prior to 21.2.0, 21.1.16, 20.3.17, and 19.2.19 have a cross-Site scripting vulnerability in the Angular internationalization (i18n) pipeline. In ICU messages (International Components for Unicode), HTML from translated content was not properly sanitized and could execute arbitrary JavaScript. Angular i18n typically involves three steps, extracting all messages from an application in the source language, sending the messages to be translated, and then merging their translations back into the final source code. Translations are frequently handled by contracts with specific partner companies, and involve sending the source messages to a separate contractor before receiving final translations for display to the end user. If the returned translations have malicious content, it could be rendered into the application and execute arbitrary JavaScript. When successfully exploited, this vulnerability allows for execution of attacker controlled JavaScript in the application origin. Depending on the nature of the application being exploited this could lead to credential exfiltration and/or page vandalism. Several preconditions apply to the attack. The attacker must compromise the translation file (xliff, xtb, etc.). Unlike most XSS vulnerabilities, this issue is not exploitable by arbitrary users. An attacker must first compromise an application's translation file before they can escalate privileges into the Angular application client. The victim application must use Angular i18n, use one or more ICU messages, render an ICU message, and not defend against XSS via a safe content security policy. Versions 21.2.0, 21.1.6, 20.3.17, and 19.2.19 patch the issue. Until the patch is applied, developers should consider reviewing and verifying translated content received from untrusted third parties before incorporating it in an Angular application, enabling strict CSP controls to block unauthorized JavaScript from executing on the page, and enabling Trusted Types to enforce proper HTML sanitization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27973 | Audiobookshelf has Stored XSS in ItemSearchCard.vue via Audiobook Metadata (Search Results on Mobile App)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27973</link><description>Audiobookshelf is a self-hosted audiobook and podcast server. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 0.12.0-beta of the Audiobookshelf mobile application that allows arbitrary JavaScript execution through malicious library metadata. Attackers with library modification privileges can execute code in victim users' browsers/WebViews, potentially leading to session hijacking, data exfiltration, and unauthorized access to native device APIs. The issue is fixed in audiobookshelf-app version 0.12.0-beta, corresponding to audiobookshelf version 2.12.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2029 | Livemesh Addons for Beaver Builder &amp;lt;= 3.9.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;title&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;value&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2029</link><description>The Livemesh Addons for Beaver Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `[labb_pricing_item]` shortcode's `title` and `value` attributes in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. Specifically, the plugin uses `htmlspecialchars_decode()` after `wp_kses_post()`, which decodes HTML entities back into executable code after sanitization has occurred. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2489 | TP2WP Importer &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;Watched domains&amp;#x27; Textarea</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2489</link><description>The TP2WP Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Watched domains' textarea on the attachment importer settings page in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping when domains are saved via AJAX and rendered with echo implode() without esc_textarea(). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the attachment importer settings page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2498 | WP Social Meta &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2498</link><description>The WP Social Meta plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2499 | Custom Logo &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Logo Path Setting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2499</link><description>The Custom Logo plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2506 | EM Cost Calculator &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;customer_name&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2506</link><description>The EM Cost Calculator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including, 2.3.1. This is due to the plugin storing attacker-controlled 'customer_name' data and rendering it in the admin customer list without output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts that execute when an administrator views the EMCC Customers page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22728 | sealed-secrets /v1/rotate can widen sealing scope to cluster-wide via attacker-controlled template annotations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22728</link><description>Bitnami Sealed Secrets is vulnerable to a scope-widening attack during
the secret rotation (/v1/rotate) flow. The rotation handler derives the
sealing scope for the newly encrypted output from untrusted
spec.template.metadata.annotations present in the input SealedSecret.
By submitting a victim SealedSecret to the rotate endpoint with the
annotation sealedsecrets.bitnami.com/cluster-wide=true injected into the
template metadata, a remote attacker can obtain a rotated version of the
secret that is cluster-wide. This bypasses original "strict" or
"namespace-wide" constraints, allowing the attacker to retarget and unseal
the secret in any namespace or under any name to recover the plaintext
credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27887 | Spin has memory leaks in various WIT interfaces</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27887</link><description>Spin is an open source developer tool for building and running serverless applications powered by WebAssembly. When Spin is configured to allow connections to a database or web server which could return responses of unbounded size (e.g. tables with many rows or large content bodies), Spin may in some cases attempt to buffer the entire response before delivering it to the guest, which can lead to the host process running out of memory, panicking, and crashing. In addition, a malicious guest application could incrementally insert a large number of rows or values into a database and then retrieve them all in a single query, leading to large host allocations. Spin 3.6.1, SpinKube 0.6.2, and `containerd-shim-spin` 0.22.1 have been patched to address the issue. As a workaround, configure Spin to only allow access to trusted databases and HTTP servers which limit response sizes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27899 | WireGuard Portal Vulnerable to Privilege Escalation to Admin via User Self-Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27899</link><description>WireGuard Portal (or wg-portal) is a web-based configuration portal for WireGuard server management. Prior to version 2.1.3, any authenticated non-admin user can become a full administrator by sending a single PUT request to their own user profile endpoint with `"IsAdmin": true` in the JSON body. After logging out and back in, the session picks up admin privileges from the database. When a user updates their own profile, the server parses the full JSON body into the user model, including the `IsAdmin` boolean field. A function responsible for preserving calculated or protected attributes pins certain fields to their database values (such as base model data, linked peer count, and authentication data), but it does not do this for `IsAdmin`. As a result, whatever value the client sends for `IsAdmin` is written directly to the database. After the exploit, the attacker has full admin access to the WireGuard VPN management portal. The problem was fixed in v2.1.3. The docker images for the tag 'latest' built from the master branch also include the fix.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27900 | Terraform Provider Debug Logs Vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27900</link><description>The Terraform Provider for Linode versions prior to v3.9.0 logged sensitive information including some passwords, StackScript content, and object storage data in debug logs without redaction. Provider debug logging is not enabled by default. This issue is exposed when debug/provider logs are explicitly enabled (for example in local troubleshooting, CI/CD jobs, or centralized log collection). If enabled, sensitive values may be written to logs and then retained, shared, or exported beyond the original execution environment. An authenticated user with access to provider debug logs (through log aggregation systems, CI/CD pipelines, or debug output) would thus be able to extract these sensitive credentials. Versions 3.9.0 and later sanitize debug logs by logging only non-sensitive metadata such as labels, regions, and resource IDs while redacting credentials, tokens, keys, scripts, and other sensitive content. Some other mitigations and workarounds are available. Disable Terraform/provider debug logging or set it to `WARN` level or above, restrict access to existing and historical logs, purge/retention-trim logs that may contain sensitive values, and/or rotate potentially exposed secrets/credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27901 | Svelte vulnerable to XSS during SSR with contenteditable `bind:innerText` and `bind:textContent`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27901</link><description>Svelte performance oriented web framework. Prior to version 5.53.5, the contents of `bind:innerText` and `bind:textContent` on `contenteditable` elements were not properly escaped. This could enable HTML injection and Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) if rendering untrusted data as the binding's initial value on the server. Version 5.53.5 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27902 | Svelte Vulnerable to XSS via HTML Comment Injection in SSR Error Boundary Hydration Markers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27902</link><description>Svelte performance oriented web framework. Prior to version 5.53.5, errors from `transformError` were not correctly escaped prior to being embedded in the HTML output, causing potential HTML injection and XSS if attacker-controlled content is returned from `transformError`. Version 5.53.5 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27903 | minimatch has a ReDoS: matchOne() combinatorial backtracking via multiple non-adjacent GLOBSTAR segments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27903</link><description>minimatch is a minimal matching utility for converting glob expressions into JavaScript RegExp objects. Prior to version 10.2.3, 9.0.7, 8.0.6, 7.4.8, 6.2.2, 5.1.8, 4.2.5, and 3.1.3, `matchOne()` performs unbounded recursive backtracking when a glob pattern contains multiple non-adjacent `**` (GLOBSTAR) segments and the input path does not match. The time complexity is O(C(n, k)) -- binomial -- where `n` is the number of path segments and `k` is the number of globstars. With k=11 and n=30, a call to the default `minimatch()` API stalls for roughly 5 seconds. With k=13, it exceeds 15 seconds. No memoization or call budget exists to bound this behavior. Any application where an attacker can influence the glob pattern passed to `minimatch()` is vulnerable. The realistic attack surface includes build tools and task runners that accept user-supplied glob arguments (ESLint, Webpack, Rollup config), multi-tenant systems where one tenant configures glob-based rules that run in a shared process, admin or developer interfaces that accept ignore-rule or filter configuration as globs, and CI/CD pipelines that evaluate user-submitted config files containing glob patterns. An attacker who can place a crafted pattern into any of these paths can stall the Node.js event loop for tens of seconds per invocation. The pattern is 56 bytes for a 5-second stall and does not require authentication in contexts where pattern input is part of the feature. Versions 10.2.3, 9.0.7, 8.0.6, 7.4.8, 6.2.2, 5.1.8, 4.2.5, and 3.1.3 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27904 | minimatch ReDoS: nested *() extglobs generate catastrophically backtracking regular expressions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27904</link><description>minimatch is a minimal matching utility for converting glob expressions into JavaScript RegExp objects. Prior to version 10.2.3, 9.0.7, 8.0.6, 7.4.8, 6.2.2, 5.1.8, 4.2.5, and 3.1.4, nested `*()` extglobs produce regexps with nested unbounded quantifiers (e.g. `(?:(?:a|b)*)*`), which exhibit catastrophic backtracking in V8. With a 12-byte pattern `*(*(*(a|b)))` and an 18-byte non-matching input, `minimatch()` stalls for over 7 seconds. Adding a single nesting level or a few input characters pushes this to minutes. This is the most severe finding: it is triggered by the default `minimatch()` API with no special options, and the minimum viable pattern is only 12 bytes. The same issue affects `+()` extglobs equally. Versions 10.2.3, 9.0.7, 8.0.6, 7.4.8, 6.2.2, 5.1.8, 4.2.5, and 3.1.4 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27938 | WPGraphQL Repo Vulnerable to Command Injection via Unsanitized GitHub Actions Expression in Release Workflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27938</link><description>WPGraphQL provides a GraphQL API for WordPress sites. Prior to version 2.9.1, the `wp-graphql/wp-graphql` repository contains a GitHub Actions workflow (`release.yml`) vulnerable to OS command injection through direct use of `${{ github.event.pull_request.body }}` inside a `run:` shell block. When a pull request from `develop` to `master` is merged, the PR body is injected verbatim into a shell command, allowing arbitrary command execution on the Actions runner. Version 2.9.1 contains a fix for the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27941 | OpenLIT Vulnerable to Remote Code Execution and Secret Exposure via Misuse of `pull_request_target` in GitHub Actions Workflows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27941</link><description>OpenLIT is an open source platform for AI engineering. Prior to version 1.37.1, several GitHub Actions workflows in OpenLIT's GitHub repository use the `pull_request_target` event while checking out and executing untrusted code from forked pull requests. These workflows run with the security context of the base repository, including a write-privileged `GITHUB_TOKEN` and numerous sensitive secrets (API keys, database/vector store tokens, and a Google Cloud service account key). Version 1.37.1 contains a fix.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27829 | Astro is vulnerable to SSRF due to missing allowlist enforcement in remote image inferSize</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27829</link><description>Astro is a web framework. In versions 9.0.0 through 9.5.3, a bug in Astro's image pipeline allows bypassing `image.domains` / `image.remotePatterns` restrictions, enabling the server to fetch content from unauthorized remote hosts. Astro provides an `inferSize` option that fetches remote images at render time to determine their dimensions. Remote image fetches are intended to be restricted to domains the site developer has manually authorized (using the `image.domains` or `image.remotePatterns` options). However, when `inferSize` is used, no domain validation is performed — the image is fetched from any host regardless of the configured restrictions. An attacker who can influence the image URL (e.g., via CMS content or user-supplied data) can cause the server to fetch from arbitrary hosts. This allows bypassing `image.domains` / `image.remotePatterns` restrictions to make server-side requests to unauthorized hosts. This includes the risk of server-side request forgery (SSRF) against internal network services and cloud metadata endpoints. Version 9.5.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27830 | c3p0 vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via unsafe deserialization of userOverridesAsString property</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27830</link><description>c3p0, a JDBC Connection pooling library, is vulnerable to attack via maliciously crafted Java-serialized objects and `javax.naming.Reference` instances. Several c3p0 `ConnectionPoolDataSource` implementations have a property called `userOverridesAsString` which conceptually represents a `Map&gt;`. Prior to v0.12.0, that property was maintained as a hex-encoded serialized object. Any attacker able to reset this property, on an existing `ConnectionPoolDataSource` or via maliciously crafted serialized objects or `javax.naming.Reference` instances could be tailored execute unexpected code on the application's `CLASSPATH`. The danger of this vulnerability was strongly magnified by vulnerabilities in c3p0's main dependency, mchange-commons-java. This library includes code that mirrors early implementations of JNDI functionality, including ungated support for remote `factoryClassLocation` values. Attackers could set c3p0's `userOverridesAsString` hex-encoded serialized objects that include objects "indirectly serialized" via JNDI references. Deserialization of those objects and dereferencing of the embedded `javax.naming.Reference` objects could provoke download and execution of malicious code from a remote `factoryClassLocation`. Although hazard presented by c3p0's vulnerabilites are exarcerbated by vulnerabilities in mchange-commons-java, use of Java-serialized-object hex as the format for a writable Java-Bean property, of objects that may be exposed across JNDI interfaces, represents a serious independent fragility. The `userOverridesAsString` property of c3p0 `ConnectionPoolDataSource` classes has been reimplemented to use a safe CSV-based format, rather than rely upon potentially dangerous Java object deserialization. c3p0-0.12.0+ and above depend upon mchange-commons-java 0.4.0+, which gates support for remote `factoryClassLocation` values by configuration parameters that default to restrictive values. c3p0 additionally enforces the new mchange-commons-java `com.mchange.v2.naming.nameGuardClassName` to prevent injection of unexpected, potentially remote JNDI names. There is no supported workaround for versions of c3p0 prior to 0.12.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27831 | rldns Vulnerable to Heap-based Out-of-Bounds Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27831</link><description>rldns is an open source DNS server. Version 2.3 has a heap-based out-of-bounds read that leads to denial of service. Version 1.4 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27837 | Dottie vulnerable to prototype pollution bypass via non-first path segments in set() and transform()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27837</link><description>Dottie provides nested object access and manipulation in JavaScript. Versions 2.0.4 through 2.0.6 contain an incomplete fix for CVE-2023-26132. The prototype pollution guard introduced in commit `7d3aee1` only validates the first segment of a dot-separated path, allowing an attacker to bypass the protection by placing `__proto__` at any position other than the first. Both `dottie.set()` and `dottie.transform()` are affected. Version 2.0.7 contains an updated fix to address the residual vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27840 | ZITADEL&amp;#x27;s truncated opaque tokens are still valid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27840</link><description>ZITADEL is an open source identity management platform. Starting in version 2.31.0 and prior to versions 3.4.7 and 4.11.0, opaque OIDC access tokens in the v2 format truncated to 80 characters are still considered valid.  Zitadel uses a symmetric AES encryption for opaque tokens. The cleartext payload is a concatenation of a couple of identifiers, such as a token ID and user ID. Internally Zitadel has 2 different versions of token payloads. v1 tokens are no longer created, but are still verified as to not invalidate existing session after upgrade. The cleartext payload has a format of `:`. v2 tokens distinguished further where the `token_id` is of the format `v2_-at_`. V1 token authZ/N session data is retrieved from the database using the (simple) `token_id` value and `user_id` value. The `user_id` (called `subject` in some parts of our code) was used as being the trusted user ID. V2 token authZ/N session data is retrieved from the database using the `oidc_session_id` and `access_token_id` and in this case the `user_id` from the token is ignored and taken from the session data in the database. By truncating the token to 80 chars, the user_id is now missing from the cleartext of the v2 token. The back-end still accepts this for above reasons. This issue is not considered exploitable, but may look awkward when reproduced. The patch in versions 4.11.0 and 3.4.7 resolves the issue by verifying the `user_id` from the token against the session data from the database. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27884 | NetExec vulnerable to arbitrary file write via path traversal in spider_plus module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27884</link><description>NetExec is a network execution tool. Prior to version 1.5.1, the module spider_plus improperly creates the output file and folder path when saving files from SMB shares. It does not take into account that it is possible for Linux SMB shares to have path traversal characters such as `../` in them. An attacker can craft a filename in an SMB share that includes these characters, which when spider_plus crawls and downloads, can write or overwrite arbitrary files. The issue is patched in v1.5.1. As a workaround, do not run spider_plus with DOWNLOAD=true against targets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27888 | pypdf: Manipulated FlateDecode XFA streams can exhaust RAM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27888</link><description>pypdf is a free and open-source pure-python PDF library. Prior to 6.7.3, an attacker who uses this vulnerability can craft a PDF which leads to the RAM being exhausted. This requires accessing the `xfa` property of a reader or writer and the corresponding stream being compressed using `/FlateDecode`. This has been fixed in pypdf 6.7.3. As a workaround, apply the patch manually.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27896 | MCP Go SDK Vulnerable to Improper Handling of Case Sensitivity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27896</link><description>The Go MCP SDK used Go's standard encoding/json.Unmarshal for JSON-RPC and MCP protocol message parsing in versions prior to 1.3.1. Go's standard library performs case-insensitive matching of JSON keys to struct field tags — a field tagged json:"method" would also match "Method", "METHOD", etc. This violated the JSON-RPC 2.0 specification, which defines exact field names. A malicious MCP peer may have been able to send protocol messages with non-standard field casing that the SDK would silently accept. This had the potential for bypassing intermediary inspection and coss-implementation inconsistency. Go's standard JSON unmarshaling was replaced with a case-sensitive decoder in commit 7b8d81c. Users are advised to update to v1.3.1 to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27945 | ZITADEL has potential SSRF via Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27945</link><description>ZITADEL is an open source identity management platform. Zitadel Action V2 (introduced as early preview in 2.59.0, beta in 3.0.0 and GA in 4.0.0) is a webhook based approach to allow developers act on API request to Zitadel and customize flows such the issue of a token. Zitadel's Action target URLs can point to local hosts, potentially allowing adversaries to gather internal network information and connect to internal services. When the URL points to a local host / IP address, an adversary might gather information about the internal network structure, the services exposed on internal hosts etc. This is sometimes called a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF). Zitadel Actions expect responses according to specific schemas, which reduces the threat vector. The patch in version 4.11.1 resolves the issue by checking the target URL against a denylist. By default localhost, resp. loopback IPs are denied. Note that this fix was only released on v4.x. Due to the stage (preview / beta) in which the functionality was in v2.x and v3.x, the changes that have been applied to it since then and the severity, respectively the actual thread vector, a backport to the corresponding versions was not feasible. Please check the workaround section for alternative solutions if an upgrade to v4.x is not possible. If an upgrade is not possible, prevent actions from using unintended endpoints by setting network policies or firewall rules in one's own infrastructure. Note that this is outside of the functionality provided by Zitadel.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27946 | ZITADEL Users Can Self-Verify Email/Phone via UpdateHumanUser API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27946</link><description>ZITADEL is an open source identity management platform. Prior to versions 4.11.1 and 3.4.7, a vulnerability in Zitadel's self-management capability allowed users to mark their email and phone as verified without going through an actual verification process. The patch in versions 4.11.1 and 3.4.7 resolves the issue by requiring the correct permission in case the verification flag is provided and only allows self-management of the email address and/or phone number itself. If an upgrade is not possible, an action (v2) could be used to prevent setting the verification flag on the own user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26186 | Fleet has a SQL injection via backtick escape in ORDER BY parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26186</link><description>Fleet is open source device management software. A SQL injection vulnerability in versions prior to 4.80.1 allowed authenticated users to inject arbitrary SQL expressions via the `order_key` query parameter. Due to unsafe use of `goqu.I()` when constructing the `ORDER BY` clause, specially crafted input could escape identifier quoting and be interpreted as executable SQL. An authenticated attacker with access to the affected endpoint could inject SQL expressions into the underlying MySQL query. Although the injection occurs in an `ORDER BY` context, it is sufficient to enable blind SQL injection techniques that can disclose database information through conditional expressions that affect result ordering. Crafted expressions may also cause excessive computation or query failures, potentially leading to degraded performance or denial of service. No direct evidence of reliable data modification or stacked query execution was demonstrated. Version 4.80.1 fixes the issue. If an immediate upgrade is not possible, users should restrict access to the affected endpoint to trusted roles only and ensure that any user-supplied sort or column parameters are strictly allow-listed at the application or proxy layer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27809 | psd-tools: Compression module has unguarded zlib decompression, missing dimension validation, and hardening gaps</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27809</link><description>psd-tools is a Python package for working with Adobe Photoshop PSD files. Prior to version 1.12.2, when a PSD file contains malformed RLE-compressed image data (e.g. a literal run that extends past the expected row size), decode_rle() raises ValueError which propagated all the way to the user, crashing psd.composite() and psd-tools export. decompress() already had a fallback that replaces failed channels with black pixels when result is None, but it never triggered because the ValueError from decode_rle() was not caught. The fix in version 1.12.2 wraps the decode_rle() call in a try/except so the existing fallback handles the error gracefully.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27812 | Sub2API Vulnerable to Password Reset Poisoning via Host Header Trust Issue, Leading to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27812</link><description>Sub2API is an AI API gateway platform designed to distribute and manage API quotas from AI product subscriptions. A vulnerability in versions prior to 0.1.85 is a Password Reset Poisoning (Host Header / Forwarded Header trust issue), which allows attackers to manipulate the password reset link. Attackers can exploit this flaw to inject their own domain into the password reset link, leading to the potential for account takeover. The vulnerability has been fixed in version v0.1.85. If upgrading is not immediately possible, users can mitigate the vulnerability by disabling the "forgot password" feature until an upgrade to a patched version can be performed. This will prevent attackers from exploiting the vulnerability via the affected endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27818 | TerriaJS-Server has a domain validation bypass vulnerability in its proxy allowlist</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27818</link><description>TerriaJS-Server is a NodeJS Express server for TerriaJS, a library for building web-based geospatial data explorers. A validation bug in versions prior to 4.0.3 allows an attacker to proxy domains not explicitly allowed in the `proxyableDomains` configuration. Version 4.0.3 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27821 | GPAC NHML Demuxer (dmx_nhml.c) Vulnerable to Stack Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27821</link><description>GPAC is an open-source multimedia framework. In versions up to and including 26.02.0, a stack buffer overflow occurs during NHML file parsing in `src/filters/dmx_nhml.c`. The value of the xmlHeaderEnd XML attribute is copied from att-&gt;value into szXmlHeaderEnd[1000] using strcpy() without any length validation. If the input exceeds 1000 bytes, it overwrites beyond the stack buffer boundary. Commit 9bd7137fded2db40de61a2cf3045812c8741ec52 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27735 | mcp-server-git : Path traversal in git_add allows staging files outside repository boundaries</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27735</link><description>Model Context Protocol Servers is a collection of reference implementations for the model context protocol (MCP). In mcp-server-git versions prior to 2026.1.14, the git_add tool did not validate that file paths provided in the files argument were within the repository boundaries. Because the tool used GitPython's repo.index.add() rather than the Git CLI, relative paths containing `../` sequences that resolve outside the repository were accepted and staged into the Git index. Users are advised to upgrade to 2026.1.14 or newer to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27804 | Parse Server: Account takeover via JWT algorithm confusion in Google auth adapter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27804</link><description>Parse Server is an open source backend that can be deployed to any infrastructure that can run Node.js. Prior to versions 8.6.3 and 9.1.1-alpha.4, an unauthenticated attacker can forge a Google authentication token with `alg: "none"` to log in as any user linked to a Google account, without knowing their credentials. All deployments with Google authentication enabled are affected. The fix in versions 8.6.3 and 9.1.1-alpha.4 hardcodes the expected `RS256` algorithm instead of trusting the JWT header, and replaces the Google adapter's custom key fetcher with `jwks-rsa` which rejects unknown key IDs. As a workaround, dsable Google authentication until upgrading is possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27808 | Mailpit is Vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via Link Check API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27808</link><description>Mailpit is an email testing tool and API for developers. Prior to version 1.29.2, the Link Check API (/api/v1/message/{ID}/link-check) is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF). The server performs HTTP HEAD requests to every URL found in an email without validating target hosts or filtering private/internal IP addresses. The response returns status codes and status text per link, making this a non-blind SSRF. In the default configuration (no authentication on SMTP or API), this is fully exploitable remotely with zero user interaction. This is the same class of vulnerability that was fixed in the HTML Check API (CVE-2026-23845 / GHSA-6jxm-fv7w-rw5j) and the screenshot proxy (CVE-2026-21859 / GHSA-8v65-47jx-7mfr), but the Link Check code path was not included in either fix. Version 1.29.2 fixes this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:02:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27709 | NanaZip .NET Single-File Manifest Parser Vulnerable to Out-of-Bounds Read via Unchecked RelativePathLength</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27709</link><description>NanaZip is an open source file archive. Starting in version 5.0.1252.0 and prior to versions 6.0.1638.0 and 6.5.1638.0, NanaZip’s `.NET Single File Application` parser has an out-of-bounds read vulnerability in manifest parsing. A crafted bundle can provide a malformed `RelativePathLength` so the parser constructs a `std::string` from memory beyond `HeaderBuffer`, leading to crash and potential in-process memory disclosure. Versions 6.0.1638.0 and 6.5.1638.0 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27710 | NanaZip .NET Single-File Parser Integer Underflow Leads to Unbounded Allocation (DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27710</link><description>NanaZip is an open source file archive. Starting in version 5.0.1252.0 and prior to versions 6.0.1638.0 and 6.5.1638.0, a denial-of-service vulnerability exists in NanaZip’s `.NET Single File Application` parser. A crafted bundle can force an integer underflow in header-size calculation and trigger an unbounded memory allocation attempt during archive open. Versions 6.0.1638.0 and 6.5.1638.0 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27711 | NanaZip UFS Archive Parser Memory Corruption via Unvalidated Directory Record Length</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27711</link><description>NanaZip is an open source file archive. Starting in version 5.0.1252.0 and prior to versions 6.0.1638.0 and 6.5.1638.0, a memory corruption vulnerability in NanaZip’s UFS parser allows a crafted `.ufs/.ufs2/.img` file to trigger out-of-bounds memory access during archive open/listing. The bug is reachable via normal user file-open flow and can cause process crash, hang, and potentially exploitable heap corruption. Versions 6.0.1638.0 and 6.5.1638.0 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27967 | Symlink Escape in Agent File Tools</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27967</link><description>Zed, a code editor, has a symlink escape vulnerability in versions prior to 0.225.9 in Agent file tools (`read_file`, `edit_file`). It allows reading and writing files **outside the project directory** when a project contains symbolic links pointing to external paths. This bypasses the intended workspace boundary and privacy protections (`file_scan_exclusions`, `private_files`), potentially leaking sensitive user data to the LLM. Version 0.225.9 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27976 | Zed Extension Sandbox Escape via Tar Symlink Following</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27976</link><description>Zed, a code editor, has an extension installer allows tar/gzip downloads. Prior to version 0.224.4, the tar extractor (`async_tar::Archive::unpack`) creates symlinks from the archive without validation, and the path guard (`writeable_path_from_extension`) only performs lexical prefix checks without resolving symlinks. An attacker can ship a tar that first creates a symlink inside the extension workdir pointing outside (e.g., `escape -&gt; /`), then writes files through the symlink, causing writes to arbitrary host paths. This escapes the extension sandbox and enables code execution. Version 0.224.4 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:53:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27798 | ImageMagick: Heap Buffer Over-read in WaveletDenoise when processing small images</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27798</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a heap buffer over-read vulnerability occurs when processing an image with small dimension using the `-wavelet-denoise` operator. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:53:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27799 | ImageMagick has a heap Buffer Over-read in its DJVU image format handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27799</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a heap buffer over-read vulnerability exists in the DJVU image format handler. The vulnerability occurs due to integer truncation when calculating the stride (row size) for pixel buffer allocation. The stride calculation overflows a 32-bit signed integer, resulting in an out-of-bounds memory reads. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:53:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27800 | Zed has Zip Slip Path Traversal in Extension Archive Extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27800</link><description>Zed, a code editor, has a Zip Slip (Path Traversal) vulnerability exists in its extension archive extraction functionality prior to version 0.224.4. The `extract_zip()` function in `crates/util/src/archive.rs` fails to validate ZIP entry filenames for path traversal sequences (e.g., `../`). This allows a malicious extension to write files outside its designated sandbox directory by downloading and extracting a crafted ZIP archive. Version 0.224.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:53:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27630 | TinyWeb vulnerable to Remote Denial of Service via Thread/Connection Exhaustion (Slowloris)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27630</link><description>TinyWeb is a web server (HTTP, HTTPS) written in Delphi for Win32. Versions prior to version 2.02 are vulnerable to a Denial of Service (DoS) attack known as Slowloris. The server spawns a new OS thread for every incoming connection without enforcing a maximum concurrency limit or an appropriate request timeout. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exhaust server concurrency limits and memory by opening numerous connections and sending data exceptionally slowly (e.g. 1 byte every few minutes). Anyone hosting services using TinyWeb is impacted. Version 2.02 fixes the issue. The patch introduces a `CMaxConnections` limit (set to 512) and a `CConnectionTimeoutSecs` idle timeout (set to 30 seconds). As a temporary workaround if upgrading is not immediately possible, consider placing the server behind a robust reverse proxy or Web Application Firewall (WAF) such as nginx, HAProxy, or Cloudflare, configured to buffer incomplete requests and aggressively enforce connection limits and timeouts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:27:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27633 | TinyWeb has Unbounded Content-Length Memory Exhaustion (DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27633</link><description>TinyWeb is a web server (HTTP, HTTPS) written in Delphi for Win32. Versions prior to version 2.02 have a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability via memory exhaustion. Unauthenticated remote attackers can send an HTTP POST request to the server with an exceptionally large `Content-Length` header (e.g., `2147483647`). The server continuously allocates memory for the request body (`EntityBody`) while streaming the payload without enforcing any maximum limit, leading to all available memory being consumed and causing the server to crash. Anyone hosting services using TinyWeb is impacted. Version 2.02 fixes the issue. The patch introduces a `CMaxEntityBodySize` limit (set to 10MB) for the maximum size of accepted payloads. As a temporary workaround if upgrading is not immediately possible, consider placing the server behind a Web Application Firewall (WAF) or reverse proxy (like nginx or Cloudflare) configured to explicitly limit the maximum allowed HTTP request body size (e.g., `client_max_body_size` in nginx).</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:27:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27635 | Manyfold vulnerable to OS command injection via ZIP filename in f3d render</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27635</link><description>Manyfold is an open source, self-hosted web application for managing a collection of 3d models, particularly focused on 3d printing. Prior to version 0.133.0, when model render generation is enabled, a logged-in user can achieve RCE by uploading a ZIP containing a file with a shell metacharacter in its name. The filename reaches a Ruby backtick call unsanitized. Version 0.133.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27933 | Manyfold vulnerable to session hijack via cookie leakage in proxy caches</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27933</link><description>Manyfold is an open source, self-hosted web application for managing a collection of 3d models, particularly focused on 3d printing. Versions prior to 0.133.0 are vulnerable to session hijack via cookie leakage in proxy caches. Version 0.133.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27613 | CGI Parameter Injection (Bypass of STRICT_CGI_PARAMS and EscapeShellParam)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27613</link><description>TinyWeb is a web server (HTTP, HTTPS) written in Delphi for Win32. A vulnerability in versions prior to 2.01 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to bypass the web server's CGI parameter security controls. Depending on the server configuration and the specific CGI executable in use, the impact is either source code disclosure or remote code execution (RCE). Anyone hosting CGI scripts (particularly interpreted languages like PHP) using vulnerable versions of TinyWeb is impacted. The problem has been patched in version 2.01. If upgrading is not immediately possible, ensure `STRICT_CGI_PARAMS` is enabled (it is defined by default in `define.inc`) and/or do not use CGI executables that natively accept dangerous command-line flags (such as `php-cgi.exe`). If hosting PHP, consider placing the server behind a Web Application Firewall (WAF) that explicitly blocks URL query string parameters that begin with a hyphen (`-`) or contain encoded double quotes (`%22`).</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3209 | fosrl Pangolin Role verifyApiKeyRoleAccess access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3209</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in fosrl Pangolin up to 1.15.4-s.3. This affects the function verifyRoleAccess/verifyApiKeyRoleAccess of the component Role Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.15.4-s.4 mitigates this issue. The identifier of the patch is 5e37c4e85fae68e756be5019a28ca903b161fdd5. Upgrading the affected component is advised.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27498 | n8n has Arbitrary Command Execution via File Write and Git Operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27498</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Prior to versions 2.2.0 and 1.123.8, an authenticated user with permission to create or modify workflows could chain the Read/Write Files from Disk node with git operations to achieve remote code execution. By writing to specific configuration files and then triggering a git operation, the attacker could execute arbitrary shell commands on the n8n host. The issue has been fixed in n8n versions 2.2.0 and 1.123.8. Users should upgrade to one of these versions or later to remediate the vulnerability. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators should consider the following temporary mitigations. Limit workflow creation and editing permissions to fully trusted users only, and/or disable the Read/Write Files from Disk node by adding `n8n-nodes-base.readWriteFile` to the `NODES_EXCLUDE` environment variable. These workarounds do not fully remediate the risk and should only be used as short-term mitigation measures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 22:57:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27578 | n8n Vulnerable to Stored XSS via Various Nodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27578</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Prior to versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22, an authenticated user with permission to create or modify workflows could inject arbitrary scripts into pages rendered by the n8n application using different techniques on various nodes (Form Trigger node, Chat Trigger node, Send &amp; Wait node, Webhook Node, and Chat Node). Scripts injected by a malicious workflow execute in the browser of any user who visits the affected page, enabling session hijacking and account takeover. The issues have been fixed in n8n versions 2.10.1 and 1.123.21. Users should upgrade to one of these versions or later to remediate the vulnerability. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators should consider the following temporary mitigations. Limit workflow creation and editing permissions to fully trusted users only, and/or disable the Webhook node by adding `n8n-nodes-base.webhook` to the `NODES_EXCLUDE` environment variable. These workarounds do not fully remediate the risk and should only be used as short-term mitigation measures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 22:57:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27497 | n8n has Potential Remote Code Execution via Merge Node</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27497</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Prior to versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22, an authenticated user with permission to create or modify workflows could leverage the Merge node's SQL query mode to execute arbitrary code and write arbitrary files on the n8n server. The issues have been fixed in n8n versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22. Users should upgrade to one of these versions or later to remediate all known vulnerabilities. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators should consider the following temporary mitigations. Limit workflow creation and editing permissions to fully trusted users only, and/or disable the Merge node by adding `n8n-nodes-base.merge` to the `NODES_EXCLUDE` environment variable. These workarounds do not fully remediate the risk and should only be used as short-term mitigation measures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 22:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27577 | n8n: Expression Sandbox Escape Leads to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27577</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Prior to versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22, additional exploits in the expression evaluation of n8n have been identified and patched following CVE-2025-68613. An authenticated user with permission to create or modify workflows could abuse crafted expressions in workflow parameters to trigger unintended system command execution on the host running n8n. The issues have been fixed in n8n versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22. Users should upgrade to one of these versions or later to remediate all known vulnerabilities. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators should consider the following temporary mitigations. Limit workflow creation and editing permissions to fully trusted users only, and/or deploy n8n in a hardened environment with restricted operating system privileges and network access to reduce the impact of potential exploitation. These workarounds do not fully remediate the risk and should only be used as short-term mitigation measures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 22:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27493 | n8n has Unauthenticated Expression Evaluation via Form Node</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27493</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Prior to versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22, a second-order expression injection vulnerability existed in n8n's Form nodes that could allow an unauthenticated attacker to inject and evaluate arbitrary n8n expressions by submitting crafted form data. When chained with an expression sandbox escape, this could escalate to remote code execution on the n8n host. The vulnerability requires a specific workflow configuration to be exploitable. First, a form node with a field interpolating a value provided by an unauthenticated user, e.g. a form submitted value. Second, the field value must begin with an `=` character, which caused n8n to treat it as an expression and triggered a double-evaluation of the field content. There is no practical reason for a workflow designer to prefix a field with `=` intentionally — the character is not rendered in the output, so the result would not match the designer's expectations. If added accidentally, it would be noticeable and very unlikely to persist. An unauthenticated attacker would need to either know about this specific circumstance on a target instance or discover a matching form by chance. Even when the preconditions are met, the expression injection alone is limited to data accessible within the n8n expression context. Escalation to remote code execution requires chaining with a separate sandbox escape vulnerability. The issue has been fixed in n8n versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22. Users should upgrade to one of these versions or later to remediate the vulnerability. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators should consider the following temporary mitigations. Review usage of form nodes manually for above mentioned preconditions, disable the Form node by adding `n8n-nodes-base.form` to the `NODES_EXCLUDE` environment variable, and/or disable the Form Trigger node by adding `n8n-nodes-base.formTrigger` to the `NODES_EXCLUDE` environment variable. These workarounds do not fully remediate the risk and should only be used as short-term mitigation measures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 22:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27494 | n8n has Arbitrary File Read via Python Code Node Sandbox Escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27494</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Prior to versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22, an authenticated user with permission to create or modify workflows could use the Python Code node to escape the sandbox. The sandbox did not sufficiently restrict access to certain built-in Python objects, allowing an attacker to exfiltrate file contents or achieve RCE. On instances using internal Task Runners (default runner mode), this could result in full compromise of the n8n host. On instances using external Task Runners, the attacker might gain access to or impact other task executed on the Task Runner. Task Runners must be enabled using `N8N_RUNNERS_ENABLED=true`. The issue has been fixed in n8n versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22. Users should upgrade to this version or later to remediate the vulnerability. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators should consider the following temporary mitigations. Limit workflow creation and editing permissions to fully trusted users only., and/or disable the Code node by adding `n8n-nodes-base.code` to the `NODES_EXCLUDE` environment variable. These workarounds do not fully remediate the risk and should only be used as short-term mitigation measures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 22:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27495 | n8n has a Sandbox Escape in its JavaScript Task Runner</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27495</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Prior to versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22, an authenticated user with permission to create or modify workflows could exploit a vulnerability in the JavaScript Task Runner sandbox to execute arbitrary code outside the sandbox boundary. On instances using internal Task Runners (default runner mode), this could result in full compromise of the n8n host. On instances using external Task Runners, the attacker might gain access to or impact other task executed on the Task Runner. Task Runners must be enabled using `N8N_RUNNERS_ENABLED=true`. The issue has been fixed in n8n versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22. Users should upgrade to one of these versions or later to remediate the vulnerability. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators should consider the following temporary mitigations. Limit workflow creation and editing permissions to fully trusted users only, and/or use external runner mode (`N8N_RUNNERS_MODE=external`) to limit the blast radius. These workarounds do not fully remediate the risk and should only be used as short-term mitigation measures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 22:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27148 | Storybook Dev Server Vulnerable to WebSocket Hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27148</link><description>Storybook is a frontend workshop for building user interface components and pages in isolation. Prior to versions 7.6.23, 8.6.17, 9.1.19, and 10.2.10, the WebSocket functionality in Storybook's dev server, used to create and update stories, is vulnerable to WebSocket hijacking. This vulnerability only affects the Storybook dev server; production builds are not impacted. Exploitation requires a developer to visit a malicious website while their local Storybook dev server is running. Because the WebSocket connection does not validate the origin of incoming connections, a malicious site can silently send WebSocket messages to the local instance without any further user interaction. If the Storybook dev server is intentionally exposed publicly (e.g. for design reviews or stakeholder demos) the risk is higher, as no malicious site visit is required. Any unauthenticated attacker can send WebSocket messages to it directly. The vulnerability affects the WebSocket message handlers for creating and saving stories. Both are vulnerable to injection via unsanitized input in the componentFilePath field, which can be exploited to achieve persistent XSS or Remote Code Execution (RCE). Versions 7.6.23, 8.6.17, 9.1.19, and 10.2.10 contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27575 | Vijkunja has Weak Password Policy Combined with Persistent Sessions After Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27575</link><description>Vikunja is an open-source self-hosted task management platform. Prior to version 2.0.0, the application allows users to set weak passwords (e.g., 1234, password) without enforcing minimum strength requirements. Additionally, active sessions remain valid after a user changes their password. An attacker who compromises an account (via brute-force or credential stuffing) can maintain persistent access even after the victim resets their password. Version 2.0.0 contains a fix.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27616 | Vikunja Vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via Unsanitized SVG Attachment Upload Leading to Token Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27616</link><description>Vikunja is an open-source self-hosted task management platform. Prior to version 2.0.0, the application allows users to upload SVG files as task attachments. SVG is an XML-based format that supports JavaScript execution through elements such as</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27819 | Vikunja has Path Traversal in CLI Restore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27819</link><description>Vikunja is an open-source self-hosted task management platform. Prior to version 2.0.0, the restoreConfig function in vikunja/pkg/modules/dump/restore.go of the go-vikunja/vikunja repository fails to sanitize file paths within the provided ZIP archive. A maliciously crafted ZIP can bypass the intended extraction directory to overwrite arbitrary files on the host system. Additionally, we’ve discovered that a malformed archive triggers a runtime panic, crashing the process immediately after the database has been wiped permanently. The application trusts the metadata in the ZIP archive. It uses the Name attribute of the zip.File struct directly in os.OpenFile calls without validation, allowing files to be written outside the intended directory. The restoration logic assumes a specific directory structure within the ZIP. When provided with a "minimalist" malicious ZIP, the application fails to validate the length of slices derived from the archive contents. Specifically, at line 154, the code attempts to access an index of len(ms)-2 on an insufficiently populated slice, triggering a panic. Version 2.0.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26985 | LORIS vulnerable to path traversal in electrophysiology_browser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26985</link><description>LORIS (Longitudinal Online Research and Imaging System) is a self-hosted web application that provides data- and project-management for neuroimaging research. Starting in version 24.0.0 and prior to versions 26.0.5, 27.0.2, and 28.0.0, an authenticated user with the appropriate authorization can read configuration files on the server by exploiting a path traversal vulnerability. Some of these files contain hard-coded credentials. The vulnerability allows an attacker to read configuration files containing hard-coded credentials. The attacker could then authenticate to the database or other services if those credentials are reused. The attacker must be authenticated and have the required permissions. However, the vulnerability is easy to exploit and the application source code is public. This problem is fixed in LORIS v26.0.5 and v27.0.2 and above, and v28.0.0 and above. As a workaround, the electrophysiogy_browser in LORIS can be disabled by an administrator using the module manager.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27116 | Vikunja has Reflected HTML Injection via filter Parameter in Projects Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27116</link><description>Vikunja is an open-source self-hosted task management platform. Prior to version 2.0.0, a reflected HTML injection vulnerability exists in the Projects module where the `filter` URL parameter is rendered into the DOM without output encoding when the user clicks "Filter." While `&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2694 | The Events Calendar &amp;lt;= 6.15.16 - Improper Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Event/Organizer/Venue Update/Trash via REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2694</link><description>The The Events Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to an improper capability check on the 'can_edit' and 'can_delete' function in all versions up to, and including, 6.15.16. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to update or trash events, organizers and venues via REST API.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26984 | LORIS media module vulnerable to remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26984</link><description>LORIS (Longitudinal Online Research and Imaging System) is a self-hosted web application that provides data- and project-management for neuroimaging research. Prior to versions 26.0.5, 27.0.2, and 28.0.0, an authenticated user with sufficient privileges can exploit a path traversal vulnerability to upload a malicious file to an arbitrary location on the server. Once uploaded, the file can be used to achieve remote code execution (RCE). An attacker must be authenticated and have the appropriate permissions to exploit this issue. If the server is configured as read-only, remote code execution (RCE) is not possible; however, the malicious file upload may still be achievable. This problem is fixed in LORIS v26.0.5 and above, v27.0.2 and above, and v28.0.0 and above. As a workaround, LORIS administrators can disable the media module if it is not being used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26986 | FreeRDP has heap-use-after-free in rail_window_free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26986</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, `rail_window_free` dereferences a freed `xfAppWindow` pointer during `HashTable_Free` cleanup because `xf_rail_window_common` calls `free(appWindow)` on title allocation failure without first removing the entry from the `railWindows` hash table, leaving a dangling pointer that is freed again on disconnect. Version 3.23.0 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27950 | FreeRDP heap-use-after-free in update_pointer_new(SDL): Fix Applied in the Wrong File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27950</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, the fix for the heap-use-after-free described in CVE-2026-24680 is incomplete. While the vulnerable execution flow referenced in the advisory exists in the SDL2 implementation, the fix appears to have been applied only to the SDL3 code path. In the SDL2 implementation, the pointer is not nulled after free. This creates a situation where the advisory suggests the vulnerability is fully resolved, while builds or environments still using SDL2 may retain the vulnerable logic. A complete fix is available in version 3.23.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:23:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27951 | FreeRDP has possible Integer overflow in Stream_EnsureCapacity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27951</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, the function `Stream_EnsureCapacity` can create an endless blocking loop. This may affect all client and server implementations using `FreeRDP`. For practical exploitation this will only work on 32bit systems where the available physical memory is `&gt;= SIZE_MAX`. Version 3.23.0 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:23:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26955 | FreeRDP has Out-of-bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26955</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, a malicious RDP server can trigger a heap buffer overflow in FreeRDP clients using the GDI surface pipeline (e.g., `xfreerdp`) by sending an RDPGFX ClearCodec surface command with an out-of-bounds destination rectangle. The `gdi_SurfaceCommand_ClearCodec()` handler does not call `is_within_surface()` to validate the command rectangle against the destination surface dimensions, allowing attacker-controlled `cmd-&gt;left`/`cmd-&gt;top` (and subcodec rectangle offsets) to reach image copy routines that write into `surface-&gt;data` without bounds enforcement. The OOB write corrupts an adjacent `gdiGfxSurface` struct's `codecs*` pointer with attacker-controlled pixel data, and corruption of `codecs*` is sufficient to reach an indirect function pointer call (`NSC_CONTEXT.decode` at `nsc.c:500`) on a subsequent codec command — full instruction pointer (RIP) control demonstrated in exploitability harness. Users should upgrade to version 3.23.0 to receive a patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26965 | FreeRDP has Out-of-bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26965</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, in the RLE planar decode path, `planar_decompress_plane_rle()` writes into `pDstData` at `((nYDst+y) * nDstStep) + (4*nXDst) + nChannel` without verifying that `(nYDst+nSrcHeight)` fits in the destination height or that `(nXDst+nSrcWidth)` fits in the destination stride. When `TempFormat != DstFormat`, `pDstData` becomes `planar-&gt;pTempData` (sized for the desktop), while `nYDst` is only validated against the **surface** by `is_within_surface()`. A malicious RDP server can exploit this to perform a heap out-of-bounds write with attacker-controlled offset and pixel data on any connecting FreeRDP client. The OOB write reaches up to 132,096 bytes past the temp buffer end, and  on the brk heap (desktop ≤ 128×128), an adjacent `NSC_CONTEXT` struct's `decode` function pointer is overwritten with attacker-controlled pixel data — control-flow–relevant corruption (function pointer overwritten) demonstrated under deterministic heap layout (`nsc-&gt;decode = 0xFF414141FF414141`). Version 3.23.0 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3172 | pgvector buffer overflow in parallel HNSW index build</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3172</link><description>Buffer overflow in parallel HNSW index build in pgvector 0.6.0 through 0.8.1 allows a database user to leak sensitive data from other relations or crash the database server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0542 | Remote Code Execution in ServiceNow AI Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0542</link><description>ServiceNow has addressed a remote code execution vulnerability that was identified in the ServiceNow AI platform.  This vulnerability could enable an unauthenticated user, in certain circumstances, to execute code within the ServiceNow Sandbox.   





ServiceNow addressed this vulnerability by deploying a security update to hosted instances. Relevant security updates also have been provided to ServiceNow self-hosted customers and partners. Further, the vulnerability is addressed in the listed patches and hot fixes. While we are not currently aware of exploitation against customer instances, we recommend customers promptly apply appropriate updates or upgrade if they have not already done so.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:49:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25954 | FreeRDP has heap-use-after-free in xf_rail_server_local_move_size</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25954</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, `xf_rail_server_local_move_size` dereferences a freed `xfAppWindow` pointer because `xf_rail_get_window` returns an unprotected pointer from the `railWindows` hash table, and the main thread can concurrently delete the window (via a window delete order) while the RAIL channel thread is still using the pointer. Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:49:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25955 | FreeRDP has heap-use-after-free in xf_AppUpdateWindowFromSurface (stale XImage)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25955</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, `xf_AppUpdateWindowFromSurface` reuses a cached `XImage` whose `data` pointer references a freed RDPGFX surface buffer, because `gdi_DeleteSurface` frees `surface-&gt;data` without invalidating the `appWindow-&gt;image` that aliases it. Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25959 | FreeRDP has heap-use-after-free in xf_cliprdr_provide_data_</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25959</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, `xf_cliprdr_provide_data_` passes freed `pDstData` to `XChangeProperty` because the cliprdr channel thread calls `xf_cliprdr_server_format_data_response` which converts and uses the clipboard data without holding any lock, while the X11 event thread concurrently calls `xf_cliprdr_clear_cached_data` → `HashTable_Clear` which frees the same data via `xf_cached_data_free`, triggering a heap use after free. Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25997 | FreeRDP has heap-use-after-free in xf_clipboard_format_equal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25997</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, `xf_clipboard_format_equal` reads freed `lastSentFormats` memory because `xf_clipboard_formats_free` (called from the cliprdr channel thread during auto-reconnect) frees the array while the X11 event thread concurrently iterates it in `xf_clipboard_changed`, triggering a heap use after free. Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26271 | Buffer Overread in FreeRDP Icon Processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26271</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, a buffer overread in `freerdp_image_copy_from_icon_data()` (libfreerdp/codec/color.c) can be triggered by crafted RDP Window Icon (TS_ICON_INFO) data. The bug is reachable over the network when a client processes icon data from an RDP server (or from a man-in-the-middle). Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27015 | FreeRDP: Smartcard NDR Alignment Padding Triggers Reachable WINPR_ASSERT Abort (Client DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27015</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, a missing bounds check in `smartcard_unpack_read_size_align()` (`libfreerdp/utils/smartcard_pack.c:1703`) allows a malicious RDP server to crash the FreeRDP client via a reachable `WINPR_ASSERT` → `abort()`. The crash occurs in upstream builds where `WITH_VERBOSE_WINPR_ASSERT=ON` (default in FreeRDP 3.22.0 / current WinPR CMake defaults). Smartcard redirection must be explicitly enabled by the user (e.g., `xfreerdp /smartcard`; `/smartcard-logon` implies `/smartcard`). Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25952 | FreeRDP has heap-use-after-free in xf_SetWindowMinMaxInfo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25952</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, `xf_SetWindowMinMaxInfo` dereferences a freed `xfAppWindow` pointer because `xf_rail_get_window` in `xf_rail_server_min_max_info` returns an unprotected pointer from the `railWindows` hash table, and the main thread can concurrently delete the window (via a window delete order) while the RAIL channel thread is still using the pointer. Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25953 | FreeRDP has heap-use-after-free in xf_AppUpdateWindowFromSurface (freed appWindow)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25953</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, `xf_AppUpdateWindowFromSurface` reads from a freed `xfAppWindow` because the RDPGFX DVC thread obtains a bare pointer via `xf_rail_get_window` without any lifetime protection, while the main thread can concurrently delete the window through a fastpath window-delete order. Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14511 | Improper Validation of Specified Quantity in Input in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14511</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 12.2 before 18.7.5, 18.8 before 18.8.5, and 18.9 before 18.9.1 that could have allowed an unauthenticated user to cause denial of service by sending specially crafted files to the container registry event endpoint under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0752 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0752</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.2 before 18.7.5, 18.8 before 18.8.5, and 18.9 before 18.9.1 that under certain circumstances, could have allowed an unauthenticated user to inject arbitrary scripts into the Mermaid sandbox UI.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1388 | Inefficient Regular Expression Complexity in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1388</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 9.2 before 18.7.5, 18.8 before 18.8.5, and 18.9 before 18.9.1 that could have allowed an unauthenticated user to cause regular expression denial of service by sending specially crafted input to a merge request endpoint under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1662 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1662</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 14.4 before 18.7.5, 18.8 before 18.8.5, and 18.9 before 18.9.1 that could have allowed an unauthenticated user to cause Denial of Service by sending specially crafted requests to the Jira events endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1725 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1725</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting versions from 18.9 before 18.9.1 that could have under certain conditions, allowed an unauthenticated user to cause denial of service by sending specially crafted requests to a CI jobs API endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1747 | Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1747</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 17.11 before 18.7.5, 18.8 before 18.8.5, and 18.9 before 18.9.1 that, under certain conditions, could have allowed Developer-role users with insufficient privileges to make unauthorized modifications to protected Conan packages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22721 | VMware Aria Operations privilege escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22721</link><description>VMware Aria Operations contains a privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with privileges in vCenter to access Aria Operations may leverage this vulnerability to obtain administrative access in VMware Aria Operations. To remediate CVE-2026-22721, apply the patches listed in the 'Fixed Version' column of the 'Response Matrix' found in  VMSA-2026-0001 https://support.broadcom.com/web/ecx/support-content-notification/-/external/content/SecurityAdvisories/0/36947 .</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25942 | FreeRDP has global-buffer-overflow in xf_rail_server_execute_result</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25942</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, `xf_rail_server_execute_result` indexes the global `error_code_names[]` array (7 elements, indices 0–6) with an unchecked `execResult-&gt;execResult` value received from the server, allowing an out-of-bounds read when the server sends an `execResult` value of 7 or greater. Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2845 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2845</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 11.2 before 18.7.5, 18.8 before 18.8.5, and 18.9 before 18.9.1 that could have allowed an authenticated user to cause denial of service by exploiting a Bitbucket Server import endpoint via repeatedly sending large responses.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3200 | z-9527 admin user.js getUsers sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3200</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in z-9527 admin 1.0/2.0. The affected element is the function checkName/register/login/getUser/getUsers of the file /server/controller/user.js. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27691 | iccDEV has SIO in parse3DTable() at iccFromCube.cpp Line 218</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27691</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools for working with ICC color management profiles. In versions up to and including 2.3.1.4, signed integer overflow in iccFromCube.cpp during multiplication triggers undefined behavior, potentially causing crashes or incorrect ICC profile generation when processing crafted/large cube inputs. Commit 43ae18dd69fc70190d3632a18a3af2f3da1e052a fixes the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3187 | feiyuchuixue sz-boot-parent API Endpoint upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3187</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in feiyuchuixue sz-boot-parent up to 1.3.2-beta. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/admin/sys-file/upload of the component API Endpoint. Such manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. Upgrading to version 1.3.3-beta can resolve this issue. The name of the patch is aefaabfd7527188bfba3c8c9eee17c316d094802. Upgrading the affected component is recommended. The project was informed beforehand and acted very professional: "We have introduced a whitelist restriction on the /api/admin/sys-file/upload endpoint via the oss.allowedExts and oss.allowedMimeTypes configuration options, allowing the specification of permitted file extensions and MIME types for uploads."</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3201 | Improperly Controlled Sequential Memory Allocation in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3201</link><description>USB HID protocol dissector memory exhaustion in Wireshark 4.6.0 to 4.6.3 and 4.4.0 to 4.4.13 allows denial of service</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3202 | NULL Pointer Dereference in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3202</link><description>NTS-KE protocol dissector crash in Wireshark 4.6.0 to 4.6.3 allows denial of service</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3203 | Buffer Over-read in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3203</link><description>RF4CE Profile protocol dissector crash in Wireshark 4.6.0 to 4.6.3 and 4.4.0 to 4.4.13 allows denial of service</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3185 | feiyuchuixue sz-boot-parent API Endpoint sys-message authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3185</link><description>A vulnerability was found in feiyuchuixue sz-boot-parent up to 1.3.2-beta. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/admin/sys-message/ of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument messageId results in authorization bypass. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. Upgrading to version 1.3.3-beta is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as aefaabfd7527188bfba3c8c9eee17c316d094802. The affected component should be upgraded. The project was informed beforehand and acted very professional: "We have implemented message ownership verification, so that users can only query messages related to themselves."</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3186 | feiyuchuixue sz-boot-parent Password Reset password default password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3186</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in feiyuchuixue sz-boot-parent up to 1.3.2-beta. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /api/admin/sys-user/reset/password/ of the component Password Reset Handler. This manipulation of the argument userId causes use of default password. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Upgrading to version 1.3.3-beta addresses this issue. Patch name: aefaabfd7527188bfba3c8c9eee17c316d094802. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component. The project was informed beforehand and acted very professional: "We have added authorization validation to the password reset interface; now only users with the corresponding permissions are allowed to perform password resets."</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28193 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.121962 apps were able to send requests to the app permissions endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28193</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.121962 apps were able to send requests to the app permissions endpoint</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28194 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.11.3 open redirect was possible in the React project creation flow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28194</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.11.3 open redirect was possible in the React project creation flow</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28195 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.11.3 missing authorization allowed project developers to add parameters to build configurations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28195</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.11.3 missing authorization allowed project developers to add parameters to build configurations</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28196 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.11.3 disabling versioned settings left a credentials config on disk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28196</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.11.3 disabling versioned settings left a credentials config on disk</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21725 | Authorization Bypass via TOCTOU in Grafana Datasource Deletion by Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21725</link><description>A time-of-create-to-time-of-use (TOCTOU) vulnerability lets recently deleted-then-recreated data sources be re-deleted without permission to do so.

This requires several very stringent conditions to be met:

- The attacker must have admin access to the specific datasource prior to its first deletion.
- Upon deletion, all steps within the attack must happen within the next 30 seconds and on the same pod of Grafana.
- The attacker must delete the datasource, then someone must recreate it.
- The new datasource must not have the attacker as an admin.
- The new datasource must have the same UID as the prior datasource. These are randomised by default.
- The datasource can now be re-deleted by the attacker.
- Once 30 seconds are up, the attack is spent and cannot be repeated.
- No datasource with any other UID can be attacked.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:04:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2624 | Authentication Bypass in ePati&amp;#x27;s Antikor NGFW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2624</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in ePati Cyber ​​Security Technologies Inc. Antikor Next Generation Firewall (NGFW) allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Antikor Next Generation Firewall (NGFW): from v.2.0.1298 before v.2.0.1301.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0704 | In affected version of Octopus Deploy it was possible to remove files and/or contents of files on the host using an API endpoint. The field ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0704</link><description>In affected version of Octopus Deploy it was possible to remove files and/or contents of files on the host using an API endpoint. The field lacked validation which could potentially result in ways to circumvent expected workflows.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3118 | Rhdh: graphql injection leading to platform-wide denial of service (dos) in rh developer hub orchestrator plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3118</link><description>A security flaw was identified in the Orchestrator Plugin of Red Hat Developer Hub (Backstage). The issue occurs due to insufficient input validation in GraphQL query handling. An authenticated user can inject specially crafted input into API requests, which disrupts backend query processing. This results in the entire Backstage application crashing and restarting, leading to a platform-wide Denial of Service (DoS). As a result, legitimate users temporarily lose access to the platform.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25701 | An Insecure Temporary File vulnerability in openSUSE sdbootutil allows local users to pre-create a directory to achieve various effects like...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25701</link><description>An Insecure Temporary File vulnerability in openSUSE sdbootutil allows local users to pre-create a directory to achieve various effects like:
  *  gain access to possible private information found in /var/lib/pcrlock.d
  *  manipulate the data backed up in /tmp/pcrlock.d.bak, therefore violating the integrity of the data should it be restored.
  *   overwrite protected system files with data from /var/lib/pcrlock.d by placing symlinks to existing files in the directory tree in /tmp/pcrlock.d.bak.


This issue affects sdbootutil: from ? before 5880246d3a02642dc68f5c8cb474bf63cdb56bca.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62878 | Local Path Provisioner vulnerable to Path Traversal via parameters.pathPattern</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62878</link><description>A malicious user can manipulate the parameters.pathPattern to create PersistentVolumes in arbitrary locations on the host node, potentially overwriting sensitive files or gaining access to unintended directories.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67601 | Rancher CLI skips TLS verification on Rancher CLI login command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67601</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified within Rancher Manager, where using self-signed CA certificates and passing the -skip-verify flag to the Rancher CLI login command without also passing the –cacert flag results in the CLI attempting to fetch CA certificates stored in Rancher’s setting cacerts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26104 | Udisks: missing authorization check allows unprivileged users to back up luks headers via udisks d-bus api</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26104</link><description>A flaw was found in the udisks storage management daemon that allows unprivileged users to back up LUKS encryption headers without authorization. The issue occurs because a privileged D-Bus method responsible for exporting encryption metadata does not perform a policy check. As a result, sensitive cryptographic metadata can be read and written to attacker-controlled locations. This weakens the confidentiality guarantees of encrypted storage volumes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67860 | NeuVector scanner insecurely handles passwords as command arguments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67860</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the NeuVector scanner where the scanner process accepts registry and controller credentials as command-line arguments, potentially exposing sensitive credentials to local users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26103 | Udisks: missing authorization check allows unprivileged users to restore luks headers via udisks d-bus api</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26103</link><description>A flaw was found in the udisks storage management daemon that exposes a privileged D-Bus API for restoring LUKS encryption headers without proper authorization checks. The issue allows a local unprivileged user to instruct the root-owned udisks daemon to overwrite encryption metadata on block devices. This can permanently invalidate encryption keys and render encrypted volumes inaccessible. Successful exploitation results in a denial-of-service condition through irreversible data loss.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14742 | WP Recipe Maker &amp;lt;= 10.2.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14742</link><description>The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ajax_search_recipes' and 'ajax_get_recipe' functions in all versions up to, and including, 10.2.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve sensitive recipe information including draft, pending, and private recipes that they shouldn't be able to access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2301 | Post Duplicator &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Protected Post Meta Insertion via &amp;#x27;customMetaData&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2301</link><description>The Post Duplicator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary protected post meta insertion in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.8. This is due to the `duplicate_post()` function in `includes/api.php` using `$wpdb-&gt;insert()` directly to the `wp_postmeta` table instead of WordPress's standard `add_post_meta()` function, which would call `is_protected_meta()` to prevent lower-privileged users from setting protected meta keys (those starting with `_`). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary protected post meta keys such as `_wp_page_template`, `_wp_attached_file`, and other sensitive meta keys on duplicated posts via the `customMetaData` JSON array parameter in the `/wp-json/post-duplicator/v1/duplicate-post` REST API endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2367 | Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking &amp;lt;= 5.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2367</link><description>The Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ays_block' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2410 | Disable Admin Notices – Hide Dashboard Notifications &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2410</link><description>The Disable Admin Notices – Hide Dashboard Notifications plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2. This is due to missing nonce validation in the `showPageContent()` function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add arbitrary URLs to the blocked redirects list via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3171 | SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System queue.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3171</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /queue.php. This manipulation of the argument firstname/lastname causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1916 | WPGSI: Spreadsheet Integration &amp;lt;= 3.8.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post Creation and Deletion via Forged Base64 Token</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1916</link><description>The WPGSI: Spreadsheet Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and loss of data due to missing capability checks and an insecure authentication mechanism on the `wpgsi_callBackFuncAccept` and `wpgsi_callBackFuncUpdate` REST API functions in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3. Both REST endpoints use `permission_callback =&gt; '__return_true'`, allowing unauthenticated access. The plugin's custom token-based validation relies on a Base64-encoded JSON object containing the user ID and email address, but is not cryptographically signed. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to forge tokens using publicly enumerable information (admin user ID and email) to create, modify, and delete arbitrary WordPress posts and pages, granted they know the administrator's email address and an active integration ID with remote updates enabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1929 | Advanced Woo Labels &amp;lt;= 2.37 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Remote Code Execution via &amp;#x27;callback&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1929</link><description>The Advanced Woo Labels plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.37. This is due to the use of `call_user_func_array()` with user-controlled callback and parameters in the `get_select_option_values()` AJAX handler without an allowlist of permitted callbacks or a capability check. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to execute arbitrary PHP functions and operating system commands on the server via the 'callback' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2416 | Geo Mashup &amp;lt;= 1.13.17 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;sort&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2416</link><description>The Geo Mashup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'sort' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.17. This is due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2479 | Responsive Lightbox &amp;amp; Gallery &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Server-Side Request Forgery via Remote Library Image Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2479</link><description>The Responsive Lightbox &amp; Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.1. This is due to the use of `strpos()` for substring-based hostname validation instead of strict host comparison in the `ajax_upload_image()` function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application, which can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3170 | SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System patient-search.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3170</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /patient-search.php. The manipulation of the argument First Name/Last Name results in cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3169 | Tenda F453 httpd SafeEmailFilter fromSafeEmailFilter buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3169</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda F453 1.0.0.3. This impacts the function fromSafeEmailFilter of the file /goform/SafeEmailFilter of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument page leads to buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11563 | wcurl path traversal with percent-encoded slashes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11563</link><description>URLs containing percent-encoded slashes (`/` or `\`) can trick wcurl into
saving the output file outside of the current directory without the user
explicitly asking for it.

This flaw only affects the wcurl command line tool.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1614 | Rise Blocks – A Complete Gutenberg Page Builder &amp;lt;= 3.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Site Identity Block Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1614</link><description>The Rise Blocks – A Complete Gutenberg Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘logoTag’ Site Identity block attribute in all versions up to, and including, 3.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3167 | Tenda F453 httpd webtypelibrary formWebTypeLibrary buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3167</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda F453 1.0.0.3. The impacted element is the function formWebTypeLibrary of the file /goform/webtypelibrary of the component httpd. Performing a manipulation of the argument webSiteId results in buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3168 | Tenda F453 httpd NatStaticSetting fromNatStaticSetting buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3168</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda F453 1.0.0.3. This affects the function fromNatStaticSetting of the file /goform/NatStaticSetting of the component httpd. Executing a manipulation of the argument page can lead to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3166 | Tenda F453 httpd RouteStatic fromRouteStatic buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3166</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda F453 1.0.0.3. The affected element is the function fromRouteStatic of the file /goform/RouteStatic of the component httpd. Such manipulation of the argument page leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25785 | Path traversal vulnerability exists in Lanscope Endpoint Manager (On-Premises) Sub-Manager Server Ver.9.4.7.3 and earlier, which may allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25785</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability exists in Lanscope Endpoint Manager (On-Premises) Sub-Manager Server Ver.9.4.7.3 and earlier, which may allow an attacker to tamper with arbitrary files and execute arbitrary code on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3100 | An improper certificate validation vulnerability was found in the FTP Backup on the ADM.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3100</link><description>The FTP Backup on the ADM will not properly strictly enforce TLS certificate verification while connecting to an FTP server using FTPES/FTPS. An improper validated TLS/SSL certificates allows a remote attacker can intercept network traffic to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MitM) attack, which may intercept, modify, or obtain sensitive information such as authentication credentials and backup data.
Affected products and versions include: from ADM 4.1.0 through ADM 4.3.3.ROF1 as well as from ADM 5.0.0 through ADM 5.1.2.RE51.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3164 | itsourcecode News Portal Project contactus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3164</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode News Portal Project 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/contactus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3165 | Tenda F453 httpd AdvSetWrlsafeset fromSetWifiGusetBasic buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3165</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda F453 1.0.0.3. Impacted is the function fromSetWifiGusetBasic of the file /goform/AdvSetWrlsafeset of the component httpd. This manipulation of the argument mit_ssid causes buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3179 | A path traversal vulnerability was found in the FTP Backup on the ADM.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3179</link><description>The FTP Backup on the ADM does not properly sanitize filenames received from the FTP server when parsing directory listings. A malicious server or MITM attacker can craft filenames containing path traversal sequences, causing the client to write files outside the intended backup directory. A path traversal vulnerability may allow an attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on the system and potentially achieve privilege escalation or remote code execution.
Affected products and versions include: from ADM 4.1.0 through ADM 4.3.3.ROF1 as well as from ADM 5.0.0 through ADM 5.1.2.RE51.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3153 | itsourcecode Document Management System register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3153</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Document Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /register.php. Such manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3163 | SourceCodester Website Link Extractor URL file_get_contents server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3163</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Website Link Extractor 1.0. This vulnerability affects the function file_get_contents of the component URL Handler. The manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3151 | itsourcecode College Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3151</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode College Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /login/login.php. The manipulation of the argument email results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3152 | itsourcecode College Management System teacher-salary.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3152</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode College Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/teacher-salary.php. This manipulation of the argument teacher_id causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0976 | Information Exposure Vulnerability in Hitachi Configuration Manager, Hitachi Ops Center API Configuration Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0976</link><description>Information Exposure Vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center API Configuration Manager, Hitachi Configuration Manager.This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center API Configuration Manager: from 10.0.0-00 before 11.0.4-00; Hitachi Configuration Manager: from 8.6.1-00 before 11.0.5-00.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27624 | Coturn: IPv4-mapped IPv6 (::ffff:0:0/96) bypasses denied-peer-ip ACL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27624</link><description>Coturn is a free open source implementation of TURN and STUN Server. Coturn is commonly configured to block loopback and internal ranges using "denied-peer-ip" and/or default loopback restrictions. CVE-2020-26262 addressed bypasses involving "0.0.0.0", "[::1]" and "[::]", but IPv4-mapped IPv6 is not covered. When sending a "CreatePermission" or "ChannelBind" request with the "XOR-PEER-ADDRESS" value of "::ffff:127.0.0.1", a successful response is received, even though "127.0.0.0/8" is blocked via "denied-peer-ip". The root cause is that, prior to the updated fix implemented in version 4.9.0, three functions in "src/client/ns_turn_ioaddr.c" do not check "IN6_IS_ADDR_V4MAPPED". "ioa_addr_is_loopback()" checks "127.x.x.x" (AF_INET) and "::1" (AF_INET6), but not "::ffff:127.0.0.1." "ioa_addr_is_zero()" checks "0.0.0.0" and "::", but not "::ffff:0.0.0.0." "addr_less_eq()" used by "ioa_addr_in_range()" for "denied-peer-ip" matching: when the range is AF_INET and the peer is AF_INET6, the comparison returns 0 without extracting the embedded IPv4. Version 4.9.0 contains an updated fix to address the bypass of the fix for CVE-2020-26262.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27645 | changedetection.io Vulnerable to Reflected XSS in RSS Single Watch Error Response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27645</link><description>changedetection.io is a free open source web page change detection tool. In versions prior to 0.54.1, the RSS single-watch endpoint reflects the UUID path parameter directly in the HTTP response body without HTML escaping. Since Flask returns text/html by default for plain string responses, the browser parses and executes injected JavaScript. Version 0.54.1 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27696 | changedetection.io Vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via Watch URLs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27696</link><description>changedetection.io is a free open source web page change detection tool. In versions prior to 0.54.1, changedetection.io is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) because the URL validation function `is_safe_valid_url()` does not validate the resolved IP address of watch URLs against private, loopback, or link-local address ranges. An authenticated user (or any user when no password is configured, which is the default) can add a watch for internal network URLs. The application fetches these URLs server-side, stores the response content, and makes it viewable through the web UI — enabling full data exfiltration from internal services. Version 0.54.1 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3148 | SourceCodester Simple and Nice Shopping Cart Script signup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3148</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Simple and Nice Shopping Cart Script 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /signup.php. This manipulation of the argument Username causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3149 | itsourcecode College Management System asign-single-student-subjects.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3149</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode College Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/asign-single-student-subjects.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument course_code can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3150 | itsourcecode College Management System display-teacher.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3150</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode College Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/display-teacher.php. The manipulation of the argument teacher_id leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27597 | @enclave-vm/core is vulnerable to Sandbox Escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27597</link><description>Enclave is a secure JavaScript sandbox designed for safe AI agent code execution. Prior to version 2.11.1, it is possible to escape the security boundraries set by `@enclave-vm/core`, which can be used to achieve remote code execution (RCE). The issue has been fixed in version 2.11.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27627 | Karakeep&amp;#x27;s Reddit plugin content bypasses DOMPurify sanitization, enabling stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27627</link><description>Karakeep is a elf-hostable bookmark-everything app. In version 0.30.0, when the Reddit metascraper plugin returns `readableContentHtml`, the HTML parsing subprocess uses it directly without running it through DOMPurify. Every other content source in the crawler goes through Readability + DOMPurify, but the Reddit path skips both. Since this content ends up in `dangerouslySetInnerHTML` in the reader view, any malicious HTML in the Reddit response gets executed in the user's browser. Version 0.31.0 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27636 | FreeScout: Missing .htaccess in Restricted File Extensions Allows Remote Code Execution on Apache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27636</link><description>FreeScout is a free help desk and shared inbox built with PHP's Laravel framework. Prior to version 1.8.206, FreeScout's file upload restriction list in `app/Misc/Helper.php` does not include `.htaccess` or `.user.ini` files. On Apache servers with `AllowOverride All` (a common configuration), an authenticated user can upload a `.htaccess` file to redefine how files are processed, enabling Remote Code Execution. This vulnerability can be exploited on its own or in combination with CVE-2026-27637. Version 1.8.206 fixes both vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27637 | FreeScout&amp;#x27;s Predictable Authentication Token Enables Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27637</link><description>FreeScout is a free help desk and shared inbox built with PHP's Laravel framework. Prior to version 1.8.206, FreeScout's `TokenAuth` middleware uses a predictable authentication token computed as `MD5(user_id + created_at + APP_KEY)`. This token is static (never expires/rotates), and if an attacker obtains the `APP_KEY` — a well-documented and common exposure vector in Laravel applications — they can compute a valid token for any user, including the administrator, achieving full account takeover without any password. This vulnerability can be exploited on its own or in combination with CVE-2026-27636. Version 1.8.206 fixes both vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27639 | Mercator vulnerable to stored XSS via unescaped Blade directives in display templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27639</link><description>Mercator is an open source web application designed to enable mapping of information systems. A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Mercator prior to version 2026.02.22 due to the use of unescaped Blade directives (`{!! !!}`) in display templates. An authenticated user with the User role can inject arbitrary JavaScript payloads into fields such as "contact point" when creating or editing entities. The payload is then executed in the browser of any user who views the affected page, including administrators. Version 2026.02.22 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27640 | tfplan2md has Sensitive Value Exposure in Generated Reports</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27640</link><description>tfplan2md is software for converting Terraform plan JSON files into human-readable Markdown reports. Prior to version 1.26.1, a bug in tfplan2md affected several distinct rendering paths: AzApi resource body properties, AzureDevOps variable groups, Scriban template context variables, and hierarchical sensitivity detection. This caused reports to render values that should have been masked as "(sensitive)" instead. This issue is fixed in v1.26.1. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27641 | Flask-Reuploaded vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via Server-Side Template Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27641</link><description>Flask-Reuploaded provides file uploads for Flask. A critical path traversal and extension bypass vulnerability in versions prior to 1.5.0 allows remote attackers to achieve arbitrary file write and remote code execution through Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI). Flask-Reuploaded has been patched in version 1.5.0. Some workarounds are available. Do not pass user input to the `name` parameter, use auto-generated filenames only, and implement strict input validation if `name` must be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27743 | SPIP referer_spam &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27743</link><description>The SPIP referer_spam plugin versions prior to 1.3.0 contain an unauthenticated SQL injection vulnerability in the referer_spam_ajouter and referer_spam_supprimer action handlers. The handlers read the url parameter from a GET request and interpolate it directly into SQL LIKE clauses without input validation or parameterization. The endpoints do not enforce authorization checks and do not use SPIP action protections such as securiser_action(), allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL queries.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27744 | SPIP tickets &amp;lt; 4.3.3 Unauthenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27744</link><description>The SPIP tickets plugin versions prior to 4.3.3 contain an unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability in the forum preview handling for public ticket pages. The plugin appends untrusted request parameters into HTML that is later rendered by a template using unfiltered environment rendering (#ENV**), which disables SPIP output filtering. As a result, an unauthenticated attacker can inject crafted content that is evaluated through SPIP's template processing chain, leading to execution of code in the context of the web server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27745 | SPIP interface_traduction_objets &amp;lt; 2.2.2 Authenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27745</link><description>The SPIP interface_traduction_objets plugin versions prior to 4.3.3 contain an authenticated remote code execution vulnerability in the translation interface workflow. The plugin incorporates untrusted request data into a hidden form field that is rendered without SPIP output filtering. Because fields prefixed with an underscore bypass protection mechanisms and the hidden content is rendered with filtering disabled, an authenticated attacker with editor-level privileges can inject crafted content that is evaluated through SPIP's template processing chain, resulting in execution of code in the context of the web server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27746 | SPIP jeux &amp;lt; 4.1.1 Reflected XSS via index Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27746</link><description>The SPIP jeux plugin versions prior to 4.1.1 contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the pre_propre pipeline. The plugin incorporates untrusted request parameters into HTML output without proper output encoding, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary script content into pages that render a jeux block. When a victim is induced to visit a crafted URL, the injected content is reflected into the response and executed in the victim's browser context.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27747 | SPIP interface_traduction_objets &amp;lt; 2.2.2 Authenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27747</link><description>The SPIP interface_traduction_objets plugin versions prior to 4.3.3 contain an authenticated SQL injection vulnerability in interface_traduction_objets_pipelines.php. When handling translation requests, the plugin reads the id_parent parameter from user-supplied input and concatenates it directly into a SQL WHERE clause in a call to sql_getfetsel() without input validation or parameterization. An authenticated attacker with editor-level privileges can inject crafted SQL expressions into the id_parent parameter to manipulate the backend query. Successful exploitation can result in disclosure or modification of database contents and may lead to denial of service depending on the database configuration and privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3147 | libvips csvload.c vips_foreign_load_csv_build heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3147</link><description>A vulnerability was found in libvips up to 8.18.0. This affects the function vips_foreign_load_csv_build of the file libvips/foreign/csvload.c. The manipulation results in heap-based buffer overflow. The attack requires a local approach. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The patch is identified as b3ab458a25e0e261cbd1788474bbc763f7435780. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5781 | Information Exposure Vulnerability in Hitachi Configuration Manager, Hitachi Ops Center API Configuration Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5781</link><description>Information Exposure Vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center API Configuration Manager, Hitachi Configuration Manager, Hitachi Device Manager allows Session Hijacking.This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center API Configuration Manager: from 10.0.0-00 before 11.0.5-00; Hitachi Configuration Manager: from 8.5.1-00 before 11.0.5-00; Hitachi Device Manager: from 8.4.1-00 before 8.6.5-00.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25135 | OpenEMR&amp;#x27;s location resource for Group.$export operation returns entire patient/user population contact information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25135</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Versions prior to 8.0.0 have an information disclosure vulnerability that leaks the entire contact information for all users, organizations, and patients in the system to anyone who has the system/(Group,Patient,*).$export operation and system/Location.read capabilities.  This vulnerability will impact OpenEMR versions since 2023. This disclosure will only occur in extremely high trust environments as it requires using a confidential client with secure key exchange that requires an administrator to enable and grant permission before the app can even be used. This will typically only occur in server-server communication across trusted clients that already have established legal agreements. Version 8.0.0 contains a patch. As a workaround, disable clients that have the vulnerable scopes and only allow clients that do not have the system/Location.read scope until a fix has been deployed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27595 | Parse Dashboard has incomplete authentication on AI Agent endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27595</link><description>Parse Dashboard is a standalone dashboard for managing Parse Server apps. In versions 7.3.0-alpha.42 through 9.0.0-alpha.7, the AI Agent API endpoint (POST `/apps/:appId/agent`) has multiple security vulnerabilities that, when chained, allow unauthenticated remote attackers to perform arbitrary read and write operations against any connected Parse Server database using the master key. The agent feature is opt-in; dashboards without an agent config are not affected. The fix in version 9.0.0-alpha.8 adds authentication, CSRF validation, and per-app authorization middleware to the agent endpoint. Read-only users are restricted to the `readOnlyMasterKey` with write permissions stripped server-side. A cache key collision between master key and read-only master key was also corrected. As a workaround, remove or comment out the agent configuration block from your Parse Dashboard configuration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27606 | Rollup 4 has Arbitrary File Write via Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27606</link><description>Rollup is a module bundler for JavaScript. Versions prior to 2.80.0, 3.30.0, and 4.59.0 of the Rollup module bundler (specifically v4.x and present in current source) is vulnerable to an Arbitrary File Write via Path Traversal. Insecure file name sanitization in the core engine allows an attacker to control output filenames (e.g., via CLI named inputs, manual chunk aliases, or malicious plugins) and use traversal sequences (`../`) to overwrite files anywhere on the host filesystem that the build process has permissions for. This can lead to persistent Remote Code Execution (RCE) by overwriting critical system or user configuration files. Versions 2.80.0, 3.30.0, and 4.59.0 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27607 | RustFS&amp;#x27;s Missing Post Policy Validation leads to Arbitrary Object Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27607</link><description>RustFS is a distributed object storage system built in Rust. In versions 1.0.0-alpha.56 through 1.0.0-alpha.82, RustFS does not validate policy conditions in presigned POST uploads (PostObject), allowing attackers to bypass content-length-range, starts-with, and Content-Type constraints. This enables unauthorized file uploads exceeding size limits, uploads to arbitrary object keys, and content-type spoofing, potentially leading to storage exhaustion, unauthorized data access, and security bypasses. Version 1.0.0-alpha.83 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27608 | Parse Dashboard Missing Authorization on Agent Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27608</link><description>Parse Dashboard is a standalone dashboard for managing Parse Server apps. In versions 7.3.0-alpha.42 through 9.0.0-alpha.7, the AI Agent API endpoint (`POST /apps/:appId/agent`) does not enforce authorization. Authenticated users scoped to specific apps can access any other app's agent endpoint by changing the app ID in the URL. Read-only users are given the full master key instead of the read-only master key and can supply write permissions in the request body to perform write and delete operations. Only dashboards with `agent` configuration enabled are affected. The fix in version 9.0.0-alpha.8 adds per-app authorization checks and restricts read-only users to the `readOnlyMasterKey` with write permissions stripped server-side. As a workaround, remove the `agent` configuration block from your dashboard configuration. Dashboards without an `agent` config are not affected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27609 | Parse Dashboard Missing CSRF Protection on Agent Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27609</link><description>Parse Dashboard is a standalone dashboard for managing Parse Server apps. In versions 7.3.0-alpha.42 through 9.0.0-alpha.7, the AI Agent API endpoint (`POST /apps/:appId/agent`) lacks CSRF protection. An attacker can craft a malicious page that, when visited by an authenticated dashboard user, submits requests to the agent endpoint using the victim's session. The fix in version 9.0.0-alpha.8 adds CSRF middleware to the agent endpoint and embeds a CSRF token in the dashboard page. As a workaround, remove the `agent` configuration block from your dashboard configuration. Dashboards without an `agent` config are not affected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27610 | Parse Dashboard Has a Cache Key Collision that Leaks Master Key to Read-Only Sessions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27610</link><description>Parse Dashboard is a standalone dashboard for managing Parse Server apps. In versions 7.3.0-alpha.42 through 9.0.0-alpha.7, the `ConfigKeyCache` uses the same cache key for both master key and read-only master key when resolving function-typed keys. Under specific timing conditions, a read-only user can receive the cached full master key, or a regular user can receive the cached read-only master key. The fix in version 9.0.0-alpha.8 uses distinct cache keys for master key and read-only master key. As a workaround, avoid using function-typed master keys, or remove the `agent` configuration block from your dashboard configuration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27611 | FileBrowser Quantum: Password Protection Not Enforced on Shared File Links</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27611</link><description>FileBrowser Quantum is a free, self-hosted, web-based file manager. Prior to versions 1.1.3-stable and 1.2.6-beta, when users share password-protected files, the recipient can completely bypass the password and still download the file. This happens because the API returns a direct download link in the details of the share, which is accessible to anyone with JUST THE SHARE LINK, even without the password. Versions 1.1.3-stable and 1.2.6-beta fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27612 | Repostat Vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via repo prop in RepoCard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27612</link><description>Repostat is a React component to fetch and display GitHub repository info. Prior to version 1.0.1, the `RepoCard` component is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). The vulnerability occurs because the component uses React's `dangerouslySetInnerHTML` to render the repository name (`repo` prop) during the loading state without any sanitization. If a developer using this package passes unvalidated user input directly into the `repo` prop (for example, reading it from a URL query parameter), an attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the user's browser. In version 1.0.1, the use of dangerouslySetInnerHTML has been removed, and the repo prop is now safely rendered using standard React JSX data binding, which automatically escapes HTML entities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27614 | Bugsink is vulnerable to Stored XSS via Pygments fallback in stacktrace rendering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27614</link><description>Bugsink is a self-hosted error tracking tool. In versions prior to 2.0.13, an unauthenticated attacker who can submit events to a Bugsink project can store arbitrary JavaScript in an event. The payload executes only if a user explicitly views the affected Stacktrace in the web UI. When Pygments returns more lines than it was given (a known upstream quirk that triggers with Ruby heredoc-style input), `_pygmentize_lines()` in `theme/templatetags/issues.py:75-77` falls back to returning the raw input lines. `mark_safe()` at line 111-113 is then applied unconditionally - including to those unsanitized raw lines. Since DSN endpoints are public by Sentry protocol, no account is needed to inject. The payload sits in the database until an admin looks at the event. Successful exploitation requires that the attacker to be able to submit events to the project (i.e. knows the DSN or can access a client that uses it), the Bugsink ingest endpoint is reachable to the attacker, and an administrator explicitly views the crafted event in the UI. Under those conditions, the attacker can execute JavaScript in the administrator’s browser and act with that user’s privileges within Bugsink. Version 2.0.13 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27615 | ADB-Explorer: UNC Path Support in ManualAdbPath Leads to Remote Code Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27615</link><description>ADB Explorer is a fluent UI for ADB on Windows. In versions prior to Beta 0.9.26022, ADB-Explorer allows the `ManualAdbPath` settings variable, which determines the path of the ADB binary to be executed, to be set to a Universal Naming Convention (UNC) path in the application's settings file. This allows an attacker to set the binary's path to point to a remote network resource, hosted on an attacker-controlled network share, thus granting the attacker full control over the binary being executed by the app. An attacker may leverage this vulnerability to execute code remotely on a victim's machine with the privileges of the user running the app. Exploitation is made possible by convincing a victim to run a shortcut of the app that points to a custom `App.txt` settings file, which sets `ManualAdbPath` (for example, when downloaded in an archive file). Version Beta 0.9.26022 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27621 | TypiCMS Core has Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27621</link><description>TypiCMS is a multilingual content management system based on the Laravel framework. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the file upload module of TypiCMS prior to version 16.1.7. The application allows users with file upload permissions to upload SVG files. While there is a MIME type validation, the content of the SVG file is not sanitized. An attacker can upload a specially crafted SVG file containing malicious JavaScript code. When another user (such as an administrator) views or accesses this file through the application, the script executes in their browser, leading to a compromise of that user's session. The issue is exacerbated by a bug in the SVG parsing logic, which can cause a 500 error if the uploaded SVG does not contain a `viewBox` attribute. However, this does not mitigate the XSS vulnerability, as an attacker can easily include a valid `viewBox` attribute in their malicious payload. Version 16.1.7 of TypiCMS Core fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27626 | OliveTin vulnerable to OS Command Injection via `password` argument type and webhook JSON extraction bypasses shell safety checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27626</link><description>OliveTin gives access to predefined shell commands from a web interface. In versions up to and including 3000.10.0, OliveTin's shell mode safety check (`checkShellArgumentSafety`) blocks several dangerous argument types but not `password`. A user supplying a `password`-typed argument can inject shell metacharacters that execute arbitrary OS commands. A second independent vector allows unauthenticated RCE via webhook-extracted JSON values that skip type safety checks entirely before reaching `sh -c`. When exploiting vector 1, any authenticated user (registration enabled by default, `authType: none` by default) can execute arbitrary OS commands on the OliveTin host with the permissions of the OliveTin process. When exploiting vector 2, an unauthenticated attacker can achieve the same if the instance receives webhooks from external sources, which is a primary OliveTin use case. When an attacker exploits both vectors, this results in unauthenticated RCE on any OliveTin instance using Shell mode with webhook-triggered actions. As of time of publication, a patched version is not available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27628 | pypdf has a possible infinite loop when loading circular /Prev entries in cross-reference streams</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27628</link><description>pypdf is a free and open-source pure-python PDF library. Prior to 6.7.2, an attacker who uses this vulnerability can craft a PDF which leads to an infinite loop. This requires reading the file. This has been fixed in pypdf 6.7.2. As a workaround, one may apply the patch manually.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27629 | InvenTree Vulnerable to Server Side Template Injection (SSTI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27629</link><description>InvenTree is an Open Source Inventory Management System. Prior to version 1.2.3, insecure server-side templates can be hijacked to expose secure information to the client. When generating custom batch codes, the InvenTree server makes use of a customizable jinja2 template, which can be modified by a staff user to exfiltrate sensitive information or perform code execution on the server. This issue requires access by a user with granted staff permissions, followed by a request to generate a custom batch code via the API. Once the template has been modified in a malicious manner, the API call to generate a new batch code could be made by other users, and the template code will be executed with their user context. The code has been patched to ensure that all template generation is performed within a secure sandboxed context. This issue has been addressed in version 1.2.3, and any versions from 1.3.0 onwards. Some workarounds are available. The batch code template is a configurable global setting which can be adjusted via any user with staff access. To prevent this setting from being edited, it can be overridden at a system level to a default value, preventing it from being edited. This requires system administrator access, and cannot be changed from the client side once the server is running. It is recommended that for InvenTree installations prior to 1.2.3 the `STOCK_BATCH_CODE_TEMPLATE` and `PART_NAME_FORMAT` global settings are overridden at the system level to prevent editing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27632 | Talishar Vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27632</link><description>Talishar is a fan-made Flesh and Blood project. Prior to commit 6be3871a14c192d1fb8146cdbc76f29f27c1cf48, the Talishar application lacks Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) protections on critical state-changing endpoints, specifically within `SubmitChat.php` and other game interaction handlers. By failing to require unique, unpredictable session tokens, the application allows third-party malicious websites to forge requests on behalf of authenticated users, leading to unauthorized actions within active game sessions. The attacker would need to know both the proper gameName and playerID for the player. The player would also need to be browsing and interact with the infected website while playing a game. The vulnerability is fixed in commit 6be3871a14c192d1fb8146cdbc76f29f27c1cf48.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27822 | Rust has Critical Stored XSS in Preview Modal, leading to Administrative Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27822</link><description>RustFS is a distributed object storage system built in Rust. Prior to version 1.0.0-alpha.83, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the RustFS Console allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the management console. By bypassing the PDF preview logic, an attacker can steal administrator credentials from `localStorage`, leading to full account takeover and system compromise. Version 1.0.0-alpha.83 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3145 | libvips matrixload.c vips_foreign_load_matrix_header memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3145</link><description>A flaw has been found in libvips up to 8.18.0. The affected element is the function vips_foreign_load_matrix_file_is_a/vips_foreign_load_matrix_header of the file libvips/foreign/matrixload.c. Executing a manipulation can lead to memory corruption. The attack needs to be launched locally. This patch is called d4ce337c76bff1b278d7085c3c4f4725e3aa6ece. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3146 | libvips matrixload.c vips_foreign_load_matrix_header null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3146</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in libvips up to 8.18.0. The impacted element is the function vips_foreign_load_matrix_header of the file libvips/foreign/matrixload.c. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack needs to be performed locally. The identifier of the patch is d4ce337c76bff1b278d7085c3c4f4725e3aa6ece. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69231 | OpenEMR has a Stored XSS in GAD-7 Form that Enables Session Hijacking and Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69231</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 8.0.0, a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the GAD-7 anxiety assessment form allows authenticated users with clinician privileges to inject malicious JavaScript that executes when other users view the form. This enables session hijacking, account takeover, and privilege escalation from clinician to administrator. Version 8.0.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21443 | OpenEMR allows inconsistent escaping of translation function output</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21443</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 8.0.0, the `xl()` translation function returns unescaped strings. While wrapper functions exist for escaping in different contexts (`xlt()` for HTML, `xla()` for attributes, `xlj()` for JavaScript), there are places in the codebase where `xl()` output is used directly without escaping. If an attacker could insert malicious content into the translation database, these unescaped outputs could lead to XSS. Version 8.0.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24847 | OpenEMR has Open Redirect in Eye Exam Form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24847</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 8.0.0, the Eye Exam form module allows any authenticated user to be redirected to an arbitrary external URL. This can be exploited for phishing attacks against healthcare providers using OpenEMR. Version 8.0.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24849 | OpenEMR Arbitrary File Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24849</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 7.0.4, the `disposeDocument()` method in `EtherFaxActions.php` allows authenticated users to read arbitrary files from the server filesystem. Any authenticated user (regardless of privilege level) can exploit this vulnerability to read sensitive files. Version 7.0.4 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24896 | OpenEMR has Broken Access Control that allows unauthorized access to EDI Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24896</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 8.0.0, a Broken Access Control vulnerability exists in OpenEMR’s edih_main.php endpoint, which allows any authenticated user—including low-privilege roles like Receptionist—to access EDI log files by manipulating the log_select parameter in a GET request. The back-end fails to enforce role-based access control (RBAC), allowing sensitive system logs to be accessed outside the GUI-enforced permission boundaries. Version 8.0.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25124 | OpenEMR has Broken Access Control in Report/Clients/Message List CSV Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25124</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 8.0.0, the OpenEMR application is vulnerable to an access control flaw that allows low-privileged users, such as receptionists, to export the entire message list containing sensitive patient and user data. The vulnerability lies in the message_list.php report export functionality, where there is no permission check before executing sensitive database queries. The only control in place is CSRF token verification, which does not prevent unauthorized data access if the token is acquired through other means. Version 8.0.0 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25127 | OpenEMR has Broken Access Control on Care Coordination Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25127</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 8.0.0, the server does not properly validate user permission. Unauthorized users can view the information of authorized users. Version 8.0.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25131 | OpenEMR has Broken Access Control in Procedures Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25131</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 8.0.0, a Broken Access Control vulnerability exists in the OpenEMR order types management system, allowing low-privilege users (such as Receptionist) to add and modify procedure types without proper authorization. This vulnerability is present in the /openemr/interface/orders/types_edit.php endpoint. Version 8.0.0 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2914 | CyberArk Endpoint Privilege Manager Agent versions 25.10.0 and lower allow potential unauthorized privilege elevation leveraging CyberArk el...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2914</link><description>CyberArk Endpoint Privilege Manager Agent versions 25.10.0 and lower allow potential unauthorized privilege elevation leveraging CyberArk elevation dialogs</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67752 | OpenEMR Has Disabled SSL Certificate Verification in HTTP Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67752</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 7.0.4, OpenEMR's HTTP client wrapper (`oeHttp`/`oeHttpRequest`) disables SSL/TLS certificate verification by default (`verify: false`), making all external HTTPS connections vulnerable to man-in-the-middle (MITM) attacks. This affects communication with government healthcare APIs and user-configurable external services, potentially exposing Protected Health Information (PHI). Version 7.0.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68277 | OpenEMR allows links sent via Secure Messaging to be opened in OpenEMR and Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68277</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 7.0.4, when a link is sent via Secure Messaging, clicking the link opens the website within the OpenEMR/Portal site. This behavior could be exploited for phishing. Version 7.0.4 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67491 | OpenEMR has Stored XSS in ub04 helper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67491</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Versions 5.0.0.5 through 7.0.3.4 have a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the ub04 helper of the billing interface. The variable `$data` is passed in a click event handler enclosed in single quotes without proper sanitization. Thus, despite `json_encode` a malicious user can still inject a payload such as ` ac' &gt;&lt;img src="x" /&gt; ` to trigger the bug. This vulnerability allows low privileged users to embed malicious JS payloads on the server and perform stored XSS attack. This, in turn makes it possible for malicious users to steal the session cookies and perform unauthorized actions impersonating administrators. Version 7.0.4 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27598 | Dagu: Path traversal in DAG creation allows arbitrary YAML file write outside DAGs directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27598</link><description>Dagu is a workflow engine with a built-in Web user interface. In versions up to and including 1.16.7, the `CreateNewDAG` API endpoint (`POST /api/v1/dags`) does not validate the DAG name before passing it to the file store. An authenticated user with DAG write permissions can write arbitrary YAML files anywhere on the filesystem (limited by the process permissions). Since dagu executes DAG files as shell commands, writing a malicious DAG to the DAGs directory of another instance or overwriting config files can lead to remote code execution. Commit e2ed589105d79273e4e6ac8eb31525f765bb3ce4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3135 | itsourcecode News Portal Project add-category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3135</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode News Portal Project 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/add-category.php. This manipulation of the argument Category causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3137 | CodeAstro Food Ordering System food_ordering.exe stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3137</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in CodeAstro Food Ordering System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file food_ordering.exe. Such manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can only be performed from a local environment. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>