<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:00:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-2733 | Org.keycloak/keycloak-services: keycloak: missing check on disabled client for docker registry protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2733</link><description>A flaw was identified in the Docker v2 authentication endpoint of Keycloak, where tokens continue to be issued even after a Docker registry client has been administratively disabled. This means that turning the client “Enabled” setting to OFF does not fully prevent access. As a result, previously valid credentials can still be used to obtain authentication tokens. This weakens administrative controls and could allow unintended access to container registry resources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:00:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2711 | zhutoutoutousan worldquant-miner URL ssrf_proxy.py server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2711</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in zhutoutoutousan worldquant-miner up to 1.0.9. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file worldquant-miner-master/agent-dify-api/core/helper/ssrf_proxy.py of the component URL Handler. The manipulation of the argument make_request leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1994 | s2Member &amp;lt;= 260127 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1994</link><description>The s2Member plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 260127. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their password. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2681 | Github.com/supranational/blst: blst cryptographic library: denial of service via out-of-bounds stack write in key generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2681</link><description>A flaw was found in the blst cryptographic library. This out-of-bounds stack write vulnerability, specifically in the blst_sha256_bcopy assembly routine, occurs due to a missing zero-length guard. A remote attacker can exploit this by providing a zero-length salt parameter to key generation functions, such as blst_keygen_v5(), if the application exposes this functionality. Successful exploitation leads to memory corruption and immediate process termination, resulting in a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:17:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2731 | Unauthenticated RCE in Dynamicweb 9 and Dynamicweb 8</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2731</link><description>Path traversal and content injection in JobRunnerBackground.aspx in DymaicWeb 8 (all) and 9 (&lt;9.19.7 and &lt;9.20.3) allows unauthenticated attackers to execute code via simple web requests</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:17:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2709 | busy Callback app.js redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2709</link><description>A flaw has been found in busy up to 2.5.5. The affected element is an unknown function of the file source-code/busy-master/src/server/app.js of the component Callback Handler. Executing a manipulation of the argument state can lead to open redirect. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2706 | code-projects Patient Record Management System fecalysis_not.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2706</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /fecalysis_not.php. This manipulation of the argument comp_id causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:15:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2705 | Open Babel MOL2 File atom.h SetFormalCharge out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2705</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Open Babel up to 3.1.1. The impacted element is the function OBAtom::SetFormalCharge in the library include/openbabel/atom.h of the component MOL2 File Handler. The manipulation results in out-of-bounds read. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:15:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12975 | CTX Feed – WooCommerce Product Feed Manager &amp;lt;= 6.6.11 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Shop Manager+) Arbitrary Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12975</link><description>The CTX Feed – WooCommerce Product Feed Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary plugin installation due to a missing capability check on the woo_feed_plugin_installing() function in all versions up to, and including, 6.6.11. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level access and above, to install arbitrary plugins which can be leveraged to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13091 | Shopire &amp;lt;= 1.0.57 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Plugin Install</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13091</link><description>The Shopire theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the shopire_admin_install_plugin() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.57. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to install the 'fable-extra' plugin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13413 | Country Blocker for AdSense &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13413</link><description>The Country Blocker for AdSense plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the CBFA_guardar_cbfa() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13438 | Page Title, Description &amp;amp; Open Graph Updater &amp;lt;= 1.02 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Page Title Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13438</link><description>The Page Title, Description &amp; Open Graph Updater plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.02. This is due to missing nonce validation on multiple AJAX actions including dieno_update_page_title. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update page titles and metadata via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13563 | Lizza LMS Pro &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13563</link><description>The Lizza LMS Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This is due to the 'lizza_lms_pro_register_user_front_end' function not restricting what user roles a user can register with. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to supply the 'administrator' role during registration and gain administrator access to the site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13587 | Two Factor (2FA) Authentication via Email &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Two-Factor Authentication Bypass via token</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13587</link><description>The Two Factor (2FA) Authentication via Email plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Two-Factor Authentication Bypass in versions up to, and including, 1.9.8. This is because the SS88_2FAVE::wp_login() method only enforces the 2FA requirement if the 'token' HTTP GET parameter is undefined, which makes it possible to bypass two-factor authentication by supplying any value in the 'token' parameter during login, including an empty one.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13603 | WP AUDIO GALLERY &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Read via .htaccess Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13603</link><description>The WP AUDIO GALLERY plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unauthorized Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 2.0. This is due to insufficient capability checks and lack of nonce verification on the "wpag_htaccess_callback" function This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to overwrite the site's .htaccess file with arbitrary content, which can lead to arbitrary file read on the server under certain configurations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13612 | Album and Image Gallery Plus Lightbox &amp;lt;= 2.1.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Plugin&amp;#x27;s Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13612</link><description>The Album and Image Gallery plus Lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `aigpl-gallery-album` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13617 | Apollo13 Framework Extension &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via `a13_alt_link` Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13617</link><description>The Apollo13 Framework Extensions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘a13_alt_link’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13732 | s2Member &amp;lt;= 251005 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13732</link><description>The s2Member – Excellent for All Kinds of Memberships, Content Restriction Paywalls &amp; Member Access Subscriptions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 's2Eot' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 251005 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13738 | Easy Table of Contents &amp;lt;= 2.0.78 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13738</link><description>The Easy Table of Contents plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `ez-toc` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.78 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13842 | Breadcrumb NavXT &amp;lt;= 7.5.0 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13842</link><description>The Breadcrumb NavXT plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass through user-controlled key in versions up to and including 7.5.0. This is due to the Gutenberg block renderer trusting the $_REQUEST['post_id'] parameter without verification in the includes/blocks/build/breadcrumb-trail/render.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enumerate and view breadcrumb trails for draft or private posts by manipulating the post_id parameter, revealing post titles and hierarchy that should remain hidden.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13851 | Buyent Theme (with Buyent Classified Plugin) &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via User Registration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13851</link><description>The Buyent Classified plugin for WordPress (bundled with Buyent theme) is vulnerable to privilege escalation via user registration in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7. This is due to the plugin not validating or restricting the user role during registration via the REST API endpoint. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register accounts with arbitrary roles, including administrator, by manipulating the _buyent_classified_user_type parameter during the registration process, granting them complete control over the WordPress site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13864 | Breeze – WordPress Cache Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.21 - Missing Authorization to Cache Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13864</link><description>The Breeze - WordPress Cache Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized cache clearing in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.21. This is due to the REST API endpoint `/wp-json/breeze/v1/clear-all-cache` being registered with `permission_callback =&gt; '__return_true'` and authentication being disabled by default when the API is enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to clear all site caches (page cache, Varnish, and Cloudflare) via a simple POST request, granted the administrator has enabled the API integration feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13930 | Checkout Field Manager (Checkout Manager) for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 7.8.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Attachment Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13930</link><description>The Checkout Field Manager (Checkout Manager) for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in versions up to, and including, 7.8.5. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to delete an attachment combined with flawed guest order ownership validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete attachments associated with guest orders using only the publicly available wooccm_upload nonce and attachment ID.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14076 | iXML – Google XML sitemap generator &amp;lt;= 0.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;iXML_email&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14076</link><description>The iXML – Google XML sitemap generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'iXML_email' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14167 | Remove Post Type Slug &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14167</link><description>The Remove Post Type Slug plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2. This is due to incorrect nonce validation logic that uses OR (||) instead of AND (&amp;&amp;), causing the validation to fail when the nonce field is not empty OR when verification fails, rather than when it's empty AND verification fails. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's post type slug removal settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14270 | OneClick Chat to Order &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Editor+) Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14270</link><description>The OneClick Chat to Order plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in versions up to, and including, 1.0.9. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action in the wa_order_number_save_number_field function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to modify WhatsApp phone numbers used by the plugin, redirecting customer orders and messages to attacker-controlled phone numbers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14294 | Razorpay for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.7.8 - Missing Authentication to Unauthenticated Order Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14294</link><description>The Razorpay for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the getCouponList() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.7.8. This is due to the checkAuthCredentials() permission callback always returning true, providing no actual authentication. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the billing and shipping contact information (email and phone) of any WooCommerce order by knowing or guessing the order ID.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14342 | SEO Plugin by Squirrly SEO &amp;lt;= 12.4.14 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Cloud Service Disconnection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14342</link><description>The SEO Plugin by Squirrly SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the sq_ajax_uninstall function in all versions up to, and including, 12.4.14. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to disconnect the site from Squirrly's cloud service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14357 | Mega Store Woocommerce &amp;lt;= 5.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Page Creation and Settings Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14357</link><description>The Mega Store Woocommerce theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the setup_widgets() function in core/includes/importer/whizzie.php in all versions up to, and including, 5.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create arbitrary pages and modify site settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14427 | Shield Security: Blocks Bots, Protects Users, and Prevents Security Breaches &amp;lt;= 21.0.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Email MFA Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14427</link><description>The Shield Security: Blocks Bots, Protects Users, and Prevents Security Breaches plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the `MfaEmailDisable` action in all versions up to, and including, 21.0.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to disable the global Email 2FA setting for the entire site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14445 | Image Hotspot by DevVN &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom Field Meta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14445</link><description>The Image Hotspot by DevVN plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'hotspot_content' custom field meta in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14452 | WP Customer Reviews &amp;lt;= 3.7.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;wpcr3_fname&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14452</link><description>The WP Customer Reviews plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'wpcr3_fname' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14851 | YaMaps for WordPress &amp;lt;= 0.6.40 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14851</link><description>The YaMaps for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `yamap` shortcode parameters in all versions up to, and including, 0.6.40 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14864 | Virusdie &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) API Key Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14864</link><description>The Virusdie - One-click website security plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.7. This is due to missing capability checks on the `vd_get_apikey` function which is hooked to `wp_ajax_virusdie_apikey`. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve the site's Virusdie API key, which could be used to access the site owner's Virusdie account and potentially compromise site security.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14983 | Advanced Custom Fields: Font Awesome &amp;lt;= 5.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14983</link><description>The Advanced Custom Fields: Font Awesome Field plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible forauthenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts that execute in a victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15041 | BackWPup &amp;lt;= 5.6.2 - Authenticated (BackWPup Helper+) Privilege Escalation via Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15041</link><description>The BackWPup – WordPress Backup &amp; Restore Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the save_site_option() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4521 | IDonate 2.1.5 - 2.1.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Account Takeover/Privilege Escalation via idonate_donor_profile Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4521</link><description>The IDonate – Blood Donation, Request And Donor Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check on the idonate_donor_profile() function in versions 2.1.5 to 2.1.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to hijack any account by reassigning its email address (via the donor_id they supply) and then triggering a password reset, ultimately granting themselves full administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0549 | Groups &amp;lt;= 3.10.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;groups_group_info&amp;#x27; Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0549</link><description>The Groups plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'groups_group_info' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0556 | XO Event Calendar &amp;lt;= 3.2.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;xo_event_field&amp;#x27; shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0556</link><description>The XO Event Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'xo_event_field' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0561 | Shield Security &amp;lt;= 21.0.8 - Unauthenticated Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;message&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0561</link><description>The Shield Security plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'message' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 21.0.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0722 | Shield Security &amp;lt;= 21.0.8 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0722</link><description>The Shield Security plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 21.0.8. This is due to the plugin allowing nonce verification to be bypassed via user-supplied parameter in the 'isNonceVerifyRequired' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute SQL injection attacks, extracting sensitive information from the database, via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0912 | Toret Manager &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update via AJAX actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0912</link><description>The Toret Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the 'trman_save_option' function and on the 'trman_save_option_items' in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0926 | Prodigy Commerce &amp;lt;= 3.2.9 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion via parameters[template_name]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0926</link><description>The Prodigy Commerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.9 via the 'parameters[template_name]' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and read arbitrary files or execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0974 | Orderable &amp;lt;= 1.20.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0974</link><description>The Orderable – WordPress Restaurant Online Ordering System and Food Ordering Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin installation due to a missing capability check on the 'install_plugin' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.20.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to install arbitrary plugins, which can lead to Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1043 | PostmarkApp Email Integrator &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Plugin Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1043</link><description>The PostmarkApp Email Integrator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin settings in versions up to, and including, 2.4. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the pma_api_key and pma_sender_address parameters. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the settings page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1044 | Tennis Court Bookings &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Admin Settings and Calendar Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1044</link><description>The Tennis Court Bookings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1047 | salavat counter Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.5 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;image_url&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1047</link><description>The salavat counter Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'image_url' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1055 | TalkJS &amp;lt;= 0.1.15 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;welcomeMessage&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1055</link><description>The TalkJS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1373 | Easy Author Image &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Profile Picture URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1373</link><description>The Easy Author Image plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'author_profile_picture_url' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1405 | Slider Future &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1405</link><description>The Slider Future plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'slider_future_handle_image_upload' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1455 | Whatsiplus Scheduled Notification for Woocommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to &amp;#x27;wsnfw_save_users_settings&amp;#x27; AJAX Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1455</link><description>The Whatsiplus Scheduled Notification for Woocommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to missing nonce validation on the 'wsnfw_save_users_settings' AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin configuration settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1646 | Advance Block Extend &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via TitleColor Block Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1646</link><description>The Advance Block Extend plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the TitleColor block attribute in the Latest Posts Gutenberg block in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2282 | Slidorion &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Slidorion Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2282</link><description>The Slidorion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2284 | News Element Elementor Blog Magazine &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Data Loss</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2284</link><description>The News Element Elementor Blog Magazine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8. This is due to a missing capability check and nonce verification on the 'ne_clean_data' AJAX action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to truncate 8 core WordPress database tables (posts, comments, terms, term_relationships, term_taxonomy, postmeta, commentmeta, termmeta) and delete the entire WordPress uploads directory, resulting in complete data loss.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2502 | xmlrpc attacks blocker &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;X-Forwarded-For&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2502</link><description>The xmlrpc attacks blocker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including, 1.0, via the 'X-Forwarded-For' HTTP header. This is due to the plugin trusting and logging attacker-controlled IP header data and rendering debug log entries without output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts that execute when an administrator views the debug log page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2504 | Dealia – Request a quote &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Plugin Configuration Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2504</link><description>The Dealia – Request a quote plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to missing capability checks on multiple AJAX handlers in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6. The admin nonce (DEALIA_ADMIN_NONCE) is exposed to all users with edit_posts capability (Contributor+) via wp_localize_script() in PostsController.php, while the AJAX handlers in AdminSettingsController.php only verify the nonce without checking current_user_can('manage_options'). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to reset the plugin configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2704 | Open Babel CIF File transform3d.cpp DescribeAsString out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2704</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Open Babel up to 3.1.1. The affected element is the function OpenBabel::transform3d::DescribeAsString of the file src/math/transform3d.cpp of the component CIF File Handler. The manipulation leads to out-of-bounds read. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11706 | Aruba HiSpeed Cache &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11706</link><description>The Aruba HiSpeed Cache plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the dbstatus parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11725 | Aruba HiSpeed Cache &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Plugin&amp;#x27;s Settings Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11725</link><description>The Aruba HiSpeed Cache plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability checks on the multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin's configuration settings, enable or disable features, as well as enable/disable WordPress cron jobs or debug mode</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11754 | Cookie Banner, Cookie Consent, Consent Log, Cookie Scanner, Script Blocker (for GDPR, CCPA &amp;amp; ePrivacy) : WP Cookie Consent &amp;lt;= 4.1.2 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11754</link><description>The GDPR Cookie Consent plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'gdpr/v1/settings' REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve sensitive plugin settings including API tokens, email addresses, account IDs, and site keys.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12027 | Mesmerize Companion &amp;lt;= 1.6.158 - Missing Authorization Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12027</link><description>The Mesmerize Companion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data due to a missing capability check on the "openPageInCustomizer" and "openPageInDefaultEditor" functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.158. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers - with subscriber level access and above, on websites with the Mesmerize theme activated -  to mark arbitrary pages as maintainable, wrap their content in custom sections, change page template metadata, and toggle the default editor flag without proper authorization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12081 | ACF Photo Gallery Field &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Attachment Metadata Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12081</link><description>The ACF Photo Gallery Field plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the "acf_photo_gallery_edit_save" function in all versions up to, and including, 3.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to modify the title, caption, and custom metadata of arbitrary media attachments.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12116 | Drift &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Authenticated  (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Post Title</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12116</link><description>The Drift theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the post title in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12117 | Renden &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Post Title</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12117</link><description>The Renden theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the post title in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12172 | Mailchimp List Subscribe Form &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Mailchimp List Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12172</link><description>The Mailchimp List Subscribe Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the mailchimp_sf_change_list_if_necessary() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change Mailchimp lists via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12375 | Printful Integration for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.2.11 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12375</link><description>The Printful Integration for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.11 via the advanced size chart REST API endpoint. This is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied URLs before passing them to the download_url() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application which can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12448 | Smartsupp – live chat, AI shopping assistant and chatbots &amp;lt;= 3.9.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12448</link><description>The Smartsupp – live chat, AI shopping assistant and chatbots plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'code' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12451 | Easy SVG Support &amp;lt;= 4.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12451</link><description>The Easy SVG Support plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG file uploads in all versions up to, and including, 4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12500 | Checkout Field Manager (Checkout Manager) for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 7.8.1 - Unauthenticated Limited File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12500</link><description>The Checkout Field Manager (Checkout Manager) for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthenticated limited file upload in all versions up to, and including, 7.8.1. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform file upload actions via the "ajax_checkout_attachment_upload" function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload files to the server, though file types are limited to WordPress's default allowed MIME types (images, documents, etc.).</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12707 | Library Management System &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12707</link><description>The Library Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'bid' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12821 | NewsBlogger &amp;lt;= 0.2.5.6 - 0.2.6.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12821</link><description>The NewsBlogger theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions 0.2.5.6  to 0.2.6.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the newsblogger_install_and_activate_plugin() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files and achieve remote code execution via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This is due to a reverted fix of CVE-2025-1305.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12845 | Tablesome Table – Contact Form DB – WPForms, CF7, Gravity, Forminator, Fluent 0.5.4 - 1.2.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Information Exposure and Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12845</link><description>The Tablesome Table – Contact Form DB – WPForms, CF7, Gravity, Forminator, Fluent plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data that leads to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the get_table_data() function in versions 0.5.4 to 1.2.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve plugin table data that can expose email log information. Attackers can leverage this on sites where the table log is enabled in order to trigger a password reset and obtain the reset key.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12882 | Clasifico Listing &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12882</link><description>The Clasifico Listing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions up to, and including, 2.0. This is due to the plugin allowing users who are registering new accounts to set their own role by supplying the 'listing_user_role' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to gain elevated privileges by registering an account with the administrator role.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12884 | Advanced Ads – Ad Manager &amp;amp; AdSense &amp;lt;= 2.0.14 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Ad Placements Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12884</link><description>The Advanced Ads – Ad Manager &amp; AdSense plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in versions up to, and including, 2.0.14. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action in the `placement_update_item()` function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update ad placements, allowing them to change which ad or ad group a placement serves.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13048 | Official StatCounter Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Nickname</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13048</link><description>The StatCounter – Free Real Time Visitor Stats plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the user's Nickname in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13079 | Popup Builder - Create highly converting, mobile friendly marketing popups. &amp;lt;= 4.4.2 - Improper Authorization to Unauthenticated Subscriber Removal via Predictable Tokens</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13079</link><description>The Popup Builder – Create highly converting, mobile friendly marketing popups. plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.2. This is due to the plugin generating predictable unsubscribe tokens using deterministic data. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to unsubscribe arbitrary subscribers from mailing lists via brute-forcing the unsubscribe token, granted they know the victim's email address</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13113 | Web Accessibility by accessiBe &amp;lt;= 2.11 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13113</link><description>The Web Accessibility by accessiBe plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.11. This is due to the `accessibe_render_js_in_footer()` function logging the complete plugin options array to the browser console on public pages, without restricting output to privileged users or checking for debug mode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view sensitive configuration data, including email addresses, accessiBe user IDs, account IDs, and license information, via the browser console when the widget is disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15586 | OGP-Website installs prior git commit 52f865a4fba763594453068acf8fa9e3fc38d663 are affected by a type juggling flaw which if exploited can r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15586</link><description>OGP-Website installs prior git commit 52f865a4fba763594453068acf8fa9e3fc38d663 are affected by a type juggling flaw which if exploited can result in authentication bypass without knowledge of the victim account's password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2702 | Beetel 777VR1 WPA2 PSK hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2702</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Beetel 777VR1 up to 01.00.09. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component WPA2 PSK. Performing a manipulation results in hard-coded credentials. The attacker must have access to the local network to execute the attack. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2703 | xlnt-community xlnt Encrypted XLSX File base64.cpp decode_base64 off-by-one</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2703</link><description>A weakness has been identified in xlnt-community xlnt up to 1.6.1. Impacted is the function xlnt::detail::decode_base64 of the file source/detail/cryptography/base64.cpp of the component Encrypted XLSX File Parser. Executing a manipulation can lead to off-by-one. The attack requires local access. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. This patch is called f2d7bf494e5c52706843cf7eb9892821bffb0734. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25229 | Gogs Authorization Bypass Allows Cross-Repository Label Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25229</link><description>Gogs is an open source self-hosted Git service. Versions 0.13.4 and below have a broken access control vulnerability which allows authenticated users with write access to any repository to modify labels belonging to other repositories. The UpdateLabel function in the Web UI (internal/route/repo/issue.go) fails to verify that the label being modified belongs to the repository specified in the URL path, enabling cross-repository label tampering attacks. The vulnerability exists in the Web UI's label update endpoint POST /:username/:reponame/labels/edit. The handler function UpdateLabel uses an incorrect database query function that bypasses repository ownership validation. This issue has been fixed in version 0.14.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25232 | Gogs has a Protected Branch Deletion Bypass in Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25232</link><description>Gogs is an open source self-hosted Git service. Versions 0.13.4 and below have an access control bypass vulnerability which allows any repository collaborator with Write permissions to delete protected branches (including the default branch) by sending a direct POST request, completely bypassing the branch protection mechanism. This vulnerability in the DeleteBranchPost function eenables privilege escalation from Write to Admin level, allowing low-privilege users to perform dangerous operations that should be restricted to administrators only. Although Git Hook layer correctly prevents protected branch deletion via SSH push, the web interface deletion operation does not trigger Git Hooks, resulting in complete bypass of protection mechanisms. In oder to exploit this vulnerability, attackers must have write permissions to the target repository, protected branches configured to the target repository and access to the Gogs web interface. This issue has been fixed in version 0.14.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25242 | Gogs allows unauthenticated file uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25242</link><description>Gogs is an open source self-hosted Git service. Versions 0.13.4 and below expose unauthenticated file upload endpoints by default. When the global RequireSigninView setting is disabled (default), any remote user can upload arbitrary files to the server via /releases/attachments and /issues/attachments. This enables the instance to be abused as a public file host, potentially leading to disk exhaustion, content hosting, or delivery of malware. CSRF tokens do not mitigate this attack due to same-origin cookie issuance. This issue has been fixed in version 0.14.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25474 | OpenClaw has a Telegram webhook request forgery (missing `channels.telegram.webhookSecret`) → auth bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25474</link><description>OpenClaw is a personal AI assistant. In versions 2026.1.30 and below, if channels.telegram.webhookSecret is not set when in Telegram webhook mode, OpenClaw may accept webhook HTTP requests without verifying Telegram’s secret token header. In deployments where the webhook endpoint is reachable by an attacker, this can allow forged Telegram updates (for example spoofing message.from.id). If an attacker can reach the webhook endpoint, they may be able to send forged updates that are processed as if they came from Telegram. Depending on enabled commands/tools and configuration, this could lead to unintended bot actions. Note: Telegram webhook mode is not enabled by default. It is enabled only when `channels.telegram.webhookUrl` is configured. This issue has been fixed in version 2026.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2693 | CoCoTeaNet CyreneAdmin System Info Endpoint getCount improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2693</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in CoCoTeaNet CyreneAdmin up to 1.3.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/system/dashboard/getCount of the component System Info Endpoint. Executing a manipulation can lead to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4960 | macOS Local Privilege Escalation via Improper Authorization Handling in EPSON Printer Controller Installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4960</link><description>The com.epson.InstallNavi.helper tool, deployed with the EPSON printer driver installer, contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability due to multiple flaws in its implementation. It fails to properly authenticate clients over the XPC protocol and does not correctly enforce macOS’s authorization model, exposing privileged functionality to untrusted users. Although it invokes the AuthorizationCopyRights API, it does so using overly permissive custom rights that it registers in the system’s authorization database (/var/db/auth.db).


These rights can be requested and granted by the authorization daemon to any local user, regardless of privilege level. As a result, an attacker can exploit the vulnerable service to perform privileged operations such as executing arbitrary commands or installing system components without requiring administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25120 | Gogs Allows Cross-Repository Comment Deletion via DeleteComment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25120</link><description>Gogs is an open source self-hosted Git service. In versions 0.13.4 and below, the DeleteComment API does not verify that the comment belongs to the repository specified in the URL. This allows a repository administrator to delete comments from any other repository by supplying arbitrary comment IDs, bypassing authorization controls. The DeleteComment function retrieves a comment by ID without verifying repository ownership and the Database function DeleteCommentByID performs no repository validation. This issue has been fixed in version 0.14.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2691 | itsourcecode Event Management System manage_register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2691</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Event Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/manage_register.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2692 | CoCoTeaNet CyreneAdmin Image getAvatar path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2692</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CoCoTeaNet CyreneAdmin up to 1.3.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /api/system/user/getAvatar of the component Image Handler. Performing a manipulation of the argument Avatar results in path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24764 | OpenClaw has Remote Code Execution via System Prompt Injection in Slack Channel Descriptions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24764</link><description>OpenClaw (formerly Clawdbot) is a personal AI assistant users run on their own devices. In versions 2026.2.2 and below, when the Slack integration is enabled, channel metadata (topic/description) can be incorporated into the model's system prompt. Prompt injection is a documented risk for LLM-driven systems. This issue increases the injection surface by allowing untrusted Slack channel metadata to be treated as higher-trust system input. This issue has been fixed in version 2026.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2690 | itsourcecode Event Management System Admin Login ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2690</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Event Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=login of the component Admin Login. This manipulation of the argument Username causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2689 | itsourcecode Event Management System manage_booking.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2689</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode Event Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/manage_booking.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 01:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2686 | SECCN Dingcheng G10 session_login.cgi qq os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2686</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SECCN Dingcheng G10 3.1.0.181203. This impacts the function qq of the file /cgi-bin/session_login.cgi. The manipulation of the argument User leads to os command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 01:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15585 | Fileflows versions before 25.05 are affected by an authenticated SQL injection vulnerability in the library-file search function. Successful...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15585</link><description>Fileflows versions before 25.05 are affected by an authenticated SQL injection vulnerability in the library-file search function. Successful exploitation requires the system to use MySQL as the underlying database and could result in privilege escalation or data exfiltration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 23:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2684 | Tsinghua Unigroup Electronic Archives System uploadFile.html unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2684</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tsinghua Unigroup Electronic Archives System up to 3.2.210802(62532). The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /Archive/ErecordManage/uploadFile.html. Executing a manipulation of the argument File can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 23:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24126 | Weblate has an argument injection in management console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24126</link><description>Weblate is a web based localization tool. Prior to 5.16.0, the SSH management console did not validate the passed input while adding the SSH host key, which could lead to an argument injection to `ssh-add`. Version 5.16.0 fixes the issue. As a workaround, properly limit access to the management console.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 23:26:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25926 | Notepad++ has an Untrusted Search Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25926</link><description>Notepad++ is a free and open-source source code editor. An Unsafe Search Path vulnerability (CWE-426) exists in versions prior to 8.9.2 when launching Windows Explorer without an absolute executable path. This may allow execution of a malicious explorer.exe if an attacker can control the process working directory. Under certain conditions, this could lead to arbitrary code execution in the context of the running application. Version 8.9.2 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 23:26:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15581 | Orthanc versions before 1.12.10 are affected by an authorisation logic flaw in the application's HTTP Basic Authentication implementation. 
...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15581</link><description>Orthanc versions before 1.12.10 are affected by an authorisation logic flaw in the application's HTTP Basic Authentication implementation. 

Successful exploitation could result in Privilege Escalation, potentially allowing full administrative access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 23:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25594 | InvoicePlane has Stored XSS via Family Name in Product Form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25594</link><description>InvoicePlane is a self-hosted open source application for managing invoices, clients, and payments. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in InvoicePlane 1.7.0 via the Family Name field. The `family_name` value is rendered without HTML encoding inside the family dropdown on the product form. When an administrator creates a family with a malicious name, the payload executes in the browser of any administrator who visits the product form. Version 1.7.1 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 23:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25595 | InvoicePlane has Stored XSS via Invoice Number in Invoice View and Dashboard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25595</link><description>InvoicePlane is a self-hosted open source application for managing invoices, clients, and payments. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in InvoicePlane 1.7.0 via the Invoice Number field. An authenticated administrator can inject malicious JavaScript that executes when any administrator views the affected invoice or visits the dashboard. Version 1.7.1 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 23:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25596 | InvoicePlane has Stored XSS via Product Unit Name in Invoice Item List</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25596</link><description>InvoicePlane is a self-hosted open source application for managing invoices, clients, and payments. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in InvoicePlane 1.7.0 via the Product Unit Name fields. An authenticated administrator can inject malicious JavaScript that executes when any administrator views an invoice containing a product with the malicious unit. Version 1.7.1 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 23:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26270 | InvoicePlane has Stored Cross-Site Scripting Issue in Identifier Formatting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26270</link><description>InvoicePlane is a self-hosted open source application for managing invoices, clients, and payments. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in InvoicePlane (latest version) that allows an authenticated user with permissions to manage Invoice Groups to inject malicious JavaScript into the "Identifier Format" field. This script executes when any user views the invoice list or the main dashboard. Version 1.7.1 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 23:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26281 | InvoicePlane has Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Issue in Sumex Invoice View</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26281</link><description>InvoicePlane is a self-hosted open source application for managing invoices, clients, and payments. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Sumex invoice view allows an authenticated user with client and invoice management privileges to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the browser of any user viewing the invoice. This can lead to session hijacking, data theft, or other malicious actions on behalf of the victim user. Version 1.7.1 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 23:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2683 | Tsinghua Unigroup Electronic Archives System downLoad.html path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2683</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tsinghua Unigroup Electronic Archives System 3.2.210802(62532). The affected element is an unknown function of the file /Using/Subject/downLoad.html. Performing a manipulation of the argument path results in path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 23:26:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24745 | InvoicePlane has a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24745</link><description>InvoicePlane is a self-hosted open source application for managing invoices, clients, and payments. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability occurs in the upload Login Logo functions of InvoicePlane version 1.7.0. In the Upload Login Logo, the application allows uploading svg files. Although administrator privileges are required to exploit it, this is still considered a critical vulnerability as it can cause actions such as unauthorized modification of application data, creation of persistent backdoors through stored malicious scripts, and full compromise of the application's integrity. Version 1.7.1 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:56:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25548 | InvoicePlane Vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via Local File Inclusion and Log Poisoning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25548</link><description>InvoicePlane is a self-hosted open source application for managing invoices, clients, and payments. A critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in InvoicePlane 1.7.0 through a chained Local File Inclusion (LFI) and Log Poisoning attack. An authenticated administrator can execute arbitrary system commands on the server by manipulating the `public_invoice_template` setting to include poisoned log files containing PHP code. Version 1.7.1 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:56:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2682 | Tsinghua Unigroup Electronic Archives System prinReport.html sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2682</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tsinghua Unigroup Electronic Archives System up to 3.2.210802(62532). Impacted is an unknown function of the file /mine/PublicReport/prinReport.html?token=java. Such manipulation of the argument comid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:56:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12811 | Cloud Suite and Privilege Access Service– HTTP request smuggling vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12811</link><description>Improper Inconsistent Interpretation of
HTTP Requests ('HTTP Request Smuggling') in Delinea Inc. Cloud Suite and
Privileged Access Service.

If you're not using the latest Server Suite agents, this fix requires that you upgrade to Server Suite 2023.1 (agent 6.0.1) or later.  *  If you cannot upgrade to Release 2023.1 (agent version 6.0.1) or later, you can choose one of the following versions:

  *  Server Suite release 2023.0.5 (agent version 6.0.0-158)


  *  Server Suite release 2022.1.10 (agent version 5.9.1-337)</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12812 | Cloud Suite and Privilege Access Service – SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12812</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command
('SQL Injection') in Delinea Inc. Cloud Suite and Privileged Access Service.


Remediation: This issue is fixed in Cloud Suite: 25.1</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2676 | GoogTech sms-ssm API LoginInterceptor.java preHandle improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2676</link><description>A weakness has been identified in GoogTech sms-ssm up to e8534c766fd13f5f94c01dab475d75f286918a8d. Affected by this issue is the function preHandle of the file LoginInterceptor.java of the component API Interface. Executing a manipulation can lead to improper authorization. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. This product utilizes a rolling release system for continuous delivery, and as such, version information for affected or updated releases is not disclosed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25326 | ipPulse 1.92 - &amp;#x27;Enter Key&amp;#x27; Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25326</link><description>ipPulse 1.92 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows local attackers to crash the application by providing an oversized input in the Enter Key field. Attackers can generate a 256-byte buffer of repeated 'A' characters to trigger an application crash when pasting the malicious content.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25349 | scadaApp for iOS 1.1.4.0 - &amp;#x27;Servername&amp;#x27; Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25349</link><description>ScadaApp for iOS 1.1.4.0 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by inputting an oversized buffer in the Servername field. Attackers can paste a 257-character buffer during login to trigger an application crash on iOS devices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25350 | XMedia Recode 3.4.8.6 - &amp;#x27;.m3u&amp;#x27; Denial Of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25350</link><description>XMedia Recode 3.4.8.6 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by loading a specially crafted .m3u playlist file. Attackers can create a malicious .m3u file with an oversized buffer to trigger an application crash when the file is opened.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25351 | Centova Cast 3.2.11 - Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25351</link><description>Centova Cast 3.2.11 contains a file download vulnerability that allows authenticated attackers to retrieve arbitrary system files through the server.copyfile API endpoint. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability by supplying crafted parameters to download sensitive files like /etc/passwd using curl and wget requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25352 | Genivia Crystal Live HTTP Server 6.01 - &amp;#x27;Crystal Live HTTP Server&amp;#x27; Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25352</link><description>Crystal Live HTTP Server 6.01 contains a directory traversal vulnerability that allows remote attackers to access system files by manipulating URL path segments. Attackers can use multiple '../' sequences to navigate outside the web root and retrieve sensitive configuration files like Windows system files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25353 | Foscam Video Management System 1.1.4.9 - &amp;#x27;Username&amp;#x27; Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25353</link><description>Foscam Video Management System 1.1.4.9 contains a denial of service vulnerability in the username input field that allows attackers to crash the application. Attackers can overwrite the username with a 520-byte buffer of repeated 'A' characters to trigger an application crash during device login.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25354 | iSmartViewPro 1.3.34 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25354</link><description>iSmartViewPro 1.3.34 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by overflowing the camera ID input field. Attackers can paste a 257-character buffer into the camera DID and password fields to trigger an application crash on iOS devices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25355 | Genivia gSOAP 2.8 - &amp;#x27;gSOAP&amp;#x27; Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25355</link><description>gSOAP 2.8 contains a directory traversal vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to access system files by manipulating HTTP path traversal techniques. Attackers can retrieve sensitive files like /etc/passwd by sending crafted GET requests with multiple '../' directory traversal sequences.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25356 | Bematech Printer MP-4200 TH Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25356</link><description>Bematech (formerly Logic Controls, now Elgin) MP-4200 TH printer contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the admin configuration page. Attackers can inject malicious scripts via crafted POST requests with malformed 'admin' and 'person' parameters, allowing execution of arbitrary JavaScript in the context of an authenticated user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25357 | Control Center PRO 6.2.9 - Local Stack Based BufferOverflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25357</link><description>Control Center PRO 6.2.9 contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the user creation module's username field that allows attackers to overwrite Structured Exception Handler (SEH). Attackers can craft a malicious payload exceeding 664 bytes to inject shellcode and potentially execute arbitrary code on vulnerable Windows systems.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25358 | FileOptimizer 14.00.2524 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25358</link><description>FileOptimizer 14.00.2524 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by manipulating the FileOptimizer32.ini configuration file. Attackers can overwrite the TempDirectory parameter with a 5000-character buffer to cause the application to crash when opening options.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25359 | SD.NET RIM 4.7.3c - &amp;#x27;idtyp&amp;#x27; SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25359</link><description>SD.NET RIM versions before 4.7.3c contain a SQL injection vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious SQL statements through POST parameters 'idtyp' and 'idgremium'. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by crafting specially formed POST requests to the /vorlagen/ endpoint, enabling unauthorized database manipulation and potential information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25360 | Aida64 6.10.5200 - Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25360</link><description>Aida64 Engineer 6.10.5200 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the CSV logging configuration that allows attackers to execute malicious code by crafting a specially designed payload. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability by creating a malformed log file with carefully constructed SEH (Structured Exception Handler) overwrite techniques to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25361 | Ayukov NFTP client 1.71 -  &amp;#x27;SYST&amp;#x27; Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25361</link><description>Ayukov NFTP client 1.71 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the SYST command handling that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code. Attackers can send a specially crafted SYST command with oversized payload to trigger a buffer overflow and execute a bind shell on port 5150.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25362 | WMV to AVI MPEG DVD WMV Convertor 4.6.1217 - Buffer OverFlow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25362</link><description>WMV to AVI MPEG DVD WMV Convertor 4.6.1217 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code by overwriting the license name and license code fields. Attackers can craft a malicious payload of 6000 bytes to trigger a bind shell on port 4444 by exploiting a stack-based buffer overflow in the application's input handling.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25363 | WMV to AVI MPEG DVD WMV Convertor 4.6.1217 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25363</link><description>WMV to AVI MPEG DVD WMV Convertor 4.6.1217 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by providing an oversized license input. Attackers can generate a 6000-byte payload and paste it into the 'License Name and License Code' field to trigger an application crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25364 | Win10 MailCarrier 2.51 - &amp;#x27;POP3 User&amp;#x27; Remote Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25364</link><description>MailCarrier 2.51 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the POP3 USER command that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code. Attackers can send a crafted oversized buffer to the POP3 service, overwriting memory and potentially gaining remote system access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25365 | ChaosPro 2.0 - Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25365</link><description>ChaosPro 2.0 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the configuration file path handling that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code by overwriting the Structured Exception Handler. Attackers can craft a malicious configuration file with carefully constructed payload to overwrite memory and gain remote code execution on vulnerable Windows XP systems.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25401 | Bematech Printer MP-4200 TH Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25401</link><description>Bematech (formerly Logic Controls, now Elgin) MP-4200 TH printer contains a denial of service vulnerability in the admin configuration page. Remote attackers can send crafted POST requests with malformed 'admin' and 'person' parameters to crash the printer's web service, causing a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2648 | Heap buffer overflow in PDFium in Google Chrome prior to 145.0.7632.109 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memory write v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2648</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in PDFium in Google Chrome prior to 145.0.7632.109 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memory write via a crafted PDF file. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2649 | Integer overflow in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 145.0.7632.109 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2649</link><description>Integer overflow in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 145.0.7632.109 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2650 | Heap buffer overflow in Media in Google Chrome prior to 145.0.7632.109 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2650</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in Media in Google Chrome prior to 145.0.7632.109 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2672 | Tsinghua Unigroup Electronic Archives System downLoad download path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2672</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tsinghua Unigroup Electronic Archives System 3.2.210802(62532). Affected by this vulnerability is the function Download of the file /Search/Subject/downLoad. Performing a manipulation of the argument path results in path traversal. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 22:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25396 | IPFire 2.21 Core Update 127 Reflected XSS via updatexlrator.cgi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25396</link><description>IPFire 2.21 Core Update 127 contains a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in the updatexlrator.cgi script that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts through POST parameters. Attackers can submit crafted requests with script payloads in the MAX_DISK_USAGE or MAX_DOWNLOAD_RATE parameters to execute arbitrary JavaScript in users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:48:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25397 | IPFire 2.21 Core Update 127 Cross-Site Scripting via hosts.cgi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25397</link><description>IPFire 2.21 Core Update 127 contains multiple reflected cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in the hosts.cgi script that allow attackers to inject malicious scripts through unvalidated parameters. Attackers can submit POST requests with script payloads in the KEY1, IP, HOST, or DOM parameters to execute arbitrary JavaScript in users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:48:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25398 | IPFire 2.21 Core Update 127 Cross-Site Scripting via ovpnmain.cgi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25398</link><description>IPFire 2.21 Core Update 127 contains multiple cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in the ovpnmain.cgi script that allow attackers to inject malicious scripts through VPN configuration parameters. Attackers can submit POST requests with script payloads in parameters like VPN_IP, DMTU, ccdname, ccdsubnet, DOVPN_SUBNET, DHCP_DOMAIN, DHCP_DNS, DHCP_WINS, ROUTES_PUSH, FRAGMENT, KEEPALIVE_1, and KEEPALIVE_2 to execute arbitrary JavaScript in administrator browsers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:48:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25399 | IPFire 2.21 Core Update 127 Stored XSS via extrahd.cgi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25399</link><description>IPFire 2.21 Core Update 127 contains multiple stored cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in the extrahd.cgi script that allow attackers to inject malicious scripts through the FS, PATH, and UUID parameters. Attackers can submit POST requests with script payloads in these parameters to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of authenticated administrator sessions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25400 | IPFire 2.21 Core Update 127 Multiple XSS via fwhosts.cgi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25400</link><description>IPFire 2.21 Core Update 127 contains multiple reflected cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in the fwhosts.cgi script that allow attackers to inject malicious scripts through multiple parameters including HOSTNAME, IP, SUBNET, NETREMARK, HOSTREMARK, newhost, grp_name, remark, SRV_NAME, SRV_PORT, SRVGRP_NAME, SRVGRP_REMARK, and updatesrvgrp. Attackers can submit POST requests with script payloads in these parameters to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of authenticated users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24743 | InvoicePlane has a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24743</link><description>InvoicePlane is a self-hosted open source application for managing invoices, clients, and payments. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability occurs in the upload Invoice Logo functions of InvoicePlane version 1.7.0. The Upload Invoice Logo function allows the application to upload svg files. Although administrator privileges are required to exploit it, this is still considered a critical vulnerability as it can cause actions such as unauthorized modification of application data, creation of persistent backdoors through stored malicious scripts, and full compromise of the application's integrity. Version 1.7.1 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24744 | InvoicePlane has a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24744</link><description>InvoicePlane is a self-hosted open source application for managing invoices, clients, and payments. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability occurs in the Edit Invoices functions of InvoicePlane version 1.7.0. When editing invoices, the application does not validate user input at the `invoice_number` parameter. Although administrator privileges are required to exploit it, this is still considered a critical vulnerability as it can cause actions such as unauthorized modification of application data, creation of persistent backdoors through stored malicious scripts, and full compromise of the application's integrity. Version 1.7.1 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27174 | MajorDoMo Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution via Admin Console Eval</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27174</link><description>MajorDoMo (aka Major Domestic Module) allows unauthenticated remote code execution via the admin panel's PHP console feature. An include order bug in modules/panel.class.php causes execution to continue past a redirect() call that lacks an exit statement, allowing unauthenticated requests to reach the ajax handler in inc_panel_ajax.php. The console handler within that file passes user-supplied input from GET parameters (via register_globals) directly to eval() without any authentication check. An attacker can execute arbitrary PHP code by sending a crafted GET request to /admin.php with ajax_panel, op, and command parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27175 | MajorDoMo Command Injection in rc/index.php via Race Condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27175</link><description>MajorDoMo (aka Major Domestic Module) is vulnerable to unauthenticated OS command injection via rc/index.php. The $param variable from user input is interpolated into a command string within double quotes without sanitization via escapeshellarg(). The command is inserted into a database queue by safe_exec(), which performs no sanitization. The cycle_execs.php script, which is web-accessible without authentication, retrieves queued commands and passes them directly to exec(). An attacker can exploit a race condition by first triggering cycle_execs.php (which purges the queue and enters a polling loop), then injecting a malicious command via the rc endpoint while the worker is polling. The injected shell metacharacters expand inside double quotes, achieving remote code execution within one second.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27176 | MajorDoMo Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in command.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27176</link><description>MajorDoMo (aka Major Domestic Module) contains a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in command.php. The $qry parameter is rendered directly into the HTML page without sanitization via htmlspecialchars(), both in an input field value attribute and in a paragraph element. An attacker can inject arbitrary JavaScript by crafting a URL with malicious content in the qry parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27177 | MajorDoMo Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Property Set Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27177</link><description>MajorDoMo (aka Major Domestic Module) contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the /objects/?op=set endpoint, which is intentionally unauthenticated for IoT device integration. User-supplied property values are stored raw in the database without sanitization. When an administrator views the property editor in the admin panel, the stored values are rendered without escaping in both a paragraph tag (SOURCE field) and a textarea element (VALUE field). The XSS fires on page load without requiring any click from the admin. Additionally, the session cookie lacks the HttpOnly flag, enabling session hijack via document.cookie exfiltration. An attacker can enumerate properties via the unauthenticated /api.php/data/ endpoint and poison any property with malicious JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27178 | MajorDoMo Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Method Parameters to Shoutbox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27178</link><description>MajorDoMo (aka Major Domestic Module) contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through method parameter injection into the shoutbox. The /objects/?method= endpoint allows unauthenticated execution of stored methods with attacker-controlled parameters. Default methods such as ThisComputer.VolumeLevelChanged pass the user-supplied VALUE parameter directly into the say() function, which stores the message raw in the shouts database table without escaping. The shoutbox widget renders stored messages without sanitization in both PHP rendering code and HTML templates. Because the dashboard widget auto-refreshes every 3 seconds, the injected script executes automatically when any administrator loads the dashboard, enabling session hijack through cookie exfiltration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27179 | MajorDoMo Unauthenticated SQL Injection in Commands Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27179</link><description>MajorDoMo (aka Major Domestic Module) contains an unauthenticated SQL injection vulnerability in the commands module. The commands_search.inc.php file directly interpolates the $_GET['parent'] parameter into multiple SQL queries without sanitization or parameterized queries. The commands module is loadable without authentication via the /objects/?module=commands endpoint, which includes arbitrary modules by name and calls their usual() method. Time-based blind SQL injection is exploitable using UNION SELECT SLEEP() syntax. Because MajorDoMo stores admin passwords as unsalted MD5 hashes in the users table, successful exploitation enables extraction of credentials and subsequent admin panel access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27180 | MajorDoMo Supply Chain Remote Code Execution via Update URL Poisoning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27180</link><description>MajorDoMo (aka Major Domestic Module) is vulnerable to unauthenticated remote code execution through supply chain compromise via update URL poisoning. The saverestore module exposes its admin() method through the /objects/?module=saverestore endpoint without authentication because it uses gr('mode') (which reads directly from $_REQUEST) instead of the framework's $this-&gt;mode. An attacker can poison the system update URL via the auto_update_settings mode handler, then trigger the force_update handler to initiate the update chain. The autoUpdateSystem() method fetches an Atom feed from the attacker-controlled URL with trivial validation, downloads a tarball via curl with TLS verification disabled (CURLOPT_SSL_VERIFYPEER set to FALSE), extracts it using exec('tar xzvf ...'), and copies all extracted files to the document root using copyTree(). This allows an attacker to deploy arbitrary PHP files, including webshells, to the webroot with two GET requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27181 | MajorDoMo Unauthenticated Module Uninstall via Market Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27181</link><description>MajorDoMo (aka Major Domestic Module) allows unauthenticated arbitrary module uninstallation through the market module. The market module's admin() method reads gr('mode') from $_REQUEST and assigns it to $this-&gt;mode at the start of execution, making all mode-gated code paths reachable without authentication via the /objects/?module=market endpoint. The uninstall mode handler calls uninstallPlugin(), which deletes module records from the database, executes the module's uninstall() method via eval(), recursively deletes the module's directory and template files using removeTree(), and removes associated cycle scripts. An attacker can iterate through module names and wipe the entire MajorDoMo installation with a series of unauthenticated GET requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27182 | Saturn Remote Mouse Server UDP Command Injection RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27182</link><description>Saturn Remote Mouse Server contains a command injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands by sending specially crafted UDP JSON frames to port 27000. Attackers on the local network can send malformed packets with unsanitized command data that the service forwards directly to OS execution functions, enabling remote code execution under the service account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2669 | Rongzhitong Visual Integrated Command and Dispatch Platform User delete access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2669</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Rongzhitong Visual Integrated Command and Dispatch Platform up to 20260206. This impacts an unknown function of the file /dm/dispatch/user/delete of the component User Handler. This manipulation of the argument ID causes improper access controls. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2670 | Advantech WISE-6610 Background Management openvpn_apply os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2670</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Advantech WISE-6610 1.2.1_20251110. Affected is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/luci/admin/openvpn_apply of the component Background Management. Such manipulation of the argument delete_file leads to os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14876 | Qemu-kvm: unbounded allocation in virtio-crypto</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14876</link><description>A flaw was found in the virtio-crypto device of QEMU. A malicious guest operating system can exploit a missing length limit in the AKCIPHER path, leading to uncontrolled memory allocation. This can result in a denial of service (DoS) on the host system by causing the QEMU process to terminate unexpectedly.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8860 | Qemu-kvm: uefi-vars: information disclosure vulnerability in uefi_vars_write callback</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8860</link><description>A flaw was found in QEMU in the uefi-vars virtual device. When the guest writes to register UEFI_VARS_REG_BUFFER_SIZE, the .write callback `uefi_vars_write` is invoked. The function allocates a heap buffer without zeroing the memory, leaving the buffer filled with residual data from prior allocations. When the guest later reads from register UEFI_VARS_REG_PIO_BUFFER_TRANSFER, the .read callback `uefi_vars_read` returns leftover metadata or other sensitive process memory from the previously allocated buffer, leading to an information disclosure vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0665 | Qemu-kvm: heap off-by-one in kvm xen physdevop_map_pirq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0665</link><description>An off-by-one error was found in QEMU's KVM Xen guest support. A malicious guest could use this flaw to trigger out-of-bounds heap accesses in the QEMU process via the emulated Xen physdev hypercall interface, leading to a denial of service or potential memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1355 | Missing Authorization Check in GitHub Enterprise Server Allows Unauthorized Uploads to Repository Migration Exports</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1355</link><description>A Missing Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to upload unauthorized content to another user’s repository migration export due to a missing authorization check in the repository migration upload endpoint. By supplying the migration identifier, an attacker could overwrite or replace a victim’s migration archive, potentially causing victims to download attacker-controlled repository data during migration restores or automated imports. An attacker would require authentication to the victim's GitHub Enterprise Server instance. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.20 and was fixed in versions 3.19.2, 3.18.5, 3.17.11, 3.16.14, 3.15.18, 3.14.23. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1999 | Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed unauthorized merging of pull requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1999</link><description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to merge their own pull request into a repository without having push access by exploiting an authorization bypass in the enable_auto_merge mutation for pull requests. This issue only affected repositories that allow forking as the attack relies on opening a pull request from an attacker-controlled fork into the target repository. Exploitation was only possible in specific scenarios. It required a clean pull request status and only applied to branches without branch protection rules enabled. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server versions prior to 3.19.2, 3.18.5, and 3.17.11, and was fixed in versions 3.19.2, 3.18.5, and 3.17.11. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24746 | InvoicePlane has a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24746</link><description>InvoicePlane is a self-hosted open source application for managing invoices, clients, and payments. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability occurs in the Edit Quotes functions of InvoicePlane version 1.7.0. Although administrator privileges are required to exploit it, this is still considered a critical vulnerability as it can cause actions such as unauthorized modification of application data, creation of persistent backdoors through stored malicious scripts, and full compromise of the application's integrity. Version 1.7.1 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0577 | Glibc: vdso getrandom acceleration may return predictable randomness</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0577</link><description>An insufficient entropy vulnerability was found in glibc. The getrandom and arc4random family of functions may return predictable randomness if these functions are called again after the fork, which happens concurrently with a call to any of these functions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10256 | Ffmpeg: null pointer dereference in firequalizer filter (libavfilter/af_firequalizer.c)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10256</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability exists in FFmpeg’s Firequalizer filter (libavfilter/af_firequalizer.c) due to a missing check on the return value of av_malloc_array() in the config_input() function. An attacker could exploit this by tricking a victim into processing a crafted media file with the Firequalizer filter enabled, causing the application to dereference a NULL pointer and crash, leading to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12343 | Ffmpeg: double-free vulnerability in ffmpeg tensorflow dnn backend</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12343</link><description>A flaw was found in FFmpeg’s TensorFlow backend within the libavfilter/dnn_backend_tf.c source file. The issue occurs in the dnn_execute_model_tf() function, where a task object is freed multiple times in certain error-handling paths. This redundant memory deallocation can lead to a double-free condition, potentially causing FFmpeg or any application using it to crash when processing TensorFlow-based DNN models. This results in a denial-of-service scenario but does not allow arbitrary code execution under normal conditions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1272 | Kernel: secure boot does not automatically enable kernel lockdown</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1272</link><description>The Linux Kernel lockdown mode for kernel versions starting on 6.12 and above for Fedora Linux has the lockdown mode disabled without any warning. This may allow an attacker to gain access to sensitive information such kernel memory mappings, I/O ports, BPF and kprobes. Additionally unsigned modules can be loaded, leading to execution of untrusted code breaking breaking any Secure Boot protection. This vulnerability affects only Fedora Linux.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0573 | Improper Handling of HTTP Redirects vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed leaking of authorization token and enabled remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0573</link><description>An URL redirection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed attacker-controlled redirects to leak sensitive authorization tokens. The repository_pages API insecurely followed HTTP redirects when fetching artifact URLs, preserving the authorization header containing a privileged JWT. An authenticated user could redirect these requests to an attacker-controlled domain, exfiltrate the Actions.ManageOrgs JWT, and leverage it for potential remote code execution. Attackers would require access to the target GitHub Enterprise Server instance and the ability to exploit a legacy redirect to an attacker-controlled domain. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.19 and was fixed in versions 3.19.2, 3.18.4, 3.17.10, 3.16.13, 3.15.17, and 3.14.22. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2667 | Rongzhitong Visual Integrated Command and Dispatch Platform api access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2667</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Rongzhitong Visual Integrated Command and Dispatch Platform up to 20260206. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /dispatch/api?cmd=userinfo. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2668 | Rongzhitong Visual Integrated Command and Dispatch Platform User add access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2668</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Rongzhitong Visual Integrated Command and Dispatch Platform up to 20260206. This affects an unknown function of the file /dm/dispatch/user/add of the component User Handler. The manipulation results in improper access controls. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1200 | Live555: live555: remote code execution via segmentation fault in increasebufferto function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1200</link><description>A flaw was found in the rgaufman/live555 fork of live555. A remote attacker could exploit a segmentation fault, in the `increaseBufferTo` function. This vulnerability can lead to memory corruption problems and potentially other consequences.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2665 | huanzi-qch base-admin JSP Parser SysFileController.java upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2665</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in huanzi-qch base-admin up to 57a8126bb3353a004f3c7722089e3b926ea83596. Impacted is the function Upload of the file SysFileController.java of the component JSP Parser. Performing a manipulation of the argument File results in unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2666 | mingSoft MCMS Template Archive uploadTemplate.do unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2666</link><description>A flaw has been found in mingSoft MCMS 6.1.1. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /ms/file/uploadTemplate.do of the component Template Archive Handler. Executing a manipulation of the argument File can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0874 | CATPART File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0874</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPART file, when parsed through certain Autodesk products, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability. A malicious actor may leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, cause data corruption, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0875 | MODEL File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0875</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed through certain Autodesk products, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability. A malicious actor may leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, cause data corruption, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23491 | InvoicePlane has Unauthenticated Path Traversal in Guest Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23491</link><description>InvoicePlane is a self-hosted open source application for managing invoices, clients, and payments. a path traversal vulnerability exists in the `get_file` method of the `Guest` module's `Get` controller in InvoicePlane up to and including through 1.6.3. The vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files on the server by manipulating the input filename. This leads to the disclosure of sensitive information, including configuration files with database credentials. Version 1.6.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2662 | FascinatedBox lily lily_emitter.c count_transforms out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2662</link><description>A weakness has been identified in FascinatedBox lily up to 2.3. This vulnerability affects the function count_transforms of the file src/lily_emitter.c. This manipulation causes out-of-bounds read. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2663 | Alixhan xh-admin-backend Database Query query sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2663</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Alixhan xh-admin-backend up to 1.7.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /frontend-api/system-service/api/system/role/query of the component Database Query Handler. Such manipulation of the argument prop leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71225 | md: suspend array while updating raid_disks via sysfs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71225</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

md: suspend array while updating raid_disks via sysfs

In raid1_reshape(), freeze_array() is called before modifying the r1bio
memory pool (conf-&gt;r1bio_pool) and conf-&gt;raid_disks, and
unfreeze_array() is called after the update is completed.

However, freeze_array() only waits until nr_sync_pending and
(nr_pending - nr_queued) of all buckets reaches zero. When an I/O error
occurs, nr_queued is increased and the corresponding r1bio is queued to
either retry_list or bio_end_io_list. As a result, freeze_array() may
unblock before these r1bios are released.

This can lead to a situation where conf-&gt;raid_disks and the mempool have
already been updated while queued r1bios, allocated with the old
raid_disks value, are later released. Consequently, free_r1bio() may
access memory out of bounds in put_all_bios() and release r1bios of the
wrong size to the new mempool, potentially causing issues with the
mempool as well.

Since only normal I/O might increase nr_queued while an I/O error occurs,
suspending the array avoids this issue.

Note: Updating raid_disks via ioctl SET_ARRAY_INFO already suspends
the array. Therefore, we suspend the array when updating raid_disks
via sysfs to avoid this issue too.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71226 | wifi: iwlwifi: Implement settime64 as stub for MVM/MLD PTP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71226</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: iwlwifi: Implement settime64 as stub for MVM/MLD PTP

Since commit dfb073d32cac ("ptp: Return -EINVAL on ptp_clock_register if
required ops are NULL"), PTP clock registered through ptp_clock_register
is required to have ptp_clock_info.settime64 set, however, neither MVM
nor MLD's PTP clock implementation sets it, resulting in warnings when
the interface starts up, like

WARNING: drivers/ptp/ptp_clock.c:325 at ptp_clock_register+0x2c8/0x6b8, CPU#1: wpa_supplicant/469
CPU: 1 UID: 0 PID: 469 Comm: wpa_supplicant Not tainted 6.18.0+ #101 PREEMPT(full)
ra: ffff800002732cd4 iwl_mvm_ptp_init+0x114/0x188 [iwlmvm]
ERA: 9000000002fdc468 ptp_clock_register+0x2c8/0x6b8
iwlwifi 0000:01:00.0: Failed to register PHC clock (-22)

I don't find an appropriate firmware interface to implement settime64()
for iwlwifi MLD/MVM, thus instead create a stub that returns
-EOPTNOTSUPP only, suppressing the warning and allowing the PTP clock to
be registered.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71227 | wifi: mac80211: don&amp;#x27;t WARN for connections on invalid channels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71227</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: mac80211: don't WARN for connections on invalid channels

It's not clear (to me) how exactly syzbot managed to hit this,
but it seems conceivable that e.g. regulatory changed and has
disabled a channel between scanning (channel is checked to be
usable by cfg80211_get_ies_channel_number) and connecting on
the channel later.

With one scenario that isn't covered elsewhere described above,
the warning isn't good, replace it with a (more informative)
error message.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71228 | LoongArch: Set correct protection_map[] for VM_NONE/VM_SHARED</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71228</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

LoongArch: Set correct protection_map[] for VM_NONE/VM_SHARED

For 32BIT platform _PAGE_PROTNONE is 0, so set a VMA to be VM_NONE or
VM_SHARED will make pages non-present, then cause Oops with kernel page
fault.

Fix it by set correct protection_map[] for VM_NONE/VM_SHARED, replacing
_PAGE_PROTNONE with _PAGE_PRESENT.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1404 | Ultimate Member &amp;lt;= 2.11.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via Filter Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1404</link><description>The Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the filter parameters (e.g., 'filter_first_name') in all versions up to, and including, 2.11.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1426 | Advanced AJAX Product Filters &amp;lt;= 3.1.9.6 - Authenticated (Author+) PHP Object Injection via Live Composer Compatibility</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1426</link><description>The Advanced AJAX Product Filters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.9.6 via deserialization of untrusted input in the shortcode_check function within the Live Composer compatibility layer. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present. Note: This vulnerability requires the Live Composer plugin to also be installed and active.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23211 | mm, swap: restore swap_space attr aviod kernel panic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23211</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm, swap: restore swap_space attr aviod kernel panic

commit 8b47299a411a ("mm, swap: mark swap address space ro and add context
debug check") made the swap address space read-only.  It may lead to
kernel panic if arch_prepare_to_swap returns a failure under heavy memory
pressure as follows,

el1_abort+0x40/0x64
el1h_64_sync_handler+0x48/0xcc
el1h_64_sync+0x84/0x88
errseq_set+0x4c/0xb8 (P)
__filemap_set_wb_err+0x20/0xd0
shrink_folio_list+0xc20/0x11cc
evict_folios+0x1520/0x1be4
try_to_shrink_lruvec+0x27c/0x3dc
shrink_one+0x9c/0x228
shrink_node+0xb3c/0xeac
do_try_to_free_pages+0x170/0x4f0
try_to_free_pages+0x334/0x534
__alloc_pages_direct_reclaim+0x90/0x158
__alloc_pages_slowpath+0x334/0x588
__alloc_frozen_pages_noprof+0x224/0x2fc
__folio_alloc_noprof+0x14/0x64
vma_alloc_zeroed_movable_folio+0x34/0x44
do_pte_missing+0xad4/0x1040
handle_mm_fault+0x4a4/0x790
do_page_fault+0x288/0x5f8
do_translation_fault+0x38/0x54
do_mem_abort+0x54/0xa8

Restore swap address space as not ro to avoid the panic.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23212 | bonding: annotate data-races around slave-&amp;gt;last_rx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23212</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bonding: annotate data-races around slave-&gt;last_rx

slave-&gt;last_rx and slave-&gt;target_last_arp_rx[...] can be read and written
locklessly. Add READ_ONCE() and WRITE_ONCE() annotations.

syzbot reported:

BUG: KCSAN: data-race in bond_rcv_validate / bond_rcv_validate

write to 0xffff888149f0d428 of 8 bytes by interrupt on cpu 1:
  bond_rcv_validate+0x202/0x7a0 drivers/net/bonding/bond_main.c:3335
  bond_handle_frame+0xde/0x5e0 drivers/net/bonding/bond_main.c:1533
  __netif_receive_skb_core+0x5b1/0x1950 net/core/dev.c:6039
  __netif_receive_skb_one_core net/core/dev.c:6150 [inline]
  __netif_receive_skb+0x59/0x270 net/core/dev.c:6265
  netif_receive_skb_internal net/core/dev.c:6351 [inline]
  netif_receive_skb+0x4b/0x2d0 net/core/dev.c:6410
...

write to 0xffff888149f0d428 of 8 bytes by interrupt on cpu 0:
  bond_rcv_validate+0x202/0x7a0 drivers/net/bonding/bond_main.c:3335
  bond_handle_frame+0xde/0x5e0 drivers/net/bonding/bond_main.c:1533
  __netif_receive_skb_core+0x5b1/0x1950 net/core/dev.c:6039
  __netif_receive_skb_one_core net/core/dev.c:6150 [inline]
  __netif_receive_skb+0x59/0x270 net/core/dev.c:6265
  netif_receive_skb_internal net/core/dev.c:6351 [inline]
  netif_receive_skb+0x4b/0x2d0 net/core/dev.c:6410
  br_netif_receive_skb net/bridge/br_input.c:30 [inline]
  NF_HOOK include/linux/netfilter.h:318 [inline]
...

value changed: 0x0000000100005365 -&gt; 0x0000000100005366</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23213 | drm/amd/pm: Disable MMIO access during SMU Mode 1 reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23213</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/pm: Disable MMIO access during SMU Mode 1 reset

During Mode 1 reset, the ASIC undergoes a reset cycle and becomes
temporarily inaccessible via PCIe. Any attempt to access MMIO registers
during this window (e.g., from interrupt handlers or other driver threads)
can result in uncompleted PCIe transactions, leading to NMI panics or
system hangs.

To prevent this, set the `no_hw_access` flag to true immediately after
triggering the reset. This signals other driver components to skip
register accesses while the device is offline.

A memory barrier `smp_mb()` is added to ensure the flag update is
globally visible to all cores before the driver enters the sleep/wait
state.

(cherry picked from commit 7edb503fe4b6d67f47d8bb0dfafb8e699bb0f8a4)</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23214 | btrfs: reject new transactions if the fs is fully read-only</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23214</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: reject new transactions if the fs is fully read-only

[BUG]
There is a bug report where a heavily fuzzed fs is mounted with all
rescue mount options, which leads to the following warnings during
unmount:

  BTRFS: Transaction aborted (error -22)
  Modules linked in:
  CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 9758 Comm: repro.out Not tainted
  6.19.0-rc5-00002-gb71e635feefc #7 PREEMPT(full)
  Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.15.0-1 04/01/2014
  RIP: 0010:find_free_extent_update_loop fs/btrfs/extent-tree.c:4208 [inline]
  RIP: 0010:find_free_extent+0x52f0/0x5d20 fs/btrfs/extent-tree.c:4611
  Call Trace:
   
   btrfs_reserve_extent+0x2cd/0x790 fs/btrfs/extent-tree.c:4705
   btrfs_alloc_tree_block+0x1e1/0x10e0 fs/btrfs/extent-tree.c:5157
   btrfs_force_cow_block+0x578/0x2410 fs/btrfs/ctree.c:517
   btrfs_cow_block+0x3c4/0xa80 fs/btrfs/ctree.c:708
   btrfs_search_slot+0xcad/0x2b50 fs/btrfs/ctree.c:2130
   btrfs_truncate_inode_items+0x45d/0x2350 fs/btrfs/inode-item.c:499
   btrfs_evict_inode+0x923/0xe70 fs/btrfs/inode.c:5628
   evict+0x5f4/0xae0 fs/inode.c:837
   __dentry_kill+0x209/0x660 fs/dcache.c:670
   finish_dput+0xc9/0x480 fs/dcache.c:879
   shrink_dcache_for_umount+0xa0/0x170 fs/dcache.c:1661
   generic_shutdown_super+0x67/0x2c0 fs/super.c:621
   kill_anon_super+0x3b/0x70 fs/super.c:1289
   btrfs_kill_super+0x41/0x50 fs/btrfs/super.c:2127
   deactivate_locked_super+0xbc/0x130 fs/super.c:474
   cleanup_mnt+0x425/0x4c0 fs/namespace.c:1318
   task_work_run+0x1d4/0x260 kernel/task_work.c:233
   exit_task_work include/linux/task_work.h:40 [inline]
   do_exit+0x694/0x22f0 kernel/exit.c:971
   do_group_exit+0x21c/0x2d0 kernel/exit.c:1112
   __do_sys_exit_group kernel/exit.c:1123 [inline]
   __se_sys_exit_group kernel/exit.c:1121 [inline]
   __x64_sys_exit_group+0x3f/0x40 kernel/exit.c:1121
   x64_sys_call+0x2210/0x2210 arch/x86/include/generated/asm/syscalls_64.h:232
   do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 [inline]
   do_syscall_64+0xe8/0xf80 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:94
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f
  RIP: 0033:0x44f639
  Code: Unable to access opcode bytes at 0x44f60f.
  RSP: 002b:00007ffc15c4e088 EFLAGS: 00000246 ORIG_RAX: 00000000000000e7
  RAX: ffffffffffffffda RBX: 00000000004c32f0 RCX: 000000000044f639
  RDX: 000000000000003c RSI: 00000000000000e7 RDI: 0000000000000001
  RBP: 0000000000000001 R08: ffffffffffffffc0 R09: 0000000000000000
  R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000246 R12: 00000000004c32f0
  R13: 0000000000000001 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: 0000000000000001
   

Since rescue mount options will mark the full fs read-only, there should
be no new transaction triggered.

But during unmount we will evict all inodes, which can trigger a new
transaction, and triggers warnings on a heavily corrupted fs.

[CAUSE]
Btrfs allows new transaction even on a read-only fs, this is to allow
log replay happen even on read-only mounts, just like what ext4/xfs do.

However with rescue mount options, the fs is fully read-only and cannot
be remounted read-write, thus in that case we should also reject any new
transactions.

[FIX]
If we find the fs has rescue mount options, we should treat the fs as
error, so that no new transaction can be started.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23215 | x86/vmware: Fix hypercall clobbers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23215</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/vmware: Fix hypercall clobbers

Fedora QA reported the following panic:

  BUG: unable to handle page fault for address: 0000000040003e54
  #PF: supervisor write access in kernel mode
  #PF: error_code(0x0002) - not-present page
  Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS edk2-20251119-3.fc43 11/19/2025
  RIP: 0010:vmware_hypercall4.constprop.0+0x52/0x90
  ..
  Call Trace:
   vmmouse_report_events+0x13e/0x1b0
   psmouse_handle_byte+0x15/0x60
   ps2_interrupt+0x8a/0xd0
   ...

because the QEMU VMware mouse emulation is buggy, and clears the top 32
bits of %rdi that the kernel kept a pointer in.

The QEMU vmmouse driver saves and restores the register state in a
"uint32_t data[6];" and as a result restores the state with the high
bits all cleared.

RDI originally contained the value of a valid kernel stack address
(0xff5eeb3240003e54).  After the vmware hypercall it now contains
0x40003e54, and we get a page fault as a result when it is dereferenced.

The proper fix would be in QEMU, but this works around the issue in the
kernel to keep old setups working, when old kernels had not happened to
keep any state in %rdi over the hypercall.

In theory this same issue exists for all the hypercalls in the vmmouse
driver; in practice it has only been seen with vmware_hypercall3() and
vmware_hypercall4().  For now, just mark RDI/RSI as clobbered for those
two calls.  This should have a minimal effect on code generation overall
as it should be rare for the compiler to want to make RDI/RSI live
across hypercalls.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23216 | scsi: target: iscsi: Fix use-after-free in iscsit_dec_conn_usage_count()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23216</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

scsi: target: iscsi: Fix use-after-free in iscsit_dec_conn_usage_count()

In iscsit_dec_conn_usage_count(), the function calls complete() while
holding the conn-&gt;conn_usage_lock. As soon as complete() is invoked, the
waiter (such as iscsit_close_connection()) may wake up and proceed to free
the iscsit_conn structure.

If the waiter frees the memory before the current thread reaches
spin_unlock_bh(), it results in a KASAN slab-use-after-free as the function
attempts to release a lock within the already-freed connection structure.

Fix this by releasing the spinlock before calling complete().</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23217 | riscv: trace: fix snapshot deadlock with sbi ecall</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23217</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

riscv: trace: fix snapshot deadlock with sbi ecall

If sbi_ecall.c's functions are traceable,

echo "__sbi_ecall:snapshot" &gt; /sys/kernel/tracing/set_ftrace_filter

may get the kernel into a deadlock.

(Functions in sbi_ecall.c are excluded from tracing if
CONFIG_RISCV_ALTERNATIVE_EARLY is set.)

__sbi_ecall triggers a snapshot of the ringbuffer. The snapshot code
raises an IPI interrupt, which results in another call to __sbi_ecall
and another snapshot...

All it takes to get into this endless loop is one initial __sbi_ecall.
On RISC-V systems without SSTC extension, the clock events in
timer-riscv.c issue periodic sbi ecalls, making the problem easy to
trigger.

Always exclude the sbi_ecall.c functions from tracing to fix the
potential deadlock.

sbi ecalls can easiliy be logged via trace events, excluding ecall
functions from function tracing is not a big limitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23218 | gpio: loongson-64bit: Fix incorrect NULL check after devm_kcalloc()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23218</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

gpio: loongson-64bit: Fix incorrect NULL check after devm_kcalloc()

Fix incorrect NULL check in loongson_gpio_init_irqchip().
The function checks chip-&gt;parent instead of chip-&gt;irq.parents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23219 | mm/slab: Add alloc_tagging_slab_free_hook for memcg_alloc_abort_single</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23219</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/slab: Add alloc_tagging_slab_free_hook for memcg_alloc_abort_single

When CONFIG_MEM_ALLOC_PROFILING_DEBUG is enabled, the following warning
may be noticed:

[ 3959.023862] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[ 3959.023891] alloc_tag was not cleared (got tag for lib/xarray.c:378)
[ 3959.023947] WARNING: ./include/linux/alloc_tag.h:155 at alloc_tag_add+0x128/0x178, CPU#6: mkfs.ntfs/113998
[ 3959.023978] Modules linked in: dns_resolver tun brd overlay exfat btrfs blake2b libblake2b xor xor_neon raid6_pq loop sctp ip6_udp_tunnel udp_tunnel ext4 crc16 mbcache jbd2 rfkill sunrpc vfat fat sg fuse nfnetlink sr_mod virtio_gpu cdrom drm_client_lib virtio_dma_buf drm_shmem_helper drm_kms_helper ghash_ce drm sm4 backlight virtio_net net_failover virtio_scsi failover virtio_console virtio_blk virtio_mmio dm_mirror dm_region_hash dm_log dm_multipath dm_mod i2c_dev aes_neon_bs aes_ce_blk [last unloaded: hwpoison_inject]
[ 3959.024170] CPU: 6 UID: 0 PID: 113998 Comm: mkfs.ntfs Kdump: loaded Tainted: G        W           6.19.0-rc7+ #7 PREEMPT(voluntary)
[ 3959.024182] Tainted: [W]=WARN
[ 3959.024186] Hardware name: QEMU KVM Virtual Machine, BIOS unknown 2/2/2022
[ 3959.024192] pstate: 604000c5 (nZCv daIF +PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
[ 3959.024199] pc : alloc_tag_add+0x128/0x178
[ 3959.024207] lr : alloc_tag_add+0x128/0x178
[ 3959.024214] sp : ffff80008b696d60
[ 3959.024219] x29: ffff80008b696d60 x28: 0000000000000000 x27: 0000000000000240
[ 3959.024232] x26: 0000000000000000 x25: 0000000000000240 x24: ffff800085d17860
[ 3959.024245] x23: 0000000000402800 x22: ffff0000c0012dc0 x21: 00000000000002d0
[ 3959.024257] x20: ffff0000e6ef3318 x19: ffff800085ae0410 x18: 0000000000000000
[ 3959.024269] x17: 0000000000000000 x16: 0000000000000000 x15: 0000000000000000
[ 3959.024281] x14: 0000000000000000 x13: 0000000000000001 x12: ffff600064101293
[ 3959.024292] x11: 1fffe00064101292 x10: ffff600064101292 x9 : dfff800000000000
[ 3959.024305] x8 : 00009fff9befed6e x7 : ffff000320809493 x6 : 0000000000000001
[ 3959.024316] x5 : ffff000320809490 x4 : ffff600064101293 x3 : ffff800080691838
[ 3959.024328] x2 : 0000000000000000 x1 : 0000000000000000 x0 : ffff0000d5bcd640
[ 3959.024340] Call trace:
[ 3959.024346]  alloc_tag_add+0x128/0x178 (P)
[ 3959.024355]  __alloc_tagging_slab_alloc_hook+0x11c/0x1a8
[ 3959.024362]  kmem_cache_alloc_lru_noprof+0x1b8/0x5e8
[ 3959.024369]  xas_alloc+0x304/0x4f0
[ 3959.024381]  xas_create+0x1e0/0x4a0
[ 3959.024388]  xas_store+0x68/0xda8
[ 3959.024395]  __filemap_add_folio+0x5b0/0xbd8
[ 3959.024409]  filemap_add_folio+0x16c/0x7e0
[ 3959.024416]  __filemap_get_folio_mpol+0x2dc/0x9e8
[ 3959.024424]  iomap_get_folio+0xfc/0x180
[ 3959.024435]  __iomap_get_folio+0x2f8/0x4b8
[ 3959.024441]  iomap_write_begin+0x198/0xc18
[ 3959.024448]  iomap_write_iter+0x2ec/0x8f8
[ 3959.024454]  iomap_file_buffered_write+0x19c/0x290
[ 3959.024461]  blkdev_write_iter+0x38c/0x978
[ 3959.024470]  vfs_write+0x4d4/0x928
[ 3959.024482]  ksys_write+0xfc/0x1f8
[ 3959.024489]  __arm64_sys_write+0x74/0xb0
[ 3959.024496]  invoke_syscall+0xd4/0x258
[ 3959.024507]  el0_svc_common.constprop.0+0xb4/0x240
[ 3959.024514]  do_el0_svc+0x48/0x68
[ 3959.024520]  el0_svc+0x40/0xf8
[ 3959.024526]  el0t_64_sync_handler+0xa0/0xe8
[ 3959.024533]  el0t_64_sync+0x1ac/0x1b0
[ 3959.024540] ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---

When __memcg_slab_post_alloc_hook() fails, there are two different
free paths depending on whether size == 1 or size != 1. In the
kmem_cache_free_bulk() path, we do call alloc_tagging_slab_free_hook().
However, in memcg_alloc_abort_single() we don't, the above warning will be
triggered on the next allocation.

Therefore, add alloc_tagging_slab_free_hook() to the
memcg_alloc_abort_single() path.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27099 | Jenkins 2.483 through 2.550 (both inclusive), LTS 2.492.1 through 2.541.1 (both inclusive) does not escape the user-provided description of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27099</link><description>Jenkins 2.483 through 2.550 (both inclusive), LTS 2.492.1 through 2.541.1 (both inclusive) does not escape the user-provided description of the "Mark temporarily offline" offline cause, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exploitable by attackers with Agent/Configure or Agent/Disconnect permission.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27100 | Jenkins 2.550 and earlier, LTS 2.541.1 and earlier accepts Run Parameter values that refer to builds the user submitting the build does not ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27100</link><description>Jenkins 2.550 and earlier, LTS 2.541.1 and earlier accepts Run Parameter values that refer to builds the user submitting the build does not have access to, allowing attackers with Item/Build and Item/Configure permission to obtain information about the existence of jobs, the existence of builds, and if a specified build exists, its display name.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2329 | Grandstream GXP1600 VoIP Phones - Unauthenticated stack buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2329</link><description>An unauthenticated stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the HTTP API endpoint /cgi-bin/api.values.get. A remote attacker can leverage this vulnerability to achieve unauthenticated remote code execution (RCE) with root privileges on a target device. The vulnerability affects all six device models in the series: GXP1610, GXP1615, GXP1620, GXP1625, GXP1628, and GXP1630.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:06:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33236 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where malicious data created by an attacker could cause code injection. A successful exploit ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33236</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where malicious data created by an attacker could cause code injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33239 | NVIDIA Megatron Bridge contains a vulnerability in a data merging tutorial, where malicious input could cause a code injection. A successful...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33239</link><description>NVIDIA Megatron Bridge contains a vulnerability in a data merging tutorial, where malicious input could cause a code injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33240 | NVIDIA Megatron Bridge contains a vulnerability in a data shuffling tutorial, where malicious input could cause a code injection. A successf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33240</link><description>NVIDIA Megatron Bridge contains a vulnerability in a data shuffling tutorial, where malicious input could cause a code injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33241 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause remote code execution by loading a maliciously crafted file. A ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33241</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause remote code execution by loading a maliciously crafted file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33243 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause remote code execution in distributed environments. A successful...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33243</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause remote code execution in distributed environments. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33245 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where malicious data could cause remote code execution. A successful exploit of this vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33245</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where malicious data could cause remote code execution. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33246 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the ASR Evaluator utility, where a user could cause a command injection ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33246</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the ASR Evaluator utility, where a user could cause a command injection by supplying crafted input to a configuration parameter. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, data tampering, or information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33249 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in a voice-preprocessing script, where malicious input created by an attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33249</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in a voice-preprocessing script, where malicious input created by an attacker could cause a code injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33250 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause remote code execution. A successful exploit of this vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33250</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause remote code execution. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33251 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause remote code execution. A successful exploit of this vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33251</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause remote code execution. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33252 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause remote code execution. A successful exploit of this vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33252</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause remote code execution. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33253 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause remote code execution by convincing a user to load a maliciousl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33253</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause remote code execution by convincing a user to load a maliciously crafted file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60035 | A vulnerability has been identified in the OPC.Testclient utility, which is included in Rexroth IndraWorks. All versions prior to 15V24 are ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60035</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the OPC.Testclient utility, which is included in Rexroth IndraWorks. All versions prior to 15V24 are affected. This flaw allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the user's system by parsing a manipulated file containing malicious serialized data. Exploitation requires user interaction, specifically opening a specially crafted file, which then causes the application to deserialize the malicious data, enabling Remote Code Execution (RCE). This can lead to a complete compromise of the system running the OPC.Testclient.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60036 | A vulnerability has been identified in the UA.Testclient utility, which is included in Rexroth IndraWorks. All versions prior to 15V24 are a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60036</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the UA.Testclient utility, which is included in Rexroth IndraWorks. All versions prior to 15V24 are affected. This flaw allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the user's system by parsing a manipulated file containing malicious serialized data. Exploitation requires user interaction, specifically opening a specially crafted file, which then causes the application to deserialize the malicious data, enabling Remote Code Execution (RCE). This can lead to a complete compromise of the system running the UA.Testclient.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60037 | A vulnerability has been identified in Rexroth IndraWorks. This flaw allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the user's system by pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60037</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Rexroth IndraWorks. This flaw allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the user's system by parsing a manipulated file containing malicious serialized data. Exploitation requires user interaction, specifically opening a specially crafted file, which then causes the application to deserialize the malicious data, enabling Remote Code Execution (RCE). This can lead to a complete compromise of the system running Rexroth IndraWorks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60038 | A vulnerability has been identified in Rexroth IndraWorks. This flaw allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the user's system by pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60038</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Rexroth IndraWorks. This flaw allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the user's system by parsing a manipulated file containing malicious serialized data. Exploitation requires user interaction, specifically opening a specially crafted file, which then causes the application to deserialize the malicious data, enabling Remote Code Execution (RCE). This can lead to a complete compromise of the system running Rexroth IndraWorks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2464 | Directory Traversal in AMR Printer Management by AMR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2464</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability in the AMR Printer Management 1.01 Beta web service, which allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files from the underlying Windows system by using specially crafted path traversal sequences in requests directed to the web management service. The service is accessible without authentication and runs with elevated privileges, amplifying the impact of the vulnerability. An attacker can exploit this condition to access sensitive and privileged files on the system using path traversal payloads. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could lead to the unauthorized disclosure of internal system information, compromising the confidentiality of the affected environment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2655 | ChaiScript chaiscript_defines.hpp operator use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2655</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in ChaiScript up to 6.1.0. The impacted element is the function chaiscript::str_less::operator of the file include/chaiscript/chaiscript_defines.hpp. The manipulation results in use after free. The attack requires a local approach. The attack requires a high level of complexity. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14340 | Admin Account Takeover via malicious URL payload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14340</link><description>Cross-site scripting in REST Management Interface in Payara Server &lt;4.1.2.191.54, &lt;5.83.0, &lt;6.34.0, &lt;7.2026.1 allows an attacker to mislead the administrator to change the admin password via URL Payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59920 | SQL injection in time@work from systems@work</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59920</link><description>When hours are entered in time@work, version 7.0.5, it performs a query to display the projects assigned to the user. If the query URL is copied and opened in a new browser window, the ‘IDClient’ parameter is vulnerable to a blind authenticated SQL injection. If the request is made with the TWAdmin user with the sysadmin role enabled, exploiting the vulnerability will allow commands to be executed on the system; if the user does not belong to the sysadmin role, they will still be able to query data from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8308 | Reflected XSS in Key Software&amp;#x27;s INFOREX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8308</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Key Software Solutions Inc. INFOREX- General Information Management System allows XSS Through HTTP Headers.This issue affects INFOREX- General Information Management System: from 2025 and before through 18022026.

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1435 | Incorrect management of session invalidation vulnerability in Graylog Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1435</link><description>Not properly invalidated session vulnerability in Graylog Web Interface, version 2.2.3, due to incorrect management of session invalidation after new logins. The application generates a new 'sessionId' each time a user authenticates, but does not invalidate previously issued session identifiers, which remain valid even after multiple consecutive logins by the same user. As a result, a stolen or leaked 'sessionId' can continue to be used to authenticate valid requests. Exploiting this vulnerability would allow an attacker with access to the web service/API network (port 9000 or HTTP/S endpoint of the server) to reuse an old session token to gain unauthorized access to the application, interact with the API/web, and compromise the integrity of the affected account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1436 | Improper Access Control (IDOR) vulnerability in Graylog Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1436</link><description>Improper Access Control (IDOR) in the Graylog API, version 2.2.3, which occurs when modifying the user ID in the URL. An authenticated user can access other user's profiles without proper authorization checks. Exploiting this vulnerability allows valid users of the system to be listed and sensitive third-party information to be accessed, such as names, email addresses, internal identifiers, and last activity. The endpoint 'http://:12900/users/' does not implement object-level authorization validations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1437 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Graylog Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1437</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Graylog Web Interface console, version 2.2.3, caused by a lack of proper sanitization and escaping in HTML output. Several endpoints include segments of the URL directly in the response without applying output encoding, allowing an attacker to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript code when a user visits a specially crafted URL. Exploitation of this vulnerability may allow script execution in the victim's browser and limited manipulation of the affected user's session context, through the '/system/authentication/users/edit/' endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1438 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Graylog Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1438</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Graylog Web Interface console, version 2.2.3, caused by a lack of proper sanitization and escaping in HTML output. Several endpoints include segments of the URL directly in the response without applying output encoding, allowing an attacker to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript code when a user visits a specially crafted URL. Exploitation of this vulnerability may allow script execution in the victim's browser and limited manipulation of the affected user's session context, through the  '/system/nodes/' endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1439 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Graylog Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1439</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Graylog Web Interface console, version 2.2.3, caused by a lack of proper sanitization and escaping in HTML output. Several endpoints include segments of the URL directly in the response without applying output encoding, allowing an attacker to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript code when a user visits a specially crafted URL. Exploitation of this vulnerability may allow script execution in the victim's browser and limited manipulation of the affected user's session context, through the  '/

alerts

/' endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1440 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Graylog Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1440</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Graylog Web Interface console, version 2.2.3, caused by a lack of proper sanitization and escaping in HTML output. Several endpoints include segments of the URL directly in the response without applying output encoding, allowing an attacker to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript code when a user visits a specially crafted URL. Exploitation of this vulnerability may allow script execution in the victim's browser and limited manipulation of the affected user's session context, through the  '/system/pipelines/' endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1441 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Graylog Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1441</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Graylog Web Interface console, version 2.2.3, caused by a lack of proper sanitization and escaping in HTML output. Several endpoints include segments of the URL directly in the response without applying output encoding, allowing an attacker to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript code when a user visits a specially crafted URL. Exploitation of this vulnerability may allow script execution in the victim's browser and limited manipulation of the affected user's session context, through the  '/system/index_sets/' endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2654 | huggingface smolagents LocalPythonExecutor requests.post server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2654</link><description>A weakness has been identified in huggingface smolagents 1.24.0. Impacted is the function requests.get/requests.post of the component LocalPythonExecutor. Executing a manipulation can lead to server-side request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8781 | Bookster – WordPress Appointment Booking Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;raw&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8781</link><description>The Bookster – WordPress Appointment Booking Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘raw’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1317 | WP Import – Ultimate CSV XML Importer for WordPress &amp;lt;= 7.37 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via File Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1317</link><description>The WP Import – Ultimate CSV XML Importer for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection in all versions up to, and including, 7.37. This is due to insufficient escaping on the `file_name` parameter which is stored in the database during file upload and later used in raw SQL queries without proper sanitization. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with Subscriber-level access or higher to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries via a malicious filename, which can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. The vulnerability can only be exploited when the 'Single Import/Export' option is enabled, and the server is running a PHP version &lt; 8.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1582 | WP All Export &amp;lt;= 1.4.14 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via PHP Type Juggling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1582</link><description>The WP All Export plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.14 via the export download endpoint. This is due to a PHP type juggling vulnerability in the security token comparison which uses loose comparison (==) instead of strict comparison (===). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass authentication using "magic hash" values when the expected MD5 hash prefix happens to be numeric-looking (matching pattern ^0e\d+$), allowing download of sensitive export files containing PII, business data, or database information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2386 | The Plus Addons for Elementor – Addons for Elementor, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 6.4.7 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary Draft Post Creation via &amp;#x27;post_type&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2386</link><description>The The Plus Addons for Elementor – Addons for Elementor, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Incorrect Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.7. This is due to the tpae_create_page() AJAX handler authorizing users only with current_user_can('edit_posts') while accepting a user-controlled 'post_type' value passed directly to wp_insert_post() without post-type-specific capability checks. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to create arbitrary draft posts for restricted post types (e.g., 'page' and 'nxt_builder') via the 'post_type' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7630 | OTP Password Brute Forcing in DorukNet&amp;#x27;s Wispotter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7630</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts, Improper Authentication vulnerability in Doruk Communication and Automation Industry and Trade Inc. Wispotter allows Password Brute Forcing, Brute Force.This issue affects Wispotter: from 1.0 before v2025.10.08.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14799 | Brevo - Email, SMS, Web Push, Chat, and more. &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Unauthenticated Authorization Bypass via Type Juggling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14799</link><description>The Brevo - Email, SMS, Web Push, Chat, and more. plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to type juggling in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.0. This is due to the use of loose comparison (==) instead of strict comparison (===) when validating the installation ID in the `/wp-json/mailin/v1/mailin_disconnect` REST API endpoint. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to disconnect the Brevo integration, delete the API key, remove all subscription forms, and reset plugin settings by sending a boolean `true` value for the `id` parameter, which bypasses the authorization check through PHP type juggling.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2653 | admesh normals.c stl_check_normal_vector heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2653</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in admesh up to 0.98.5. This issue affects the function stl_check_normal_vector of the file src/normals.c. Performing a manipulation results in heap-based buffer overflow. The attack must be initiated from a local position. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. It looks like this product is not really maintained anymore.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:23:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14444 | RegistrationMagic – Custom Registration Forms, User Registration, Payment, and User Login &amp;lt;= 6.0.6.9 - Unauthenticated Payment Bypass via rm_process_paypal_sdk_payment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14444</link><description>The RegistrationMagic – Custom Registration Forms, User Registration, Payment, and User Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to payment bypass due to insufficient verification of data authenticity on the 'process_paypal_sdk_payment' function in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.6.9. This is due to the plugin trusting client-supplied values for payment verification without validating that the payment actually went through PayPal. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass paid registration by manipulating payment status and activating their account without completing a real PayPal payment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 10:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1942 | Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp;amp; Scheduler &amp;lt;= 8.7.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1942</link><description>The Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp; Scheduler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the b2s_curation_draft AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 8.7.4. The curationDraft() function only verifies current_user_can('read') without checking whether the user has edit_post permission for the target post. Combined with the plugin granting UI access and nonce exposure to all roles, this makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to overwrite the title and content of arbitrary posts and pages by supplying a target post ID via the 'b2s-draft-id' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 10:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2426 | WP-DownloadManager &amp;lt;= 1.69 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Path Traversal to Arbitrary File Deletion via &amp;#x27;file&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2426</link><description>The WP-DownloadManager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.69 via the 'file' parameter in the file deletion functionality. This is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied file paths, allowing directory traversal sequences. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can lead to remote code execution when critical files like wp-config.php are deleted.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 10:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11185 | Complianz | GDPR/CCPA Cookie Consent &amp;lt;= 7.4.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11185</link><description>The Complianz – GDPR/CCPA Cookie Consent plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's cmplz-accept-link shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 7.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13727 | Video Share VOD &amp;lt;= 2.7.11 - Authenticated (Editor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom Field Meta Values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13727</link><description>The Video Share VOD – Turnkey Video Site Builder Script plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via plugin settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2126 | User Submitted Posts &amp;lt;= 20260113 - Incorrect Authorization to Unauthenticated Category Restriction Bypass via &amp;#x27;user-submitted-category&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2126</link><description>The User Submitted Posts – Enable Users to Submit Posts from the Front End plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Incorrect Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 20260113. This is due to the `usp_get_submitted_category()` function accepting user-submitted category IDs from the POST body without validating them against the admin-configured allowed categories stored in `usp_options['categories']`. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to assign submitted posts to arbitrary categories, including restricted ones, by crafting a direct POST request with manipulated `user-submitted-category[]` values, bypassing the frontend category restrictions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1649 | Community Events &amp;lt;= 1.5.7 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;ce_venue_name&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1649</link><description>The Community Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'ce_venue_name' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1656 | Business Directory Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.20 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Listing Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1656</link><description>The Business Directory Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to a missing authorization check in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.20. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify arbitrary listings, including changing titles, content, and email addresses, by directly referencing the listing ID in crafted requests to the wpbdp_ajax AJAX action.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1941 | WP Event Aggregator &amp;lt;= 1.8.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1941</link><description>The WP Event Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wp_events' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2127 | SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle &amp;lt;= 1.70.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2127</link><description>The SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.70.4. This is due to a missing capability check on the `siteorigin_widget_preview_widget_action()` function which is registered via the `wp_ajax_so_widgets_preview` AJAX action. The function only verifies a nonce (`widgets_action`) but does not check user capabilities. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary shortcodes by invoking the `SiteOrigin_Widget_Editor_Widget` via the preview endpoint. The required nonce is exposed on the public frontend when the Post Carousel widget is present on a page, embedded in the `data-ajax-url` HTML attribute.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2495 | WPNakama &amp;lt;= 0.6.5 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;order&amp;#x27; REST API Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2495</link><description>The WPNakama – Team and multi-Client Collaboration, Editorial and Project Management plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'order' parameter of the '/wp-json/WPNakama/v1/boards' REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 0.6.5. This is due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1655 | EventPrime &amp;lt;= 4.2.8.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Event Modification via &amp;#x27;event_id&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1655</link><description>The EventPrime plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized post modification due to missing authorization checks in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.8.4. This is due to the save_frontend_event_submission function accepting a user-controlled event_id parameter and updating the corresponding event post without enforcing ownership or capability checks. This makes it possible for authenticated (Customer+) attackers to modify posts created by administrators by manipulating the event_id parameter granted they can obtain a valid nonce.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1831 | YayMail &amp;lt;= 4.3.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Shop Manager+) Plugin Installation and Activation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1831</link><description>The YayMail - WooCommerce Email Customizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin installation and activation due to missing capability checks on the 'yaymail_install_yaysmtp' AJAX action and `/yaymail/v1/addons/activate` REST endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level access and above, to install and activate the YaySMTP plugin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1860 | Kali Forms &amp;lt;= 2.4.8 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Form Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1860</link><description>The Kali Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.8. This is due to the `get_items_permissions_check()` permission callback on the `/kaliforms/v1/forms/{id}` REST API endpoint only checking for the `edit_posts` capability without verifying that the requesting user has ownership or authorization over the specific form resource. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read form configuration data belonging to other users (including administrators) by enumerating form IDs. Exposed data includes form field structures, Google reCAPTCHA secret keys (if configured), email notification templates, and server paths.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1938 | YayMail &amp;lt;= 4.3.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Shop Manager+) License Key Deletion via &amp;#x27;/yaymail-license/v1/license/delete&amp;#x27; Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1938</link><description>The YayMail – WooCommerce Email Customizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized license key deletion due to a missing authorization check on the `/yaymail-license/v1/license/delete` REST endpoint in versions up to, and including, 4.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level access and above, to delete the plugin's license key via the '/yaymail-license/v1/license/delete' endpoint granted they can obtain the REST API nonce.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1943 | YayMail &amp;lt;= 4.3.2 - Authenticated (Shop Manager+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Template Elements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1943</link><description>The YayMail – WooCommerce Email Customizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via settings in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2112 | Dam Spam &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Pending Comment Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2112</link><description>The Dam Spam plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8. This is due to missing nonce verification on the pending comment deletion action in the cleanup page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete all pending comments via a forged request granted they can trick an admin into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2419 | WP-DownloadManager &amp;lt;= 1.69 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Path Traversal to Arbitrary File Read via &amp;#x27;download_path&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2419</link><description>The WP-DownloadManager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.69 via the 'download_path' configuration parameter. This is due to insufficient validation of the download path setting, which allows directory traversal sequences to bypass the WP_CONTENT_DIR prefix check. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to configure the plugin to list and access arbitrary files on the server by exploiting the file browser functionality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1640 | Taskbuilder &amp;lt;= 5.0.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Project/Task Comment Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1640</link><description>The Taskbuilder – WordPress Project Management &amp; Task Management plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.2. This is due to missing authorization checks on the project and task comment submission functions (AJAX actions: wppm_submit_proj_comment and wppm_submit_task_comment). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to create comments on any project or task (including private projects they cannot view or are not assigned to), and inject arbitrary HTML and CSS via the insufficiently sanitized comment_body parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1666 | Download Manager &amp;lt;= 3.3.46 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;redirect_to&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1666</link><description>The Download Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'redirect_to' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.46. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'redirect_to' GET parameter in the login form shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1807 | InteractiveCalculator for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;id&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1807</link><description>The InteractiveCalculator for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'interactivecalculator' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1857 | Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP &amp;lt;= 3.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Server-Side Request Forgery via &amp;#x27;endpoint&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1857</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.1. This is due to insufficient validation of the `endpoint` parameter in the `get_items()` function of the GetResponse REST API handler. The endpoint's permission check only requires `edit_posts` capability (Contributor role) rather than `manage_options` (Administrator). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to make server-side requests to arbitrary endpoints on the configured GetResponse API server, retrieving sensitive data such as contacts, campaigns, and mailing lists using the site's stored API credentials. The stored API key is also leaked in the request headers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1937 | YayMail &amp;lt;= 4.3.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Shop Manager+) Arbitrary Options Update via &amp;#x27;yaymail_import_state&amp;#x27; AJAX Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1937</link><description>The YayMail – WooCommerce Email Customizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the `yaymail_import_state` AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2019 | Cart All In One For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.21 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Code Injection via &amp;#x27;sc_assign_page&amp;#x27; Setting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2019</link><description>The Cart All In One For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Code Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.21. This is due to insufficient input validation on the 'Assign page' field which is passed directly to the eval() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to execute arbitrary PHP code on the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2281 | Private Comment &amp;lt;= 0.0.4 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Label Text Setting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2281</link><description>The Private Comment plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Label text' setting in all versions up to, and including, 0.0.4. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the plugin's label text option. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2296 | Product Addons for Woocommerce – Product Options with Custom Fields &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Authenticated (Shop Manager+) Code Injection via Conditional Logic &amp;#x27;operator&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2296</link><description>The Product Addons for Woocommerce – Product Options with Custom Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Code Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.0. This is due to insufficient input validation of the 'operator' field in conditional logic rules within the evalConditions() function, which passes unsanitized user input directly to PHP's eval() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level access and above, to inject and execute arbitrary PHP code on the server via the conditional logic 'operator' parameter when saving addon form field rules.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2633 | Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP &amp;lt;= 3.6.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Unauthorized Media Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2633</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.1. This is due to a missing capability check in the `process_image_data_ajax_callback()` function which handles the `kadence_import_process_image_data` AJAX action. The function's authorization check via `verify_ajax_call()` only validates `edit_posts` capability but fails to check for the `upload_files` capability. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary images from remote URLs to the WordPress Media Library, bypassing the standard WordPress capability restriction that prevents Contributors from uploading files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:17:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2644 | niklasso minisat DIMACS File SolverTypes.h value out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2644</link><description>A weakness has been identified in niklasso minisat up to 2.2.0. This issue affects the function Solver::value in the library core/SolverTypes.h of the component DIMACS File Parser. This manipulation of the argument variable index with the input 2147483648 causes out-of-bounds read. The attack needs to be launched locally. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:17:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2642 | ggreer the_silver_searcher search.c search_stream null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2642</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in ggreer the_silver_searcher up to 2.2.0. The impacted element is the function search_stream of the file src/search.c. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:17:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1368 | Video Conferencing with Zoom API &amp;lt; 4.6.6 - Unauthenticated SDK Signature Generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1368</link><description>The Video Conferencing with Zoom WordPress plugin before 4.6.6 contains an AJAX handler that has its nonce verification commented out, allowing unauthenticated attackers to generate valid Zoom SDK signatures for any meeting ID and retrieve the site's Zoom SDK key.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11737 | VK All in One Expansion Unit &amp;lt;= 9.112.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SNS Title</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11737</link><description>The VK All in One Expansion Unit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'vkExUnit_sns_title' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 9.112.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12122 | Popup Box – Easily Create WordPress Popups &amp;lt;= 3.2.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12122</link><description>The Popup Box – Easily Create WordPress Popups plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'iframeBox' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12356 | Tickera – WordPress Event Ticketing &amp;lt;= 3.5.6.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Event/Post Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12356</link><description>The Tickera – Sell Tickets &amp; Manage Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_change_ticket_status' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.6.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update post/event statuses.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1072 | Keybase.io Verification &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1072</link><description>The Keybase.io Verification plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.5. This is due to missing nonce validation when updating plugin settings. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the Keybase verification text via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1304 | Membership Plugin – Restrict Content &amp;lt;= 3.2.18 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Invoice Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1304</link><description>The Membership Plugin – Restrict Content for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple invoice settings fields in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.18 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1639 | Taskbuilder &amp;lt;= 5.0.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;order&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;sort_by&amp;#x27; Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1639</link><description>The Taskbuilder – WordPress Project Management &amp; Task Management plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based blind SQL Injection via the 'order' and 'sort_by' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1906 | PDF Invoices &amp;amp; Packing Slips for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.6.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Peppol Identifier Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1906</link><description>The PDF Invoices &amp; Packing Slips for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.0 via the `wpo_ips_edi_save_order_customer_peppol_identifiers` AJAX action due to missing capability checks and order ownership validation. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify Peppol/EDI endpoint identifiers (`peppol_endpoint_id`, `peppol_endpoint_eas`) for any customer by specifying an arbitrary `order_id` parameter on systems using Peppol invoicing. This can affect order routing on the Peppol network and may result in payment disruptions and data leakage.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2023 | WP Plugin Info Card &amp;lt;= 6.2.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Custom Plugin Entry Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2023</link><description>The WP Plugin Info Card plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.2.0. This is due to missing nonce validation in the ajax_save_custom_plugin() function, which is disabled by prefixing the check with 'false &amp;&amp;'. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create or modify custom plugin entries via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2641 | universal-ctags V Language v.c parseExprList recursion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2641</link><description>A weakness has been identified in universal-ctags ctags up to 6.2.1. The affected element is the function parseExpression/parseExprList of the file parsers/v.c of the component V Language Parser. Executing a manipulation can lead to uncontrolled recursion. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12037 | WP 404 Auto Redirect &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12037</link><description>The WP 404 Auto Redirect to Similar Post plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12071 | Frontend User Notes &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Note Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12071</link><description>The Frontend User Notes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.0 via the 'funp_ajax_modify_notes' AJAX endpoint due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify arbitrary notes that do not belong to them.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12074 | Context Blog &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Unauthenticated Private Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12074</link><description>The Context Blog theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5 via the 'context_blog_modal_popup' due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12075 | Order Splitter for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.3.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Order Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12075</link><description>The Order Splitter for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wos_troubleshooting' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view information pertaining to other user's orders.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13959 | Filestack &amp;lt;= 2.0.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13959</link><description>The Filestack plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'filepicker' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6460 | Display During Conditional Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via message Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6460</link><description>The Display During Conditional Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘message’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1277 | URL Shortify &amp;lt;= 1.12.1 - Unauthenticated Open Redirect via &amp;#x27;redirect_to&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1277</link><description>The URL Shortify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Open Redirect in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.1 due to insufficient validation on the 'redirect_to' parameter in the promotional dismissal handler. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users to potentially malicious sites via a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1296 | Frontend Post Submission Manager Lite &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 - Unauthenticated Open Redirect via &amp;#x27;requested_page&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1296</link><description>The Frontend Post Submission Manager Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Open Redirection in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.7 due to insufficient validation on the 'requested_page' POST parameter in the verify_username_password function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users to potentially malicious sites if they can successfully trick them into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1714 | ShopLentor &amp;lt;= 3.3.2 - Unauthenticated Email Relay Abuse via &amp;#x27;woolentor_suggest_price_action&amp;#x27; AJAX Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1714</link><description>The ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg +21 Modules – All in One Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Email Relay Abuse in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.2. This is due to the lack of validation on the 'send_to', 'product_title', 'wlmessage', and 'wlemail' parameters in the 'woolentor_suggest_price_action' AJAX endpoint. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send arbitrary emails to any recipient with full control over the subject line, message content, and sender address (via CRLF injection in the 'wlemail' parameter), effectively turning the website into a full email relay for spam or phishing campaigns.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1925 | EmailKit – Email Customizer for WooCommerce &amp;amp; WP &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Title Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1925</link><description>The EmailKit – Email Customizer for WooCommerce &amp; WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized data modification due to a missing capability check on the 'update_template_data' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify the title of any post on the site, including posts, pages, and custom post types.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1931 | Rent Fetch &amp;lt;= 0.32.4 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;keyword&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1931</link><description>The Rent Fetch plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'keyword' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.32.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2576 | Business Directory Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.21 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via payment Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2576</link><description>The Business Directory Plugin – Easy Listing Directories for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the 'payment' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27171 | zlib before 1.3.2 allows CPU consumption via crc32_combine64 and crc32_combine_gen64 because x2nmodp can do right shifts within a loop that ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27171</link><description>zlib before 1.3.2 allows CPU consumption via crc32_combine64 and crc32_combine_gen64 because x2nmodp can do right shifts within a loop that has no termination condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 03:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1344 | Insecure file permissions in Enforce Recovery Key Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1344</link><description>Tanium addressed an insecure file permissions vulnerability in Enforce Recovery Key Portal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22048 | StorageGRID (formerly StorageGRID Webscale) versions prior to 11.9.0.12 and 12.0.0.4 with Single Sign-on enabled and configured to use Micro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22048</link><description>StorageGRID (formerly StorageGRID Webscale) versions prior to 11.9.0.12 and 12.0.0.4 with Single Sign-on enabled and configured to use Microsoft Entra ID (formerly Azure AD) as an IdP are susceptible to a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability. Successful exploit could allow an authenticated attacker with low privileges to delete configuration data or deny access to some resources.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23599 | Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability in HPE Aruba Networking Clear Pass Policy Manager OnGuard for Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23599</link><description>A local privilege-escalation vulnerability has been discovered in the HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass OnGuard Software for Linux. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow a local attacker to achieve arbitrary code execution with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62183 | Pega Platform versions 8.1.0 through 25.1.1 are affected by a Stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in a user interface component. Requires an administrative user and given extensive access rights, impact to Confidentiality and Integrity are low.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62183</link><description>Pega Platform versions 8.1.0 through 25.1.1 are affected by a Stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in a user interface component.  Requires an administrative user and given extensive access rights, impact to Confidentiality and Integrity are low.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1670 | Honeywell CCTV Products Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1670</link><description>The affected products are vulnerable to an unauthenticated API endpoint exposure, which may allow an attacker to remotely change the "forgot password" recovery email address.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26119 | Windows Admin Center Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26119</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13333 | IBM WebSphere Application Server could provide weaker than expected security</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13333</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 9.0, and 8.5 could provide weaker than expected security during system administration of security settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 22:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13689 | DataStage on Cloud Pak for Data is vulnerable to arbitrary code injection due to runtime environment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13689</link><description>IBM DataStage on Cloud Pak for Data could allow an authenticated user to execute arbitrary commands and gain access to sensitive information due to unrestricted file uploads.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 22:53:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2629 | jishi node-sonos-http-api TTS Provider mac-os.js Promise os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2629</link><description>A weakness has been identified in jishi node-sonos-http-api up to 3776f0ee2261c924c7b7204de121a38100a08ca7. Affected is the function Promise of the file lib/tts-providers/mac-os.js of the component TTS Provider. This manipulation of the argument phrase causes os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 22:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38005 | Improper Access Control and Exposure of Information Through Directory Listing vulnerabilities affect IBM Cloud Pak System[, ]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38005</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak System 2.3.3.6, 2.3.3.7, 2.3.4.0, 2.3.4.1, and 2.3.5.0 could allow an authenticated user to perform unauthorized tasks due to improper access controls.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 22:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33088 | Multiple Vulnerabilities in IBM Concert Software.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33088</link><description>IBM Concert 1.0.0 through 2.1.0 could allow a local user with specific knowledge about the system's architecture to escalate their privileges due to incorrect file permissions for critical resources.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33135 | IBM Financial Transaction Manager for ACH Services and Check Services is impacted by multiple vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33135</link><description>IBM Financial Transaction Manager for ACH Services and Check Services for Multi-Platform 3.0.0.0 through 3.0.5.4 Interim Fix 027 IBM Financial Transaction Manager for Check Services v3 (Multiplatforms) is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36183 | Privileged User File Upload Vulnerability Leading to Limited Server-Side Execution affects watsonx.data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36183</link><description>IBM watsonx.data 2.2 through 2.2.1 IBM Lakehouse could allow a privileged user to upload malicious files that could be executed server to modify limited files or data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36348 | The Dashboard of IBM Sterling B2B Integrator and IBM Sterling File Gateway is Vulnerable to Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36348</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator versions 6.1.0.0 through 6.1.2.7_2, 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.5, and 6.2.1.0 through 6.2.1.1, and IBM Sterling File Gateway versions 6.1.0.0 through 6.1.2.7_2, 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.5, and 6.2.1.0 through 6.2.1.1 may expose sensitive information to a remote privileged attacker due to the application returning detailed technical error messages in the browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2627 | Softland FBackup Backup/Restore HID.dll link following</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2627</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Softland FBackup up to 9.9. This impacts an unknown function in the library C:\Program Files\Common Files\microsoft shared\ink\HID.dll of the component Backup/Restore. The manipulation results in link following. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55271 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability has been identified in phpgurukul Gym Management System 1.0. This issue is present in the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55271</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability has been identified in phpgurukul Gym Management System 1.0. This issue is present in the profile update functionality of the User Panel, specifically the /profile.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-41650 | WordPress Custom Content by Country plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41650</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Paul Custom Content by Country (by Shield Security) custom-content-by-country.This issue affects Custom Content by Country (by Shield Security): from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31118 | WordPress SP Project &amp;amp; Document Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 4.70 - Broken Access Control to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31118</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Smartypants SP Project &amp; Document Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects SP Project &amp; Document Manager: from n/a through 4.70.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70829 | An information exposure vulnerability in Datart v1.0.0-rc.3 allows authenticated attackers to access sensitive data via a custom H2 JDBC con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70829</link><description>An information exposure vulnerability in Datart v1.0.0-rc.3 allows authenticated attackers to access sensitive data via a custom H2 JDBC connection string.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2616 | Beetel 777VR1 Web Management hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2616</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Beetel 777VR1 up to 01.00.09. The impacted element is an unknown function of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. The attack needs to be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is advisable to modify the configuration settings. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22208 | OpenS100 Portrayal Engine Unrestricted Lua Standard Library Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22208</link><description>OpenS100 (the reference implementation S-100 viewer) prior to commit 753cf29 contain a remote code execution vulnerability via an unrestricted Lua interpreter. The Portrayal Engine initializes Lua using luaL_openlibs() without sandboxing or capability restrictions, exposing standard libraries such as 'os' and 'io' to untrusted portrayal catalogues. An attacker can provide a malicious S-100 portrayal catalogue containing Lua scripts that execute arbitrary commands with the privileges of the OpenS100 process when a user imports the catalogue and loads a chart.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23861 | Dell Unisphere for PowerMax vApp, version(s) 9.2.4.x, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23861</link><description>Dell Unisphere for PowerMax vApp, version(s) 9.2.4.x, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a victim user's web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application. Exploitation may lead to information disclosure, session theft, or client-side request forgery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7706 | Improper Access Control in TUBITAK BILGEM&amp;#x27;s Liderahenk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7706</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in TUBITAK BILGEM Software Technologies Research Institute Liderahenk allows Remote Code Inclusion.This issue affects Liderahenk: from 3.0.0 to 3.3.1 before 3.5.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25087 | Apache Arrow: Potential use-after-free when reading IPC file with pre-buffering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25087</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Apache Arrow C++.

This issue affects Apache Arrow C++ from 15.0.0 through 23.0.0. It can be triggered when reading an Arrow IPC file (but not an IPC stream) with pre-buffering enabled, if the IPC file contains data with variadic buffers (such as Binary View and String View data). Depending on the number of variadic buffers in a record batch column and on the temporal sequence of multi-threaded IO, a write to a dangling pointer could occur. The value (a `std::shared_ptr` object) that is written to the dangling pointer is not under direct control of the attacker.

Pre-buffering is disabled by default but can be enabled using a specific C++ API call (`RecordBatchFileReader::PreBufferMetadata`). The functionality is not exposed in language bindings (Python, Ruby, C GLib), so these bindings are not vulnerable.

The most likely consequence of this issue would be random crashes or memory corruption when reading specific kinds of IPC files. If the application allows ingesting IPC files from untrusted sources, this could plausibly be exploited for denial of service. Inducing more targeted kinds of misbehavior (such as confidential data extraction from the running process) depends on memory allocation and multi-threaded IO temporal patterns that are unlikely to be easily controlled by an attacker.

Advice for users of Arrow C++:

1. check whether you enable pre-buffering on the IPC file reader (using `RecordBatchFileReader::PreBufferMetadata`)

2. if so, either disable pre-buffering (which may have adverse performance consequences), or switch to Arrow 23.0.1 which is not vulnerable</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2615 | Wavlink WL-NU516U1 firewall.cgi singlePortForwardDelete command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2615</link><description>A flaw has been found in Wavlink WL-NU516U1 up to 20251208. The affected element is the function singlePortForwardDelete of the file /cgi-bin/firewall.cgi. Executing a manipulation of the argument del_flag can lead to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8303 | XSS in EKA Software&amp;#x27;s Real Estate Script V5 (With Doping Module – Store Module – New Language System)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8303</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in EKA Software Computer Information Advertising Services Ltd. Real Estate Script V5 (With Doping Module – Store Module – New Language System) allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Real Estate Script V5 (With Doping Module – Store Module – New Language System): through 17022026.

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7631 | Time-Based Blind SQLi in Tumeva Internet Technologies&amp;#x27; Tumeva News Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7631</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Tumeva Internet Technologies Software Information Advertising and Consulting Services Trade Ltd. Co. Tumeva News Software allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Tumeva News Software: through 17022026. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2247 | SQL Injection in Clickedu&amp;#x27;s SaaS platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2247</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability (SQLi) in Clicldeu SaaS, specifically in the generation of reports, which occurs when a previously authenticated remote attacker executes a malicious payload in the URL generated after downloading the student's report card in the ‘Day-to-day’ section from the mobile application.

In the URL of the generated PDF, the session token used does not expire, so it remains valid for days after its generation, and unusual characters can be entered after the ‘id_alu’ parameter, resulting in two types of SQLi: boolean-based blind and time-based blind. Exploiting this vulnerability could allow an attacker to access confidential information in the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2608 | Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks &amp;lt;= 3.5.32 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2608</link><description>The Kadence Blocks — Page Builder Toolkit for Gutenberg Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on a function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.32. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to perform an unauthorized action.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25903 | Apache NiFi: Missing Authorization of Restricted Permissions for Component Updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25903</link><description>Apache NiFi 1.1.0 through 2.7.2 are missing authorization when updating configuration properties on extension components that have specific Required Permissions based on the Restricted annotation. The Restricted annotation indicates additional privileges required to add the annotated component to the flow configuration, but framework authorization did not check restricted status when updating a component previously added. The missing authorization requires a more privileged user to add a restricted component to the flow configuration, but permits a less privileged user to make property configuration changes. Apache NiFi installations that do not implement different levels of authorization for Restricted components are not subject to this vulnerability because the framework enforces write permissions as the security boundary. Upgrading to Apache NiFi 2.8.0 is the recommended mitigation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:03:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1216 | RSS Aggregator &amp;lt;= 5.0.10 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;template&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1216</link><description>The RSS Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'template' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 10:06:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0829 | Frontend File Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 23.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Email Sending</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0829</link><description>The Frontend File Manager Plugin WordPress plugin through 23.5 allows unauthenticated users to send emails through the site without any security checks. This lets attackers use the WordPress site as an open relay for spam or phishing emails to anyone. Attackers can also guess file IDs to access and share uploaded files without permission, exposing sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1657 | EventPrime &amp;lt;= 4.2.8.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Image Upload via &amp;#x27;ep_upload_file_media&amp;#x27; AJAX Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1657</link><description>The EventPrime plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized image file upload in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.8.4. This is due to the plugin registering the upload_file_media AJAX action as publicly accessible (nopriv-enabled) without implementing any authentication, authorization, or nonce verification despite a nonce being created. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload image files to the WordPress uploads directory and create Media Library attachments via the ep_upload_file_media endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2002 | Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp;amp; Custom Form Builder &amp;lt;= 1.50.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2002</link><description>The Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp; Custom Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the form_name parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.50.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The plugin allows admins to give form management permissions to lower level users, which could make this exploitable by users such as subscribers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2592 | Zarinpal Gateway for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.0.16 - Improper Access Control to Payment Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2592</link><description>The Zarinpal Gateway for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Improper Access Control to Payment Status Update in all versions up to and including 5.0.16. This is due to the payment callback handler 'Return_from_ZarinPal_Gateway' failing to validate that the authority token provided in the callback URL belongs to the specific order being marked as paid. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to potentially mark orders as paid without proper payment by reusing a valid authority token from a different transaction of the same amount.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26220 | LightLLM &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 PD Mode Unsafe Deserialization RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26220</link><description>LightLLM version 1.1.0 and prior contain an unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability in PD (prefill-decode) disaggregation mode. The PD master node exposes WebSocket endpoints that receive binary frames and pass the data directly to pickle.loads() without authentication or validation. A remote attacker who can reach the PD master can send a crafted payload to achieve arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 02:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>