<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 04:38:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-6787 | MXview One Series vulnerable to Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6787</link><description>This vulnerability occurs when an attacker exploits a race condition between the time a file is checked and the time it is used (TOCTOU). By exploiting this race condition, an attacker can write arbitrary files to the system. This could allow the attacker to execute malicious code and potentially cause file losses.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 04:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6785 | MXview One and MXview One Central Manger Series store cleartext credentials in a local file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6785</link><description>The configuration file stores credentials in cleartext. An attacker with local access rights can read or modify the configuration file, potentially resulting in the service being abused due to sensitive information exposure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 04:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6786 | MXview One Series vulnerable to Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6786</link><description>The vulnerability allows an attacker to craft MQTT messages that include relative path traversal sequences, enabling them to read arbitrary files on the system. This could lead to the disclosure of sensitive information, such as configuration files and JWT signing secrets.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 04:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46644 | eNMS 4.4.0 to 4.7.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via edit_file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46644</link><description>eNMS 4.4.0 to 4.7.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via edit_file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 20:53:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46645 | eNMS 4.0.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via get_tree_files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46645</link><description>eNMS 4.0.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via get_tree_files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 20:53:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46646 | eNMS up to 4.7.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via /download/file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46646</link><description>eNMS up to 4.7.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via /download/file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 20:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46647 | eNMS 4.4.0 to 4.7.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via upload_files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46647</link><description>eNMS 4.4.0 to 4.7.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via upload_files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 20:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46648 | eNMS 4.4.0 to 4.7.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via scan_folder.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46648</link><description>eNMS 4.4.0 to 4.7.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via scan_folder.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 20:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46649 | eNMS up to 4.7.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via download/folder.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46649</link><description>eNMS up to 4.7.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via download/folder.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 20:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46101 | GDidees CMS &lt;= v3.9.1 has a file upload vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46101</link><description>GDidees CMS &lt;= v3.9.1 has a file upload vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 20:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46640 | SeaCMS 13.2 has a remote code execution vulnerability located in the file sql.class.chp. Although the system has a check function, the check...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46640</link><description>SeaCMS 13.2 has a remote code execution vulnerability located in the file sql.class.chp. Although the system has a check function, the check function is not executed during execution, allowing remote code execution by writing to the file through the MySQL slow query method.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 20:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46103 | SEMCMS 4.8 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via SEMCMS_Main.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46103</link><description>SEMCMS 4.8 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via SEMCMS_Main.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 20:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45793 | Cross-site Scripting from in Confidant API call</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45793</link><description>Confidant is a open source secret management service that provides user-friendly storage and access to secrets. The following endpoints are subject to a cross site scripting vulnerability: GET /v1/credentials, GET /v1/credentials/, GET /v1/archive/credentials/, GET /v1/archive/credentials, POST /v1/credentials, PUT /v1/credentials/, PUT /v1/credentials//, GET /v1/services, GET /v1/services/, GET /v1/archive/services/, GET /v1/archive/services, PUT /v1/services/, PUT /v1/services//. The attacker needs to be authenticated and have privileges to create new credentials, but could use this to show information and run scripts to other users into the same Confidant instance. This issue has been patched in version 6.6.2. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 19:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47061 | Arbitrary DOM attributes in element.attributes and leaf.attributes in Platejs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47061</link><description>Plate is a javascript toolkit that makes it easier for you to develop with Slate, a popular framework for building text editors. One longstanding feature of Plate is the ability to add custom DOM attributes to any element or leaf using the `attributes` property. These attributes are passed to the node component using the `nodeProps` prop. It has come to our attention that this feature can be used for malicious purposes, including cross-site scripting (XSS) and information exposure (specifically, users' IP addresses and whether or not they have opened a malicious document). Note that the risk of information exposure via attributes is only relevant to applications in which web requests to arbitrary URLs are not ordinarily allowed. Plate editors that allow users to embed images from arbitrary URLs, for example, already carry the risk of leaking users' IP addresses to third parties. All Plate editors using an affected version of @udecode/plate-core are vulnerable to these information exposure attacks via the style attribute and other attributes that can cause web requests to be sent. In addition, whether or not a Plate editor is vulnerable to cross-site scripting attacks using attributes depends on a number of factors. The most likely DOM attributes to be vulnerable are href and src on links and iframes respectively. Any component that spreads {...nodeProps} onto an &lt;a&gt; or  element and does not later override href or src will be vulnerable to XSS. In patched versions of Plate, we have disabled element.attributes and leaf.attributes for most attribute names by default, with some exceptions including target, alt, width, height, colspan and rowspan on the link, image, video, table cell and table header cell plugins. If this is a breaking change for you, you can selectively re-enable attributes for certain plugins as follows. Please carefully research and assess the security implications of any attribute you allow, as even seemingly innocuous attributes such as style can be used maliciously. If you are unable to upgrade to any of the patched versions, you should use a tool like patch-package or yarn patch to remove the logic from @udecode/plate-core that adds attributes to nodeProps.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 19:13:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47062 | Multiple SQL Injections and ORM Leak in navidrome</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47062</link><description>Navidrome is an open source web-based music collection server and streamer. Navidrome automatically adds parameters in the URL to SQL queries. This can be exploited to access information by adding parameters like `password=...` in the URL (ORM Leak). Furthermore, the names of the parameters are not properly escaped, leading to SQL Injections. Finally, the username is used in a `LIKE` statement, allowing people to log in with `%` instead of their username. When adding parameters to the URL, they are automatically included in an SQL `LIKE` statement (depending on the parameter's name). This allows attackers to potentially retrieve arbitrary information. For example, attackers can use the following request to test whether some encrypted passwords start with `AAA`. This results in an SQL query like `password LIKE 'AAA%'`, allowing attackers to slowly brute-force passwords. When adding parameters to the URL, they are automatically added to an SQL query. The names of the parameters are not properly escaped. This behavior can be used to inject arbitrary SQL code (SQL Injection). These vulnerabilities can be used to leak information and dump the contents of the database and have been addressed in release version 0.53.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 19:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42346 | Stored Cross Site Scripting (Stored XSS) in Galaxy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42346</link><description>Galaxy is a free, open-source system for analyzing data, authoring workflows, training and education, publishing tools, managing infrastructure, and more. The editor visualization, /visualizations endpoint, can be used to store HTML tags and trigger javascript execution upon edit operation. All supported branches of Galaxy (and more back to release_20.05) were amended with the supplied patches. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 19:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42351 | Possible Data Tampering &amp;amp; Loss of Public Datasets in Galaxy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42351</link><description>Galaxy is a free, open-source system for analyzing data, authoring workflows, training and education, publishing tools, managing infrastructure, and more. An attacker can potentially replace the contents of public datasets resulting in data loss or tampering. All supported branches of Galaxy (and more back to release_21.05) were amended with the below patch. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 19:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46654 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Add Scheduled Task module of Maccms10 v2024.1000.4040 allows attackers to execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46654</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Add Scheduled Task module of Maccms10 v2024.1000.4040 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 19:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45229 | The Versa Director offers REST APIs for orchestration and management. By design, certain APIs, such as the login screen, banner display, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45229</link><description>The Versa Director offers REST APIs for orchestration and management. By design, certain APIs, such as the login screen, banner display, and device registration, do not require authentication. However, it was discovered that for Directors directly connected to the Internet, one of these APIs can be exploited by injecting invalid arguments into a GET request, potentially exposing the authentication tokens of other currently logged-in users. These tokens can then be used to invoke additional APIs on port 9183. This exploit does not disclose any username or password information. 

Currently, there are no workarounds in Versa Director. However, if there is Web Application Firewall (WAF) or API Gateway fronting the Versa Director, it can be used to block access to the URLs of vulnerable API.  /vnms/devicereg/device/* (on ports 9182 &amp; 9183) and /versa/vnms/devicereg/device/* (on port 443). Versa recommends that Directors be upgraded to one of the remediated software versions. This vulnerability is not exploitable on Versa Directors not exposed to the Internet.We have validated that no Versa-hosted head ends have been affected by this vulnerability. Please contact Versa Technical Support or Versa account team for any further assistance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 18:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8612 | Qemu-kvm: information leak in virtio devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8612</link><description>A flaw was found in QEMU, in the virtio-scsi, virtio-blk, and virtio-crypto devices. The size for virtqueue_push as set in virtio_scsi_complete_req / virtio_blk_req_complete / virito_crypto_req_complete could be larger than the true size of the data which has been sent to guest. Once virtqueue_push() finally calls dma_memory_unmap to ummap the in_iov, it may call the address_space_write function to write back the data. Some uninitialized data may exist in the bounce.buffer, leading to an information leak.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 17:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42697 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Leotheme Leo Product Search Module v.2.1.6 and earlier allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42697</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Leotheme Leo Product Search Module v.2.1.6 and earlier allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the q parameter of the product search function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 17:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47480 | An issue in Pure Data 0.54-0 and fixed in 0.54-1 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the set*id () function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47480</link><description>An issue in Pure Data 0.54-0 and fixed in 0.54-1 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the set*id () function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 17:28:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37879 | Improper input validation in /admin/config/save in User-friendly SVN (USVN) before v1.0.12 and below allows administrators to execute arbitr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37879</link><description>Improper input validation in /admin/config/save in User-friendly SVN (USVN) before v1.0.12 and below allows administrators to execute arbitrary code via the fields "siteTitle", "siteIco" and "siteLogo".</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 17:28:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45489 | Arc before 2024-08-26 allows remote code execution in JavaScript boosts. Boosts that run JavaScript cannot be shared by default; however, it...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45489</link><description>Arc before 2024-08-26 allows remote code execution in JavaScript boosts. Boosts that run JavaScript cannot be shared by default; however, it is possible to create or update a boost using another user's ID. This installs the boost in the victim's browser and runs arbitrary Javascript on that browser in a privileged context.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 16:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9040 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System Password cleartext storage in a file or on disk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9040</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Password Handler. The manipulation leads to cleartext storage in a file or on disk. An attack has to be approached locally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 16:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9041 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9041</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /ajax.php?action=update_account. The manipulation of the argument firstname/lastname/email leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 16:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9038 | Codezips Online Shopping Portal insert-product.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9038</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Codezips Online Shopping Portal 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file insert-product.php. The manipulation of the argument productimage1/productimage2/productimage3 leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 16:24:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9039 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9039</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /ajax.php?action=signup. The manipulation of the argument firstname/lastname/email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 16:24:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46652 | Tenda AC8v4 V16.03.34.06 has a stack overflow vulnerability in the fromAdvSetMacMtuWan function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46652</link><description>Tenda AC8v4 V16.03.34.06 has a stack overflow vulnerability in the fromAdvSetMacMtuWan function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9036 | itsourcecode Online Bookstore admin_add.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9036</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Bookstore 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin_add.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9037 | Codezips Internal Marks Calculation index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9037</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Codezips Internal Marks Calculation 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument tid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9034 | code-projects Patient Record Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9034</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 15:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9035 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System Admin Login login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9035</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/login.php of the component Admin Login. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 15:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9033 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System ajax.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9033</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /ajax.php?action=save_category. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 14:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9032 | SourceCodester Simple Forum-Discussion System index.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9032</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Simple Forum-Discussion System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument page leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 13:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9030 | CodeCanyon CRMGo SaaS note cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9030</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in CodeCanyon CRMGo SaaS 7.2. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /deal/{note_id}/note. The manipulation of the argument notes leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9031 | CodeCanyon CRMGo SaaS show cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9031</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in CodeCanyon CRMGo SaaS up to 7.2. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /project/task/{task_id}/show. The manipulation of the argument comment leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9043 | Cellopoint Secure Email Gateway - Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9043</link><description>Secure Email Gateway from Cellopoint has Buffer Overflow Vulnerability in authentication process. Remote unauthenticated attackers can send crafted packets to crash the process, thereby bypassing authentication and obtaining system administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 10:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41721 | bhyve(8) out-of-bounds read access via XHCI emulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41721</link><description>An insufficient boundary validation in the USB code could lead to an out-of-bounds read on the heap, which could potentially lead to an arbitrary write and remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 07:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8853 | Webo-facto &amp;lt;= 1.40 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8853</link><description>The Webo-facto plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions up to, and including, 1.40 due to insufficient restriction on the 'doSsoAuthentification' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make themselves administrators by registering with a username that contains '-wfuser'.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 07:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9011 | code-projects Crud Operation System updata.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9011</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Crud Operation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file updata.php. The manipulation of the argument sid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 01:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45806 | Potential manipulate `x-envoy` headers from external sources in envoy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45806</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native high-performance edge/middle/service proxy. A security vulnerability in Envoy allows external clients to manipulate Envoy headers, potentially leading to unauthorized access or other malicious actions within the mesh. This issue arises due to Envoy's default configuration of internal trust boundaries, which considers all RFC1918 private address ranges as internal. The default behavior for handling internal addresses in Envoy has been changed. Previously, RFC1918 IP addresses were automatically considered internal, even if the internal_address_config was empty.  The default configuration of Envoy will continue to trust internal addresses while in this release and it will not trust them by default in next release. If you have tooling such as probes on your private network which need to be treated as trusted (e.g. changing arbitrary x-envoy headers) please explicitly include those addresses or CIDR ranges into `internal_address_config`. Successful exploitation could allow attackers to bypass security controls, access sensitive data, or disrupt services within the mesh, like Istio. This issue has been addressed in versions 1.31.2, 1.30.6, 1.29.9, and 1.28.7. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 23:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45807 | oghttp2 crash on OnBeginHeadersForStream in envoy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45807</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native high-performance edge/middle/service proxy. Envoy's 1.31 is using `oghttp` as the default HTTP/2 codec, and there are potential bugs around stream management in the codec. To resolve this Envoy will switch off the `oghttp2` by default. The impact of this issue is that envoy will crash. This issue has been addressed in release version 1.31.2. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 23:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45808 | Malicious log injection via access logs in envoy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45808</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native high-performance edge/middle/service proxy. A vulnerability has been identified in Envoy that allows malicious attackers to inject unexpected content into access logs. This is achieved by exploiting the lack of validation for the `REQUESTED_SERVER_NAME` field for access loggers. This issue has been addressed in versions 1.31.2, 1.30.6, 1.29.9, and 1.28.7. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 23:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45809 | Jwt filter crash in the clear route cache with remote JWKs in envoy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45809</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native high-performance edge/middle/service proxy. Jwt filter will lead to an Envoy crash when clear route cache with remote JWKs. In the following case: 1. remote JWKs are used, which requires async header processing; 2. clear_route_cache is enabled on the provider; 3. header operations are enabled in JWT filter, e.g. header to claims feature; 4. the routing table is configured in a way that the JWT header operations modify requests to not match any route. When these conditions are met, a crash is triggered in the upstream code due to nullptr reference conversion from route(). The root cause is the ordering of continueDecoding and clearRouteCache. This issue has been addressed in versions 1.31.2, 1.30.6, and 1.29.9. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 23:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45810 | Envoy crashes for LocalReply in http async client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45810</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native high-performance edge/middle/service proxy. Envoy will crash when the http async client is handling `sendLocalReply` under some circumstance, e.g., websocket upgrade, and requests mirroring. The http async client will crash during the `sendLocalReply()` in http async client, one reason is http async client is duplicating the status code, another one is the destroy of router is called at the destructor of the async stream, while the stream is deferred deleted at first. There will be problems that the stream decoder is destroyed but its reference is called in `router.onDestroy()`, causing segment fault. This will impact ext_authz if the `upgrade` and `connection` header are allowed, and request mirrorring. This issue has been addressed in versions 1.31.2, 1.30.6, 1.29.9, and 1.28.7. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 23:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9009 | code-projects Online Quiz Site showtest.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9009</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Online Quiz Site 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file showtest.php. The manipulation of the argument subid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 23:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46999 | User Grant Deactivation not Working in Zitadel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46999</link><description>Zitadel is an open source identity management platform. ZITADEL's user grants deactivation mechanism did not work correctly. Deactivated user grants were still provided in token, which could lead to unauthorized access to applications and resources. Additionally, the management and auth API always returned the state as active or did not provide any information about the state. Versions 2.62.1, 2.61.1, 2.60.2, 2.59.3, 2.58.5, 2.57.5, 2.56.6, 2.55.8, and 2.54.10 have been released which address this issue. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may explicitly remove the user grants to make sure the user does not get access anymore.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 23:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47000 | Service Users Deactivation not Working in Zitadel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47000</link><description>Zitadel is an open source identity management platform. ZITADEL's user account deactivation mechanism did not work correctly with service accounts. Deactivated service accounts retained the ability to request tokens, which could lead to unauthorized access to applications and resources. Versions 2.62.1, 2.61.1, 2.60.2, 2.59.3, 2.58.5, 2.57.5, 2.56.6, 2.55.8, and 2.54.10 have been released which address this issue. Users are advised t upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may instead of deactivating the service account, consider creating new credentials and replacing the old ones wherever they are used. This effectively prevents the deactivated service account from being utilized. Be sure to revoke all existing authentication keys associated with the service account and to rotate the service account's password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 23:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47060 | Unauthorized Access After Organization or Project Deactivation in Zitadel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47060</link><description>Zitadel is an open source identity management platform. In Zitadel, even after an organization is deactivated, associated projects, respectively their applications remain active. Users across other organizations can still log in and access through these applications, leading to unauthorized access. Additionally, if a project was deactivated access to applications was also still possible. The issue stems from the fact that when an organization is deactivated in Zitadel, the applications associated with it do not automatically deactivate. The application lifecycle is not tightly coupled with the organization's lifecycle, leading to a situation where the organization or project is marked as inactive, but its resources remain accessible. This vulnerability allows for unauthorized access to projects and their resources, which should have been restricted post-organization deactivation. Versions 2.62.1, 2.61.1, 2.60.2, 2.59.3, 2.58.5, 2.57.5, 2.56.6, 2.55.8, and 2.54.10 have been released which address this issue. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may explicitly disable the application to make sure the client is not allowed anymore.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 23:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9008 | SourceCodester Best Online News Portal Comment Section news-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9008</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Best Online News Portal 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /news-details.php of the component Comment Section. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 23:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27584 | Dragonfly2 vulnerable to hard coded cyptographic key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27584</link><description>Dragonfly is an open source P2P-based file distribution and image acceleration system. It is hosted by the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) as an Incubating Level Project. Dragonfly uses JWT to verify user. However, the secret key for JWT, "Secret Key", is hard coded, which leads to authentication bypass. An attacker can perform any action as a user with admin privileges. This issue has been addressed in release version 2.0.9. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 23:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45410 | HTTP client can remove the X-Forwarded headers in Traefik</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45410</link><description>Traefik is a golang, Cloud Native Application Proxy. When a HTTP request is processed by Traefik, certain HTTP headers such as X-Forwarded-Host or X-Forwarded-Port are added by Traefik before the request is routed to the application. For a HTTP client, it should not be possible to remove or modify these headers. Since the application trusts the value of these headers, security implications might arise, if they can be modified. For HTTP/1.1, however, it was found that some of theses custom headers can indeed be removed and in certain cases manipulated. The attack relies on the HTTP/1.1 behavior, that headers can be defined as hop-by-hop via the HTTP Connection header. This issue has been addressed in release versions 2.11.9 and 3.1.3. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 23:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45614 | Header normalization allows for client to clobber proxy set headers in Puma</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45614</link><description>Puma is a Ruby/Rack web server built for parallelism. In affected versions clients could clobber values set by intermediate proxies (such as X-Forwarded-For) by providing a underscore version of the same header (X-Forwarded_For). Any users relying on proxy set variables is affected. v6.4.3/v5.6.9 now discards any headers using underscores if the non-underscore version also exists. Effectively, allowing the proxy defined headers to always win. Users are advised to upgrade. Nginx has a underscores_in_headers configuration variable to discard these headers at the proxy level as a mitigation. Any users that are implicitly trusting the proxy defined headers for security should immediately cease doing so until upgraded to the fixed versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 22:52:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46983 | Remote Command Execution(RCE) Vulnerbility in sofa-hessian</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46983</link><description>sofa-hessian is an internal improved version of Hessian3/4 powered by Ant Group CO., Ltd. The SOFA Hessian protocol uses a blacklist mechanism to restrict deserialization of potentially dangerous classes for security protection. But there is a gadget chain that can bypass the SOFA Hessian blacklist protection mechanism, and this gadget chain only relies on JDK and does not rely on any third-party components. This issue is fixed by an update to the blacklist, users can upgrade to sofahessian version 3.5.5 to avoid this issue. Users unable to upgrade may maintain a blacklist themselves in the directory `external/serialize.blacklist`.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 22:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46984 | XML External Entity Reference (XXE) vulnerability can lead to a Server Side Request Forgery attack in gematik app-referencevalidator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46984</link><description>The reference validator is a tool to perform advanced validation of FHIR resources for TI applications and interoperability standards. The profile location routine in the referencevalidator commons package is vulnerable to `XML External Entities` attack due to insecure defaults of the used Woodstox WstxInputFactory. A malicious XML resource can lead to network requests issued by referencevalidator and thus to a `Server Side Request Forgery` attack. The vulnerability impacts applications which use referencevalidator to process XML resources from untrusted sources. The problem has been patched with the 2.5.1 version of the referencevalidator. Users are strongly recommended to update to this version or a more recent one. A pre-processing or manual analysis of input XML resources on existence of DTD definitions or external entities can mitigate the problem.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 22:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9006 | jeanmarc77 123solar config_invt1.php code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9006</link><description>A vulnerability was found in jeanmarc77 123solar 1.8.4.5. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file config/config_invt1.php. The manipulation of the argument PASSOx leads to code injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is identified as f4a8c748ec436e5a79f91ccb6a6f73752b336aa5. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 22:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9007 | jeanmarc77 123solar detailed.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9007</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in jeanmarc77 123solar 1.8.4.5. This affects an unknown part of the file /detailed.php. The manipulation of the argument date1 leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is named 94bf9ab7ad0ccb7fbdc02f172f37f0e2ea08d48f. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 22:32:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7207 | Envoy: server-side request forgery via http header manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7207</link><description>A flaw was found in Envoy. It is possible to modify or manipulate headers from external clients when pass-through routes are used for the ingress gateway. This issue could allow a malicious user to forge what is logged by Envoy as a requested path and cause the Envoy proxy to make requests to internal-only services or arbitrary external systems. This is a regression of the fix for CVE-2023-27487.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 22:32:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9003 | Jinan Chicheng Company JFlow Attachment EntityMutliFile_Load.do AttachmentUploadController access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9003</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Jinan Chicheng Company JFlow 2.0.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function AttachmentUploadController of the file /WF/Ath/EntityMutliFile_Load.do of the component Attachment Handler. The manipulation of the argument oid leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 21:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9004 | D-Link DAR-7000 Backup_Server_commit.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9004</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in D-Link DAR-7000 up to 20240912. Affected is an unknown function of the file /view/DBManage/Backup_Server_commit.php. The manipulation of the argument host leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 21:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43489 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43489</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 20:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43496 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43496</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 20:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38221 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38221</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 20:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9001 | TOTOLINK T10 cstecgi.cgi setTracerouteCfg os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9001</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK T10 4.1.8cu.5207. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setTracerouteCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument command leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 20:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33109 | Directory Traversal in the web interface of the Tiptel IP 286 with firmware version 2.61.13.10 allows attackers to overwrite arbitrary files...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33109</link><description>Directory Traversal in the web interface of the Tiptel IP 286 with firmware version 2.61.13.10 allows attackers to overwrite arbitrary files on the phone via the Ringtone upload function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 19:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40125 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Media Manager function of Closed-Loop Technology CLESS Server v4.5.2 allows attackers to execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40125</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Media Manager function of Closed-Loop Technology CLESS Server v4.5.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PHP file to the upload endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 19:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25673 | Couchbase Server 7.6.x before 7.6.2, 7.2.x before 7.2.6, and all earlier versions allows HTTP Host header injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25673</link><description>Couchbase Server 7.6.x before 7.6.2, 7.2.x before 7.2.6, and all earlier versions allows HTTP Host header injection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 18:57:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47159 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.44799 user without appropriate permissions could restore workflows attached to a project</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47159</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.44799 user without appropriate permissions could restore workflows attached to a project</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 17:32:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47160 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.44799 access to global app config data without appropriate permissions was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47160</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.44799 access to global app config data without appropriate permissions was possible</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 17:32:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47162 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.44799 token could be revealed on Imports page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47162</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.44799 token could be revealed on Imports page</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 17:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8963 | Path Traversal in the Ivanti CSA before 4.6 Patch 519 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to access restricted functionality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8963</link><description>Path Traversal in the Ivanti CSA before 4.6 Patch 519 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to access restricted functionality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 17:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38016 | Microsoft Office Visio Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38016</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 17:19:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31570 | libfreeimage in FreeImage 3.4.0 through 3.18.0 has a stack-based buffer overflow in the PluginXPM.cpp Load function via an XPM file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31570</link><description>libfreeimage in FreeImage 3.4.0 through 3.18.0 has a stack-based buffer overflow in the PluginXPM.cpp Load function via an XPM file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 16:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8652 | Netcat CMS: reflected cross-site scripting in openstat module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8652</link><description>A vulnerability in NetCat CMS allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in a user's browser when they visit specific path on the site.
This issue affects NetCat CMS v. 6.4.0.24126.2 and possibly others.

Apply patch from vendor  https://netcat.ru/ https://netcat.ru/] . Versions 6.4.0.24248 and on have the patch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 16:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8653 | Netcat CMS: multiple reflected cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in netshop module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8653</link><description>A vulnerability in NetCat CMS allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in a user's browser when they visit specific paths on the site.
This issue affects NetCat CMS v. 6.4.0.24126.2 and possibly others.

Apply patch from vendor  https://netcat.ru/ https://netcat.ru/] . Versions 6.4.0.24248 and on have the patch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 16:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8651 | Netcat CMS: user enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8651</link><description>A vulnerability in NetCat CMS allows an attacker to send a specially crafted http request that can be used to check whether a user exists in the system, which could be a basis for further attacks.
This issue affects NetCat CMS v. 6.4.0.24126.2 and possibly others.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 16:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45861 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials in Kastle Systems Access Control System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45861</link><description>Kastle Systems firmware prior to May 1, 2024, contained a hard-coded credential, which if accessed may allow an attacker to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 16:09:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45862 | Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information in Kastle Systems Access Control System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45862</link><description>Kastle Systems firmware prior to May 1, 2024, stored machine credentials in cleartext, which may allow an attacker to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 16:09:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8375 | Object deserialization in Reverb leading to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8375</link><description>There exists a use after free vulnerability in Reverb.Reverb supports the VARIANT datatype, which is supposed to represent an arbitrary object in C++. When a tensor proto of type VARIANT is unpacked, memory is first allocated to store the entire tensor, and a ctor is called on each instance. Afterwards, Reverb copies the content in tensor_contentto the previously mentioned pre-allocated memory, which results in the bytes in tensor_contentoverwriting the vtable pointers of all the objects which were previously allocated.Reverb exposes 2 relevant gRPC endpoints: InsertStream and SampleStream. The attacker can insert this stream into the servers database, then when the client next calls SampleStream they will unpack the tensor into RAM, and when any method on that object is called (including its destructor) the attacker gains control of the Program Counter. We recommend upgrading past git commit https://github.com/google-deepmind/reverb/commit/6a0dcf4c9e842b7f999912f792aaa6f6bd261a25</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 16:09:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8698 | Keycloak-saml-core: improper verification of saml responses leading to privilege escalation in keycloak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8698</link><description>A flaw exists in the SAML signature validation method within the Keycloak XMLSignatureUtil class. The method incorrectly determines whether a SAML signature is for the full document or only for specific assertions based on the position of the signature in the XML document, rather than the Reference element used to specify the signed element. This flaw allows attackers to create crafted responses that can bypass the validation, potentially leading to privilege escalation or impersonation attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:52:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8883 | Keycloak: vulnerable redirect uri validation results in open redirec</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8883</link><description>A misconfiguration flaw was found in Keycloak. This issue can allow an attacker to redirect users to an arbitrary URL if a 'Valid Redirect URI' is set to http://localhost or http://127.0.0.1, enabling sensitive information such as authorization codes to be exposed to the attacker, potentially leading to session hijacking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45752 | logiops through 0.3.4, in its default configuration, allows any unprivileged user to configure its logid daemon via an unrestricted D-Bus se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45752</link><description>logiops through 0.3.4, in its default configuration, allows any unprivileged user to configure its logid daemon via an unrestricted D-Bus service, including setting malicious keyboard macros. This allows for privilege escalation with minimal user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7736 | Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7736</link><description>A reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7737 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DSwym in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7737</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DSwym in 3DSwymer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7785 | Reflected XSS in Ece Software&amp;#x27;s Electronic Ticket System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7785</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ece Software Electronic Ticket System allows Reflected XSS, Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Electronic Ticket System: before 2024.08.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 13:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46394 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /admin/?/user/add</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46394</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /admin/?/user/add</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 13:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46382 | A SQL injection vulnerability in linlinjava litemall 1.8.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the goodsId, goodsSn...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46382</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in linlinjava litemall 1.8.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the goodsId, goodsSn, and name parameters in AdminGoodscontroller.java.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 13:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8986 | Information Leakage in grafana-plugin-sdk-go</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8986</link><description>The grafana plugin SDK bundles build metadata into the binaries it compiles; this metadata includes the repository URI for the plugin being built, as retrieved by running `git remote get-url origin`.
 
If credentials are included in the repository URI (for instance, to allow for fetching of private dependencies), the final binary will contain the full URI, including said credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 11:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8354 | Qemu-kvm: usb: assertion failure in usb_ep_get()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8354</link><description>A flaw was found in QEMU. An assertion failure was present in the usb_ep_get() function in hw/net/core.c when trying to get the USB endpoint from a USB device. This flaw may allow a malicious unprivileged guest user to crash the QEMU process on the host and cause a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 10:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45769 | Pcp: pmcd heap corruption through metric pmstore operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45769</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Performance Co-Pilot (PCP). This flaw allows an attacker to send specially crafted data to the system, which could cause the program to misbehave or crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 08:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45770 | Pcp: pmpost symlink attack allows escalating pcp to root user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45770</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Performance Co-Pilot (PCP). This flaw can only be exploited if an attacker has access to a compromised PCP system account. The issue is related to the pmpost tool, which is used to log messages in the system. Under certain conditions, it runs with high-level privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 08:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47087 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47087</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Apex Softcell LD Geo due to improper validation of the certain parameters (Client ID, DPID or BOID) in the API endpoint. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating parameters in the API request body leading to exposure of sensitive information belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 06:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47088 | User Enumeration vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47088</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Apex Softcell LD Geo due to missing restrictions for excessive failed authentication attempts on its API based login. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by conducting a brute force attack on login OTP, which could lead to gain unauthorized access to other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 06:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47089 | Unauthorized Transaction Manipulation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47089</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the Apex Softcell LD Geo due to improper validation of the transaction token ID in the API endpoint. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the transaction token ID in the API request leading to unauthorized access and modification of transactions belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 06:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47086 | OTP Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47086</link><description>This vulnerability exists in LD DP Back Office due to improper implementation of OTP validation mechanism in certain API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by providing arbitrary OTP value for authentication and subsequently changing its API response.  

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to bypass OTP verification for other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 06:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47085 | Parameter Manipulation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47085</link><description>This vulnerability exists in LD DP Back Office due to improper validation of certain parameters cCdslClicentcode and cLdClientCode in the API endpoint. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating parameters in the API request body leading to exposure of sensitive information belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 06:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46946 | langchain_experimental (aka LangChain Experimental) 0.1.17 through 0.3.0 for LangChain allows attackers to execute arbitrary code through sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46946</link><description>langchain_experimental (aka LangChain Experimental) 0.1.17 through 0.3.0 for LangChain allows attackers to execute arbitrary code through sympy.sympify (which uses eval) in LLMSymbolicMathChain. LLMSymbolicMathChain was introduced in fcccde406dd9e9b05fc9babcbeb9ff527b0ec0c6 (2023-10-05).</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 05:12:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4533 | Limit Login Attempts Plus &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - IP Address Spoofing to Protection Mechanism Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4533</link><description>The Limit Login Attempts Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP Address Spoofing in versions up to, and including, 1.1.0. This is due to insufficient restrictions on where the IP Address information is being retrieved for request logging and login restrictions. Attackers can supply the X-Forwarded-For header with with a different IP Address that will be logged and can be used to bypass settings that may have blocked out an IP address or country from logging in.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 04:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8364 | WP Custom Fields Search &amp;lt;= 1.2.35 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wpcfs-preset Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8364</link><description>The WP Custom Fields Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wpcfs-preset shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.35 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 04:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8850 | MC4WP: Mailchimp for WordPress 4.9.9 - 4.9.16 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8850</link><description>The MC4WP: Mailchimp for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'email' parameter when a placeholder such as {email} is used for the field in versions 4.9.9 to 4.9.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 04:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7254 | Stack overflow in Protocol Buffers Java Lite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7254</link><description>Any project that parses untrusted Protocol Buffers datacontaining an arbitrary number of nested groups / series of SGROUPtags can corrupted by exceeding the stack limit i.e. StackOverflow. Parsing nested groups as unknown fields with DiscardUnknownFieldsParser or Java Protobuf Lite parser, or against Protobuf map fields, creates unbounded recursions that can be abused by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 01:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>