<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:02:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-15422 | EmpireSoft EmpireCMS IP Address connect.php egetip protection mechanism</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15422</link><description>A flaw has been found in EmpireSoft EmpireCMS up to 8.0. This issue affects the function egetip of the file e/class/connect.php of the component IP Address Handler. This manipulation causes protection mechanism failure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:02:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15421 | Yonyou KSOA HTTP GET Parameter agent_worksadd.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15421</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Yonyou KSOA 9.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /worksheet/agent_worksadd.jsp of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:02:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15419 | Open5GS GTPv2-C Flow s5c-handler.c sgwc_s5c_handle_create_session_response denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15419</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. Affected by this issue is the function sgwc_s5c_handle_create_session_response of the file src/sgwc/s5c-handler.c of the component GTPv2-C Flow Handler. Executing manipulation can lead to denial of service. The attack needs to be launched locally. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. This patch is called 5aaa09907e7b9e0a326265a5f08d56f54280b5f2. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:02:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15420 | Yonyou KSOA agent_work_report.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15420</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Yonyou KSOA 9.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /worksheet/agent_work_report.jsp. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:02:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15418 | Open5GS Bearer QoS IE Length types.c ogs_gtp2_parse_bearer_qos denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15418</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. Affected by this vulnerability is the function ogs_gtp2_parse_bearer_qos in the library lib/gtp/v2/types.c of the component Bearer QoS IE Length Handler. Performing manipulation results in denial of service. The attack must be initiated from a local position. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The patch is named 4e913d21f2c032b187815f063dbab5ebe65fe83a. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 23:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15417 | Open5GS GTPv2-C F-TEID s11-handler.c sgwc_s11_handle_create_session_request denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15417</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. Affected is the function sgwc_s11_handle_create_session_request of the file src/sgwc/s11-handler.c of the component GTPv2-C F-TEID Handler. Such manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack must be carried out locally. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The name of the patch is 465273d13ba5d47b274c38c9d1b07f04859178a1. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 23:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15416 | xnx3 wangmarket Add Global Variable save.do cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15416</link><description>A vulnerability was found in xnx3 wangmarket up to 6.4. This affects an unknown function of the file /siteVar/save.do of the component Add Global Variable Handler. The manipulation of the argument Remark/Variable Value results in cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 22:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15415 | xnx3 wangmarket XML File uploadImage.do uploadImage unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15415</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in xnx3 wangmarket up to 6.4. The impacted element is the function uploadImage of the file /sits/uploadImage.do of the component XML File Handler. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 22:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15414 | go-sonic Theme Fetching API git_fetcher.go FetchTheme server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15414</link><description>A flaw has been found in go-sonic sonic up to 1.1.4. The affected element is the function FetchTheme of the file service/theme/git_fetcher.go of the component Theme Fetching API. Executing manipulation of the argument uri can lead to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 21:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15413 | wasm3 m3_exec.h op_CallIndirect memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15413</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in wasm3 up to 0.5.0. Impacted is the function op_SetSlot_i32/op_CallIndirect of the file m3_exec.h. Performing manipulation results in memory corruption. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit is now public and may be used. Unfortunately, the project has no active maintainer at the moment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 21:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15412 | WebAssembly wabt wasm-decompile VarName out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15412</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in WebAssembly wabt up to 1.0.39. This issue affects the function wabt::Decompiler::VarName of the file /src/repro/wabt/bin/wasm-decompile of the component wasm-decompile. Such manipulation leads to out-of-bounds read. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. Unfortunately, the project has no active maintainer at the moment. In a reply to the issue report somebody recommended to the researcher to provide a PR himself.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 20:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15411 | WebAssembly wabt wasm-decompile InsertNode memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15411</link><description>A weakness has been identified in WebAssembly wabt up to 1.0.39. This vulnerability affects the function wabt::AST::InsertNode of the file /src/repro/wabt/bin/wasm-decompile of the component wasm-decompile. This manipulation causes memory corruption. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. Unfortunately, the project has no active maintainer at the moment. In a reply to the issue report somebody recommended to the researcher to provide a PR himself.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15410 | code-projects Online Guitar Store login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15410</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Online Guitar Store 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument L_email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15409 | code-projects Online Guitar Store Delete_product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15409</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Online Guitar Store 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/Delete_product.php. Executing manipulation of the argument del_pro can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55065 | CWE-89 Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection')</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55065</link><description>CWE-89 Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection')</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68619 | Signal K Server Vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via Malicious npm Package</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68619</link><description>Signal K Server is a server application that runs on a central hub in a boat. Versions prior to 2.19.0 of the appstore interface allow administrators to install npm packages through a REST API endpoint. While the endpoint validates that the package name exists in the npm registry as a known plugin or webapp, the version parameter accepts arbitrary npm version specifiers including URLs. npm supports installing packages from git repositories, GitHub shorthand syntax, and HTTP/HTTPS URLs pointing to tarballs. When npm installs a package, it can automatically execute any `postinstall` script defined in `package.json`, enabling arbitrary code execution. The vulnerability exists because npm's version specifier syntax is extremely flexible, and the SignalK code passes the version parameter directly to npm without sanitization. An attacker with admin access can install a package from an attacker-controlled source containing a malicious `postinstall` script. Version 2.19.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68620 | Signal K Server vulnerable to JWT Token Theft via WebSocket Enumeration and Unauthenticated Polling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68620</link><description>Signal K Server is a server application that runs on a central hub in a boat. Versions prior to 2.19.0 expose two features that can be chained together to steal JWT authentication tokens without any prior authentication. The attack combines WebSocket-based request enumeration with unauthenticated polling of access request status. The first is Unauthenticated WebSocket Request Enumeration: When a WebSocket client connects to the SignalK stream endpoint with the `serverevents=all` query parameter, the server sends all cached server events including `ACCESS_REQUEST` events that contain details about pending access requests. The `startServerEvents` function iterates over `app.lastServerEvents` and writes each cached event to any connected client without verifying authorization level. Since WebSocket connections are allowed for readonly users (which includes unauthenticated users when `allow_readonly` is true), attackers receive these events containing request IDs, client identifiers, descriptions, requested permissions, and IP addresses. The second is Unauthenticated Token Polling: The access request status endpoint at `/signalk/v1/access/requests/:id` returns the full state of an access request without requiring authentication. When an administrator approves a request, the response includes the issued JWT token in plaintext. The `queryRequest` function returns the complete request object including the token field, and the REST endpoint uses readonly authentication, allowing unauthenticated access. An attacker has two paths to exploit these vulnerabilities. Either the attacker creates their own access request (using the IP spoofing vulnerability to craft a convincing spoofed request), then polls their own request ID until an administrator approves it, receiving the JWT token; or the attacker passively monitors the WebSocket stream to discover request IDs from legitimate devices, then polls those IDs and steals the JWT tokens when administrators approve them, hijacking legitimate device credentials. Both paths require zero authentication and enable complete authentication bypass. Version 2.19.0 fixes the underlying issues.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69203 | Signal K Server Vulnerable to Access Request Spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69203</link><description>Signal K Server is a server application that runs on a central hub in a boat. Versions prior to 2.19.0 of the access request system have two related features that when combined by themselves and with an information disclosure vulnerability enable convincing social engineering attacks against administrators. When a device creates an access request, it specifies three fields: `clientId`, `description`, and `permissions`. The SignalK admin UI displays the `description` field prominently to the administrator when showing pending requests, but the actual `permissions` field (which determines the access level granted) is less visible or displayed separately. This allows an attacker to request `admin` permissions while providing a description that suggests readonly access. The access request handler trusts the `X-Forwarded-For` HTTP header without validation to determine the client's IP address. This header is intended to preserve the original client IP when requests pass through reverse proxies, but when trusted unconditionally, it allows attackers to spoof their IP address. The spoofed IP is displayed to administrators in the access request approval interface, potentially making malicious requests appear to originate from trusted internal network addresses. Since device/source names can be enumerated via the information disclosure vulnerability, an attacker can impersonate a legitimate device or source, craft a convincing description, spoof a trusted internal IP address, and request elevated permissions, creating a highly convincing social engineering scenario that increases the likelihood of administrator approval. Users should upgrade to version 2.19.0 to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68273 | Signal K Server Vulnerable to Unauthenticated Information Disclosure via Exposed Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68273</link><description>Signal K Server is a server application that runs on a central hub in a boat. An unauthenticated information disclosure vulnerability in versions prior to 2.19.0 allows any user to retrieve sensitive system information, including the full SignalK data schema, connected serial devices, and installed analyzer tools. This exposure facilitates reconnaissance for further attacks. Version 2.19.0 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15408 | code-projects Online Guitar Store Create_product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15408</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Guitar Store 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/Create_product.php. Performing manipulation of the argument dre_title results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68272 | Signal K Server Vulnerable to Denial of Service via Unrestricted Access Request Flooding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68272</link><description>Signal K Server is a server application that runs on a central hub in a boat. A Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in versions prior to 2.19.0 allows an unauthenticated attacker to crash the SignalK Server by flooding the access request endpoint (`/signalk/v1/access/requests`). This causes a "JavaScript heap out of memory" error due to unbounded in-memory storage of request objects. Version 2.19.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21436 | eopkg has Path Traversal: &amp;#x27;../filedir&amp;#x27; vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21436</link><description>eopkg is a Solus package manager implemented in python3. In versions prior to 4.4.0, a malicious package could escape the directory set by `--destdir`. This requires the installation of a package from a malicious or compromised source. Files in such packages would not be installed in the path given by `--destdir`, but on a different location on the host. The issue has been fixed in v4.4.0. Users only installing packages from the Solus repositories are not affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21437 | eopkg vulnerable to package file list integrity bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21437</link><description>eopkg is a Solus package manager implemented in python3. In versions prior to 4.4.0, a malicious package could include files that are not tracked by `eopkg`. This requires the installation of a package from a malicious or compromised source. Files in such packages would not be shown by `lseopkg` and related tools. The issue has been fixed in v4.4.0. Users only installing packages from the Solus repositories are not affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66398 | Signal K Server has Unauthenticated State Pollution leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66398</link><description>Signal K Server is a server application that runs on a central hub in a boat. Prior to version 2.19.0, an unauthenticated attacker can pollute the internal state (`restoreFilePath`) of the server via the `/skServer/validateBackup` endpoint. This allows the attacker to hijack the administrator's "Restore" functionality to overwrite critical server configuration files (e.g., `security.json`, `package.json`), leading to account takeover and Remote Code Execution (RCE). Version 2.19.0 patches this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21428 | cpp-httplib has CRLF injection in http headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21428</link><description>cpp-httplib is a C++11 single-file header-only cross platform HTTP/HTTPS library. Prior to version 0.30.0, the ``write_headers`` function does not check for CR &amp; LF characters in user supplied headers, allowing untrusted header value to escape header lines.
This vulnerability allows attackers to add extra headers, modify request body unexpectedly &amp; trigger an SSRF attack. When combined with a server that supports http1.1 pipelining (springboot, python twisted etc), this can be used for server side request forgery (SSRF). Version 0.30.0 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15407 | code-projects Online Guitar Store Create_category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15407</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Online Guitar Store 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/Create_category.php. Such manipulation of the argument dre_Ctitle leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15406 | PHPGurukul Online Course Registration authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15406</link><description>A flaw has been found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration up to 3.1. This affects an unknown function. This manipulation causes missing authorization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47411 | Apache StreamPipes: Leverage of User ID for Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47411</link><description>A user with a legitimate non-administrator account can exploit a vulnerability in the user ID creation mechanism in Apache StreamPipes that allows them to swap the username of an existing user with that of an administrator. 

This vulnerability allows an attacker to gain administrative control over the application by manipulating JWT tokens, which can lead to data tampering, unauthorized access and other security issues.






This issue affects Apache StreamPipes: through 0.97.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.98.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14428 | My Sticky Elements &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Bulk Lead Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14428</link><description>The All-in-one Sticky Floating Contact Form, Call, Click to Chat, and 50+ Social Icon Tabs - My Sticky Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized data loss due to a missing capability check on the 'my_sticky_elements_bulks' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete all contact form leads stored by the plugin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14627 | WP Import – Ultimate CSV XML Importer for WordPress &amp;lt;= 7.35 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Server-Side Request Forgery via Bitly Shortlink Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14627</link><description>The WP Import – Ultimate CSV XML Importer for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 7.35. This is due to inadequate validation of the resolved URL after following Bitly shortlink redirects in the `upload_function()` method. While the initial URL is validated using `wp_http_validate_url()`, when a Bitly shortlink is detected, the `unshorten_bitly_url()` function follows redirects to the final destination URL without re-validating it. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with Contributor-level access or higher to make the server perform HTTP requests to arbitrary internal endpoints, including localhost, private IP ranges, and cloud metadata services (e.g., 169.254.169.254), potentially exposing sensitive internal data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48768 | Apache NuttX RTOS: fs/inode: fs_inoderemove root inode removal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48768</link><description>Release of Invalid Pointer or Reference vulnerability was discovered in fs/inode/fs_inoderemove code of the Apache NuttX RTOS that allowed root filesystem inode removal leading to a debug assert trigger (that is disabled by default), NULL pointer dereference (handled differently depending on the target architecture), or in general, a Denial of Service.

This issue affects Apache NuttX RTOS: from 10.0.0 before 12.10.0.

Users of filesystem based services with write access that were exposed over the network (i.e. FTP) are affected and recommended to upgrade to version 12.10.0 that fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48769 | Apache NuttX RTOS: fs/vfs/fs_rename: use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48769</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability was discovered in fs/vfs/fs_rename code of the Apache NuttX RTOS, that due recursive implementation and single buffer use by two different pointer variables allowed arbitrary user provided size buffer reallocation and write to the previously freed heap chunk, that in specific cases could cause unintended virtual filesystem rename/move operation results.

This issue affects Apache NuttX RTOS: from 7.20 before 12.11.0.

Users of virtual filesystem based services with write access especially when exposed over the network (i.e. FTP) are affected and recommended to upgrade to version 12.11.0 that fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:46:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66023 | NanoMQ has Use-After-Free of malformed bridging message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66023</link><description>NanoMQ MQTT Broker (NanoMQ) is an all-around Edge Messaging Platform. Versions prior to 0.24.5 have a Heap-Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability within the MQTT bridge client component (implemented via the underlying NanoNNG library). The vulnerability is triggered when NanoMQ acts as a bridge connecting to a remote MQTT broker. A malicious remote broker can trigger a crash (Denial of Service) or potential memory corruption by accepting the connection and immediately sending a malformed packet sequence. Version 0.34.5 contains a patch. The patch enforces stricter protocol adherence in the MQTT client SDK embedded in NanoMQ. Specifically, it ensures that CONNACK is always the first packet processed in the line. This prevents the state confusion that led to the Heap-Use-After-Free (UAF) when a malicious server sent a malformed packet sequence immediately after connection establishment. As a workaround, validate the remote broker before bridging.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15405 | PHPEMS cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15405</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in PHPEMS up to 11.0. The impacted element is an unknown function. The manipulation results in cross-site request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15404 | campcodes School File Management System save_file.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15404</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in campcodes School File Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /save_file.php. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 13:55:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0544 | itsourcecode School Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0544</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode School Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /student/index.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11157 | Arbitrary Code Execution in feast-dev/feast</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11157</link><description>A high-severity remote code execution vulnerability exists in feast-dev/feast version 0.53.0, specifically in the Kubernetes materializer job located at `feast/sdk/python/feast/infra/compute_engines/kubernetes/main.py`. The vulnerability arises from the use of `yaml.load(..., Loader=yaml.Loader)` to deserialize `/var/feast/feature_store.yaml` and `/var/feast/materialization_config.yaml`. This method allows for the instantiation of arbitrary Python objects, enabling an attacker with the ability to modify these YAML files to execute OS commands on the worker pod. This vulnerability can be exploited before the configuration is validated, potentially leading to cluster takeover, data poisoning, and supply-chain sabotage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13820 | Comments – wpDiscuz &amp;lt; 7.6.40 - Unauthenticated Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13820</link><description>The Comments  WordPress plugin before 7.6.40 does not properly validate user's identity when using the disqus.com provider, allowing an attacker to log in to any user (when knowing their email address) when such user does not have an account on disqus.com yet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 06:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69413 | In Gitea before 1.25.2, /api/v1/user has different responses for failed authentication depending on whether a username exists.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69413</link><description>In Gitea before 1.25.2, /api/v1/user has different responses for failed authentication depending on whether a username exists.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:05:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69412 | KDE messagelib before 25.11.90 ignores SSL errors for threatMatches:find in the Google Safe Browsing Lookup API (aka phishing API), which mi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69412</link><description>KDE messagelib before 25.11.90 ignores SSL errors for threatMatches:find in the Google Safe Browsing Lookup API (aka phishing API), which might allow spoofing of threat data. NOTE: this Lookup API is not contacted in the messagelib default configuration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67711 | Reflected XSS vulnerability in ArcGIS Server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67711</link><description>There is a stored cross site scripting issue in Esri ArcGIS Server 11.4 and earlier on Windows and Linux that in some configurations allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to store files that contain malicious code that may execute in the context of a victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67703 | Stored XSS vulnerability in ArcGIS Server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67703</link><description>There is a stored cross site scripting issue in Esri ArcGIS Server 11.4 and earlier on Windows and Linux that in some configurations allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to store files that contain malicious code that may execute in the context of a victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67704 | Stored XSS vulnerability in ArcGIS Server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67704</link><description>There is a stored cross site scripting issue in Esri ArcGIS Server 11.4 and earlier on Windows and Linux that in some configurations allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to store files that contain malicious code that may execute in the context of a victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67705 | Reflected XSS vulnerability in ArcGIS Server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67705</link><description>There is a stored cross site scripting issue in Esri ArcGIS Server 11.4 and earlier on Windows and Linux that in some configurations allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to store files that contain malicious code that may execute in the context of a victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67706 | Unvalidated File Upload vulnerability in ArcGIS Server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67706</link><description>ArcGIS Server version 11.5 and earlier on Windows and Linux does not properly validate uploaded files file, which allows remote attackers to upload arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67707 | Unvalidated File Upload vulnerability in ArcGIS Server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67707</link><description>ArcGIS Server version 11.5 and earlier on Windows and Linux does not properly validate uploaded files file, which allows remote attackers to upload arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67708 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ArcGIS Server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67708</link><description>There is a stored cross site scripting issue in Esri ArcGIS Server 11.4 and earlier on Windows and Linux that in some configurations allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to store files that contain malicious code that may execute in the context of a victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67709 | There is a cross site scripting issue in ArcGIS Server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67709</link><description>There is a stored cross site scripting issue in Esri ArcGIS Server 11.4 and earlier on Windows and Linux that in some configurations allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to store files that contain malicious code that may execute in the context of a victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67710 | Stored XSS vulnerability in ArcGIS Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67710</link><description>There is a stored cross site scripting issue in Esri ArcGIS Server 11.4 and earlier on Windows and Linux that in some configurations allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to store files that contain malicious code that may execute in the context of a victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15398 | Uasoft badaso Token BadasoAuthController.php forgetPassword password recovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15398</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Uasoft badaso up to 2.9.7. Affected is the function forgetPassword of the file src/Controllers/BadasoAuthController.php of the component Token Handler. Such manipulation leads to weak password recovery. The attack can be executed remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69288 | Titra has Remote Code Execution in Admin Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69288</link><description>Titra is open source project time tracking software. Prior to version 0.99.49, Titra allows any authenticated Admin user to modify the timeEntryRule in the database. The value is then passed to a NodeVM value to execute as code. Without sanitization, it leads to a Remote Code Execution. Version 0.99.49 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69286 | RAGFlow has Predictable Token Generation Leading to Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69286</link><description>RAGFlow is an open-source RAG (Retrieval-Augmented Generation) engine. In versions prior to 0.22.0, the use of an insecure key generation algorithm in the API key and beta (assistant/agent share auth) token generation process allows these tokens to be mutually derivable. Specifically, both tokens are generated using the same `URLSafeTimedSerializer` with predictable inputs, enabling an unauthorized user who obtains the shared assistant/agent URL to derive the personal API key. This grants them full control over the assistant/agent owner's account. Version 0.22.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7332 | PocketMine-MP &amp;lt; 4.18.1 Improper Validation of Dropped Item Count Allows Remote Server Crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7332</link><description>PocketMine-MP versions prior to 4.18.1 contain an improper input validation vulnerability in inventory transaction handling. A remote attacker with a valid player session can request that the server drop more items than are available in the player's hotbar, triggering a server crash and resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34469 | Cowrie &amp;lt; 2.9.0 Unrestricted wget/curl Emulation Enables SSRF-Based DDoS Amplification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34469</link><description>Cowrie versions prior to 2.9.0 contain a server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the emulated shell implementation of wget and curl. In the default emulated shell configuration, these command emulations perform real outbound HTTP requests to attacker-supplied destinations. Because no outbound request rate limiting was enforced, unauthenticated remote attackers could repeatedly invoke these commands to generate unbounded HTTP traffic toward arbitrary third-party targets, allowing the Cowrie honeypot to be abused as a denial-of-service amplification node and masking the attacker’s true source address behind the honeypot’s IP.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68700 | RAGFlow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68700</link><description>RAGFlow is an open-source RAG (Retrieval-Augmented Generation) engine. In versions prior to 0.23.0, a low-privileged authenticated user (normal login account) can execute arbitrary system commands on the server host process via the frontend Canvas CodeExec component, completely bypassing sandbox isolation. This occurs because untrusted data (stdout) is parsed using eval() with no filtering or sandboxing. The intended design was to "automatically convert string results into Python objects," but this effectively executes attacker-controlled code. Additional endpoints lack access control or contain inverted permission logic, significantly expanding the attack surface and enabling chained exploitation. Version 0.23.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7331 | PKrystian Full-Stack-Bank User sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7331</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in PKrystian Full-Stack-Bank up to bf73a0179e3ff07c0d7dc35297cea0be0e5b1317. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component User Handler. Performing manipulation results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The patch is named 25c9965a872c704f3a9475488dc5d3196902199a. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-10145 | Gargoyle 1.5.x Authenticated OS Command Execution via run_commands.sh</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10145</link><description>Gargoyle router management utility versions 1.5.x contain an authenticated OS command execution vulnerability in /utility/run_commands.sh. The application fails to properly restrict or validate input supplied via the 'commands' parameter, allowing an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary shell commands on the underlying system. Successful exploitation may result in full compromise of the device, including unauthorized access to system files and execution of attacker-controlled commands.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53235 | WordPress Easy Social plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53235</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in osuthorpe Easy Social allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Easy Social: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28949 | WordPress Mediabay - WordPress Media Library Folders &amp;lt;= 1.4 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28949</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Codedraft Mediabay - WordPress Media Library Folders allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Mediabay - WordPress Media Library Folders: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28973 | WordPress Pro Bulk Watermark Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Path Traversal Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28973</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in AA-Team Pro Bulk Watermark Plugin for WordPress allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Pro Bulk Watermark Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30628 | WordPress Amazon Affiliates Addon for WPBakery Page Builder (formerly Visual Composer) plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30628</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in AA-Team Amazon Affiliates Addon for WPBakery Page Builder (formerly Visual Composer) allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Amazon Affiliates Addon for WPBakery Page Builder (formerly Visual Composer): from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31054 | WordPress Bloggie theme &amp;lt;= 2.0.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31054</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Themefy Bloggie allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Bloggie: from n/a through 2.0.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47566 | WordPress ZoomSounds plugin &amp;lt;= 6.91 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47566</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ZoomSounds allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ZoomSounds: from n/a through 6.91.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50053 | WordPress Blappsta Mobile App Plugin – Your native, mobile iPhone App and Android App Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.8.8.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50053</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in nebelhorn Blappsta Mobile App Plugin &amp; Your native, mobile iPhone App and Android App allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Blappsta Mobile App Plugin &amp;#8211; Your native, mobile iPhone App and Android App: from n/a through 0.8.8.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52739 | WordPress Sala theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52739</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in uxper Sala allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Sala: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23667 | WordPress custom-post-edit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23667</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Christopher Churchill allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects custom-post-edit: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23705 | WordPress Zielke Design Project Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23705</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Terry Zielke Zielke Design Project Gallery allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Zielke Design Project Gallery: from n/a through 2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23707 | WordPress En Masse plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23707</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Matamko En Masse allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects En Masse: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23719 | WordPress ZhinaTwitterWidget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23719</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in zckevin ZhinaTwitterWidget allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ZhinaTwitterWidget: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23757 | WordPress ZD Scribd iPaper plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23757</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Proloy Chakroborty ZD Scribd iPaper allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ZD Scribd iPaper: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66144 | WordPress Worker for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66144</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in merkulove Worker for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Worker for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66145 | WordPress Worker for WPBakery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66145</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in merkulove Worker for WPBakery allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Worker for WPBakery: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66146 | WordPress Logger for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66146</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in merkulove Logger for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Logger for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66148 | WordPress Conformer for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66148</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in merkulove Conformer for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Conformer for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15394 | iCMS POST Parameter ConfigAdmincp.php save code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15394</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in iCMS up to 8.0.0. Affected is the function Save of the file app/config/ConfigAdmincp.php of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument config results in code injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:22:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36903 | Selea CarPlateServer 4.0.1.6 Local Privilege Escalation via Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36903</link><description>Selea CarPlateServer 4.0.1.6 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the Windows service configuration that allows local users to potentially execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the service's unquoted binary path by inserting malicious code in the system root path that could execute with LocalSystem privileges during application startup or reboot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36904 | Selea CarPlateServer 4.0.1.6 Remote Program Execution via Configuration Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36904</link><description>Selea CarPlateServer 4.0.1.6 contains a remote program execution vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary Windows binaries by manipulating the NO_LIST_EXE_PATH configuration parameter. Attackers can bypass authentication through the /cps/ endpoint and modify server configuration, including changing admin passwords and executing system commands.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47725 | STVS ProVision 5.9.10 Authenticated Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via Files Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47725</link><description>STVS ProVision 5.9.10 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the 'files' POST parameter that allows authenticated attackers to inject arbitrary HTML code. Attackers can exploit the unvalidated input to execute malicious scripts within a user's browser session in the context of the affected site.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47726 | NuCom 11N Wireless Router 5.07.90 Privilege Escalation via Configuration Backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47726</link><description>NuCom 11N Wireless Router 5.07.90 contains a privilege escalation vulnerability that allows non-privileged users to access administrative credentials through the configuration backup endpoint. Attackers can send a crafted HTTP GET request to the backup configuration page with a specific cookie to retrieve and decode the admin password in Base64 format.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47740 | KZTech JT3500V 4G LTE CPE 2.0.1 Insufficient Session Expiration Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47740</link><description>KZTech JT3500V 4G LTE CPE 2.0.1 contains a session management vulnerability that allows attackers to reuse old session credentials without proper expiration. Attackers can exploit the weak session handling to maintain unauthorized access and potentially compromise device authentication mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47741 | ZBL EPON ONU Broadband Router V100R001 Privilege Escalation via Configuration Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47741</link><description>ZBL EPON ONU Broadband Router V100R001 contains a privilege escalation vulnerability that allows limited administrative users to elevate access by sending requests to configuration endpoints. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability by accessing the configuration backup or password page to disclose the super user password and gain additional privileged functionalities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47742 | Epic Games Psyonix Rocket League &amp;lt;=1.95 Elevation of Privileges via Insecure Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47742</link><description>Epic Games Psyonix Rocket League &lt;=1.95 contains an insecure permissions vulnerability that allows authenticated users to modify executable files with full access permissions. Attackers can leverage the 'F' (Full) flag for the 'Authenticated Users' group to change executable files and potentially escalate system privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47743 | COMMAX Biometric Access Control System 1.0.0 Reflected XSS via Cookie Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47743</link><description>COMMAX Biometric Access Control System 1.0.0 contains an unauthenticated reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in cookie parameters 'CMX_ADMIN_NM' and 'CMX_COMPLEX_NM'. Attackers can inject malicious HTML and JavaScript code into these cookie values to execute arbitrary scripts in a victim's browser session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47744 | Cypress Solutions CTM-200/CTM-ONE 1.3.6 Hard-coded Credentials Remote Root</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47744</link><description>Cypress Solutions CTM-200/CTM-ONE 1.3.6 contains hard-coded credentials vulnerability in Linux distribution that exposes root access. Attackers can exploit the static 'Chameleon' password to gain remote root access via Telnet or SSH on affected devices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47745 | Cypress Solutions CTM-200 2.7.1 Root Remote OS Command Injection via Firmware Upgrade</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47745</link><description>Cypress Solutions CTM-200 2.7.1 contains an authenticated command injection vulnerability in the firmware upgrade script that allows remote attackers to execute shell commands. Attackers can exploit the 'fw_url' parameter in the ctm-config-upgrade.sh script to inject and execute arbitrary commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47747 | meterN 1.2.3 Authenticated Remote Code Execution via Admin Scripts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47747</link><description>meterN 1.2.3 contains an authenticated remote code execution vulnerability in admin_meter2.php and admin_indicator2.php scripts. Attackers can exploit the 'COMMANDx' and 'LIVECOMMANDx' POST parameters to execute arbitrary system commands with administrative privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15393 | Kohana KodiCMS Layout API Endpoint file.php save code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15393</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Kohana KodiCMS up to 13.82.135. This impacts the function Save of the file cms/modules/kodicms/classes/kodicms/model/file.php of the component Layout API Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument content leads to code injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34467 | ZwiiCMS &amp;lt; 13.7.00 Lock Persistence Authenticated DoS Against Administrative Pages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34467</link><description>ZwiiCMS versions prior to 13.7.00 contain a denial-of-service vulnerability in multiple administrative endpoints due to improper authorization checks combined with flawed resource state management. When an authenticated low-privilege user requests an administrative page, the application returns "404 Not Found" as expected, but incorrectly acquires and associates a temporary lock on the targeted resource with the attacker session prior to authorization. This lock prevents other users, including administrators, from accessing the affected functionality until the attacker navigates away or the session is terminated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34468 | libcoap Stack-Based Buffer Overflow in Address Resolution DoS or Potential RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34468</link><description>libcoap versions up to and including 4.3.5, prior to commit 30db3ea, contain a stack-based buffer overflow in address resolution when attacker-controlled hostname data is copied into a fixed 256-byte stack buffer without proper bounds checking. A remote attacker can trigger a crash and potentially achieve remote code execution depending on compiler options and runtime memory protections. Exploitation requires the proxy logic to be enabled (i.e., the proxy request handling code path in an application using libcoap).</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66149 | WordPress UnGrabber plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66149</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in merkulove UnGrabber allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects UnGrabber: from n/a through 3.1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66150 | WordPress Appender plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66150</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in merkulove Appender allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Appender: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66151 | WordPress Countdowner for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66151</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in merkulove Countdowner for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Countdowner for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66152 | WordPress Criptopayer for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66152</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in merkulove Criptopayer for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Criptopayer for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66153 | WordPress Headinger for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66153</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in merkulove Headinger for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Headinger for Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15392 | Kohana KodiCMS Search API Endpoint page.php like sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15392</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Kohana KodiCMS up to 13.82.135. This affects the function like of the file cms/modules/pages/classes/kodicms/model/page.php of the component Search API Endpoint. Executing manipulation of the argument keyword can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15391 | D-Link DIR-806A SSDP Request ssdpcgi_main command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15391</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-806A 100CNb11. Affected is the function ssdpcgi_main of the component SSDP Request Handler. This manipulation causes command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49337 | WordPress Dashboard Beacon plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49337</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in janhenckens Dashboard Beacon allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Dashboard Beacon: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49355 | WordPress Accessibility Press plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49355</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ikaes Accessibility Press allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Accessibility Press: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59135 | WordPress Behance Portfolio Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59135</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in eLEOPARD Behance Portfolio Manager allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Behance Portfolio Manager: from n/a through 1.7.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62989 | WordPress Cooked plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62989</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Boxy Studio Cooked allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Cooked: from n/a through 1.11.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23608 | WordPress LIVE TV plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23608</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Omar Mohamed Mohamoud LIVE TV allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects LIVE TV: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25262 | elinicksic Razgover Chat Message send.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25262</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in elinicksic Razgover up to db37dfc5c82f023a40f2f7834ded6633fb2b5262. This affects an unknown part of the file Chattify/send.php of the component Chat Message Handler. Such manipulation of the argument msg leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. This product utilizes a rolling release system for continuous delivery, and as such, version information for affected or updated releases is not disclosed. The name of the patch is 995dd89d0e3ec5522966724be23a5d58ca1bdac3. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59138 | WordPress Genemy theme &amp;lt;= 1.6.6 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59138</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Jthemes Genemy allows Server Side Request Forgery.This issue affects Genemy: from n/a through 1.6.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62088 | WordPress WordPress &amp;amp; WooCommerce Scraper plugin, Import Data from Any Site plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62088</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in extendons WordPress &amp; WooCommerce Scraper Plugin, Import Data from Any Site allows Server Side Request Forgery.This issue affects WordPress &amp; WooCommerce Scraper Plugin, Import Data from Any Site: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66154 | WordPress Couponer for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66154</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in merkulove Couponer for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Couponer for Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66155 | WordPress Questionar for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66155</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in merkulove Questionar for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Questionar for Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66156 | WordPress Watcher for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66156</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in merkulove Watcher for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Watcher for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66157 | WordPress Slider for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66157</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in merkulove Slider for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Slider for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66158 | WordPress Gmaper for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66158</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in merkulove Gmaper for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Gmaper for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66159 | WordPress Walker for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66159</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in merkulove Walker for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Walker for Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66160 | WordPress Select Graphist for Elementor	 Graphist for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66160</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in merkulove Select Graphist for Elementor Graphist for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Select Graphist for Elementor Graphist for Elementor: from n/a through 1.2.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62099 | WordPress Signature Add-On for Gravity Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62099</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Approveme Signature Add-On for Gravity Forms allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Signature Add-On for Gravity Forms: from n/a through 1.8.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62874 | WordPress AnyComment plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62874</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Alexander AnyComment allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects AnyComment: from n/a through 0.3.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63021 | WordPress Valenti Engine plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63021</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in codetipi Valenti Engine allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Valenti Engine: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49339 | WordPress Direct Payments WP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49339</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Digages Direct Payments WP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Direct Payments WP: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49340 | WordPress Direct Payments WP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49340</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Digages Direct Payments WP allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Direct Payments WP: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49352 | WordPress Order Cancellation &amp;amp; Returns for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.10 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49352</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in YoOhw Studio Order Cancellation &amp; Returns for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Order Cancellation &amp; Returns for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.1.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62078 | WordPress Easy Upload Files During Checkout plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62078</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Fahad Mahmood Easy Upload Files During Checkout allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Easy Upload Files During Checkout: from n/a through 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62083 | WordPress BoomDevs WordPress Coming Soon plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62083</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in WP Messiah BoomDevs WordPress Coming Soon Plugin allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects BoomDevs WordPress Coming Soon Plugin: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62101 | WordPress Pardakht Delkhah plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62101</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Omid Shamloo Pardakht Delkhah allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Pardakht Delkhah: from n/a through 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62113 | WordPress Co-marquage service-public.fr plugin &amp;lt;= 0.5.77 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62113</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in emendo_seb Co-marquage service-public.Fr allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Co-marquage service-public.Fr: from n/a through 0.5.77.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62115 | WordPress Hide Plugins plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62115</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThemeBoy Hide Plugins allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Hide Plugins: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62123 | WordPress WP Gmail SMTP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62123</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ink themes WP Gmail SMTP allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects WP Gmail SMTP: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63038 | WordPress WP Custom Admin Interface plugin &amp;lt;= 7.40 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63038</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Northern Beaches Websites WP Custom Admin Interface allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Custom Admin Interface: from n/a through 7.40.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49356 | WordPress Orders Chat for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49356</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mykola Lukin Orders Chat for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Orders Chat for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59130 | WordPress Appointify plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59130</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Appointify allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Appointify: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62087 | WordPress Sticky Notes for WP Dashboard plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62087</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Web Builder 143 Sticky Notes for WP Dashboard allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Sticky Notes for WP Dashboard: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62130 | WordPress Accordion Slider Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62130</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPdiscover Accordion Slider Gallery allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Accordion Slider Gallery: from n/a through 2.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62131 | WordPress Tasty Recipes Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62131</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Strategy11 Team Tasty Recipes Lite allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Tasty Recipes Lite: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62132 | WordPress Tasty Recipes Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62132</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Strategy11 Team Tasty Recipes Lite allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Tasty Recipes Lite: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62133 | WordPress FormFacade plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62133</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Manidoraisamy FormFacade allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects FormFacade: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62751 | WordPress Vireo theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.24 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62751</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Extend Themes Vireo allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Vireo: from n/a through 1.0.24.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63004 | WordPress All in One Accessibility plugin &amp;lt;= 1.14 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63004</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Skynet Technologies USA LLC All in One Accessibility allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects All in One Accessibility: from n/a through 1.14.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63040 | WordPress Post Snippets plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.11 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63040</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Saad Iqbal Post Snippets allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Post Snippets: from n/a through 4.0.11.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62084 | WordPress iNext Woo Pincode Checker plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62084</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Imdad Next Web iNext Woo Pincode Checker allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects iNext Woo Pincode Checker: from n/a through 2.3.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:01:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62089 | WordPress Mergado Pack plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62089</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in MERGADO Mergado Pack allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Mergado Pack: from n/a through 4.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:01:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63014 | WordPress Gmedia Photo Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.24.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63014</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Serhii Pasyuk Gmedia Photo Gallery allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Gmedia Photo Gallery: from n/a through 1.24.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:01:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64699 | An incorrect NULL DACL issue exists in SevenCs ORCA G2 2.0.1.35 (EC2007 Kernel v5.22). The regService process, which runs with SYSTEM privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64699</link><description>An incorrect NULL DACL issue exists in SevenCs ORCA G2 2.0.1.35 (EC2007 Kernel v5.22). The regService process, which runs with SYSTEM privileges, applies a Security Descriptor to a device object with no explicitly configured DACL. This condition could allow an attacker to perform unauthorized raw disk operations, which could lead to system disruption (DoS) and exposure of sensitive data, and may facilitate local privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:01:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62080 | WordPress Live Shopping &amp;amp; Shoppable Videos For WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62080</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Channelize.Io Team Live Shopping &amp; Shoppable Videos For WooCommerce allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Live Shopping &amp; Shoppable Videos For WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62143 | WordPress Post Video Players plugin &amp;lt;= 1.163 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62143</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in nicashmu Post Video Players allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Post Video Players: from n/a through 1.163.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62148 | WordPress Robots.txt rewrite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62148</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Eugen Bobrowski Robots.Txt rewrite allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Robots.Txt rewrite: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62150 | WordPress History Timeline plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62150</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Themesawesome History Timeline allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects History Timeline: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49338 | WordPress Flowbox plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49338</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Flowbox allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Flowbox: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61037 | A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in SevenCs ORCA G2 2.0.1.35 (EC2007 Kernel v5.22). The flaw is a Time-of-Check Time-of-Use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61037</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in SevenCs ORCA G2 2.0.1.35 (EC2007 Kernel v5.22). The flaw is a Time-of-Check Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) race condition in the license management logic. The regService process, which runs with SYSTEM privileges, creates a fixed directory and writes files without verifying whether the path is an NTFS reparse point. By exploiting this race condition, an attacker can replace the target directory with a junction pointing to a user-controlled path. This causes the SYSTEM-level process to drop binaries in a location fully controlled by the attacker, allowing arbitrary code execution with SYSTEM privileges. The vulnerability can be exploited by any standard user with only a single UAC confirmation, making it highly practical and dangerous in real-world environments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62079 | WordPress WP Export Categories &amp;amp; Taxonomies plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62079</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Damian WP Export Categories &amp; Taxonomies allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Export Categories &amp;amp; Taxonomies: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62114 | WordPress Download Media Library plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62114</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Marcelo Torres Download Media Library allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Download Media Library: from n/a through 0.2.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62116 | WordPress AI Copilot plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62116</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Quadlayers AI Copilot allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects AI Copilot: from n/a through 1.4.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62122 | WordPress Trash Duplicate and 301 Redirect plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62122</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Solwininfotech Trash Duplicate and 301 Redirect allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Trash Duplicate and 301 Redirect: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62126 | WordPress Varnish/Nginx Proxy Caching plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.3 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62126</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Razvan Stanga Varnish/Nginx Proxy Caching allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Varnish/Nginx Proxy Caching: from n/a through 1.8.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62154 | WordPress AI Content Writing Assistant (Content Writer, ChatGPT, Image Generator) All in One plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62154</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Recorp AI Content Writing Assistant (Content Writer, ChatGPT, Image Generator) All in One allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects AI Content Writing Assistant (Content Writer, ChatGPT, Image Generator) All in One: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62747 | WordPress Featured Image Generator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62747</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Aum Watcharapon Featured Image Generator allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Featured Image Generator: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15390 | PHPGurukul Small CRM edit-user.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15390</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in PHPGurukul Small CRM 4.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/edit-user.php. The manipulation results in missing authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49334 | WordPress MyD Delivery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49334</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Eduardo Villão MyD Delivery allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects MyD Delivery: from n/a through 1.3.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59136 | WordPress Gerencianet Oficial plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59136</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Efí Bank Gerencianet Oficial allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Gerencianet Oficial: from n/a through 3.1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62092 | WordPress Wiremo plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.99 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62092</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Wiremo allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Wiremo: from n/a through 1.4.99.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62129 | WordPress RestroPress plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.4.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62129</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Magnigenie RestroPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects RestroPress: from n/a through 3.2.4.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62755 | WordPress GS Portfolio for Envato plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62755</link><description>Unauthenticated Broken Access Control in GS Portfolio for Envato &lt;= 1.4.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62081 | WordPress Live Shopping &amp;amp; Shoppable Videos For WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62081</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Channelize.Io Team Live Shopping &amp; Shoppable Videos For WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Live Shopping &amp; Shoppable Videos For WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62139 | WordPress Terms descriptions plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.9 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62139</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Vladimir Statsenko Terms descriptions allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Terms descriptions: from n/a through 3.4.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62141 | WordPress Wawp plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62141</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in 101gen Wawp allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Wawp: from n/a through 4.0.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62145 | WordPress DMCA Protection Badge plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62145</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in NewClarity DMCA Protection Badge allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects DMCA Protection Badge: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62147 | WordPress Realbig plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62147</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Nik Melnik Realbig allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Realbig: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:26:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63016 | WordPress QuadLayers TikTok Feed plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63016</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Quadlayers QuadLayers TikTok Feed allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects QuadLayers TikTok Feed: from n/a through 4.6.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:26:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63022 | WordPress Simple Like Page plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63022</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Illia Simple Like Page allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Simple Like Page: from n/a through 1.5.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:26:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63031 | WordPress EasyTest plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63031</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Grids EasyTest allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects EasyTest: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:26:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63001 | WordPress Hotel Booking plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63001</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in nicdark Hotel Booking allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Hotel Booking: from n/a through 3.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:26:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63053 | WordPress Master Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.9.9.4 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63053</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Jewel Theme Master Addons for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Master Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 2.0.9.9.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49349 | WordPress Reuters Direct plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49349</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Reuters News Agency Reuters Direct allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Reuters Direct: from n/a through 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62098 | WordPress Portfolio Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62098</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Totalsoft Portfolio Gallery allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Portfolio Gallery: from n/a through 1.4.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62091 | WordPress Serial Codes Generator and Validator with WooCommerce Support plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62091</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Vollstart Serial Codes Generator and Validator with WooCommerce Support allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Serial Codes Generator and Validator with WooCommerce Support: from n/a through 2.8.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62108 | WordPress Add Custom Codes plugin &amp;lt;= 4.80 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62108</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in SaifuMak Add Custom Codes allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Add Custom Codes: from n/a through 4.80.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62888 | WordPress WP Attachments plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62888</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Marco Milesi WP Attachments allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Attachments: from n/a through 5.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62117 | WordPress EasyIndex plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1704 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62117</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jayce53 EasyIndex easyindex allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects EasyIndex: from n/a through 1.1.1704.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62120 | WordPress OpenHook plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62120</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rick Beckman OpenHook allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects OpenHook: from n/a through 4.3.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62134 | WordPress Contact Form Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62134</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in A WP Life Contact Form Widget allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Contact Form Widget: from n/a through 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62138 | WordPress WP Advanced PDF plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Other vulnerability Type vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62138</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CedCommerce WP Advanced PDF allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Advanced PDF: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59003 | WordPress Black Rider theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59003</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Inkthemescom Black Rider allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Black Rider: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62119 | WordPress Add Featured Image Custom Link plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62119</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ViitorCloud Technologies Pvt Ltd Add Featured Image Custom Link allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Add Featured Image Custom Link: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62121 | WordPress Logo Slider , Logo Carousel , Logo showcase , Client Logo plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62121</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Imran Emu Logo Slider , Logo Carousel , Logo showcase , Client Logo allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Logo Slider , Logo Carousel , Logo showcase , Client Logo: from n/a through 1.8.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62144 | WordPress Core Web Vitals &amp;amp; PageSpeed Booster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.27 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62144</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mohammed Kaludi Core Web Vitals &amp; PageSpeed Booster allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Core Web Vitals &amp; PageSpeed Booster: from n/a through 1.0.27.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62124 | WordPress WP Post Signature plugin &amp;lt;= 0.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62124</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Soli WP Post Signature allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Post Signature: from n/a through 0.4.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62140 | WordPress Locatoraid Store Locator plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.65 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62140</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Plainware Locatoraid Store Locator allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Locatoraid Store Locator: from n/a through 3.9.65.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62750 | WordPress WooCommerce Parcelas plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62750</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Filipe Seabra WooCommerce Parcelas allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects WooCommerce Parcelas: from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62095 | WordPress Bootstrap Modals plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62095</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Neilgee Bootstrap Modals allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Bootstrap Modals: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62096 | WordPress Maximum Products per User for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62096</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPFactory Maximum Products per User for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Maximum Products per User for WooCommerce: from n/a through 4.4.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62097 | WordPress SEO Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62097</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SEOthemes SEO Slider allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects SEO Slider: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62142 | WordPress Cincopa video and media plug-in plugin &amp;lt;= 1.163 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62142</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in nicashmu Cincopa video and media plugin allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Cincopa video and media plug-in: from n/a through 1.163.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62149 | WordPress Add Custom Codes plugin &amp;lt;= 4.80 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62149</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SaifuMak Add Custom Codes allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Add Custom Codes: from n/a through 4.80.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63020 | WordPress Postie plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.73 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63020</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wayne Allen Postie postie allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Postie: from n/a through 1.9.73.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49357 | WordPress Audiomack plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49357</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Audiomack allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Audiomack: from n/a through 1.4.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62111 | WordPress Extra Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62111</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Webvitaly Extra Shortcodes allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Extra Shortcodes: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62118 | WordPress AdWords Conversion Tracking Code plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62118</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in kcseopro AdWords Conversion Tracking Code allows Stored XSS.This issue affects AdWords Conversion Tracking Code: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62125 | WordPress Custom Background Changer plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62125</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Anshul Gangrade Custom Background Changer custom-background-changer allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Custom Background Changer: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62742 | WordPress Curator.io plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62742</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Curator.Io allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Curator.Io: from n/a through 1.9.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62743 | WordPress MyBookTable Bookstore plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62743</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in zookatron MyBookTable Bookstore allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MyBookTable Bookstore: from n/a through 3.5.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62744 | WordPress Page Title Splitter plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62744</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Chris Steman Page Title Splitter allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Page Title Splitter: from n/a through 2.5.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:41:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62990 | WordPress Livemesh Addons for Beaver Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62990</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Livemesh Livemesh Addons for Beaver Builder addons-for-beaver-builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Livemesh Addons for Beaver Builder: from n/a through 3.9.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:41:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49358 | WordPress Content Fetcher plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49358</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ruhul Amin Content Fetcher allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Content Fetcher: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62748 | WordPress Web and WooCommerce Addons for WPBakery Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62748</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Genetech Products Web and WooCommerce Addons for WPBakery Builder allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Web and WooCommerce Addons for WPBakery Builder: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62749 | WordPress User Specific Content plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62749</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bainternet User Specific Content allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects User Specific Content: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62135 | WordPress Responsive Block Control plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62135</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in landwire Responsive Block Control allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Responsive Block Control: from n/a through 1.2.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62752 | WordPress Calendar.online / Kalender.digital plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62752</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in kalender.Digital Calendar.Online / Kalender.Digital allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Calendar.Online / Kalender.Digital: from n/a through 1.0.11.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62756 | WordPress The Moneytizer plugin &amp;lt;= 10.0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62756</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in lvaudore The Moneytizer allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects The Moneytizer: from n/a through 10.0.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62757 | WordPress WebMan Amplifier plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.12 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62757</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WebMan Design | Oliver Juhas WebMan Amplifier allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects WebMan Amplifier: from n/a through 1.5.12.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62991 | WordPress Minamaze theme &amp;lt;= 1.10.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62991</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThinkUpThemes Minamaze allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Minamaze: from n/a through 1.10.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63032 | WordPress Consulting theme &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63032</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThinkUpThemes Consulting allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Consulting: from n/a through 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15389 | QNO Technology｜VPN Firewall - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15389</link><description>VPN Firewall developed by QNO Technology has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary OS commands and execute them on the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15388 | QNO Technology｜VPN Firewall - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15388</link><description>VPN Firewall developed by QNO Technology has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary OS commands and execute them on the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49028 | WordPress Zoho ZeptoMail plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49028</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Zoho Mail Zoho ZeptoMail allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Zoho ZeptoMail: from n/a through 3.3.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62136 | WordPress Melos theme &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62136</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThinkUpThemes Melos allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Melos: from n/a through 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62992 | WordPress Everest Backup plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62992</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Everest themes Everest Backup allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Everest Backup: from n/a through 2.3.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62137 | WordPress Shuttle theme &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62137</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Shuttlethemes Shuttle allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Shuttle: from n/a through 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62758 | WordPress Funnelforms Free plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62758</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Funnelforms Funnelforms Free allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Funnelforms Free: from n/a through 3.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62759 | WordPress Series plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62759</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Justin Tadlock Series allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Series: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62760 | WordPress BuddyPress Activity Shortcode plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62760</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BuddyDev BuddyPress Activity Shortcode allows Stored XSS.This issue affects BuddyPress Activity Shortcode: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63000 | WordPress Sermon Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.30.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63000</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP for church Sermon Manager allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Sermon Manager: from n/a through 2.30.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62146 | WordPress MX Time Zone Clocks plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62146</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Maksym Marko MX Time Zone Clocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MX Time Zone Clocks: from n/a through 5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62761 | WordPress Knowledge Base documentation &amp;amp; wiki plugin – BasePress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.17.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62761</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BasePress Knowledge Base documentation &amp; wiki plugin – BasePress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Knowledge Base documentation &amp; wiki plugin – BasePress: from n/a through 2.17.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63005 | WordPress WordPress Tooltips plugin &amp;lt;= 10.7.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63005</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tomas WordPress Tooltips allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WordPress Tooltips: from n/a through 10.7.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15387 | QNO Technology｜VPN Firewall - Insufficient Entropy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15387</link><description>VPN Firewall developed by QNO Technology has a Insufficient Entropy vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to obtain any logged-in user session through brute-force attacks and subsequently log into the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15017 | A vulnerability exists in serial device servers where active debug code remains enabled in the UART interface. An attacker with physical acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15017</link><description>A vulnerability exists in serial device servers where active debug code remains enabled in the UART interface. An attacker with physical access to the device can directly connect to the UART interface and, without authentication, user interaction, or execution conditions, gain unauthorized access to internal debug functionality. Exploitation is low complexity and allows an attacker to execute privileged operations and access sensitive system resources, resulting in a high impact to the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the affected device. No security impact to external or dependent systems has been identified.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2026 | The NPort 6100-G2/6200-G2 Series is affected by a high-severity vulnerability (CVE-2025-2026) that allows remote attackers to execute a null...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2026</link><description>The NPort 6100-G2/6200-G2 Series is affected by a high-severity vulnerability (CVE-2025-2026) that allows remote attackers to execute a null byte injection through the device’s web API. This may lead to an unexpected device reboot and result in a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.

An authenticated remote attacker with web read-only privileges can exploit the vulnerable API to inject malicious input. Successful exploitation may cause the device to reboot, disrupting normal operations and causing a temporary denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1977 | The NPort 6100-G2/6200-G2 Series is affected by an execution with unnecessary privileges vulnerability (CVE-2025-1977) that allows an authen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1977</link><description>The NPort 6100-G2/6200-G2 Series is affected by an execution with unnecessary privileges vulnerability (CVE-2025-1977) that allows an authenticated user with read-only access to perform unauthorized configuration changes through the MCC (Moxa CLI Configuration) tool. The issue can be exploited remotely over the network with low-attack complexity and no user interaction but requires specific system conditions or configurations to be present. Successful exploitation may result in changes to device settings that were not intended to be permitted for the affected user role, potentially leading to a high impact on the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the device. No impact on other systems has been identified.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15269 | FontForge SFD File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15269</link><description>FontForge SFD File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of FontForge. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SFD files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-28564.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15270 | FontForge SFD File Parsing Improper Validation of Array Index Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15270</link><description>FontForge SFD File Parsing Improper Validation of Array Index Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of FontForge. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SFD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated array. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-28563.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15271 | FontForge SFD File Parsing Improper Validation of Array Index Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15271</link><description>FontForge SFD File Parsing Improper Validation of Array Index Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of FontForge. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SFD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated array. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-28562.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15272 | FontForge SFD File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15272</link><description>FontForge SFD File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of FontForge. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SFD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-28547.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15273 | FontForge PFB File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15273</link><description>FontForge PFB File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of FontForge. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PFB files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-28546.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15274 | FontForge SFD File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15274</link><description>FontForge SFD File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of FontForge. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SFD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-28544.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15275 | FontForge SFD File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15275</link><description>FontForge SFD File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of FontForge. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SFD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-28543.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15276 | FontForge SFD File Parsing Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15276</link><description>FontForge SFD File Parsing Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of FontForge. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SFD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-28198.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15277 | FontForge GUtils SGI File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15277</link><description>FontForge GUtils SGI File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of FontForge. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of scanlines within SGI files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-27920.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15278 | FontForge GUtils XBM File Parsing Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15278</link><description>FontForge GUtils XBM File Parsing Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of FontForge. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of pixels within XBM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an integer overflow before allocating a buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-27865.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15279 | FontForge GUtils BMP File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15279</link><description>FontForge GUtils BMP File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of FontForge. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of pixels within BMP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-27517.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15280 | FontForge SFD File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15280</link><description>FontForge SFD File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of FontForge. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SFD files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-28525.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14783 | Easy Digital Downloads &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 - Unvalidated Redirect in Password Reset Flow via edd_redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14783</link><description>The Easy Digital Downloads plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unvalidated Redirect in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.2. This is due to insufficient validation on the redirect url supplied via the 'edd_redirect' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users with the password reset email to potentially malicious sites if they can successfully trick them into performing an action.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:55:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13029 | Knowband Mobile App Builder for wooCommerce &amp;lt; 3.0.0 – Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13029</link><description>The Knowband Mobile App Builder WordPress plugin before 3.0.0 does not have authorisation when deleting users via its REST API, allowing unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14434 | Ultimate Post Kit &amp;lt; 4.0.16 – Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post Content Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14434</link><description>The Ultimate Post Kit Addons for Elementor WordPress plugin before 4.0.16 exposes multiple AJAX “load more” endpoints such as upk_alex_grid_loadmore_posts without ensuring that posts to be displayed are published authentication. This allows an unauthenticated attacker to query arbitrary posts and retrieve rendered HTML content of private and unpublished ones.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49342 | WordPress Custom Style plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49342</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Wolfgang Häfelinger Custom Style allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Custom Style: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69277 | libsodium before ad3004e, in atypical use cases involving certain custom cryptography or untrusted data to crypto_core_ed25519_is_valid_poin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69277</link><description>libsodium before ad3004e, in atypical use cases involving certain custom cryptography or untrusted data to crypto_core_ed25519_is_valid_point, mishandles checks for whether an elliptic curve point is valid because it sometimes allows points that aren't in the main cryptograpbic group.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:55:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49353 | WordPress Noindex by Path plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49353</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Marcin Kijak Noindex by Path allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Noindex by Path: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:55:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49354 | WordPress Recent Posts From Each Category plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49354</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Mindstien Technologies Recent Posts From Each Category allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Recent Posts From Each Category: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68885 | WordPress Custom Post Status plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68885</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Page Carbajal Custom Post Status allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Custom Post Status: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49343 | WordPress Social Profilr plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49343</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Socialprofilr Social Profilr allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Social Profilr: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49344 | WordPress SensitiveTagCloud plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49344</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rene Ade SensitiveTagCloud allows Stored XSS.This issue affects SensitiveTagCloud: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49345 | WordPress WP-EasyArchives plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49345</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in mg12 WP-EasyArchives allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP-EasyArchives: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15375 | EyouCMS arcpagelist Ajax.php unserialize deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15375</link><description>A flaw has been found in EyouCMS up to 1.7.7. The impacted element is the function unserialize of the file application/api/controller/Ajax.php of the component arcpagelist Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument attstr can lead to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor is "[a]cknowledging the existence of the vulnerability, we have completed the fix and will release a new version, v1.7.8".</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:25:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15374 | EyouCMS Ask Module Ask.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15374</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in EyouCMS up to 1.7.7. The affected element is an unknown function of the file application/home/model/Ask.php of the component Ask Module. Performing manipulation of the argument content results in cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor is "[a]cknowledging the existence of the vulnerability, we have completed the fix and will release a new version, v1.7.8".</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49346 | WordPress Simple Archive Generator plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49346</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Peter Sterling Simple Archive Generator allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Simple Archive Generator: from n/a through 5.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59137 | WordPress Behance Portfolio Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59137</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in eLEOPARD Behance Portfolio Manager allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Behance Portfolio Manager: from n/a through 1.7.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15373 | EyouCMS function.php saveRemote server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15373</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in EyouCMS up to 1.7.7. Impacted is the function saveRemote of the file application/function.php. Such manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor is "[a]cknowledging the existence of the vulnerability, we have completed the fix and will release a new version, v1.7.8".</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15223 | Philipinho Simple-PHP-Blog login.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15223</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Philipinho Simple-PHP-Blog up to 94b5d3e57308bce5dfbc44c3edafa9811893d958. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /login.php. Performing manipulation of the argument Username results in cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure and makes clear that the product is "[f]or educational purposes only".</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15372 | youlaitech vue3-element-admin Notice index.vue cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15372</link><description>A weakness has been identified in youlaitech vue3-element-admin up to 3.4.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file src/views/system/notice/index.vue of the component Notice Handler. This manipulation causes cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68131 | CBORDecoder reuse can leak shareable values across decode calls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68131</link><description>cbor2 provides encoding and decoding for the Concise Binary Object Representation (CBOR) serialization format. Starting in version 3.0.0 and prior to version 5.8.0, whhen a CBORDecoder instance is reused across multiple decode operations, values marked with the shareable tag (28) persist in memory and can be accessed by subsequent CBOR messages using the sharedref tag (29). This allows an attacker-controlled message to read data from previously decoded messages if the decoder is reused across trust boundaries. Version 5.8.0 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11961 | OOBR and OOBW in pcap_ether_aton() in libpcap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11961</link><description>pcap_ether_aton() is an auxiliary function in libpcap, it takes a string argument and returns a fixed-size allocated buffer.  The string argument must be a well-formed MAC-48 address in one of the supported formats, but this requirement has been poorly documented.  If an application calls the function with an argument that deviates from the expected format, the function can read data beyond the end of the provided string and write data beyond the end of the allocated buffer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11964 | OOBW in utf_16le_to_utf_8_truncated() in libpcap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11964</link><description>On Windows only, if libpcap needs to convert a Windows error message to UTF-8 and the message includes characters that UTF-8 represents using 4 bytes, utf_16le_to_utf_8_truncated() can write data beyond the end of the provided buffer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15371 | Tenda i24 Shadow File hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15371</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda i24, 4G03 Pro, 4G05, 4G08, G0-8G-PoE, Nova MW5G and TEG5328F up to 65.10.15.6. Affected is an unknown function of the component Shadow File. Such manipulation with the input Fireitup leads to hard-coded credentials. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>