<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 01:17:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-1367 | MicroWord eScan Antivirus USB Password sprintf buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1367</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MicroWord eScan Antivirus 7.0.32 on Linux. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function sprintf of the component USB Password Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. An attack has to be approached locally. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 01:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1366 | MicroWord eScan Antivirus VirusPopUp strcpy stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1366</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MicroWord eScan Antivirus 7.0.32 on Linux and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function strcpy of the component VirusPopUp. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 01:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0591 | Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in CX-Programmer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0591</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability (CWE-125) was found in CX-Programmer. Attackers may be able to read sensitive information or cause an application crash by abusing this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 01:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1365 | GNU elfutils eu-readelf readelf.c process_symtab buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1365</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in GNU elfutils 0.192. This affects the function process_symtab of the file readelf.c of the component eu-readelf. The manipulation of the argument D/a leads to buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is 5e5c0394d82c53e97750fe7b18023e6f84157b81. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 23:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1364 | MicroWord eScan Antivirus USB Protection Service passPrompt stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1364</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in MicroWord eScan Antivirus 7.0.32 on Linux and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function passPrompt of the component USB Protection Service. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 23:07:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44044 | WordPress Oshine Modules plugin &amp;lt; 3.3.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44044</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Oshine Modules allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Oshine Modules: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22284 | WordPress LTL Freight Quotes – Unishippers Edition plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22284</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in enituretechnology LTL Freight Quotes – Unishippers Edition allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects LTL Freight Quotes – Unishippers Edition: from n/a through 2.5.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22286 | WordPress LTL Freight Quotes – Worldwide Express Edition plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.21 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22286</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in enituretechnology LTL Freight Quotes – Worldwide Express Edition allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects LTL Freight Quotes – Worldwide Express Edition: from n/a through 5.0.21.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22289 | WordPress LTL Freight Quotes – Unishippers Edition plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22289</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in NotFound LTL Freight Quotes – Unishippers Edition allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects LTL Freight Quotes – Unishippers Edition: from n/a through 2.5.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22290 | WordPress LTL Freight Quotes – FreightQuote Edition Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.11 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22290</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in enituretechnology LTL Freight Quotes – FreightQuote Edition allows SQL Injection. This issue affects LTL Freight Quotes – FreightQuote Edition: from n/a through 2.3.11.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22291 | WordPress LTL Freight Quotes – Worldwide Express Edition plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.20 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22291</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in enituretechnology LTL Freight Quotes – Worldwide Express Edition allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects LTL Freight Quotes – Worldwide Express Edition: from n/a through 5.0.20.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22676 | WordPress Upcasted S3 Offload plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22676</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in upcasted AWS S3 for WordPress Plugin – Upcasted allows Stored XSS. This issue affects AWS S3 for WordPress Plugin – Upcasted: from n/a through 3.0.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22680 | WordPress Ad Inserter Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.39 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22680</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Ad Inserter Pro allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Ad Inserter Pro: from n/a through 2.7.39.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22689 | WordPress Forex Calculators plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22689</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Levan Tarbor Forex Calculators allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Forex Calculators: from n/a through 1.3.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23975 | WordPress Botnet Attack Blocker plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23975</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Botnet Attack Blocker allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Botnet Attack Blocker: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26755 | WordPress WP Airbnb Review Slider Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26755</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in jgwhite33 WP Airbnb Review Slider allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects WP Airbnb Review Slider: from n/a through 3.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26759 | WordPress Content Snippet Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26759</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in alexvtn Content Snippet Manager allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Content Snippet Manager: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26761 | WordPress Easy Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26761</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HashThemes Easy Elementor Addons allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Easy Elementor Addons: from n/a through 2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26765 | WordPress Distance Based Shipping Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.22 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26765</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in enituretechnology Distance Based Shipping Calculator allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Distance Based Shipping Calculator: from n/a through 2.0.22.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26766 | WordPress Leyka plugin &amp;lt;= 3.31.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26766</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VaultDweller Leyka allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Leyka: from n/a through 3.31.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26767 | WordPress Qubely – Advanced Gutenberg Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.12 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26767</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themeum Qubely – Advanced Gutenberg Blocks allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Qubely – Advanced Gutenberg Blocks: from n/a through 1.8.12.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26768 | WordPress what3words Address Field plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.15 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26768</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in what3words what3words Address Field allows Stored XSS. This issue affects what3words Address Field: from n/a through 4.0.15.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26779 | WordPress Keep Backup Daily plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26779</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Fahad Mahmood Keep Backup Daily allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Keep Backup Daily: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1360 | Internet Web Solutions Sublime CRM HTTP POST Request inicio.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1360</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Internet Web Solutions Sublime CRM up to 20250207. Affected is an unknown function of the file /crm/inicio.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument msg_to leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 20:36:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1359 | SIAM Industria de Automação e Monitoramento qrcode.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1359</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SIAM Industria de Automação e Monitoramento SIAM 2.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /qrcode.jsp. The manipulation of the argument url leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 20:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1358 | Pix Software Vivaz cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1358</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Pix Software Vivaz 6.0.10. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 19:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1357 | Seventh D-Guard HTTP GET Request path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1357</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Seventh D-Guard up to 20250206. This affects an unknown part of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 18:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1356 | needyamin Library Card System card.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1356</link><description>A vulnerability was found in needyamin Library Card System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file card.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 17:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1355 | needyamin Library Card System Add Picture signup.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1355</link><description>A vulnerability was found in needyamin Library Card System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /signup.php of the component Add Picture. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 17:08:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1354 | Asus RT-N12E sysinfo.asp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1354</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Asus RT-N12E 2.0.0.19. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file sysinfo.asp. The manipulation of the argument SSID leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 15:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1353 | Kong Insomnia profapi.dll untrusted search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1353</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kong Insomnia up to 10.3.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing in the library profapi.dll. The manipulation leads to untrusted search path. An attack has to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 15:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1352 | GNU elfutils eu-readelf libdw_alloc.c __libdw_thread_tail memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1352</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in GNU elfutils 0.192 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function __libdw_thread_tail in the library libdw_alloc.c of the component eu-readelf. The manipulation of the argument w leads to memory corruption. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is 2636426a091bd6c6f7f02e49ab20d4cdc6bfc753. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 14:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1341 | PMWeb Setting weak password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1341</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in PMWeb 7.2.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation leads to weak password requirements. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to change the configuration settings. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 14:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1340 | TOTOLINK X18 cstecgi.cgi setPasswordCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1340</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK X18 9.1.0cu.2024_B20220329. Affected is the function setPasswordCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation as part of String leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 13:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1339 | TOTOLINK X18 cstecgi.cgi setL2tpdConfig os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1339</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X18 9.1.0cu.2024_B20220329. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setL2tpdConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument enable leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 12:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1338 | NUUO Camera handle_config.php print_file command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1338</link><description>A vulnerability was found in NUUO Camera up to 20250203. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function print_file of the file /handle_config.php. The manipulation of the argument log leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 11:16:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1337 | Eastnets PaymentSafe BIC Search cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1337</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Eastnets PaymentSafe 2.5.26.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component BIC Search. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 10:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1336 | CmsEasy image_admin.php deleteimg_action path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1336</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CmsEasy 7.7.7.9 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function deleteimg_action in the library lib/admin/image_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument imgname leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 09:10:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1335 | CmsEasy file_admin.php deleteimg_action path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1335</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in CmsEasy 7.7.7.9. Affected is the function deleteimg_action in the library lib/admin/file_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument imgname leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 04:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57971 | DataSourceResource.java in the SpagoBI API support in Knowage Server in KNOWAGE before 8.1.30 does not ensure that java:comp/env/jdbc/ occur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57971</link><description>DataSourceResource.java in the SpagoBI API support in Knowage Server in KNOWAGE before 8.1.30 does not ensure that java:comp/env/jdbc/ occurs at the beginning of a JNDI Name.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 03:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57970 | libarchive through 3.7.7 has a heap-based buffer over-read in header_gnu_longlink in archive_read_support_format_tar.c via a TAR archive bec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57970</link><description>libarchive through 3.7.7 has a heap-based buffer over-read in header_gnu_longlink in archive_read_support_format_tar.c via a TAR archive because it mishandles truncation in the middle of a GNU long linkname.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 03:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1332 | FastCMS Template Menu menu cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1332</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FastCMS up to 0.1.5 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /fastcms.html#/template/menu of the component Template Menu. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 01:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26793 | The Web GUI configuration panel of Hirsch (formerly Identiv and Viscount) Enterphone MESH through 2024 ships with default credentials (usern...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26793</link><description>The Web GUI configuration panel of Hirsch (formerly Identiv and Viscount) Enterphone MESH through 2024 ships with default credentials (username freedom, password viscount). The administrator is not prompted to change these credentials on initial configuration, and changing the credentials requires many steps. Attackers can use the credentials over the Internet via mesh.webadmin.MESHAdminServlet to gain access to dozens of Canadian and U.S. apartment buildings and obtain building residents' PII. NOTE: the Supplier's perspective is that the "vulnerable systems are not following manufacturers' recommendations to change the default password."</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13834 | Responsive Plus – Starter Templates, Advanced Features and Customizer Settings for Responsive Theme &amp;lt;= 3.1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Blind Server-Side Request Forgery via remote_request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13834</link><description>The Responsive Plus – Starter Templates, Advanced Features and Customizer Settings for Responsive Theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.4 via the 'remote_request' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 14:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0822 | Bit Assist &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Path Traversal to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Read via fileID Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0822</link><description>Bit Assist plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 via the fileID Parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 12:56:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10581 | DirectoryPress Frontend &amp;lt;= 2.7.9 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Listing Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10581</link><description>The DirectoryPress Frontend plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.9. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the dpfl_listingStatusChange() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update listing statuses via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 11:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13439 | Team – Team Members Showcase Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13439</link><description>The Team – Team Members Showcase Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the response() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 11:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13488 | LTL Freight Quotes – Estes Edition &amp;lt;= 3.3.7 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13488</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – Estes Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'dropship_edit_id' and 'edit_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 11:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13500 | WP Project Manager &amp;lt;= 2.6.17 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via orderby Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13500</link><description>The WP Project Manager – Task, team, and project management plugin featuring kanban board and gantt charts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘orderby’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.17 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 11:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12562 | s2Member Pro &amp;lt;= 241216 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12562</link><description>The s2Member Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 241216 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 's2member_pro_remote_op' vulnerable parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 09:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13752 | WP Project Manager  &amp;lt;= 2.6.17 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13752</link><description>The WP Project Manager – Task, team, and project management plugin featuring kanban board and gantt charts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check in the '/pm/v2/settings/notice' endpoint all versions up to, and including, 2.6.17. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to cause a persistent denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 09:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1005 | ElementsKit Elementor addons &amp;lt;= 3.4.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Image Accordion Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1005</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Image Accordion widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 09:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13525 | Customer Email Verification for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.9.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13525</link><description>The Customer Email Verification for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.4 via Shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including emails as well as hashed passwords of any user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 08:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13563 | Front End Users &amp;lt;= 3.2.30 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via forgot-password Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13563</link><description>The Front End Users plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's forgot-password shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 08:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0935 | Media Library Folders &amp;lt;= 8.3.0 - Missing Authorization to Plugin Settings Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0935</link><description>The Media Library Folders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin settings change due to a missing capability check on several AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to change plugin settings related to things such as IP-blocking.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 08:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22208 | Extension - joomsky.com - SQL injection in JS jobs component version 1.1.5 - 1.4.3 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22208</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in the JS Jobs plugin versions 1.1.5-1.4.3 for Joomla allows authenticated attackers (administrator) to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the 'filter_email' parameter in the GDPR Erase Data Request search feature.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 08:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22209 | Extension - joomsky.com - SQL injection in JS jobs component version 1.1.5 - 1.4.3 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22209</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in the JS Jobs plugin versions 1.1.5-1.4.3 for Joomla allows authenticated attackers (administrator) to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the 'searchpaymentstatus' parameter in the Employer Payment History search feature.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 08:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13513 | Oliver POS – A WooCommerce Point of Sale (POS) &amp;lt;= 2.4.2.3 - Sensitive Information Exposure to Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13513</link><description>The Oliver POS – A WooCommerce Point of Sale (POS) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.2.3 via the logging functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including the plugin's clientToken, which in turn can be used to change user account information including emails and account type. This allows attackers to then change account passwords resulting in a complete site takeover. Version 2.4.2.3 disabled logging but left sites with existing log files vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 07:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13208 | WP Google Map &amp;lt; 1.9.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13208</link><description>The Maps Plugin using Google Maps for WordPress  WordPress plugin before 1.9.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 06:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13306 | WP Google Map &amp;lt; 1.9.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13306</link><description>The Maps Plugin using Google Maps for WordPress  WordPress plugin before 1.9.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 06:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1302 | Versions of the package jsonpath-plus before 10.3.0 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) due to improper input sanitization. An att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1302</link><description>Versions of the package jsonpath-plus before 10.3.0 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) due to improper input sanitization. An attacker can execute aribitrary code on the system by exploiting the unsafe default usage of eval='safe' mode.&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;&#13;This is caused by an incomplete fix for [CVE-2024-21534](https://security.snyk.io/vuln/SNYK-JS-JSONPATHPLUS-7945884).</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 05:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0995 | Use after free in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0995</link><description>Use after free in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 02:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0996 | Inappropriate implementation in Browser UI in Google Chrome on Android prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to spoof the content...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0996</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Browser UI in Google Chrome on Android prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to spoof the contents of the Omnibox (URL bar) via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 02:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0997 | Use after free in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0997</link><description>Use after free in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted Chrome Extension. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 02:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0998 | Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code inside a sandb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0998</link><description>Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code inside a sandbox via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 02:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5461 | Command or parameter injection via unique embedded switch SNMP commands.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5461</link><description>Implementation of the Simple Network 
Management Protocol (SNMP) operating on the Brocade 6547 (FC5022) 
embedded switch blade, makes internal script calls to system.sh from 
within the SNMP binary. An authenticated attacker could perform command 
or parameter injection on SNMP operations that are only enabled on the 
Brocade 6547 (FC5022) embedded switch. This injection could allow the 
authenticated attacker to issue commands as Root.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 00:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>