<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 23:12:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-4020 | Tenda FH1206 addressNat fromAddressNat buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4020</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1206 1.2.0.8(8155) and classified as critical. This issue affects the function fromAddressNat of the file /goform/addressNat. The manipulation of the argument entrys leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261671. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 23:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4019 | Byzoro Smart S80 Management Platform importhtml.php deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4019</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Byzoro Smart S80 Management Platform up to 20240411. Affected is an unknown function of the file /importhtml.php. The manipulation of the argument sql leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261666 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 13:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4014 | The hCaptcha for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's cf7-hcaptcha shortcode in all ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4014</link><description>The hCaptcha for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's cf7-hcaptcha shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 09:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1730 | The Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor (Revolution of a slider, Hero Slider, Media Slider, Drag Drop Slider, Video Slider, Product Slider, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1730</link><description>The Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor (Revolution of a slider, Hero Slider, Media Slider, Drag Drop Slider, Video Slider, Product Slider, Ecommerce Slider) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via urls in link fields, images from URLs, and html tags used in widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.14.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 03:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1057 | The ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg +10 Modules – All in One Solution (formerly WooLentor) plugin for WordPress i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1057</link><description>The ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg +10 Modules – All in One Solution (formerly WooLentor) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wishsuite_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes like 'button_class'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 02:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1480 | Unitronics Vision Standard Unauthenticated Password Retrieval</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1480</link><description>Unitronics Vision Standard line of controllers allow the Information Mode password to be retrieved without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 21:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31994 | Mealie vulnerable to a DoS in recipe image importer (GHSL-2023-228)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31994</link><description>Mealie is a self hosted recipe manager and meal planner. Prior to 1.4.0, an attacker can point the image request to an arbitrarily large file. Mealie will attempt to retrieve this file in whole. If it can be retrieved, it may be stored on the file system in whole (leading to possible disk consumption), however the more likely scenario given resource limitations is that the container will OOM during file retrieval if the target file size is greater than the allocated memory of the container. At best this can be used to force the container to infinitely restart due to OOM (if so configured in `docker-compose.yml), or at worst this can be used to force the Mealie container to crash and remain offline. In the event that the file can be retrieved, the lack of rate limiting on this endpoint also permits an attacker to generate ongoing requests to any target of their choice, potentially contributing to an external-facing DoS attack. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 21:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30974 | SQL Injection vulnerability in autoexpress v.1.3.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary SQL commands via the carId parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30974</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in autoexpress v.1.3.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary SQL commands via the carId parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 21:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31993 | Mealie vulnerable to a GET-based SSRF in recipe image importer (GHSL-2023-227)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31993</link><description>Mealie is a self hosted recipe manager and meal planner. Prior to 1.4.0, the scrape_image function will retrieve an image based on a user-provided URL, however the provided URL is not validated to point to an external location and does not have any enforced rate limiting. The response from the Mealie server will also vary depending on whether or not the target file is an image, is not an image, or does not exist. Additionally, when a file is retrieved the file may remain stored on Mealie’s file system as original.jpg under the UUID of the recipe it was requested for. If the attacker has access to an admin account (e.g. the default changeme@example.com), this file can then be retrieved. Note that if Mealie is running in a development setting this could be leveraged by an attacker to retrieve any file that the Mealie server had downloaded in this fashion without the need for administrator access. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 21:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22905 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in ARM mbed-os v.6.17.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the hciTrSe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22905</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in ARM mbed-os v.6.17.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the hciTrSerialRxIncoming function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 21:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32391 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in MacCMS v.10 v.2024.1000.3000 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32391</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in MacCMS v.10 v.2024.1000.3000 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32392 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in CmSimple v.5.15 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the functions.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32392</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in CmSimple v.5.15 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the functions.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31584 | Pytorch before v2.2.0 has an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability via the component torch/csrc/jit/mobile/flatbuffer_loader.cpp.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31584</link><description>Pytorch before v2.2.0 has an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability via the component torch/csrc/jit/mobile/flatbuffer_loader.cpp.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31992 | Mealie contains a DoS vulnerability in recipe importer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31992</link><description>Mealie is a self hosted recipe manager and meal planner. Prior to 1.4.0, The safe_scrape_html function utilizes a user-controlled URL to issue a request to a remote server, however these requests are not rate-limited. While there are efforts to prevent DDoS by implementing a timeout on requests, it is possible for an attacker to issue a large number of requests to the server which will be handled in batches based on the configuration of the Mealie server. The chunking of responses is helpful for mitigating memory exhaustion on the Mealie server, however a single request to an arbitrarily large external file (e.g. a Debian ISO) is often sufficient to completely saturate a CPU core assigned to the Mealie container. Without rate limiting in place, it is possible to not only sustain traffic against an external target indefinitely, but also to exhaust the CPU resources assigned to the Mealie container. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31991 | Mealie vulnerable to a GET-based SSRF in recipe importer (GHSL-2023-225)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31991</link><description>Mealie is a self hosted recipe manager and meal planner. Prior to 1.4.0, the safe_scrape_html function utilizes a user-controlled URL to issue a request to a remote server. Based on the content of the response, it will either parse the content or disregard it. This function, nor those that call it, add any restrictions on the URL that can be provided, nor is it restricted to being an FQDN (i.e., an IP address can be provided). As this function’s return will be handled differently by its caller depending on the response, it is possible for an attacker to use this functionality to positively identify HTTP(s) servers on the local network with any IP/port combination. This issue can result in any authenticated user being able to map HTTP servers on a local network that the Mealie service has access to. Note that by default any user can create an account on a Mealie server, and that the default changeme@example.com user is available with its hard-coded password. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4017 | Privilege Escalation in U-Series Appliance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4017</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in BeyondTrust U-Series Appliance on Windows, 64 bit (filesystem modules) allows DLL Side-Loading.This issue affects U-Series Appliance: from 3.4 before 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4018 | Privilege Escalation in U-Series Appliance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4018</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in BeyondTrust U-Series Appliance on Windows, 64 bit (local appliance api modules) allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects U-Series Appliance: before 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1681 | Log Injection Vulnerability in corydolphin/flask-cors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1681</link><description>corydolphin/flask-cors is vulnerable to log injection when the log level is set to debug. An attacker can inject fake log entries into the log file by sending a specially crafted GET request containing a CRLF sequence in the request path. This vulnerability allows attackers to corrupt log files, potentially covering tracks of other attacks, confusing log post-processing tools, and forging log entries. The issue is due to improper output neutralization for logs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31450 | Owncast vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion in emoji.go (GHSL-2023-277)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31450</link><description>Owncast is an open source, self-hosted, decentralized, single user live video streaming and chat server. The Owncast application exposes an administrator API at the URL /api/admin. The emoji/delete endpoint of said API allows administrators to delete custom emojis, which are saved on disk. The parameter name is taken from the JSON request and directly appended to the filepath that points to the emoji to delete. By using path traversal sequences (../), attackers with administrative privileges can exploit this endpoint to delete arbitrary files on the system, outside of the emoji directory. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:17:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32652 | @hono/node-server contains Denial of Service risk when receiving Host header that cannot be parsed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32652</link><description>The adapter @hono/node-server allows you to run your Hono application on Node.js. Prior to 1.10.1, the application hangs when receiving a Host header with a value that `@hono/node-server` can't handle well. Invalid values are those that cannot be parsed by the `URL` as a hostname such as an empty string, slashes `/`, and other strings. The version 1.10.1 includes the fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 18:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47435 | An issue in the verifyPassword function of hexo-theme-matery v2.0.0 allows attackers to bypass authentication and access password protected ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47435</link><description>An issue in the verifyPassword function of hexo-theme-matery v2.0.0 allows attackers to bypass authentication and access password protected pages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 18:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3979 | COVESA vsomeip race condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3979</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in COVESA vsomeip up to 3.4.10. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to race condition. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261596.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 18:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31546 | Computer Laboratory Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "id" parameter of /admin/damage/view_damage.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31546</link><description>Computer Laboratory Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "id" parameter of /admin/damage/view_damage.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31547 | Computer Laboratory Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "id" parameter of /admin/item/view_item.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31547</link><description>Computer Laboratory Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "id" parameter of /admin/item/view_item.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2440 | Race Condition was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed maintaining admin permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2440</link><description>A race condition in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed an existing admin to maintain permissions on a detached repository by making a GraphQL mutation to alter repository permissions while the repository is detached. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.9.13, 3.10.10, 3.11.8 and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:14:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-40745 | IBM Aspera Faspex information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40745</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.7 could allow a local user to obtain sensitive information due to weaker than expected security.  IBM X-Force ID:  236452.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:14:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37397 | IBM Aspera Faspex data manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37397</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.7 could allow a local user to obtain or modify sensitive information due to improper encryption of certain data.  IBM X-Force ID:  259672.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51795 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavfilter/avf_show...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51795</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavfilter/avf_showspectrum.c:1789:52 component in showspectrumpic_request_frame</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51796 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavfilter/f_revers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51796</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavfilter/f_reverse.c:269:26 in areverse_request_frame.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51797 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavfilter/avf_show...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51797</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavfilter/avf_showwaves.c:722:24 in showwaves_filter_frame</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51798 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a floating point excepti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51798</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a floating point exception (FPE) error at libavfilter/vf_minterpolate.c:1078:60 in interpolate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31552 | CuteHttpFileServer v.3.1 version has an arbitrary file download vulnerability, which allows attackers to download arbitrary files on the ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31552</link><description>CuteHttpFileServer v.3.1 version has an arbitrary file download vulnerability, which allows attackers to download arbitrary files on the server and obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51793 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavutil/imgutils.c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51793</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavutil/imgutils.c:353:9 in image_copy_plane.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29991 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29991</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27279 | IBM Aspera Faspex denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27279</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.7 could allow a user to cause a denial of service due to missing API rate limiting.  IBM X-Force ID:  248533.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50007 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via theav_samples_set_silence...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50007</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via theav_samples_set_silence function in thelibavutil/samplefmt.c:260:9 component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50008 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the av_malloc function in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50008</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the av_malloc function in libavutil/mem.c:105:9 component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50009 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ff_gaussian_blur_8 fu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50009</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ff_gaussian_blur_8 function in libavfilter/edge_template.c:116:5 component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50010 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the set_encoder_id functi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50010</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the set_encoder_id function in /fftools/ffmpeg_enc.c component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51791 | Buffer Overflow vulenrability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavcodec/jpegxl_pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51791</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulenrability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavcodec/jpegxl_parser.c in gen_alias_map.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51792 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in libde265 v1.0.12 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the allocation size exceeding the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51792</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in libde265 v1.0.12 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the allocation size exceeding the maximum supported size of 0x10000000000.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49501 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the config_eq_output func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49501</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the config_eq_output function in the libavfilter/asrc_afirsrc.c:495:30 component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49502 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ff_bwdif_filter_intra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49502</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.n6.1-3-g466799d4f5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ff_bwdif_filter_intra_c function in the libavfilter/bwdifdsp.c:125:5 component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49963 | DYMO LabelWriter Print Server through 2.366 contains a backdoor hard-coded password that could allow an attacker to take control.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49963</link><description>DYMO LabelWriter Print Server through 2.366 contains a backdoor hard-coded password that could allow an attacker to take control.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37396 | IBM Aspera Faspex information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37396</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.7 could allow a local user to obtain sensitive information due to improper encryption of certain data.  IBM X-Force ID:  259671.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31841 | An issue was discovered in Italtel Embrace 1.6.4. The web server fails to sanitize input data, allowing remote unauthenticated attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31841</link><description>An issue was discovered in Italtel Embrace 1.6.4. The web server fails to sanitize input data, allowing remote unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files on the filesystem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32650 | Rustls vulnerable to an infinite loop in rustls::conn::ConnectionCommon::complete_io() with proper client input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32650</link><description>Rustls is a modern TLS library written in Rust. `rustls::ConnectionCommon::complete_io` could fall into an infinite loop based on network input. When using a blocking rustls server, if a client send a `close_notify` message immediately after `client_hello`, the server's `complete_io` will get in an infinite loop. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.23.5, 0.22.4, and 0.21.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22640 | TCPDF version &lt;=6.6.5 is vulnerable to ReDoS (Regular Expression Denial of Service) if parsing an untrusted HTML page with a crafted color.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22640</link><description>TCPDF version &lt;=6.6.5 is vulnerable to ReDoS (Regular Expression Denial of Service) if parsing an untrusted HTML page with a crafted color.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:24:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29183 | OpenRASP vulnerable to a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack in /login</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29183</link><description>OpenRASP is a RASP solution that directly integrates its protection engine into the application server by instrumentation. There exists a reflected XSS in the /login page due to a reflection of the redirect parameter. This allows an attacker to execute arbitrary javascript with the permissions of a user after the user logins with their account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22869 | IBM Aspera Faspex information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22869</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.7 stores potentially sensitive information in log files that could be read by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  244119.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31846 | An issue was discovered in Italtel Embrace 1.6.4. The web application does not restrict or incorrectly restricts access to a resource from a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31846</link><description>An issue was discovered in Italtel Embrace 1.6.4. The web application does not restrict or incorrectly restricts access to a resource from an unauthorized actor.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31587 | SecuSTATION Camera V2.5.5.3116-S50-SMA-B20160811A and lower allows an unauthenticated attacker to download device configuration files via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31587</link><description>SecuSTATION Camera V2.5.5.3116-S50-SMA-B20160811A and lower allows an unauthenticated attacker to download device configuration files via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:39:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32206 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component \affiche\admin\index.php of WUZHICMS v4.1.0 allows attackers to execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32206</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component \affiche\admin\index.php of WUZHICMS v4.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the $formdata parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:39:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27752 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in CSZ CMS v.1.3.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Default Keyword field in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27752</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in CSZ CMS v.1.3.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Default Keyword field in the settings function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29029 | memos vulnerable to an SSRF in /o/get/image</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29029</link><description>memos is a privacy-first, lightweight note-taking service. In memos 0.13.2, an SSRF vulnerability exists at the /o/get/image that allows unauthenticated users to enumerate the internal network and retrieve images. The response from the image request is then copied into the response of the current server request, causing a reflected XSS vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32409 | An issue in SEMCMS v.4.8 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32409</link><description>An issue in SEMCMS v.4.8 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29028 | memos vulnerable to an SSRF in /o/get/httpmeta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29028</link><description>memos is a privacy-first, lightweight note-taking service. In memos 0.13.2, an SSRF vulnerability exists at the /o/get/httpmeta that allows unauthenticated users to enumerate the internal network and receive limited html values in json form.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29030 | memos vulnerable to an SSRF in /api/resource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29030</link><description>memos is a privacy-first, lightweight note-taking service. In memos 0.13.2, an SSRF vulnerability exists at the /api/resource that allows authenticated users to enumerate the internal network.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32644 | Evmos&amp;#x27; transaction execution not accounting for all state transition after interaction with precompiles</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32644</link><description>Evmos is a scalable, high-throughput Proof-of-Stake EVM blockchain that is fully compatible and interoperable with Ethereum. Prior to 17.0.0, there is a way to mint arbitrary tokens due to the possibility to have two different states not in sync during the execution of a transaction. The exploit is based on the fact that to sync the Cosmos SDK state and the EVM one, we rely on the `stateDB.Commit()` method. When we call this method, we iterate though all the `dirtyStorage` and, **if and only if** it is different than the `originStorage`, we set the new state. Setting the new state means we update the Cosmos SDK KVStore.  If a contract storage state that is the same before and after a transaction, but is changed during the transaction and can call an external contract after the change, it can be exploited to make the transaction similar to non-atomic. The vulnerability is **critical** since this could lead to drain of funds through creative SC interactions.  The issue has been patched in versions &gt;=V17.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32478 | Git Credential Manager (GCM)&amp;#x27;s Debian package does not set root ownership on installed files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32478</link><description>Git Credential Manager (GCM) is a secure Git credential helper. Prior to 2.5.0, the Debian package does not set root ownership on installed files. This allows user 1001 on a multi-user system can replace binary and gain other users' privileges. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32038 | Wazuh Analysis Engine Event Decoder Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32038</link><description>Wazuh is a free and open source platform used for threat prevention, detection, and response. There is a buffer overflow hazard in wazuh-analysisd when handling Unicode characters from Windows Eventchannel messages. It impacts Wazuh Manager 3.8.0 and above. This vulnerability is fixed in Wazuh Manager 4.7.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49275 | Wazuh vulnerable to  NULL Pointer Dereference in wazuh-analysisd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49275</link><description>Wazuh is a free and open source platform used for threat prevention, detection, and response. A NULL pointer dereference was detected during fuzzing of the analysis engine, allowing malicious clients to DoS the analysis engine. The bug occurs when `analysisd` receives a syscollector message with the `hotfix` `msg_type` but lacking a `timestamp`. It uses `cJSON_GetObjectItem()` to get the `timestamp` object item and dereferences it without checking for a `NULL` value. A malicious client can DoS the analysis engine. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50260 | Wazuh&amp;#x27;s vulnerability in host_deny AR script allows arbitrary command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50260</link><description>Wazuh is a free and open source platform used for threat prevention, detection, and response. A wrong validation in the `host_deny` script allows to write any string in the `hosts.deny` file, which can end in an arbitrary command execution on the target system. This vulnerability is part of the active response feature, which can automatically triggers actions in response to alerts. By default, active responses are limited to a set of pre defined executables. This is enforced by only allowing executables stored under `/var/ossec/active-response/bin` to be run as an active response. However, the `/var/ossec/active-response/bin/host_deny` can be exploited. `host_deny` is used to add IP address to the `/etc/hosts.deny` file to block incoming connections on a service level by using TCP wrappers. Attacker can inject arbitrary command into the `/etc/hosts.deny` file and execute arbitrary command by using the spawn directive. The active response can be triggered by writing events either to the local `execd` queue on server or to the `ar` queue which forwards the events to agents. So, it can leads to LPE on server as root and RCE on agent as root. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.7.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3646 | Command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed privilege escalation in the Management Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3646</link><description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the instance when configuring the chat integration. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.12.2, 3.11.8, 3.10.10, and 3.9.13. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3684 | Improper Privilege Management was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed privilege escalation in the Management Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3684</link><description>A server side request forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin access to the appliance when configuring the Artifacts &amp; Logs and Migrations Storage. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.12.2, 3.11.8, 3.10.10, and 3.9.13. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3470 | Repository administrator can bypass organization&amp;#x27;s ruleset using deploy keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3470</link><description>An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to use a deploy key pertaining to an organization to bypass an organization ruleset. An attacker would require access to a valid deploy key for a repository in the organization as well as repository administrator access. This vulnerability affected versions of GitHub Enterprise Server 3.11 to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.8 and 3.12.2. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37400 | IBM Aspera Faspex privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37400</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.7 could allow a local user to escalate their privileges due to insecure credential storage.  IBM X-Force ID:  259677.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32166 | Webid v1.2.1 suffers from an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) - Broken Access Control vulnerability, allowing attackers to buy now an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32166</link><description>Webid v1.2.1 suffers from an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) - Broken Access Control vulnerability, allowing attackers to buy now an auction that is suspended (horizontal privilege escalation).</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 13:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31744 | In Jasper 4.2.2, the jpc_streamlist_remove function in src/libjasper/jpc/jpc_dec.c:2407 has an assertion failure vulnerability, allowing att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31744</link><description>In Jasper 4.2.2, the jpc_streamlist_remove function in src/libjasper/jpc/jpc_dec.c:2407 has an assertion failure vulnerability, allowing attackers to cause a denial of service attack through a specific image file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 12:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3654 | Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in Teixo by Teimas Global</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3654</link><description>An XSS vulnerability has been found in Teimas Global's Teixo, version 1.42.42-stable. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to send a specially crafted JavaScript payload via the "seconds" parameter in the program's URL, resulting in a possible takeover of a registered user's session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 12:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31745 | Libdwarf v0.9.1 was discovered to contain a heap use-after-free via the dw_empty_errlist_item function at /libdwarf/dwarf_alloc.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31745</link><description>Libdwarf v0.9.1 was discovered to contain a heap use-after-free via the dw_empty_errlist_item function at /libdwarf/dwarf_alloc.c.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 12:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32683 | WordPress WP Ultimate Review plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.5 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32683</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Wpmet Wp Ultimate Review.This issue affects Wp Ultimate Review: from n/a through 2.2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0671 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU memory processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0671</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Midgard GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user to make improper GPU memory processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Midgard GPU Kernel Driver: from r19p0 through r32p0; Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: from r7p0 through r48p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r19p0 through r48p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r48p0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 09:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1065 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU memory processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1065</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user to make improper GPU memory processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: from r45p0 through r48p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r45p0 through r48p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r45p0 through r48p0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 09:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29968 | SQL Table names, column names, and SQL queries are collected in DR standby Supportsave</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29968</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in Brocade SANnav before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a when Brocade SANnav instances are configured in disaster recovery mode. SQL Table names, column names, and SQL queries are collected in DR standby Supportsave. This could allow authenticated users to access the database structure and its contents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 05:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29969 | TLS/SSL weak message authentication code ciphers are added by default for port 18082</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29969</link><description>When a Brocade SANnav installation is upgraded from Brocade SANnav v2.2.2 to Brocade SANnav 2.3.0, TLS/SSL weak message authentication code ciphers are added by default for port 18082.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 05:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29967 | In Brocade SANnav before v2.31 and v2.3.0a, it was observed that Docker instances inside the appliance have insecure mount points</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29967</link><description>In Brocade SANnav before Brocade SANnav v2.31 and v2.3.0a, it was observed that Docker instances inside the appliance have insecure mount points, allowing reading and writing access to sensitive files. The vulnerability could allow a sudo privileged user on the host OS to read and write access to these files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 05:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2761 | Genesis Blocks &amp;lt; 3.1.3 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2761</link><description>The Genesis Blocks WordPress plugin before 3.1.3 does not properly escape data input provided to some of its blocks, allowing using with at least contributor privileges to conduct Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 05:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29966 | hard-coded credentials in the documentation that appear as the appliance root password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29966</link><description>Brocade SANnav OVA before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a contain hard-coded credentials in the documentation that appear as the appliance's root password. The vulnerability could allow an unauthenticated attacker full access to the Brocade SANnav appliance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 05:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29965 | Insecure backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29965</link><description>In Brocade SANnav before v2.3.1, and v2.3.0a, it is possible to back up the appliance from the web interface or the command line interface ("SSH"). The resulting backups are world-readable. A local attacker can recover backup files, restore them to a new malicious appliance, and retrieve the passwords of all the switches.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 04:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29964 | Docker instances in Brocade SANnav before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a have an insecure architecture and configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29964</link><description>Docker instances in Brocade SANnav before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a have an insecure architecture and configuration that leads to multiple vulnerabilities. Docker daemons are exposed to the WAN interface, and other vulnerabilities allow total control over the Ova appliance. A Docker instance could access any other instances, and a few could access sensitive files. The vulnerability could allow a sudo privileged user on the underlying OS to access and modify these files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 04:51:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29962 | Insecure file permission setting that makes files world-readable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29962</link><description>Brocade SANnav OVA before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a have an insecure file permission setting that makes files world-readable. This could allow a local user without the required privileges to access sensitive information or a Java binary.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 04:20:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29963 | Brocade SANnav contains hardcoded keys used by Docker to reach remote registries over TLS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29963</link><description>Brocade SANnav OVA before v2.3.1, and v2.3.0a, contain hardcoded keys used by Docker to reach remote registries over TLS. TLS connections with an exposed key allow an attacker to MITM the traffic. 
Note: Brocade SANnav doesn't have access to remote Docker registries.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 04:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29961 | supply-chain attack risk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29961</link><description>A vulnerability affects Brocade SANnav before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a. It allows a Brocade SANnav service to send ping commands in the background at regular intervals to gridgain.com to check if updates are available for the Component. This could make an unauthenticated, remote attacker aware of the behavior and launch a supply-chain attack against a Brocade SANnav appliance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 04:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29960 | In the Brocade SANnav server versions before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a, the SSH keys inside the OVA image are hardcoded and identical in the VM eve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29960</link><description>In the Brocade SANnav server versions before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a, the SSH keys inside the OVA image are hardcoded and identical in the VM every time SANnav is installed. Any Brocade SANnav VM based on the official OVA images is vulnerable to MITM over SSH. An attacker can decrypt and compromise the SSH traffic to the SANnav appliance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 03:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29959 | Brocade Fabric OS switch encrypted passwords in the Brocade SANnav Standby node&amp;#x27;s support save</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29959</link><description>A vulnerability in Brocade SANnav before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a prints Brocade Fabric OS switch encrypted passwords in the Brocade SANnav Standby node's support save.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 03:27:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29957 | Encryption key is stored in the DR log files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29957</link><description>When Brocade SANnav before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a servers are configured in Disaster Recovery mode, the encryption key is stored in the DR log files. This could provide attackers with an additional, less-protected path to acquiring the encryption key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 03:27:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29958 | Encryption key in the console when a privileged user executes the script to replace the Brocade SANnav Management Portal standby node.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29958</link><description>A vulnerability in Brocade SANnav before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a prints the encryption key in the console when a privileged user executes the script to replace the Brocade SANnav Management Portal standby node. This could provide attackers an additional, less protected path to acquiring the encryption key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 03:27:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3600 | The Poll Maker – Best WordPress Poll Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting due to a missing capability ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3600</link><description>The Poll Maker – Best WordPress Poll Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting due to a missing capability check on the ays_poll_maker_quick_start AJAX action in addition to insufficient escaping and sanitization in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create quizzes and inject malicious web scripts into them that execute when a user visits the page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 02:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3615 | The Media Library Folders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 's' parameter in all versions up to, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3615</link><description>The Media Library Folders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 's' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 8.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 02:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3731 | The Customer Reviews for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 's' parameter in all versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3731</link><description>The Customer Reviews for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 's' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.47.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 02:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3818 | The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3818</link><description>The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's "Social Icons" block in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 02:47:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3560 | The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the _id value in all versions up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3560</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the _id value in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 02:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3598 | The ElementsKit Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Creative Button widget in all version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3598</link><description>The ElementsKit Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Creative Button widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 02:22:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22061 | A Heap Overflow vulnerability in WLInfoRailService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22061</link><description>A Heap Overflow vulnerability in WLInfoRailService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23526 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an una...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23526</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to read sensitive information in memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23528 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an una...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23528</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to read sensitive information in memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23529 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an una...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23529</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to read sensitive information in memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23530 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an una...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23530</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to read sensitive information in memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23531 | An Integer Overflow vulnerability in WLInfoRailService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23531</link><description>An Integer Overflow vulnerability in WLInfoRailService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to perform denial of service attacks. In certain rare conditions this could also lead to reading content from memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23532 | An out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an authenticated remote attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23532</link><description>An out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an authenticated remote attacker to perform denial of service attacks. In certain conditions this could also lead to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23533 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an aut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23533</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an authenticated remote attacker to read sensitive information in memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23534 | An Unrestricted File-upload vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23534</link><description>An Unrestricted File-upload vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23535 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23535</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24991 | A Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an authenticated remote att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24991</link><description>A Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an authenticated remote attacker to perform denial of service attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24992 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24992</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24993 | A Race Condition (TOCTOU) vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24993</link><description>A Race Condition (TOCTOU) vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24994 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24994</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24995 | A Race Condition (TOCTOU) vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24995</link><description>A Race Condition (TOCTOU) vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24996 | A Heap overflow vulnerability in WLInfoRailService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24996</link><description>A Heap overflow vulnerability in WLInfoRailService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24997 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24997</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24998 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24998</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24999 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24999</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25000 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25000</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27975 | An Use-after-free vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27975</link><description>An Use-after-free vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27976 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27976</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27977 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to delete arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27977</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to delete arbitrary files, thereby leading to Denial-of-Service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27978 | A Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an authenticated remote att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27978</link><description>A Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows an authenticated remote attacker to perform denial of service attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27984 | A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to delete specific t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27984</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to delete specific type of files and/or cause denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29204 | A Heap Overflow vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29204</link><description>A Heap Overflow vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30938 | SQL Injection vulnerability in SEMCMS v.4.8 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the ID parameter in the SEMCMS_User...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30938</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in SEMCMS v.4.8 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the ID parameter in the SEMCMS_User.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 23:56:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31750 | SQL injection vulnerability in f-logic datacube3 v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the req_id parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31750</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in f-logic datacube3 v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the req_id parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 23:56:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1491 | Electrolink FM/DAB/TV Transmitter Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1491</link><description>The devices allow access to an unprotected endpoint that allows MPFS 
file system binary image upload without authentication. The MPFS2 file 
system module provides a light-weight read-only file system that can be 
stored in external EEPROM, external serial flash, or internal flash 
program memory. This file system serves as the basis for the HTTP2 web 
server module, but is also used by the SNMP module and is available to 
other applications that require basic read-only storage capabilities. 
This can be exploited to overwrite the flash program memory that holds 
the web server's main interfaces and execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 22:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21846 | Electrolink FM/DAB/TV Transmitter Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21846</link><description>An unauthenticated attacker can reset the board and stop transmitter 
operations by sending a specially-crafted GET request to the command.cgi
 gateway, resulting in a denial-of-service scenario.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 22:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21872 | Electrolink FM/DAB/TV Transmitter Reliance on Cookies without Validation and Integrity Checking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21872</link><description>The device allows an unauthenticated attacker to bypass authentication 
and modify the cookie to reveal hidden pages that allows more critical 
operations to the transmitter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 22:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22186 | Electrolink FM/DAB/TV Transmitter Reliance on Cookies without Validation and Integrity Checking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22186</link><description>The application suffers from a privilege escalation vulnerability. An 
attacker logged in as guest can escalate his privileges by poisoning the
 cookie to become administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 22:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3742 | Electrolink FM/DAB/TV Transmitter Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3742</link><description>Electrolink transmitters store credentials in clear-text. Use of these credentials could allow an attacker to access the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 22:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22179 | Electrolink FM/DAB/TV Transmitter Authentication Bypass by Assumed-Immutable Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22179</link><description>The application is vulnerable to an unauthenticated parameter 
manipulation that allows an attacker to set the credentials to blank 
giving her access to the admin panel. Also vulnerable to account 
takeover and arbitrary password change.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 22:07:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3741 | Electrolink FM/DAB/TV Transmitter Authentication Bypass by Assumed-Immutable Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3741</link><description>Electrolink transmitters are vulnerable to an authentication bypass 
vulnerability affecting the login cookie. An attacker can set an 
arbitrary value except 'NO' to the login cookie and have full system 
access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 22:07:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32473 | Moby IPv6 enabled on IPv4-only network interfaces</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32473</link><description>Moby is an open source container framework that is a key component of Docker Engine, Docker Desktop, and other distributions of container tooling or runtimes. In 26.0.0, IPv6 is not disabled on network interfaces, including those belonging to networks where `--ipv6=false`. An container with an `ipvlan` or `macvlan` interface will normally be configured to share an external network link with the host machine. Because of this direct access, (1) Containers may be able to communicate with other hosts on the local network over link-local IPv6 addresses, (2) if router advertisements are being broadcast over the local network, containers may get SLAAC-assigned addresses, and (3) the interface  will be a member of IPv6 multicast groups. This means interfaces in IPv4-only networks present an unexpectedly and unnecessarily increased attack surface. The issue is patched in 26.0.2. To completely disable IPv6 in a container, use `--sysctl=net.ipv6.conf.all.disable_ipv6=1` in the `docker create` or `docker run` command. Or, in the service configuration of a `compose` file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 22:07:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30929 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the 'back' Parameter in playlis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30929</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the 'back' Parameter in playlist.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 21:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30926 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the ./inc/kiosks.inc component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30926</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the ./inc/kiosks.inc component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 21:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30927 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the racer-results.php component...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30927</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the racer-results.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 21:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30928 | SQL Injection vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via 'classids' Parameter in ajax/q...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30928</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via 'classids' Parameter in ajax/query.slide.next.inc</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 21:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30924 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the checkin.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30924</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the checkin.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 21:22:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30925 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the photo-thumbs.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30925</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the photo-thumbs.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 21:22:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30921 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the photo.php component...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30921</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the photo.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 21:22:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30922 | SQL Injection vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the where Clause in Award Document Rende...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30922</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the where Clause in Award Document Rendering.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 21:22:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30923 | SQL Injection vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the where Clause in Racer Docu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30923</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the where Clause in Racer Document Rendering</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 21:22:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30920 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the render-document.php...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30920</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DerbyNet v9.0 and below allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the render-document.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 21:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30107 | HCL Connections is vulnerable to broken access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30107</link><description>HCL Connections contains a broken access control vulnerability that may expose sensitive information to unauthorized users in certain scenarios.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 20:24:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32477 | Race condition when flushing input stream leads to permission prompt bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32477</link><description>Deno is a JavaScript, TypeScript, and WebAssembly runtime with secure defaults. By using ANSI escape sequences and a race between `libc::tcflush(0, libc::TCIFLUSH)` and reading standard input, it's possible to manipulate the permission prompt and force it to allow an unsafe action regardless of the user input. Some ANSI escape sequences act as a info request to the master terminal emulator and the terminal emulator sends back the reply in the PTY channel. standard streams also use this channel to send and get data. For example the `\033[6n` sequence requests the current cursor position. These sequences allow us to append data to the standard input of Deno. This vulnerability allows an attacker to bypass Deno permission policy.  This vulnerability is fixed in 1.42.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 20:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32474 | Sentry&amp;#x27;s superuser cleartext password leaked in logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32474</link><description>Sentry is an error tracking and performance monitoring platform. Prior to 24.4.1, when authenticating as a superuser to Sentry with a username and password, the password is leaked as cleartext in logs under the _event_: `auth-index.validate_superuser`. An attacker with access to the log data could use these leaked credentials to login to the Sentry system as superuser. Self-hosted users on affected versions should upgrade to 24.4.1 or later. Users can configure the logging level to exclude logs of the `INFO` level and only generate logs for levels at `WARNING` or more.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 19:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20380 | ClamAV HTML Parser Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20380</link><description>A vulnerability in the HTML parser of ClamAV could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
The vulnerability is due to an issue in the C to Rust foreign function interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted file containing HTML content to be scanned by ClamAV on an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ClamAV scanning process to terminate, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected software.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 19:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3758 | Sssd: race condition during authorization leads to gpo policies functioning inconsistently</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3758</link><description>A race condition flaw was found in sssd where the GPO policy is not consistently applied for authenticated users. This may lead to improper authorization issues, granting or denying access to resources inappropriately.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 19:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29986 | Microsoft Edge for Android (Chromium-based) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29986</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 19:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29987 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29987</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 19:14:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23557 | HCL Connections is vulnerable to a user enumeration vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23557</link><description>HCL Connections contains a user enumeration vulnerability. Certain actions could allow an attacker to determine if the user is valid or not, leading to a possible brute force attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:30:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32462 | Flatpak vulnerable to a sandbox escape via RequestBackground portal due to bad argument parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32462</link><description>Flatpak is a system for building, distributing, and running sandboxed desktop applications on Linux. in versions before 1.10.9, 1.12.9, 1.14.6, and 1.15.8, a malicious or compromised Flatpak app could execute arbitrary code outside its sandbox. Normally, the `--command` argument of `flatpak run` expects to be given a command to run in the specified Flatpak app, optionally along with some arguments. However it is possible to instead pass `bwrap` arguments to `--command=`, such as `--bind`. It's possible to pass an arbitrary `commandline` to the portal interface `org.freedesktop.portal.Background.RequestBackground` from within a Flatpak app. When this is converted into a `--command` and arguments, it achieves the same effect of passing arguments directly to `bwrap`, and thus can be used for a sandbox escape. The solution is to pass the `--` argument to `bwrap`, which makes it stop processing options. This has been supported since bubblewrap 0.3.0. All supported versions of Flatpak require at least that version of bubblewrap. xdg-desktop-portal version 1.18.4 will mitigate this vulnerability by only allowing Flatpak apps to create .desktop files for commands that do not start with --. The vulnerability is patched in 1.15.8, 1.10.9, 1.12.9, and 1.14.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24910 | Local privilege escalation in Check Point ZoneAlarm Extreme Security NextGen, Identity Agent for Windows, and Identity Agent for Windows Terminal Server via crafted DLL file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24910</link><description>A local attacker can escalate privileges on affected Check Point ZoneAlarm Extreme Security NextGen, Identity Agent for Windows, and Identity Agent for Windows Terminal Server. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute local privileged code on the target system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 17:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32332 | TOTOLINK N300RT V2.1.8-B20201030.1539 contains a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WDS Settings under the Wireless Page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32332</link><description>TOTOLINK N300RT V2.1.8-B20201030.1539 contains a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WDS Settings under the Wireless Page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 16:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32327 | TOTOLINK N300RT V2.1.8-B20201030.1539 contains a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Port Forwarding under the Firewall Page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32327</link><description>TOTOLINK N300RT V2.1.8-B20201030.1539 contains a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Port Forwarding under the Firewall Page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 16:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32333 | TOTOLINK N300RT V2.1.8-B20201030.1539 contains a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MAC Filtering under the Firewall Page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32333</link><description>TOTOLINK N300RT V2.1.8-B20201030.1539 contains a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MAC Filtering under the Firewall Page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 16:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32334 | TOTOLINK N300RT V2.1.8-B20201030.1539 contains a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in IP/Port Filtering under the Firewall Page...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32334</link><description>TOTOLINK N300RT V2.1.8-B20201030.1539 contains a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in IP/Port Filtering under the Firewall Page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 16:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32335 | TOTOLINK N300RT V2.1.8-B20201030.1539 contains a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Access Control under the Wireless Page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32335</link><description>TOTOLINK N300RT V2.1.8-B20201030.1539 contains a Store Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Access Control under the Wireless Page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 16:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32325 | TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 contains a Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the ssid parameter in the setWiFiExtenderC...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32325</link><description>TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 contains a Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the ssid parameter in the setWiFiExtenderConfig function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 16:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32326 | TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 contains a Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the key parameter in the setWiFiExtenderCo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32326</link><description>TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 contains a Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the key parameter in the setWiFiExtenderConfig function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 16:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2796 | SSRF in Community Manager Developer Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2796</link><description>A server-side request forgery (SSRF) was discovered in the Akana Community Manager Developer Portal in versions prior to and including 2022.1.3. Reported by Jakob Antonsson.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 15:17:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30564 | An issue inandrei-tatar nora-firebase-common between v.1.0.41 and v.1.12.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30564</link><description>An issue inandrei-tatar nora-firebase-common between v.1.0.41 and v.1.12.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the updateState parameter of the updateStateInternal method.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 15:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32466 | Tolgee&amp;#x27;s API key scopes not checked when querying translation data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32466</link><description>Tolgee is an open-source localization platform. For the `/v2/projects/translations` and `/v2/projects/{projectId}/translations` endpoints, translation data was returned even when API key was missing `translation.view` scope. However, it was impossible to fetch the data when user was missing this scope. So this is only relevant for API keys generated by users permitted to `translation.view`. This vulnerability is fixed in v3.57.2</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 15:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32470 | Tolgee&amp;#x27; API keys created by server admin users bypass the permission check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32470</link><description>Tolgee is an open-source localization platform. When API key created by admin user is used it bypasses the permission check at all. This error was introduced in v3.57.2 and immediately fixed in v3.57.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 15:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30257 | 1Panel&amp;#x27;s password verification is suspected to have a timing attack vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30257</link><description>1Panel is an open source Linux server operation and maintenance management panel. The password verification in the source code uses the != symbol instead hmac.Equal. This may lead to a timing attack vulnerability. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.10.3-lts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 15:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28189 | Judge0 vulnerable to Sandbox Escape Patch Bypass via chown running on Symbolic Link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28189</link><description>Judge0 is an open-source online code execution system. The application uses the UNIX chown command on an untrusted file within the sandbox. An attacker can abuse this by creating a symbolic link (symlink) to a file outside the sandbox, allowing the attacker to run chown on arbitrary files outside of the sandbox. This vulnerability is not impactful on it's own, but it can be used to bypass the patch for CVE-2024-28185 and obtain a complete sandbox escape. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.13.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 14:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29021 | SSRF into Sandbox Escape through Unsafe Default Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29021</link><description>Judge0 is an open-source online code execution system. The default configuration of Judge0 leaves the service vulnerable to a sandbox escape via Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF). This allows an attacker with sufficient access to the Judge0 API to obtain unsandboxed code execution as root on the target machine. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.13.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 14:48:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28185 | Judge0 vulnerable to Sandbox Escape via Symbolic Link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28185</link><description>Judge0 is an open-source online code execution system. The application does not account for symlinks placed inside the sandbox directory, which can be leveraged by an attacker to write to arbitrary files and gain code execution outside of the sandbox. When executing a submission, Judge0 writes a `run_script` to the sandbox directory. The security issue is that an attacker can create a symbolic link (symlink) at the path `run_script` before this code is executed, resulting in the `f.write` writing to an arbitrary file on the unsandboxed system. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to overwrite scripts on the system and gain code execution outside of the sandbox.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 14:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27306 | aiohttp vulnerable to XSS on index pages for static file handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27306</link><description>aiohttp is an asynchronous HTTP client/server framework for asyncio and Python. A XSS vulnerability exists on index pages for static file handling. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.9.4. We have always recommended using a reverse proxy server (e.g. nginx) for serving static files. Users following the recommendation are unaffected. Other users can disable `show_index` if unable to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 14:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32475 | Envoy RELEASE_ASSERT using auto_sni with :authority header &amp;gt; 255 bytes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32475</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native, open source edge and service proxy. When an upstream TLS cluster is used with `auto_sni` enabled, a request containing a `host`/`:authority` header longer than 255 characters triggers an abnormal termination of Envoy process. Envoy does not gracefully handle an error when setting SNI for outbound TLS connection. The error can occur when Envoy attempts to use the `host`/`:authority` header value longer than 255 characters as SNI for outbound TLS connection. SNI length is limited to 255 characters per the standard. Envoy always expects this operation to succeed and abnormally aborts the process when it fails. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.30.1, 1.29.4, 1.28.3, and 1.27.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 14:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6892 | The EAN for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'alg_wc_ean_product_meta' shortco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6892</link><description>The EAN for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'alg_wc_ean_product_meta' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6897 | The EAN for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.2 v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6897</link><description>The EAN for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.2 via the the 'alg_wc_ean_product_meta' shortcode due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to expose potentially sensitive post metadata.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47843 | WordPress CataBlog Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47843</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Zachary Segal CataBlog.This issue affects CataBlog: from n/a through 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50885 | WordPress Store Locator WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.14 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50885</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in AGILELOGIX Store Locator WordPress.This issue affects Store Locator WordPress: from n/a through 1.4.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3948 | SourceCodester Home Clean Service System Photo student.add.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3948</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Home Clean Service System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file \admin\student.add.php of the component Photo Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261440.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3675 | Insufficient input validation when downloading certain file types.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3675</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Secomea GateManager (Web GUI) allows Reading Data from System Resources.This issue affects GateManager: from 11.0.623074018 before 11.0.623373051.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32689 | WordPress WP Social Comments plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32689</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in GenialSouls WP Social Comments.This issue affects WP Social Comments: from n/a through 1.7.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49768 | WordPress WP-FormAssembly plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49768</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FormAssembly / Drew Buschhorn WP-FormAssembly allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP-FormAssembly: from n/a through 2.0.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31229 | WordPress Really Simple SSL plugin &amp;lt;= 7.2.3 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31229</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Really Simple Plugins Really Simple SSL.This issue affects Really Simple SSL: from n/a through 7.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32551 | WordPress SP Project &amp;amp; Document Manage plugin &amp;lt;= 4.71 - Auth. SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32551</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Smartypants SP Project &amp; Document Manager.This issue affects SP Project &amp; Document Manager : from n/a through 4.71.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32602 | WordPress WooCommerce Multilingual &amp;amp; Multicurrency plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.3.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32602</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in OnTheGoSystems WooCommerce Multilingual &amp; Multicurrency.This issue affects WooCommerce Multilingual &amp; Multicurrency: from n/a through 5.3.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32686 | WordPress Backup Migration plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Log vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32686</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Inisev Backup Migration.This issue affects Backup Migration: from n/a through 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32126 | WordPress Navigation menu as dropdown Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32126</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jeroen Peters Navigation menu as Dropdown Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Navigation menu as Dropdown Widget: from n/a through 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32552 | WordPress Tagbox – UGC Galleries, Social Media Widgets, User Reviews &amp;amp; Analytics plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32552</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tagbox Taggbox allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Taggbox: from n/a through 3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32553 | WordPress Superfly Menu plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.25 - Auth. Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32553</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in looks_awesome Superfly Menu allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Superfly Menu: from n/a through 5.0.25.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32600 | WordPress Master Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.5 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32600</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Averta Master Slider.This issue affects Master Slider: from n/a through 3.9.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32554 | WordPress Knight Lab Timeline plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.3.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32554</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Knight Lab Knight Lab Timeline allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Knight Lab Timeline: from n/a through 3.9.3.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32556 | WordPress HurryTimer plugin &amp;lt;=2.9.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32556</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nabil Lemsieh HurryTimer allows Stored XSS.This issue affects HurryTimer: from n/a through 2.9.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32558 | WordPress eCommerce Product Catalog plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.32 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32558</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in impleCode eCommerce Product Catalog allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects eCommerce Product Catalog: from n/a through 3.3.32.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32559 | WordPress WP 404 Auto Redirect to Similar Post plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32559</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in hwk-fr WP 404 Auto Redirect to Similar Post allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP 404 Auto Redirect to Similar Post: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32560 | WordPress QR Code Composer plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32560</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sharabindu QR Code Composer allows Stored XSS.This issue affects QR Code Composer: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32561 | WordPress Tagembed plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32561</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tagembed allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Tagembed: from n/a through 4.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32562 | WordPress Z Y N I T H plugin &amp;lt;= 7.4.9 - Unauthenticated Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32562</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VIICTORY MEDIA LLC Z Y N I T H allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Z Y N I T H: from n/a through 7.4.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32563 | WordPress VikBooking Hotel Booking Engine &amp;amp; PMS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32563</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VikBooking Hotel Booking Engine &amp; PMS allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects VikBooking Hotel Booking Engine &amp; PMS: from n/a through 1.6.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32564 | WordPress Post Grid Blocks and WordPress News Plugin – PostX plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32564</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Post Grid Team by WPXPO PostX – Gutenberg Blocks for Post Grid allows Stored XSS.This issue affects PostX – Gutenberg Blocks for Post Grid: from n/a through 4.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32565 | WordPress App Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32565</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Appcheap.Io App Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects App Builder: from n/a through 3.8.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26921 | inet: inet_defrag: prevent sk release while still in use</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26921</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

inet: inet_defrag: prevent sk release while still in use

ip_local_out() and other functions can pass skb-&gt;sk as function argument.

If the skb is a fragment and reassembly happens before such function call
returns, the sk must not be released.

This affects skb fragments reassembled via netfilter or similar
modules, e.g. openvswitch or ct_act.c, when run as part of tx pipeline.

Eric Dumazet made an initial analysis of this bug.  Quoting Eric:
  Calling ip_defrag() in output path is also implying skb_orphan(),
  which is buggy because output path relies on sk not disappearing.

  A relevant old patch about the issue was :
  8282f27449bf ("inet: frag: Always orphan skbs inside ip_defrag()")

  [..]

  net/ipv4/ip_output.c depends on skb-&gt;sk being set, and probably to an
  inet socket, not an arbitrary one.

  If we orphan the packet in ipvlan, then downstream things like FQ
  packet scheduler will not work properly.

  We need to change ip_defrag() to only use skb_orphan() when really
  needed, ie whenever frag_list is going to be used.

Eric suggested to stash sk in fragment queue and made an initial patch.
However there is a problem with this:

If skb is refragmented again right after, ip_do_fragment() will copy
head-&gt;sk to the new fragments, and sets up destructor to sock_wfree.
IOW, we have no choice but to fix up sk_wmem accouting to reflect the
fully reassembled skb, else wmem will underflow.

This change moves the orphan down into the core, to last possible moment.
As ip_defrag_offset is aliased with sk_buff-&gt;sk member, we must move the
offset into the FRAG_CB, else skb-&gt;sk gets clobbered.

This allows to delay the orphaning long enough to learn if the skb has
to be queued or if the skb is completing the reasm queue.

In the former case, things work as before, skb is orphaned.  This is
safe because skb gets queued/stolen and won't continue past reasm engine.

In the latter case, we will steal the skb-&gt;sk reference, reattach it to
the head skb, and fix up wmem accouting when inet_frag inflates truesize.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32566 | WordPress WP Club Manager  plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32566</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Club Manager allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Club Manager: from n/a through 2.2.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32567 | WordPress DirectoryPress plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32567</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Designinvento DirectoryPress allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects DirectoryPress: from n/a through 3.6.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32568 | WordPress WP 2FA plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32568</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Melapress WP 2FA allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP 2FA: from n/a through 2.6.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32569 | WordPress Ditty plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.31 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32569</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Metaphor Creations Ditty allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ditty: from n/a through 3.1.31.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32570 | WordPress Cornerstone plugin &amp;lt;= 0.8.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32570</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Archetyped Cornerstone allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Cornerstone: from n/a through 0.8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32571 | WordPress WP Stripe Checkout plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2.41 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32571</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in naa986 WP Stripe Checkout allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Stripe Checkout: from n/a through 1.2.2.41.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32572 | WordPress Element Pack Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 5.6.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32572</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BdThemes Element Pack Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Element Pack Elementor Addons: from n/a through 5.6.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32573 | WordPress WP-Lister Lite for eBay plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32573</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Lab WP-Lister Lite for eBay allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP-Lister Lite for eBay: from n/a through 3.5.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32574 | WordPress WP Simple HTML Sitemap plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32574</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ashish Ajani WP Simple HTML Sitemap allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP Simple HTML Sitemap: from n/a through 2.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32575 | WordPress Mega Elements plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32575</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kraftplugins Mega Elements allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mega Elements: from n/a through 1.1.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2833 | The Jobs for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘job-search’ parameter in all versions u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2833</link><description>The Jobs for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘job-search’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32576 | WordPress BA Book Everything plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32576</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Booking Algorithms BA Book Everything allows Stored XSS.This issue affects BA Book Everything: from n/a through 1.6.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32577 | WordPress CBX Bookmark &amp;amp; Favorite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.20 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32577</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Codeboxr Team CBX Bookmark &amp; Favorite cbxwpbookmark allows Stored XSS.This issue affects CBX Bookmark &amp; Favorite: from n/a through 1.7.20.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32578 | WordPress Sliderby10Web plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.54 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32578</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 10Web Slider by 10Web allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Slider by 10Web: from n/a through 1.2.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32579 | WordPress Restaurant Menu – Food Ordering System – Table Reservation plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32579</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GloriaFood Restaurant Menu – Food Ordering System – Table Reservation allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Restaurant Menu – Food Ordering System – Table Reservation: from n/a through 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32580 | WordPress Master Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32580</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Averta Master Slider allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Master Slider: from n/a through 3.9.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32581 | WordPress Mortgage Calculators WP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.56 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32581</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Lenderd Mortgage Calculators WP allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mortgage Calculators WP: from n/a through 1.56.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32582 | WordPress Debug Log Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32582</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bowo Debug Log Manager allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Debug Log Manager: from n/a through 2.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32583 | WordPress Photo Gallery by 10Web plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.21 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32583</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Photo Gallery Team Photo Gallery by 10Web allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Photo Gallery by 10Web: from n/a through 1.8.21.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29003 | SolarWinds Platform Cross Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29003</link><description>The SolarWinds Platform was susceptible to a XSS vulnerability that affects the maps section of the user interface. This vulnerability requires authentication and requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32584 | WordPress TeraWallet plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32584</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in StandaloneTech TeraWallet – For WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects TeraWallet – For WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32585 | WordPress Import Content in WordPress &amp;amp; WooCommerce with Excel plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32585</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in extendWP Import Content in WordPress &amp; WooCommerce with Excel allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Import Content in WordPress &amp; WooCommerce with Excel: from n/a through 4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32586 | WordPress Gutenberg Block Editor Toolkit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.40.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32586</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Munir Kamal Gutenberg Block Editor Toolkit allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Gutenberg Block Editor Toolkit: from n/a through 1.40.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28076 | SolarWinds Platform Arbitrary Open Redirection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28076</link><description>The SolarWinds Platform was susceptible to a Arbitrary Open Redirection Vulnerability. A potential attacker can redirect to different domain when using URL parameter with relative entry in the correct format</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29001 | SolarWinds Platform SWQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29001</link><description>A SolarWinds Platform SWQL Injection Vulnerability was identified in the user interface. This vulnerability requires authentication and user interaction to be exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32587 | WordPress EnvíaloSimple plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32587</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in EnvialoSimple EnvíaloSimple allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects EnvíaloSimple: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:58:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32588 | WordPress LearnPress Export Import plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32588</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThimPress LearnPress Export Import allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects LearnPress Export Import: from n/a through 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:58:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32590 | WordPress Kattene plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32590</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Webfood Kattene allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Kattene: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:49:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32591 | WordPress Backend Designer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32591</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Daniele De Rosa Backend Designer allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Backend Designer: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32592 | WordPress Void Elementor WHMCS Elements For Elementor Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32592</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VoidCoders, innovs Void Elementor WHMCS Elements For Elementor Page Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Void Elementor WHMCS Elements For Elementor Page Builder: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32593 | WordPress WPBITS Addons For Elementor Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.4.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32593</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPBits WPBITS Addons For Elementor Page Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WPBITS Addons For Elementor Page Builder: from n/a through 1.3.4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32594 | WordPress Attesa Extra plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32594</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AttesaWP Attesa Extra allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Attesa Extra: from n/a through 1.3.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:38:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32595 | WordPress WP Helper Premium plugin &amp;lt; 4.6.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32595</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mat Bao Corp WP Helper Premium allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP Helper Premium: from n/a before 4.6.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:38:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32596 | WordPress DSGVO Youtube plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32596</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Eric-Oliver Mächler DSGVO Youtube allows Stored XSS.This issue affects DSGVO Youtube: from n/a through 1.4.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:39:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32597 | WordPress WP Smart Import plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32597</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Xylus Themes WordPress Importer allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WordPress Importer: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32598 | WordPress BA Book Everything plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32598</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Booking Algorithms BA Book Everything allows Stored XSS.This issue affects BA Book Everything: from n/a through 1.6.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32599 | WordPress WP Dummy Content Generator plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Arbitrary Code Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32599</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Deepak anand WP Dummy Content Generator.This issue affects WP Dummy Content Generator: from n/a through 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41864 | WordPress PeproDev CF7 Database plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41864</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Pepro Dev. Group PeproDev CF7 Database.This issue affects PeproDev CF7 Database: from n/a through 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32601 | WordPress Popup Anything plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32601</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP OnlineSupport, Essential Plugin Popup Anything.This issue affects Popup Anything: from n/a through 2.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32603 | WordPress WooBuddy plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.20 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32603</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ThemeKraft WooBuddy.This issue affects WooBuddy: from n/a through 3.4.20.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32604 | WordPress WP-Recall plugin &amp;lt;= 16.26.5 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32604</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Plechev Andrey WP-Recall.This issue affects WP-Recall: from n/a through 16.26.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49742 | WordPress Support Genix plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Broken Access Control lead to Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49742</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Support Genix.This issue affects Support Genix: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32142 | WordPress Ovic Responsive WPBakery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32142</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ovic Team Ovic Responsive WPBakery.This issue affects Ovic Responsive WPBakery: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31869 | Apache Airflow: Sensitive configuration for providers displayed when &amp;quot;non-sensitive-only&amp;quot; config used</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31869</link><description>Airflow versions 2.7.0 through 2.8.4 have a vulnerability that allows an authenticated user to see sensitive provider configuration via the "configuration" UI page when "non-sensitive-only" was set as "webserver.expose_config" configuration (The celery provider is the only community provider currently that has sensitive configurations). You should migrate to Airflow 2.9 or change your "expose_config" configuration to False as a workaround. This is similar, but different to  CVE-2023-46288 https://github.com/advisories/GHSA-9qqg-mh7c-chfq  which concerned API, not UI configuration page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 07:22:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2729 | Otter Blocks &amp;lt; 2.6.6 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2729</link><description>The Otter Blocks  WordPress plugin before 2.6.6 does not properly escape its mainHeadings blocks' attribute before appending it to the final rendered block, allowing contributors to conduct Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 05:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1426 | The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter G...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1426</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter Grid) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘link’ attribute of the Price List widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 04:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1429 | The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter G...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1429</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter Grid) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘tab_link’ attribute of the Panel Slider widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 04:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29956 | cleartext password in supportsave logs when a user schedules a switch Supportsave from Brocade SANnav</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29956</link><description>A vulnerability in Brocade SANnav before v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a prints the Brocade SANnav password in clear text in supportsave logs when a user schedules a switch Supportsave from Brocade SANnav.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 01:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3931 | Totara LMS Profile check.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3931</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totara LMS 18.0.1 Build 20231128.01. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/roles/check.php of the component Profile Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID Number leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261368. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 01:07:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3932 | Totara LMS cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3932</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Totara LMS 18.0.1 Build 20231128.01. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-261369 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 01:07:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>