<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 15:41:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-11941 | e107 CMS Avatar image.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11941</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in e107 CMS up to 2.3.3. This impacts an unknown function of the file /e107_admin/image.php?mode=main&amp;action=avatar of the component Avatar Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument multiaction[] results in path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 15:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11940 | LibreWolf Installer setup.nsi uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11940</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in LibreWolf up to 143.0.4-1 on Windows. This affects an unknown function of the file assets/setup.nsi of the component Installer. Such manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. The attack must be carried out locally. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is reported as difficult. Upgrading to version 144.0-1 mitigates this issue. The name of the patch is dd10e31dd873e9cb309fad8aed921d45bf905a55. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 08:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11939 | ChurchCRM Backup Restore RestoreJob.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11939</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in ChurchCRM up to 5.18.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file src/ChurchCRM/Backup/RestoreJob.php of the component Backup Restore Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument restoreFile can lead to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 08:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11938 | ChurchCRM setup.php deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11938</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ChurchCRM up to 5.18.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file setup/routes/setup.php. Performing manipulation of the argument DB_PASSWORD/ROOT_PATH/URL results in deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 07:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62672 | rplay through 3.3.2 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (SIGSEGV and daemon crash) or possibly have unspecified other impact. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62672</link><description>rplay through 3.3.2 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (SIGSEGV and daemon crash) or possibly have unspecified other impact. This occurs in memcpy in the RPLAY_DATA case in rplay_unpack in librplay/rplay.c, potentially reachable via packet data with no authentication.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 01:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47410 | Apache Geode: CSRF attacks through GET requests to the Management and Monitoring REST API that can execute gfsh commands on the target system</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47410</link><description>Apache Geode is vulnerable to CSRF attacks through GET requests to the Management and Monitoring REST API that could allow an attacker who has tricked a user into giving up their Geode session credentials to submit malicious commands on the target system on behalf of the authenticated user.


This issue affects Apache Geode: versions 1.10 through 1.15.1

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.15.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 15:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11926 | Related Posts Lite &amp;lt;= 1.12 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11926</link><description>The Related Posts Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 09:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9890 | Theme Editor &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9890</link><description>The Theme Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'theme_editor_theme' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to achieve remote code execution via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 08:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40001 | scsi: mvsas: Fix use-after-free bugs in mvs_work_queue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40001</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

scsi: mvsas: Fix use-after-free bugs in mvs_work_queue

During the detaching of Marvell's SAS/SATA controller, the original code
calls cancel_delayed_work() in mvs_free() to cancel the delayed work
item mwq-&gt;work_q. However, if mwq-&gt;work_q is already running, the
cancel_delayed_work() may fail to cancel it. This can lead to
use-after-free scenarios where mvs_free() frees the mvs_info while
mvs_work_queue() is still executing and attempts to access the
already-freed mvs_info.

A typical race condition is illustrated below:

CPU 0 (remove)            | CPU 1 (delayed work callback)
mvs_pci_remove()          |
  mvs_free()              | mvs_work_queue()
    cancel_delayed_work() |
      kfree(mvi)          |
                          |   mvi-&gt; // UAF

Replace cancel_delayed_work() with cancel_delayed_work_sync() to ensure
that the delayed work item is properly canceled and any executing
delayed work item completes before the mvs_info is deallocated.

This bug was found by static analysis.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 08:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40002 | thunderbolt: Fix use-after-free in tb_dp_dprx_work</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40002</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

thunderbolt: Fix use-after-free in tb_dp_dprx_work

The original code relies on cancel_delayed_work() in tb_dp_dprx_stop(),
which does not ensure that the delayed work item tunnel-&gt;dprx_work has
fully completed if it was already running. This leads to use-after-free
scenarios where tb_tunnel is deallocated by tb_tunnel_put(), while
tunnel-&gt;dprx_work remains active and attempts to dereference tb_tunnel
in tb_dp_dprx_work().

A typical race condition is illustrated below:

CPU 0                            | CPU 1
tb_dp_tunnel_active()            |
  tb_deactivate_and_free_tunnel()| tb_dp_dprx_start()
    tb_tunnel_deactivate()       |   queue_delayed_work()
      tb_dp_activate()           |
        tb_dp_dprx_stop()        | tb_dp_dprx_work() //delayed worker
          cancel_delayed_work()  |
    tb_tunnel_put(tunnel);       |
                                 |   tunnel = container_of(...); //UAF
                                 |   tunnel-&gt; //UAF

Replacing cancel_delayed_work() with cancel_delayed_work_sync() is
not feasible as it would introduce a deadlock: both tb_dp_dprx_work()
and the cleanup path acquire tb-&gt;lock, and cancel_delayed_work_sync()
would wait indefinitely for the work item that cannot proceed.

Instead, implement proper reference counting:
- If cancel_delayed_work() returns true (work is pending), we release
  the reference in the stop function.
- If it returns false (work is executing or already completed), the
  reference is released in delayed work function itself.

This ensures the tb_tunnel remains valid during work item execution
while preventing memory leaks.

This bug was found by static analysis.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 08:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40003 | net: mscc: ocelot: Fix use-after-free caused by cyclic delayed work</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40003</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: mscc: ocelot: Fix use-after-free caused by cyclic delayed work

The origin code calls cancel_delayed_work() in ocelot_stats_deinit()
to cancel the cyclic delayed work item ocelot-&gt;stats_work. However,
cancel_delayed_work() may fail to cancel the work item if it is already
executing. While destroy_workqueue() does wait for all pending work items
in the work queue to complete before destroying the work queue, it cannot
prevent the delayed work item from being rescheduled within the
ocelot_check_stats_work() function. This limitation exists because the
delayed work item is only enqueued into the work queue after its timer
expires. Before the timer expiration, destroy_workqueue() has no visibility
of this pending work item. Once the work queue appears empty,
destroy_workqueue() proceeds with destruction. When the timer eventually
expires, the delayed work item gets queued again, leading to the following
warning:

workqueue: cannot queue ocelot_check_stats_work on wq ocelot-switch-stats
WARNING: CPU: 2 PID: 0 at kernel/workqueue.c:2255 __queue_work+0x875/0xaf0
...
RIP: 0010:__queue_work+0x875/0xaf0
...
RSP: 0018:ffff88806d108b10 EFLAGS: 00010086
RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: 0000000000000101 RCX: 0000000000000027
RDX: 0000000000000027 RSI: 0000000000000004 RDI: ffff88806d123e88
RBP: ffffffff813c3170 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: ffffed100da247d2
R10: ffffed100da247d1 R11: ffff88806d123e8b R12: ffff88800c00f000
R13: ffff88800d7285c0 R14: ffff88806d0a5580 R15: ffff88800d7285a0
FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffff8880e5725000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 00007fe18e45ea10 CR3: 0000000005e6c000 CR4: 00000000000006f0
Call Trace:
 
 ? kasan_report+0xc6/0xf0
 ? __pfx_delayed_work_timer_fn+0x10/0x10
 ? __pfx_delayed_work_timer_fn+0x10/0x10
 call_timer_fn+0x25/0x1c0
 __run_timer_base.part.0+0x3be/0x8c0
 ? __pfx_delayed_work_timer_fn+0x10/0x10
 ? rcu_sched_clock_irq+0xb06/0x27d0
 ? __pfx___run_timer_base.part.0+0x10/0x10
 ? try_to_wake_up+0xb15/0x1960
 ? _raw_spin_lock_irq+0x80/0xe0
 ? __pfx__raw_spin_lock_irq+0x10/0x10
 tmigr_handle_remote_up+0x603/0x7e0
 ? __pfx_tmigr_handle_remote_up+0x10/0x10
 ? sched_balance_trigger+0x1c0/0x9f0
 ? sched_tick+0x221/0x5a0
 ? _raw_spin_lock_irq+0x80/0xe0
 ? __pfx__raw_spin_lock_irq+0x10/0x10
 ? tick_nohz_handler+0x339/0x440
 ? __pfx_tmigr_handle_remote_up+0x10/0x10
 __walk_groups.isra.0+0x42/0x150
 tmigr_handle_remote+0x1f4/0x2e0
 ? __pfx_tmigr_handle_remote+0x10/0x10
 ? ktime_get+0x60/0x140
 ? lapic_next_event+0x11/0x20
 ? clockevents_program_event+0x1d4/0x2a0
 ? hrtimer_interrupt+0x322/0x780
 handle_softirqs+0x16a/0x550
 irq_exit_rcu+0xaf/0xe0
 sysvec_apic_timer_interrupt+0x70/0x80
 
...

The following diagram reveals the cause of the above warning:

CPU 0 (remove)             | CPU 1 (delayed work callback)
mscc_ocelot_remove()       |
  ocelot_deinit()          | ocelot_check_stats_work()
    ocelot_stats_deinit()  |
      cancel_delayed_work()|   ...
                           |   queue_delayed_work()
      destroy_workqueue()  | (wait a time)
                           | __queue_work() //UAF

The above scenario actually constitutes a UAF vulnerability.

The ocelot_stats_deinit() is only invoked when initialization
failure or resource destruction, so we must ensure that any
delayed work items cannot be rescheduled.

Replace cancel_delayed_work() with disable_delayed_work_sync()
to guarantee proper cancellation of the delayed work item and
ensure completion of any currently executing work before the
workqueue is deallocated.

A deadlock concern was considered: ocelot_stats_deinit() is called
in a process context and is not holding any locks that the delayed
work item might also need. Therefore, the use of the _sync() variant
is safe here.

This bug was identified through static analysis. To reproduce the
issue and validate the fix, I simulated ocelot-swit
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 08:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5555 | Nixdorf Wincor PORT IO Driver IOCTL wnport.sys sub_11100 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5555</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Nixdorf Wincor PORT IO Driver up to 1.0.0.1. This affects the function sub_11100 in the library wnport.sys of the component IOCTL Handler. Such manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.0.0.1 is able to mitigate this issue. Upgrading the affected component is recommended. The vendor was contacted beforehand and was able to provide a patch very early.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 08:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10750 | PowerBI Embed Reports &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10750</link><description>The PowerBI Embed Reports plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0. This is due to missing capability checks and authentication verification on the 'testUser' endpoint accessible via the mo_epbr_admin_observer() function hooked on 'init'. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to access sensitive Azure AD user information including personal identifiable information (PII) such as displayName, mail, phones, department, or detailed OAuth error data including Azure AD Application/Client IDs, error codes, trace IDs, and correlation IDs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 07:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11256 | Kognetiks Chatbot &amp;lt;= 2.3.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Limited File Uploads and Conversation Erasing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11256</link><description>The Kognetiks Chatbot plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on several functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload limited safe files and erase conversations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 07:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10006 | WPBakery Page Builder &amp;lt;= 8.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10006</link><description>The WPBakery Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'rev_slider_vc' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 8.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This is only exploitable when RevSlider is also installed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10187 | GSpeech TTS – WordPress Text To Speech Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.17.13 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10187</link><description>The GSpeech TTS – WordPress Text To Speech Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'field' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.17.13 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11270 | Gutenberg Essential Blocks – Page Builder for Gutenberg Blocks &amp;amp; Patterns &amp;lt;= 5.7.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11270</link><description>The Gutenberg Essential Blocks – Page Builder for Gutenberg Blocks &amp; Patterns plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'titleTag' attribute in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11372 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.9.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Database Table Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11372</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to modification of data in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.9.2. This is due to missing capability checks on the Admin Tools REST endpoints which are registered with permission_callback set to __return_true. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to perform destructive database operations including dropping indexes on any table (including WordPress core tables like wp_options), creating duplicate configuration entries, and degrading site performance via the /wp-json/lp/v1/admin/tools/create-indexs endpoint granted they can provide table names.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11391 | PPOM – Product Addons &amp;amp; Custom Fields for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 33.0.15 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11391</link><description>The PPOM – Product Addons &amp; Custom Fields for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the image cropper functionality in all versions up to, and including, 33.0.15. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. While the vulnerable code is in the free version, this only affected users with the paid version of the software installed and activated.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11510 | FileBird &amp;lt;= 6.4.9 - Improper Authorization to Authenticated (Author+) Settings Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11510</link><description>The FileBird – WordPress Media Library Folders &amp; File Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the /filebird/v1/fb-wipe-clear-all-data function in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to reset all of the plugin's configuration data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11517 | Event Tickets and Registration &amp;lt;= 5.26.5 - Unauthenticated Ticket Payment Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11517</link><description>The Event Tickets and Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to payment bypass in all versions up to, and including, 5.26.5. This is due to the /wp-json/tribe/tickets/v1/commerce/free/order endpoint not verifying that a ticket type should be free allowing the user to bypass the payment. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain access to paid tickets, without paying for them, causing a loss of revenue for the target.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11519 | Image optimization service by Optimole &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Author+) Media Offload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11519</link><description>The Optimole – Optimize Images | Convert WebP &amp; AVIF | CDN &amp; Lazy Load | Image Optimization plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.0 via the /wp-json/optml/v1/move_image REST API endpoint due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to offload media that doesn't belong to them.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11691 | PPOM – Product Addons &amp;amp; Custom Fields for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 33.0.15 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11691</link><description>The PPOM – Product Addons &amp; Custom Fields for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the PPOM_Meta::get_fields_by_id() function in all versions up to, and including, 33.0.15 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. This is only exploitable when the Enable Legacy Price Calculations setting is enabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11703 | WP Go Maps (formerly WP Google Maps) &amp;lt;= 9.0.48 - Unauthenticated Cache Poisoning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11703</link><description>The WP Go Maps (formerly WP Google Maps) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cache Poisoning in all versions up to, and including, 9.0.48. This is due to the plugin not serving cached data from server-side responses and instead relying on user-input. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to poison the cache location for location search results.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11741 | WPC Smart Quick View for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.2.5 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Private Product Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11741</link><description>The WPC Smart Quick View for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.5 via the 'woosq_quickview' AJAX endpoint due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract data from password protected, private, or draft products that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9562 | Redirection for Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 3.2.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via qs_date Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9562</link><description>The Redirection for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's qs_date shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11738 | Media Library Assistant &amp;lt;= 3.29 - Unauthenticated Limited File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11738</link><description>The Media Library Assistant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to limited file reading in all versions up to, and including, 3.29 via the mla-stream-image.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary ai/eps/pdf/ps files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 05:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11742 | WPC Smart Wishlist for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.0.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11742</link><description>The WPC Smart Wishlist for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wishlist_quickview' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view other user's wishlist data and information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 05:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11857 | XX2WP Integration Tools &amp;lt;= 1.9.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11857</link><description>The XX2WP Integration Tools plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'mxp_fb2wp_display_embed' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.9. This is due to the plugin not properly sanitizing user input and output of the 'post_id' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 05:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11937 | Stored XSS through a system message in SecurePoll</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11937</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - SecurePoll Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - SecurePoll Extension: master.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 05:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62666 | DoS vector through the cirrusbuilddoc query API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62666</link><description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - CirrusSearch Extension allows HTTP DoS.This issue affects Mediawiki - CirrusSearch Extension: from master before 1.43.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:56:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62667 | Stored XSS through article extracts in GrowthExperiments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62667</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - GrowthExperiments Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - GrowthExperiments Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62668 | Insufficient permission checks in action=growthsetmentor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62668</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - GrowthExperiments Extension allows Resource Leak Exposure.This issue affects Mediawiki - GrowthExperiments Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:47:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62669 | UserInfoCard: activeLocalBlocksAllWikis does not do permissions checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62669</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - CentralAuth Extension allows Resource Leak Exposure.This issue affects Mediawiki - CentralAuth Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:47:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11361 | Essential Blocks &amp;lt;= 5.7.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11361</link><description>The Gutenberg Essential Blocks – Page Builder for Gutenberg Blocks &amp; Patterns plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.1 via the eb_save_ai_generated_image function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62670 | Stored XSS through a system message in FlexDiagrams</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62670</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - FlexDiagrams Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - FlexDiagrams Extension: master.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62671 | Stored XSS through wikitext in Cargo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62671</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - Cargo Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - Cargo Extension: master.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62662 | Stored XSS through system messages in AdvancedSearch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62662</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - AdvancedSearch Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - AdvancedSearch Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62663 | Stored XSS through a system message in UploadWizard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62663</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - UploadWizard Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - UploadWizard Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62664 | Stored XSS through a system message in ImageRating</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62664</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - ImageRating Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - ImageRating Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62665 | Stored XSS through system messages in Skin:BlueSky</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62665</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - Skin:BlueSky allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - Skin:BlueSky: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20206 | Appointments &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20206</link><description>The Appointments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 via deserialization of untrusted input from the `wpmudev_appointments` cookie. This allows unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. Attackers were actively exploiting this vulnerability with the WP_Theme() class to create backdoors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20207 | Flickr Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20207</link><description>The Flickr Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 via deserialization of untrusted input from the `pager ` parameter. This allows unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. Attackers were actively exploiting this vulnerability with the WP_Theme() class to create backdoors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20208 | RegistrationMagic - Custom Registration Forms &amp;lt;= 3.7.9.2 - PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20208</link><description>The RegistrationMagic – Custom Registration Forms, User Registration, Payment, and User Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to 3.7.9.3 (exclusive) via deserialization of untrusted input from the is_expired_by_date() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. The additional presence of a POP chain allows attackers to fetch a remote file and install it on the site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36853 | 10WebMapBuilder &amp;lt;= 1.0.63 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Plugin Settings Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36853</link><description>The 10WebMapBuilder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Plugin Settings Change in versions up to, and including, 1.0.63 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping and a lack of capability checks. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36854 | Async JavaScript &amp;lt;= 2.19.07.14 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36854</link><description>The Async JavaScript plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including,  2.19.07.14. This is due to missing authorization checks on the aj_steps AJAX aciton along with a lack on sanitization on the settings saved via the function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber level permissions and above to inject malicious web scripts into a page that execute whenever a user accesses that page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11378 | ShortPixel Image Optimizer &amp;lt;= 6.3.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Settings Import/Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11378</link><description>The ShortPixel Image Optimizer – Optimize Images, Convert WebP &amp; AVIF plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'shortpixel_ajaxRequest' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 6.3.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to export and import site options.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62655 | SQL injection in Cargo via Special:CargoExport</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62655</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki Cargo extension allows SQL Injection.This issue affects MediaWiki Cargo extension: 1.39, 1.43, 1.44.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62654 | Stored XSS through system messages in QuizGame</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62654</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki QuizGame extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MediaWiki QuizGame extension: 1.39, 1.43, 1.44.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62653 | Stored XSS through system messages in PollNY</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62653</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki PollNY extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MediaWiki PollNY extension: 1.39, 1.43, 1.44.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62652 | Stored XSS in WebAuthn key name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62652</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki WebAuthn extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MediaWiki WebAuthn extension: 1.39, 1.43, 1.44.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62650 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 relies on client-side authentication for use of the diagnost...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62650</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 relies on client-side authentication for use of the diagnostic screen.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:52:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62651 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 does not implement access control for the bathroom rating in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62651</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 does not implement access control for the bathroom rating interface.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11914 | Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus DeviceFileReport.do download path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11914</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus 1.3.40. Affected by this issue is the function Download of the file /DeviceFileReport.do?Action=Download. Performing manipulation of the argument FilePath results in path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62515 | Remote Code Execution by Pickle Deserialization via FlightServer in pyquokka</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62515</link><description>pyquokka is a framework for making data lakes work for time series. In versions 0.3.1 and prior, the FlightServer class directly uses pickle.loads() to deserialize action bodies received from Flight clients without any sanitization or validation in the do_action() method. The vulnerable code is located in pyquokka/flight.py at line 283 where arbitrary data from Flight clients is directly passed to pickle.loads(). When FlightServer is configured to listen on 0.0.0.0, this allows attackers across the entire network to perform arbitrary remote code execution by sending malicious pickled payloads through the set_configs action. Additional vulnerability points exist in the cache_garbage_collect, do_put, and do_get functions where pickle.loads is used to deserialize untrusted remote data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62647 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 provides the functionality of returning a JWT that can be us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62647</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 provides the functionality of returning a JWT that can be used to call an API to return a signed AWS upload URL, for any store's path.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62648 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 allows remote attackers to adjust Drive Thru speaker audio v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62648</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 allows remote attackers to adjust Drive Thru speaker audio volume.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62649 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 relies on client-side authentication for submission of equip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62649</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 relies on client-side authentication for submission of equipment orders.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62508 | Citizen vulnerable to stored XSS in sticky header button messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62508</link><description>Citizen is a MediaWiki skin that makes extensions part of the cohesive experience. Citizen from 3.3.0 to 3.9.0 are vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting in the sticky header button message handling. In stickyHeader.js the copyButtonAttributes function assigns innerHTML from a source element’s textContent when copying button labels. This causes escaped HTML in system message content (such as citizen-share, citizen-view-history, citizen-view-edit, and nstab-talk) to be interpreted as HTML in the sticky header, allowing injection of arbitrary script by a user with the ability to edit interface messages. The vulnerability allows a user with the editinterface right but without the editsitejs right (by default the sysop group has editinterface but may not have editsitejs) to execute arbitrary JavaScript in other users’ sessions, enabling unauthorized access to sensitive data or actions. The issue is fixed in 3.9.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62642 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 has an "Anyone Can Join This Party" signup API that does not...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62642</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 has an "Anyone Can Join This Party" signup API that does not verify user account creation, allowing a remote unauthenticated attacker to create a user account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62643 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 transmits passwords of user accounts in cleartext e-mail mes...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62643</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 transmits passwords of user accounts in cleartext e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62644 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 has a Global Store Directory that shares personal informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62644</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 has a Global Store Directory that shares personal information among authenticated users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62645 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 allows a remote authenticated attacker to obtain a token wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62645</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 allows a remote authenticated attacker to obtain a token with administrative privileges for the entire platform via the createToken GraphQL mutation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62646 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 allows remote attackers to review the stored audio of conver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62646</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 allows remote attackers to review the stored audio of conversations between associates and Drive Thru customers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11912 | Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus DeviceState.do Query sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11912</link><description>A flaw has been found in Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus 1.3.40. Affected is the function Query of the file /DeviceState.do?Action=Query. This manipulation of the argument orderField causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11913 | Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus Service.do download path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11913</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus 1.3.40. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Download of the file /Service.do?Action=Download. Such manipulation of the argument Path leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11925 | Incorrect Content-Type Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11925</link><description>Incorrect Content-Type header in one of the APIs (`text/html` instead of `application/json`) replies may potentially allow injection of HTML/JavaScript into reply.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62511 | yt-grabber-tui local arbitrary file overwrite via TOCTOU race in config file creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62511</link><description>yt-grabber-tui is a C++ terminal user interface application for downloading YouTube content. yt-grabber-tui version 1.0 contains a Time-of-Check to Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) race condition (CWE-367) in the creation of the default configuration file config.json. In version 1.0, load_json_settings in Settings.hpp checks for the existence of config.json using boost::filesystem::exists and, if the file is missing, calls create_json_settings which writes the JSON configuration with boost::property_tree::write_json. A local attacker with write access to the application’s configuration directory (~/.config/yt-grabber-tui on Linux or the current working directory on Windows) can create a symbolic link between the existence check and the subsequent write so that the write operation follows the symlink and overwrites an attacker-chosen file accessible to the running process. This enables arbitrary file overwrite within the privileges of the application process, which can corrupt files and cause loss of application or user data. If the application is executed with elevated privileges, this could extend to system file corruption. The issue is fixed in version 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11910 | Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus MemoryState.do query sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11910</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus 1.3.40. This affects the function Query of the file /MemoryState.do?Action=Query. The manipulation of the argument orderField leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11911 | Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus DeviceFault.do Query sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11911</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus 1.3.40. This impacts the function Query of the file /DeviceFault.do?Action=Query. The manipulation of the argument sortField results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31573 | XMLUnit for Java before 2.10.0, in the default configuration, might allow code execution via an untrusted stylesheet (used for an XSLT trans...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31573</link><description>XMLUnit for Java before 2.10.0, in the default configuration, might allow code execution via an untrusted stylesheet (used for an XSLT transformation), because XSLT extension functions are enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11908 | Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus FileDir.do uploadFile unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11908</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus 1.3.40. The affected element is the function uploadFile of the file /FileDir.do?Action=Upload. Performing manipulation of the argument File results in unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11909 | Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus RepairRecord.do queryLast sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11909</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus 1.3.40. The impacted element is the function queryLast of the file /RepairRecord.do?Action=QueryLast. Executing manipulation of the argument orderField can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34281 | ThingsBoard &amp;lt; v4.2.1 SVG Image Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34281</link><description>ThingsBoard versions &lt; 4.2.1 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the dashboard's Image Upload Gallery feature. An attacker can upload an SVG file containing malicious JavaScript, which may be executed when the file is rendered in the UI. This issue results from insufficient sanitization and improper content-type validation of uploaded SVG files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34282 | ThingsBoard &amp;lt; v4.2.1 SVG Image SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34282</link><description>ThingsBoard versions &lt; 4.2.1 contain a server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the dashboard's Image Upload Gallery feature. An attacker can upload a malicious SVG file that references a remote URL. If the server processes the SVG file in a way that parses external references, it may initiate unintended outbound requests. This can be used to access internal services or resources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56221 | A lack of rate limiting in the login mechanism of SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a brute force attack.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56221</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the login mechanism of SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a brute force attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56218 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PDF file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56218</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PDF file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56316 | A SQL injection vulnerability in the content_title parameter of the /cms/content/list endpoint in MCMS 5.5.0 allows remote attackers to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56316</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in the content_title parameter of the /cms/content/list endpoint in MCMS 5.5.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL queries via unsanitized input in the FreeMarker template rendering.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56320 | Enterprise Contract Management Portal v.22.4.0 is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in its chat box component. This allows a r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56320</link><description>Enterprise Contract Management Portal v.22.4.0 is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in its chat box component. This allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62505 | SSRF in lobehub/lobe-chat with native web fetch module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62505</link><description>LobeChat is an open source chat application platform. The web-crawler package in LobeChat version 1.136.1 allows server-side request forgery (SSRF) in the tools.search.crawlPages tRPC endpoint. A client can supply an arbitrary urls array together with impls containing the value naive. The service passes the user URLs to Crawler.crawl and the naive implementation performs a server-side fetch of each supplied URL without validating or restricting internal network addresses (such as localhost, 127.0.0.1, private IP ranges, or cloud instance metadata endpoints). This allows an attacker with a valid user token (or in development mode using a bypass header) to make the server disclose responses from internal HTTP services, potentially exposing internal API data or cloud metadata credentials. Version 1.136.2 fixes the issue. Update to version 1.136.2. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60514 | Tillywork v0.1.3 and below is vulnerable to SQL Injection in app/common/helpers/query.builder.helper.ts.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60514</link><description>Tillywork v0.1.3 and below is vulnerable to SQL Injection in app/common/helpers/query.builder.helper.ts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57164 | Flowise through v3.0.4 is vulnerable to remote code execution via unsanitized evaluation of user input in the "Supabase RPC Filter" field.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57164</link><description>Flowise through v3.0.4 is vulnerable to remote code execution via unsanitized evaluation of user input in the "Supabase RPC Filter" field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62430 | ClipBucket v5 stored XSS via video/photo fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62430</link><description>ClipBucket v5 is an open source video sharing platform. ClipBucket v5 through build 5.5.2 #145 allows stored cross-site scripting (XSS) in multiple video and photo metadata fields. For videos the Tags field and the Genre, Actors, Producer, Executive Producer, and Director fields in Movieinfos accept user supplied values without adequate sanitization. For photos the Photo Title and Photo Tags fields accept user supplied values without adequate sanitization. A regular user who can edit a video or photo can inject script (for example by supplying a value such as a closing delimiter followed by a script element). The injected script executes when any user, including an unauthenticated visitor or an administrator, views the affected video or photo page. Although cookies are set with the HttpOnly attribute and cannot be read directly, the injected script can issue fetch requests to endpoints such as admin_area pages and exfiltrate their contents or trigger unintended actions. Version 5.5.2 build #146 and later contain a fix. Update to build 5.5.2 #146 or later. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62424 | ClipBucket path traversal vulnerability in template editor allows arbitrary file read and write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62424</link><description>ClipBucket is a web-based video-sharing platform. In ClipBucket version 5.5.2 - #146 and earlier, the /admin_area/template_editor.php endpoint is vulnerable to path traversal. The validation of the file-loading path is inadequate, allowing authenticated administrators to read and write arbitrary files outside the intended template directory by inserting path traversal sequences into the folder parameter. An attacker with administrator privileges can exploit this vulnerability to read sensitive files such as /etc/passwd and modify writable files on the system, potentially leading to sensitive information disclosure and compromise of the application or server. This issue is fixed in version 5.5.2 - #147.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62419 | DataEase vulnerable to JDBC URL injection in DB2 and MongoDB data source configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62419</link><description>DataEase is a data visualization and analytics platform. In DataEase versions through 2.10.13, a JDBC URL injection vulnerability exists in the DB2 and MongoDB data source configuration handlers. In the DB2 data source handler, when the extraParams field is empty, the HOSTNAME, PORT, and DATABASE values are directly concatenated into the JDBC URL without filtering illegal parameters. This allows an attacker to inject a malicious JDBC string into the HOSTNAME field to bypass previously patched vulnerabilities CVE-2025-57773 and CVE-2025-58045. The vulnerability is fixed in version 2.10.14. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62420 | DataEase vulnerable to remote code execution via H2 JDBC driver bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62420</link><description>DataEase is a data visualization and analytics platform. In DataEase versions through 2.10.13, a JDBC driver bypass vulnerability exists in the H2 database connection handler. The getJdbc function in H2.java checks if the jdbcUrl starts with jdbc:h2 but returns a separate jdbc field as the actual connection URL. An attacker can provide a jdbcUrl that starts with jdbc:h2 while supplying a different jdbc field with an arbitrary JDBC driver and connection string. This allows an authenticated attacker to trigger arbitrary JDBC connections with malicious drivers, potentially leading to remote code execution. The vulnerability is fixed in version 2.10.14. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62421 | DataEase vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting via file upload bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62421</link><description>DataEase is a data visualization and analytics platform. In DataEase versions through 2.10.13, a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists due to improper file upload validation and authentication bypass. The StaticResourceApi interface defines a route upload/{fileId} that uses a URL path parameter where both the filename and extension of uploaded files are controllable by users. During permission validation, the TokenFilter invokes the WhitelistUtils#match method to determine if the URL path is in the allowlist. If the requestURI ends with .js or similar extensions, it is directly deemed safe and bypasses permission checks. This allows an attacker to access "upload/1.js" while specifying arbitrary file extensions, enabling the upload of HTML files containing malicious JavaScript. The vulnerability is fixed in version 2.10.14. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62422 | DataEase SQL injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62422</link><description>DataEase is an open source data visualization and analytics platform. In versions 2.10.13 and earlier, the /de2api/datasetData/tableField interface is vulnerable to SQL injection. An attacker can construct a malicious tableName parameter to execute arbitrary SQL commands. This issue is fixed in version 2.10.14. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62171 | ImageMagick vulnerable to denial of service via integer overflow in BMP decoder on 32-bit systems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62171</link><description>ImageMagick is an open source software suite for displaying, converting, and editing raster image files. In ImageMagick versions prior to 7.1.2-7 and 6.9.13-32, an integer overflow vulnerability exists in the BMP decoder on 32-bit systems. The vulnerability occurs in coders/bmp.c when calculating the extent value by multiplying image columns by bits per pixel. On 32-bit systems with size_t of 4 bytes, a malicious BMP file with specific dimensions can cause this multiplication to overflow and wrap to zero. The overflow check added to address CVE-2025-57803 is placed after the overflow occurs, making it ineffective. A specially crafted 58-byte BMP file with width set to 536,870,912 and 32 bits per pixel can trigger this overflow, causing the bytes_per_line calculation to become zero. This vulnerability only affects 32-bit builds of ImageMagick where default resource limits for width, height, and area have been manually increased beyond their defaults. 64-bit systems with size_t of 8 bytes are not vulnerable, and systems using default ImageMagick resource limits are not vulnerable. The vulnerability is fixed in versions 7.1.2-7 and 6.9.13-32.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62168 | Squid vulnerable to information disclosure via authentication credential leakage in error handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62168</link><description>Squid is a caching proxy for the Web. In Squid versions prior to 7.2, a failure to redact HTTP authentication credentials in error handling allows information disclosure. The vulnerability allows a script to bypass browser security protections and learn the credentials a trusted client uses to authenticate. This potentially allows a remote client to identify security tokens or credentials used internally by a web application using Squid for backend load balancing. These attacks do not require Squid to be configured with HTTP authentication. The vulnerability is fixed in version 7.2. As a workaround, disable debug information in administrator mailto links generated by Squid by configuring squid.conf with email_err_data off.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59043 | OpenBao vulnerable to denial of service via malicious JSON request processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59043</link><description>OpenBao is an open source identity-based secrets management system. In OpenBao versions prior to 2.4.1, JSON objects after decoding may use significantly more memory than their serialized version. It is possible to craft a JSON payload to maximize the factor between serialized memory usage and deserialized memory usage, similar to a zip bomb, with factors reaching approximately 35. This can be used to circumvent the max_request_size configuration parameter which is intended to protect against denial of service attacks. The request body is parsed into a map very early in the request handling chain before authentication, which means an unauthenticated attacker can send a specifically crafted JSON object and cause an out-of-memory crash. Additionally, for requests with large numbers of strings, the audit subsystem can consume large quantities of CPU. The vulnerability is fixed in version 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8414 | Zigbee Green Power Host Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8414</link><description>Due to improper input validation, a buffer overflow vulnerability is present in 

Zigbee EZSP Host Applications. If the buffer overflows, stack corruption is possible. In certain

conditions, this could lead to arbitrary code execution. Access to a network key is required to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58747 | Dify MCP OAuth Flow Vulnerable to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58747</link><description>Dify is an LLM application development platform. In Dify versions through 1.9.1, the MCP OAuth component is vulnerable to cross-site scripting when a victim connects to an attacker-controlled remote MCP server. The vulnerability exists in the OAuth flow implementation where the authorization_url provided by a remote MCP server is directly passed to window.open without validation or sanitization. An attacker can craft a malicious MCP server that returns a JavaScript URI (such as javascript:alert(1)) in the authorization_url field, which is then executed when the victim attempts to connect to the MCP server. This allows the attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the Dify application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11905 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS gather.js getArticle code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11905</link><description>A vulnerability was found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.3.2. This vulnerability affects the function getArticle of the file app\modules\cms\controller\gather.js. The manipulation results in code injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62356 | A path traversal vulnerability in all versions of the Qodo Qodo Gen IDE enables a threat actor to read arbitrary local files in and outside ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62356</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in all versions of the Qodo Qodo Gen IDE enables a threat actor to read arbitrary local files in and outside of current projects on an end user’s system. The vulnerability can be reached directly and through indirect prompt injection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26625 | Git LFS may write to arbitrary files via crafted symlinks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26625</link><description>Git LFS is a Git extension for versioning large files. In Git LFS versions 0.5.2 through 3.7.0, when populating a Git repository's working tree with the contents of Git LFS objects, certain Git LFS commands may write to files visible outside the current Git working tree if symbolic or hard links exist which collide with the paths of files tracked by Git LFS. The git lfs checkout and git lfs pull commands do not check for symbolic links before writing to files in the working tree, allowing an attacker to craft a repository containing symbolic or hard links that cause Git LFS to write to arbitrary file system locations accessible to the user running these commands. As well, when the git lfs checkout and git lfs pull commands are run in a bare repository, they could write to files visible outside the repository. The vulnerability is fixed in version 3.7.1. As a workaround, support for symlinks in Git may be disabled by setting the core.symlinks configuration option to false, after which further clones and fetches will not create symbolic links. However, any symbolic or hard links in existing repositories will still provide the opportunity for Git LFS to write to their targets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49655 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the Keras framework running versions 3.11.0 up to but not including 3.11.3, enabl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49655</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the Keras framework running versions 3.11.0 up to but not including 3.11.3, enabling a maliciously uploaded Keras file containing a TorchModuleWrapper class to run arbitrary code on an end user’s system when loaded despite safe mode being enabled. The vulnerability can be triggered through both local and remote files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57567 | A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the PluXml CMS theme editor, specifically in the minify.php file located under the def...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57567</link><description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the PluXml CMS theme editor, specifically in the minify.php file located under the default theme directory (/themes/defaut/css/minify.php). An authenticated administrator user can overwrite this file with arbitrary PHP code via the admin panel, enabling execution of system commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62353 | A path traversal vulnerability in all versions of the Windsurf IDE enables a threat actor to read and write arbitrary local files in and out...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62353</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in all versions of the Windsurf IDE enables a threat actor to read and write arbitrary local files in and outside of current projects on an end user’s system. The vulnerability can be reached directly and through indirect prompt injection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60279 | A server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Illia Cloud illia-Builder before v4.8.5 allows authenticated users to send arbitrary r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60279</link><description>A server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Illia Cloud illia-Builder before v4.8.5 allows authenticated users to send arbitrary requests to internal services via the API. An attacker can leverage this to enumerate open ports based on response discrepancies and interact with internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11904 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS hasUse sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11904</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.3.2. This affects the function hasUse of the file /cms/model/hasUse. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55085 | Web http client: Unchecked Server-Side Malicious Packet Issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55085</link><description>In NextX Duo before 6.4.4, in the HTTP client module, the network support code for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, the parsing of HTTP header fields was missing bounds verification. A crafted server response could cause undefined behavior.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60361 | radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function bochs_open.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60361</link><description>radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function bochs_open.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48087 | WordPress Memberlite Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48087</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jason C. Memberlite Shortcodes memberlite-shortcodes allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Memberlite Shortcodes: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11902 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS findField sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11902</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.3.2. Affected by this vulnerability is the function findField of the file /cms/article/findField. Performing manipulation of the argument cid results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:22:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11903 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS update sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11903</link><description>A flaw has been found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.3.2. Affected by this issue is the function update of the file /cms/article/update. Executing manipulation of the argument cid can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:22:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60359 | radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function r_bin_object_new.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60359</link><description>radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function r_bin_object_new.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60360 | radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function r2r_subprocess_init.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60360</link><description>radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function r2r_subprocess_init.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48044 | Authorization bypass when bypass policy condition evaluates to true</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48044</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in ash-project ash allows Authentication Bypass. This vulnerability is associated with program files lib/ash/policy/policy.ex and program routines 'Elixir.Ash.Policy.Policy':expression/2.

This issue affects ash: from pkg:hex/ash@3.6.3 before pkg:hex/ash@3.7.1, from 3.6.3 before 3.7.1, from 79749c2685ea031ebb2de8cf60cc5edced6a8dd0 before 8b83efa225f657bfc3656ad8ee8485f9b2de923d.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28815 | Some versions of Hikvision's iSecure Center Product contain insufficient parameter validation, resulting in a command injection vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28815</link><description>Some versions of Hikvision's iSecure Center Product contain insufficient parameter validation, resulting in a command injection vulnerability. Attackers may exploit this to gain platform privileges and execute arbitrary commands on the system.iSecure Center is software released for China's domestic market only, with no overseas release.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28814 | Some versions of Hikvision's iSecure Center Product have an improper file upload control vulnerability. Due to the improper verification of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28814</link><description>Some versions of Hikvision's iSecure Center Product have an improper file upload control vulnerability. Due to the improper verification of file to be uploaded, attackers may upload malicious files to the server. iSecure Center is software released for China's domestic market only, with no overseas release.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11895 | Binary MLM Plan &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11895</link><description>The Binary MLM Plan plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to insecure direct object reference in versions up to, and including, 3.0. This is due to the bmp_user_payout_detail_of_current_user() function selecting payout records solely by id without verifying ownership. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with the bmp_user role (often subscribers) to view other members' payout summaries via direct requests to the /bmp-account-detail/ endpoint with a crafted payout-id parameter granted they can access the shortcode output.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 09:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55087 | In NextX Duo's snmp addon versions before 6.4.4, a part of the Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, an attacker could cause an out-of-bound read by a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55087</link><description>In NextX Duo's snmp addon versions before 6.4.4, a part of the Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, an attacker could cause an out-of-bound read by a crafted SNMPv3 security parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 06:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55097 | Potential out-of-bounds read in _ux_host_class_audio_streaming_sampling_get()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55097</link><description>In USBX before 6.4.3, the USB support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _ux_host_class_audio_streaming_sampling_get() when parsing a descriptor of an USB streaming device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55098 | Potential out-of-bounds read in _ux_host_class_audio_device_type_get()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55098</link><description>In USBX before 6.4.3, the USB support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _ux_host_class_audio_device_type_get()
      when parsing a descriptor of an USB audio device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55099 | Potential out-of-bounds read in _ux_host_class_audio_alternate_setting_locate()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55099</link><description>In USBX before 6.4.3, the USB support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _ux_host_class_audio_alternate_setting_locate() when parsing a descriptor with attacker-controlled frequency fields.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55100 | Potential out-of-bounds read in _ux_host_class_audio10_sam_parse_func()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55100</link><description>In USBX before 6.4.3, the USB support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _ux_host_class_audio10_sam_parse_func() when parsing a list of sampling frequencies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55094 | Potential out-of-bounds read in _nx_icmpv6_validate_options()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55094</link><description>In NetX Duo before 6.4.4, the networking support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in  _nx_icmpv6_validate_options() when handling a packet with ICMP6 options.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55096 | Inadequate bounds check and potential underflow in _ux_host_class_hid_report_descriptor_get()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55096</link><description>In USBX before 6.4.3, the USB support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _ux_host_class_hid_report_descriptor_get()
 when parsing a descriptor of an USB HID device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55092 | Potential out of bound read in _nx_ipv4_option_process()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55092</link><description>In Eclipse Foundation NetX Duo before 6.4.4, the networking support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _nx_ipv4_option_process() when processing an IPv4 packet with the timestamp option.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55093 | Out of bound read and write in _nx_ipv4_packet_receive() when handling unicast DHCP messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55093</link><description>In NetX Duo before 6.4.4, the networking support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _nx_ipv4_packet_receive() when handling unicast DHCP messages that could cause corruption of 4 bytes of memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11849 | Versions of the package mammoth from 0.3.25 and before 1.11.0; versions of the package mammoth from 0.3.25 and before 1.11.0; versions of th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11849</link><description>Versions of the package mammoth from 0.3.25 and before 1.11.0; versions of the package mammoth from 0.3.25 and before 1.11.0; versions of the package mammoth before 1.11.0; versions of the package org.zwobble.mammoth:mammoth before 1.11.0 are vulnerable to Directory Traversal due to the lack of path or file type validation when processing a docx file containing an image with an external link (r:link attribute instead of embedded r:embed). The library resolves the URI to a file path and after reading, the content is encoded as base64 and included in the HTML output as a data URI. An attacker can read arbitrary files on the system where the conversion is performed or cause an excessive resources consumption by crafting a docx file that links to special device files such as /dev/random or /dev/zero.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11898 | Flowring Technology｜Agentflow - Arbitrary File Reading through Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11898</link><description>Agentflow developed by Flowring has an Arbitrary File Reading vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit Relative Path Traversal to download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11899 | Flowring Technology｜Agentflow - Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11899</link><description>Agentflow developed by Flowring has an Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit the fixed key to generate verification information, thereby logging into the system as any user. Attacker must first obtain an user ID in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11900 | HGiga｜iSherlock - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11900</link><description>The iSherlock developed by HGiga has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary OS commands and execute them on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:57:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6949 | An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A critical aut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6949</link><description>An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A critical authorization flaw in the API allows an authenticated, low-privileged user to create a new administrator account, including accounts with usernames identical to existing users. In certain scenarios, this vulnerability could allow an attacker to gain full administrative control over the affected device, leading to potential account impersonation. While successful exploitation can severely impact the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the affected device itself, there is no loss of confidentiality or integrity within any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6950 | An Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. The system employs a h...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6950</link><description>An Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. The system employs a hard-coded secret key to sign JSON Web Tokens (JWT) used for authentication. This insecure implementation allows an unauthenticated attacker to forge valid tokens, thereby bypassing authentication controls and impersonating any user. Exploitation of this vulnerability can result in complete system compromise, enabling unauthorized access, data theft, and full administrative control over the affected device. While successful exploitation can severely impact the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the affected device itself, there is no loss of confidentiality or integrity within any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6893 | An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in brok...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6893</link><description>An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in broken access control has been identified in the /api/v1/setting/data endpoint of the affected device. This flaw allows a low-privileged authenticated user to call the API without the required permissions, thereby gaining the ability to access or modify system configuration data. Successful exploitation may lead to privilege escalation, allowing the attacker to access or modify sensitive system settings. While the overall impact is high, there is no loss of confidentiality or integrity within any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6894 | An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6894</link><description>An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in the API authorization logic of the affected device allows an authenticated, low-privileged user to execute the administrative `ping` function, which is restricted to higher-privileged roles. This vulnerability enables the user to perform internal network reconnaissance, potentially discovering internal hosts or services that would otherwise be inaccessible. Repeated exploitation could lead to minor resource consumption. While the overall impact is limited, it may result in some loss of confidentiality and availability on the affected device. There is no impact on the integrity of the device, and the vulnerability does not affect any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6892 | An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in the API authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6892</link><description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in the API authentication mechanism allows unauthorized access to protected API endpoints, including those intended for administrative functions. This vulnerability can be exploited after a legitimate user has logged in, as the system fails to properly validate session context or privilege boundaries. An attacker may leverage this flaw to perform unauthorized privileged operations. While successful exploitation can severely impact the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the affected device itself, there is no loss of confidentiality or integrity within any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 02:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>