<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:37:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-43202 | Apache DolphinScheduler: Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43202</link><description>Exposure of Remote Code Execution in Apache Dolphinscheduler.

This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: before 3.2.2. 

We recommend users to upgrade Apache DolphinScheduler to version 3.2.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38808 | CVE-2024-38808: Spring Expression DoS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38808</link><description>In Spring Framework versions 5.3.0 - 5.3.38 and older unsupported versions, it is possible for a user to provide a specially crafted Spring Expression Language (SpEL) expression that may cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.

Specifically, an application is vulnerable when the following is true:

  *  The application evaluates user-supplied SpEL expressions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:26:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6847 | SmartSearch WP &amp;lt;= 2.4.4 - Unauthenticated SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6847</link><description>The Chatbot with ChatGPT WordPress plugin before 2.4.5 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, leading to a SQL injection exploitable by unauthenticated users when submitting messages to the chatbot.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 06:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43688 | cron/entry.c in vixie cron before 9cc8ab1, as used in OpenBSD 7.4 and 7.5, allows a heap-based buffer underflow and memory corruption. NOTE:...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43688</link><description>cron/entry.c in vixie cron before 9cc8ab1, as used in OpenBSD 7.4 and 7.5, allows a heap-based buffer underflow and memory corruption. NOTE: this issue was introduced during a May 2023 refactoring.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 05:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5576 | Tutor LMS Elementor Addons &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Course Carousel Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5576</link><description>The Tutor LMS Elementor Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'course_carousel_skin' attribute within the plugin's Course Carousel widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 05:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6864 | WP Last Modified Info &amp;lt;= 1.9.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via lmt-post-modified-info Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6864</link><description>The WP Last Modified Info plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘template’ attribute of the lmt-post-modified-info shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 04:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38810 | Missing Authorization When Using @AuthorizeReturnObject</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38810</link><description>Missing Authorization When Using @AuthorizeReturnObject in Spring Security 6.3.0 and 6.3.1 allows attacker to render security annotations inaffective.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 03:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-1206 | AdRotate – Ad manager &amp;amp; AdSense Ads &amp;lt;= 5.13.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) Double Extension Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1206</link><description>The AdRotate Banner Manager – The only ad manager you'll need plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file extension sanitization in the adrotate_insert_media() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.13.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files with double extensions on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. This is only exploitable on select instances where the configuration will execute the first extension present.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 03:31:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5763 | The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.6.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Video Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5763</link><description>The The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the video_date attribute within the plugin's Video widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 03:31:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6575 | The Plus Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 5.6.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via TP Page Scroll Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6575</link><description>The The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘res_width_value’ parameter within the plugin's tp_page_scroll widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 03:31:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7702 | Contact Form by Bit Form: Multi Step Form, Calculation Contact Form, Payment Contact Form &amp;amp; Custom Contact Form builder 2.0 - 2.13.9 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via getLogHistory Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7702</link><description>The Contact Form by Bit Form: Multi Step Form, Calculation Contact Form, Payment Contact Form &amp; Custom Contact Form builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to generic SQL Injection via the entryID parameter in versions 2.0 to 2.13.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user-supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries to already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 03:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7775 | Contact Form by Bit Form: Multi Step Form, Calculation Contact Form, Payment Contact Form &amp;amp; Custom Contact Form builder 2.0 - 2.13.9 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary JavaScript File Uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7775</link><description>The Contact Form by Bit Form: Multi Step Form, Calculation Contact Form, Payment Contact Form &amp; Custom Contact Form builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary JavaScript file uploads due to missing input validation in the addCustomCode function in versions 2.0 to 2.13.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary JavaScript files to the affected site's server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 03:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7777 | Contact Form by Bit Form: Multi Step Form, Calculation Contact Form, Payment Contact Form &amp;amp; Custom Contact Form builder 2.0 - 2.13.9 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Read And Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7777</link><description>The Contact Form by Bit Form: Multi Step Form, Calculation Contact Form, Payment Contact Form &amp; Custom Contact Form builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file read and deletion due to insufficient file path validation in multiple functions in versions 2.0 to 2.13.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to read and delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 03:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7780 | Contact Form by Bit Form: Multi Step Form, Calculation Contact Form, Payment Contact Form &amp;amp; Custom Contact Form builder 2.0 - 2.13.9 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7780</link><description>The Contact Form by Bit Form: Multi Step Form, Calculation Contact Form, Payment Contact Form &amp; Custom Contact Form builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to generic SQL Injection via the id parameter in versions 2.0 to 2.13.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user-supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 03:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7782 | Contact Form by Bit Form: Multi Step Form, Calculation Contact Form, Payment Contact Form &amp;amp; Custom Contact Form builder 2.0 - 2.13.4 - Authenticater (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7782</link><description>The Contact Form by Bit Form: Multi Step Form, Calculation Contact Form, Payment Contact Form &amp; Custom Contact Form builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the iconRemove function in versions 2.0 to 2.13.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 03:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5932 | GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform &amp;lt;= 3.14.1 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5932</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.14.1 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'give_title' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. The additional presence of a POP chain allows attackers to execute code remotely, and to delete arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 02:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5939 | GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform &amp;lt;= 3.13.0 - Missing Authorization to Limited Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5939</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'setup_wizard' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.13.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the setup wizard administrative pages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 02:29:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5940 | GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform &amp;lt;= 3.13.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Event Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5940</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'handle_request' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.13.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to edit event ticket settings if the Events beta feature is enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 02:29:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5941 | GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform &amp;lt;= 3.14.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5941</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and deletion of data due to a missing capability check on the 'handle_request' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.14.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read attachment paths and delete attachment files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 02:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7827 | Shopping Cart &amp;amp; eCommerce Store &amp;lt;= 5.7.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via model_number Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7827</link><description>The Shopping Cart &amp; eCommerce Store plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to boolean-based SQL Injection via the ‘model_number’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 02:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7850 | BP Profile Search &amp;lt;= 5.7.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7850</link><description>The BP Profile Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.5. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the bps_ajax_field_selector(), bps_ajax_template_options(), and bps_ajax_field_row() functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 02:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7948 | SourceCodester Accounts Manager App Update Account Page update-account.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7948</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Accounts Manager App 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file update-account.php of the component Update Account Page. The manipulation of the argument Account Name/Username/Password/Link leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 02:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7949 | SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System fetch_genderit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7949</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System up to 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /tracking/admin/fetch_genderit.php. The manipulation of the argument request leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 02:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7946 | itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System User Signup register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7946</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file register.php of the component User Signup. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 02:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7947 | SourceCodester Point of Sales and Inventory Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7947</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 02:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7944 | itsourcecode Laravel Property Management System DocumentsController.php UpdateDocumentsRequest unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7944</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Laravel Property Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function UpdateDocumentsRequest of the file DocumentsController.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 01:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7945 | itsourcecode Laravel Property Management System Notes Page create cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7945</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Laravel Property Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/notes/create of the component Notes Page. The manipulation of the argument Note text leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 01:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7943 | itsourcecode Laravel Property Management System PropertiesController.php upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7943</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Laravel Property Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function upload of the file PropertiesController.php. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 01:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7937 | itsourcecode Project Expense Monitoring System printtransfer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7937</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Project Expense Monitoring System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file printtransfer.php. The manipulation of the argument transfer_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7942 | SourceCodester Leads Manager Tool update-leads.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7942</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Leads Manager Tool 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file update-leads.php. The manipulation of the argument phone_number leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7936 | itsourcecode Project Expense Monitoring System transferred_report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7936</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Project Expense Monitoring System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file transferred_report.php. The manipulation of the argument start/end/employee leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 23:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7305 | DWF Vulnerability in Autodesk Desktop Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7305</link><description>A maliciously crafted DWF file, when parsed in AdDwfPdk.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 23:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7935 | itsourcecode Project Expense Monitoring System print.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7935</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Project Expense Monitoring System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file print.php. The manipulation of the argument map_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 23:17:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7933 | itsourcecode Project Expense Monitoring System Backend Login login1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7933</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Project Expense Monitoring System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file login1.php of the component Backend Login. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 22:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7934 | itsourcecode Project Expense Monitoring System execute.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7934</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Project Expense Monitoring System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file execute.php. The manipulation of the argument code leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 22:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4785 | BT: Missing Check in LL_CONNECTION_UPDATE_IND Packet Leads to Division by Zero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4785</link><description>BT: Missing Check in LL_CONNECTION_UPDATE_IND Packet Leads to Division by Zero</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 22:22:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7930 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System get_packings.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7930</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /pms/ajax/get_packings.php. The manipulation of the argument medicine_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 22:22:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7931 | SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System view_csprofile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7931</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /tracking/admin/view_csprofile.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 22:22:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7928 | FastAdmin lang path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7928</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in FastAdmin up to 1.3.3.20220121. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index/ajax/lang. The manipulation of the argument lang leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.3.4.20220530 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 21:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7929 | SourceCodester Simple Forum Website Signup Page registration.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7929</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Simple Forum Website 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /registration.php of the component Signup Page. The manipulation of the argument username leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 21:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35538 | Typecho v1.3.0 was discovered to contain a Client IP Spoofing vulnerability, which allows attackers to falsify their IP addresses by specify...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35538</link><description>Typecho v1.3.0 was discovered to contain a Client IP Spoofing vulnerability, which allows attackers to falsify their IP addresses by specifying an arbitrary IP as value of X-Forwarded-For or Client-Ip headers while performing HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 20:25:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35539 | Typecho v1.3.0 was discovered to contain a race condition vulnerability in the post commenting function. This vulnerability allows attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35539</link><description>Typecho v1.3.0 was discovered to contain a race condition vulnerability in the post commenting function. This vulnerability allows attackers to post several comments before the spam protection checks if the comments are posted too frequently.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 20:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7927 | ZZCMS class.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7927</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in ZZCMS 2023. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/class.php?dowhat=modifyclass. The manipulation of the argument skin[] leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 20:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42813 | In TRENDnet TEW-752DRU FW1.03B01, there is a buffer overflow vulnerability due to the lack of length verification for the service field in g...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42813</link><description>In TRENDnet TEW-752DRU FW1.03B01, there is a buffer overflow vulnerability due to the lack of length verification for the service field in gena.cgi. Attackers who successfully exploit this vulnerability can cause the remote target device to crash or execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 20:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42815 | In the TP-Link RE365 V1_180213, there is a buffer overflow vulnerability due to the lack of length verification for the USER_AGENT field in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42815</link><description>In the TP-Link RE365 V1_180213, there is a buffer overflow vulnerability due to the lack of length verification for the USER_AGENT field in /usr/bin/httpd. Attackers who successfully exploit this vulnerability can cause the remote target device to crash or execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 19:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43345 | WordPress Landing Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.2.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43345</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in PluginOps Landing Page Builder allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Landing Page Builder: from n/a through 1.5.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 19:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43354 | WordPress myCred plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.2 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43354</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in myCred allows Object Injection.This issue affects myCred: from n/a through 2.7.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 19:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7926 | ZZCMS about_edit.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7926</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in ZZCMS 2023. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/about_edit.php?action=modify. The manipulation of the argument skin leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 19:41:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43311 | WordPress Login As Users plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43311</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Geek Code Lab Login As Users allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Login As Users: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 19:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43317 | WordPress RegistrationMagic plugin &amp;lt;= 6.0.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43317</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Metagauss User Registration Team RegistrationMagic allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects RegistrationMagic: from n/a through 6.0.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 19:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43326 | WordPress Plugin Notes Plus plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43326</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jamie Bergen Plugin Notes Plus allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Plugin Notes Plus: from n/a through 1.2.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 19:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43328 | WordPress EmbedPress plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43328</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in WPDeveloper EmbedPress allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects EmbedPress: from n/a through 4.0.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 19:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42812 | In D-Link DIR-860L v2.03, there is a buffer overflow vulnerability due to the lack of length verification for the SID field in gena.cgi. Att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42812</link><description>In D-Link DIR-860L v2.03, there is a buffer overflow vulnerability due to the lack of length verification for the SID field in gena.cgi. Attackers who successfully exploit this vulnerability can cause the remote target device to crash or execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 19:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7592 | Quadratic complexity parsing cookies with backslashes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7592</link><description>There is a LOW severity vulnerability affecting CPython, specifically the
'http.cookies' standard library module.


When parsing cookies that contained backslashes for quoted characters in
the cookie value, the parser would use an algorithm with quadratic
complexity, resulting in excess CPU resources being used while parsing the
value.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 19:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23729 | The ColorOS Internet Browser com.heytap.browser application 45.10.3.4.1 for Android allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23729</link><description>The ColorOS Internet Browser com.heytap.browser application 45.10.3.4.1 for Android allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code via the com.android.browser.RealBrowserActivity component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 18:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7924 | ZZCMS list.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7924</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZZCMS 2023. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /I/list.php. The manipulation of the argument skin leads to path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 18:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7925 | ZZCMS eginfo.php information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7925</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZZCMS 2023. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file 3/E_bak5.1/upload/eginfo.php. The manipulation of the argument phome with the input ShowPHPInfo leads to information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 18:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43280 | WordPress Salon Booking System plugin &amp;lt;= 10.8.1 - Open Redirection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43280</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Salon Booking System Salon booking system.This issue affects Salon booking system: from n/a through 10.8.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43281 | WordPress Void Elementor Post Grid Addon for Elementor Page builder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43281</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in VOID CODERS Void Elementor Post Grid Addon for Elementor Page builder allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Void Elementor Post Grid Addon for Elementor Page builder: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43261 | WordPress Compute Links plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Remote File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43261</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Hamed Naderfar Compute Links allows PHP Remote File Inclusion.This issue affects Compute Links: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43271 | WordPress Widgets for WooCommerce Products on Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43271</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Themelocation Woo Products Widgets For Elementor allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Woo Products Widgets For Elementor: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43272 | WordPress Icegram Engage plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.24 - Unauthenticated Unpublished Campaign Viewer vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43272</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in icegram Icegram allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Icegram: from n/a through 3.1.24.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43250 | WordPress Bit Form Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.4 - Authenticated Plugin Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43250</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Bit Apps Bit Form Pro bitformpro allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Bit Form Pro: from n/a through 2.6.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43252 | WordPress Crew HRM plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43252</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Crew HRM allows Object Injection.This issue affects Crew HRM: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43256 | WordPress Leopard plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.36 - Subscriber+ Plugin Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43256</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in nouthemes Leopard - WordPress offload media allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Leopard - WordPress offload media: from n/a through 2.0.36.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43242 | WordPress Indeed Ultimate Membership Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 12.6 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43242</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in azzaroco Ultimate Membership Pro allows Object Injection.This issue affects Ultimate Membership Pro: from n/a through 12.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43245 | WordPress JobSearch plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.4 - Unauthenticated Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43245</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in eyecix JobSearch allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects JobSearch: from n/a through 2.3.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43247 | WordPress WHMpress plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2-revision-5 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43247</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in creativeon WHMpress allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects WHMpress: from n/a through 6.2-revision-5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43248 | WordPress Bit Form Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43248</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Bit Apps Bit Form Pro allows File Manipulation.This issue affects Bit Form Pro: from n/a through 2.6.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43249 | WordPress Bit Form Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.4 - Authenticated Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43249</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Bit Apps Bit Form Pro allows Command Injection.This issue affects Bit Form Pro: from n/a through 2.6.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43221 | WordPress JetGridBuilder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43221</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Crocoblock JetGridBuilder allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects JetGridBuilder: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43232 | WordPress Timeline and History slider plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43232</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in WP OnlineSupport, Essential Plugin Timeline and History slider allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Timeline and History slider: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43236 | WordPress Easy PayPal &amp;amp; Stripe Buy Now Button plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Open Redirection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43236</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Scott Paterson Easy PayPal Buy Now Button.This issue affects Easy PayPal Buy Now Button: from n/a through 1.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43240 | WordPress Indeed Ultimate Membership Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 12.6 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43240</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in azzaroco Ultimate Membership Pro allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Ultimate Membership Pro: from n/a through 12.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37099 | WordPress GiveWP plugin &amp;lt;= 3.14.1 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37099</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Liquid Web GiveWP allows Object Injection.This issue affects GiveWP: from n/a through 3.14.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42658 | An issue in wishnet Nepstech Wifi Router NTPL-XPON1GFEVN v1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the cookie's para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42658</link><description>An issue in wishnet Nepstech Wifi Router NTPL-XPON1GFEVN v1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the cookie's parameter</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32927 | In sendDeviceState_1_6 of RadioExt.cpp, there is a possible use after free due to improper locking. This could lead to local escalation of p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32927</link><description>In sendDeviceState_1_6 of RadioExt.cpp, there is a possible use after free due to improper locking. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42657 | An issue in wishnet Nepstech Wifi Router NTPL-XPON1GFEVN v1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the lack of encry...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42657</link><description>An issue in wishnet Nepstech Wifi Router NTPL-XPON1GFEVN v1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the lack of encryption during login process</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32928 | The libcurl CURLOPT_SSL_VERIFYPEER option was disabled on a subset of requests made by Nest production devices which enabled a potential man...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32928</link><description>The libcurl CURLOPT_SSL_VERIFYPEER option was disabled on a subset of requests made by Nest production devices which enabled a potential man-in-the-middle attack on requests to Google cloud services by any host the traffic was routed through.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43400 | XWiki Platform allows XSS through XClass name in string properties</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43400</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. It is possible for a user without Script or Programming rights to craft a URL pointing to a page with arbitrary JavaScript. This requires social engineer to trick a user to follow the URL. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5, 15.10.6 and 16.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43401 | In XWiki Platform, payloads stored in content is executed when a user with script/programming right edit them</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43401</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. A user without script/programming right can trick a user with elevated rights to edit a content with a malicious payload using a WYSIWYG editor. The user with elevated rights is not warned beforehand that they are going to edit possibly dangerous content. The payload is executed at edit time. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 15.10RC1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42633 | A Command Injection vulnerability exists in the do_upgrade_post function of the httpd binary in Linksys E1500 v1.0.06.001. As a result, an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42633</link><description>A Command Injection vulnerability exists in the do_upgrade_post function of the httpd binary in Linksys E1500 v1.0.06.001. As a result, an authenticated attacker can execute OS commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 15:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6348 | Predictable seed generation after ECU reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6348</link><description>Predictable seed generation in the security access mechanism of UDS in the Blind Spot Protection Sensor ECU in Nissan Altima (2022) allows attackers to predict the requested seeds and bypass security controls via repeated ECU resets and seed requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 15:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7922 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 myMusic.cgi cgi_write_playlist command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7922</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function cgi_audio_search/cgi_create_playlist/cgi_get_album_all_tracks/cgi_get_alltracks_editlist/cgi_get_artist_all_album/cgi_get_genre_all_tracks/cgi_get_tracks_list/cgi_set_airplay_content/cgi_write_playlist of the file /cgi-bin/myMusic.cgi. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 15:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43399 | Mobile Security Framework (MobSF) has a Zip Slip Vulnerability in .a Static Library Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43399</link><description>Mobile Security Framework (MobSF) is a pen-testing, malware analysis and security assessment framework capable of performing static and dynamic analysis. Before 4.0.7, there is a flaw in the Static Libraries analysis section. Specifically, during the extraction of .a extension files, the measure intended to prevent Zip Slip attacks is improperly implemented. Since the implemented measure can be bypassed, the vulnerability allows an attacker to extract files to any desired location within the server running MobSF. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.0.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 14:56:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43380 | fugit parse and parse_nat stall on lengthy input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43380</link><description>fugit contains time tools for flor and the floraison group. The fugit "natural" parser, that turns "every wednesday at 5pm" into "0 17 * * 3", accepted any length of input and went on attempting to parse it, not returning promptly, as expected. The parse call could hold the thread with no end in sight. Fugit dependents that do not check (user) input length for plausibility are impacted. A fix was released in fugit 1.11.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 14:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43379 | TruffleHog has a Blind SSRF in some Detectors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43379</link><description>TruffleHog is a secrets scanning tool. Prior to v3.81.9, this vulnerability allows a malicious actor to craft data in a way that, when scanned by specific detectors, could trigger the detector to make an unauthorized request to an endpoint chosen by the attacker. For an exploit to be effective, the target endpoint must be an unauthenticated GET endpoint that produces side effects. The victim must scan the maliciously crafted data and have such an endpoint targeted for the exploit to succeed. The vulnerability has been resolved in TruffleHog v3.81.9 and later versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 14:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25582 | Module savepoints could be abused to inject references to malicious code delivered through the same domain. Attackers could perform maliciou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25582</link><description>Module savepoints could be abused to inject references to malicious code delivered through the same domain. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Exploiting this vulnerability requires temporary access to an account or successful social engineering to make a user follow a prepared link to a malicious account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. The savepoint module path has been restricted to modules that provide the feature, excluding any arbitrary or non-existing modules. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 07:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6330 | GEO my WordPress &amp;lt; 4.4.0.2 - Unauthenticated RCE via LFI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6330</link><description>The GEO my WP WordPress plugin before 4.5.0.2 does not prevent unauthenticated attackers from including arbitrary files in PHP's execution context, which leads to Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 06:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6451 | AI Engine &amp;lt; 2.5.1 - Admin+ RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6451</link><description>AI Engine &lt; 2.4.3 is susceptible to remote-code-execution (RCE) via Log Poisoning. The AI Engine WordPress plugin before 2.5.1 fails to validate the file extension of "logs_path", allowing Administrators to change log filetypes from .log to .php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 06:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6843 | SmartSearch WP &amp;lt;= 2.4.4 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6843</link><description>The Chatbot with ChatGPT WordPress plugin before 2.4.5 does not sanitise and escape user inputs, which could allow unauthenticated users to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks against admins</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 06:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44083 | ida64.dll in Hex-Rays IDA Pro through 8.4 crashes when there is a section that has many jumps linked, and the final jump corresponds to the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44083</link><description>ida64.dll in Hex-Rays IDA Pro through 8.4 crashes when there is a section that has many jumps linked, and the final jump corresponds to the payload from where the actual entry point will be invoked. NOTE: in many use cases, this is an inconvenience but not a security issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 04:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44076 | In Microcks before 1.10.0, the POST /api/import and POST /api/export endpoints allow non-administrator access.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44076</link><description>In Microcks before 1.10.0, the POST /api/import and POST /api/export endpoints allow non-administrator access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 03:16:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44073 | The Miniscript (aka rust-miniscript) library before 12.2.0 for Rust allows stack consumption because it does not properly track tree depth.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44073</link><description>The Miniscript (aka rust-miniscript) library before 12.2.0 for Rust allows stack consumption because it does not properly track tree depth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 02:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7921 | Anhui Deshun Intelligent Technology Jieshun JieLink+ JSOTC2016 GetDataList access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7921</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Anhui Deshun Intelligent Technology Jieshun JieLink+ JSOTC2016 up to 20240805 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /report/ParkOutRecord/GetDataList. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 02:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44070 | An issue was discovered in FRRouting (FRR) through 10.1. bgp_attr_encap in bgpd/bgp_attr.c does not check the actual remaining stream length...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44070</link><description>An issue was discovered in FRRouting (FRR) through 10.1. bgp_attr_encap in bgpd/bgp_attr.c does not check the actual remaining stream length before taking the TLV value.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 02:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44069 | Pi-hole before 6 allows unauthenticated admin/api.php?setTempUnit= calls to change the temperature units of the web dashboard. NOTE: the sup...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44069</link><description>Pi-hole before 6 allows unauthenticated admin/api.php?setTempUnit= calls to change the temperature units of the web dashboard. NOTE: the supplier reportedly does "not consider the bug a security issue" but the specific motivation for letting arbitrary persons change the value (Celsius, Fahrenheit, or Kelvin), seen by the device owner, is unclear.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 01:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44067 | The T-Head XuanTie C910 CPU in the TH1520 SoC and the T-Head XuanTie C920 CPU in the SOPHON SG2042 have instructions that allow unprivileged...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44067</link><description>The T-Head XuanTie C910 CPU in the TH1520 SoC and the T-Head XuanTie C920 CPU in the SOPHON SG2042 have instructions that allow unprivileged attackers to write to arbitrary physical memory locations, aka GhostWrite.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 01:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7919 | Anhui Deshun Intelligent Technology Jieshun JieLink+ JSOTC2016 GetDataList access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7919</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Anhui Deshun Intelligent Technology Jieshun JieLink+ JSOTC2016 up to 20240805. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /report/ParkChargeRecord/GetDataList. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7920 | Anhui Deshun Intelligent Technology Jieshun JieLink+ JSOTC2016 GetParkInThroughDeivces access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7920</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Anhui Deshun Intelligent Technology Jieshun JieLink+ JSOTC2016 up to 20240805. Affected is an unknown function of the file /Report/ParkCommon/GetParkInThroughDeivces. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7916 | nafisulbari/itsourcecode Insurance Management System Add Nominee Page addNominee.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7916</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in nafisulbari/itsourcecode Insurance Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file addNominee.php of the component Add Nominee Page. The manipulation of the argument Nominee-Client ID leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 22:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7917 | DouPHP Favicon system.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7917</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in DouPHP 1.7 Release 20220822. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/system.php of the component Favicon Handler. The manipulation of the argument site_favicon leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 22:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7913 | itsourcecode Billing System addclient1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7913</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Billing System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /addclient1.php. The manipulation of the argument lname/fname/mi/address/contact/meterReader leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 22:16:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7914 | SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System SystemSettings.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7914</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /php-ycrs/classes/SystemSettings.php. The manipulation of the argument address leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 22:16:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35686 | WordPress Sensei LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 4.23.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35686</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Automattic Sensei LMS, Automattic Sensei Pro (WC Paid Courses).This issue affects Sensei LMS: from n/a through 4.23.1; Sensei Pro (WC Paid Courses): from n/a through 4.23.1.1.23.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 22:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43145 | WordPress GeoDirectory plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.61 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43145</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in AyeCode Ltd GeoDirectory.This issue affects GeoDirectory: from n/a through 2.3.61.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43207 | WordPress Unite Gallery Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.62 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43207</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Valiano Unite Gallery Lite.This issue affects Unite Gallery Lite: from n/a through 1.7.62.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43282 | WordPress Tutor LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43282</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Themeum Tutor LMS.This issue affects Tutor LMS: from n/a through 2.7.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43286 | WordPress Squirrly SEO plugin &amp;lt;= 12.3.19 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43286</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Squirrly SEO Plugin by Squirrly SEO.This issue affects SEO Plugin by Squirrly SEO: from n/a through 12.3.19.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43239 | WordPress Masteriyo LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11.4 - Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43239</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Masteriyo Masteriyo - LMS.This issue affects Masteriyo - LMS: from n/a through 1.11.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43266 | WordPress WP Job Portal – A Complete Job Board plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43266</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in WP Job Portal.This issue affects WP Job Portal: from n/a through 2.1.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43288 | WordPress wpForo Forum plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.4 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43288</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in gVectors Team wpForo Forum.This issue affects wpForo Forum: from n/a through 2.3.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43315 | WordPress Stripe Payments For WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43315</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Checkout Plugins Stripe Payments For WooCommerce by Checkout.This issue affects Stripe Payments For WooCommerce by Checkout: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43322 | WordPress Zephyr Project Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.100 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43322</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Dylan James Zephyr Project Manager.This issue affects Zephyr Project Manager: from n/a through 3.3.100.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43350 | WordPress Propovoice CRM plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.6.4 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43350</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Propovoice Propovoice CRM.This issue affects Propovoice CRM: from n/a through 1.7.6.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7912 | CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System assets exposure of information through directory listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7912</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/assets/. The manipulation leads to exposure of information through directory listing. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43241 | WordPress Indeed Ultimate Membership Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 12.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43241</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in azzaroco Ultimate Membership Pro allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Ultimate Membership Pro: from n/a through 12.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43244 | WordPress houzez Theme By FaveThemes &amp;lt;= 3.2.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43244</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in favethemes Houzez allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Houzez: from n/a through 3.2.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43246 | WordPress WHMpress plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2-revision-5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43246</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in creativeon WHMpress allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WHMpress: from n/a through 6.2-revision-5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43262 | WordPress Busiprof theme &amp;lt;= 2.4.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43262</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in webriti Busiprof allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Busiprof: from n/a through 2.4.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43263 | WordPress Visual Composer Starter theme &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43263</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Visual Composer Visual Composer Starter allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Visual Composer Starter: from n/a through 3.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43267 | WordPress Mega Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43267</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Qamar Sheeraz, Nasir Ahmad, GenialSouls Mega Addons For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mega Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 1.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43278 | WordPress  Meta Field Block plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.13 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43278</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Phi Phan Meta Field Block allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Meta Field Block: from n/a through 1.2.13.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43279 | WordPress Newsletters plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43279</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tribulant Newsletters allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Newsletters: from n/a through 4.9.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43284 | WordPress WP Travel Gutenberg Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43284</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Travel WP Travel Gutenberg Blocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Travel Gutenberg Blocks: from n/a through 3.5.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43291 | WordPress Void Contact Form 7 Widget For Elementor Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43291</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in voidCoders Void Contact Form 7 Widget For Elementor Page Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Void Contact Form 7 Widget For Elementor Page Builder: from n/a through 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43292 | WordPress Envo&amp;#x27;s Elementor Templates &amp;amp; Widgets for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.16 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43292</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in EnvoThemes Envo's Elementor Templates &amp; Widgets for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Envo's Elementor Templates &amp; Widgets for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.4.16.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43294 | WordPress Bold Timeline Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43294</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BoldThemes Bold Timeline Lite allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Bold Timeline Lite: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43303 | WordPress White Label CMS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43303</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in videousermanuals.Com White Label CMS allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects White Label CMS: from n/a through 2.7.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43304 | WordPress Cryptocurrency Widgets plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43304</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Cool Plugins Cryptocurrency Widgets – Price Ticker &amp; Coins List allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Cryptocurrency Widgets – Price Ticker &amp; Coins List: from n/a through 2.8.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 21:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7911 | SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System index.php file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7911</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /simple-online-bidding-system/bidding/index.php. The manipulation of the argument page leads to file inclusion. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 19:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6221 | Improper Access Control in corydolphin/flask-cors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6221</link><description>A vulnerability in corydolphin/flask-cors version 4.0.1 allows the `Access-Control-Allow-Private-Network` CORS header to be set to true by default, without any configuration option. This behavior can expose private network resources to unauthorized external access, leading to significant security risks such as data breaches, unauthorized access to sensitive information, and potential network intrusions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 19:15:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7910 | CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System Profile Photo Update emp-profile-avatar.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7910</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Online Railway Reservation System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/emp-profile-avatar.php of the component Profile Photo Update Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 18:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7909 | TOTOLINK EX1200L cstecgi.cgi setLanguageCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7909</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setLanguageCfg of the file /www/cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument langType leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 18:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7908 | TOTOLINK EX1200L cstecgi.cgi setDefResponse stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7908</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023. Affected is the function setDefResponse of the file /www/cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument IpAddress leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 17:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7907 | TOTOLINK X6000R cstecgi.cgi setSyslogCfg command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7907</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_20230719. This issue affects the function setSyslogCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument rtLogServer leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 16:25:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43305 | WordPress Custom Layouts – Post + Product grids made easy plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43305</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Code Amp Custom Layouts – Post + Product grids made easy allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Custom Layouts – Post + Product grids made easy: from n/a through 1.4.11.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 14:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43306 | WordPress WP-Lister Lite for eBay plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43306</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP-Lister Lite for eBay allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP-Lister Lite for eBay: from n/a through 3.6.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 14:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43307 | WordPress Structured Content (JSON-LD) #wpsc plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43307</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Gordon Böhme, Antonio Leutsch Structured Content allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Structured Content: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 14:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43308 | WordPress Gutentor – Gutenberg Blocks – Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43308</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Gutentor Gutentor - Gutenberg Blocks - Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Gutentor - Gutenberg Blocks - Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor: from n/a through 3.3.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 14:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43309 | WordPress WP Telegram Widget and Join Link plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.27 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43309</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Socio WP Telegram Widget and Join Link allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Telegram Widget and Join Link: from n/a through 2.1.27.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 14:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43313 | WordPress FormFacade – WordPress plugin for Google Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43313</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FormFacade allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects FormFacade: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 14:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43318 | WordPress E2Pdf – Export To Pdf Tool for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.25.05 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43318</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in E2Pdf.Com allows Stored XSS.This issue affects e2pdf: from n/a through 1.25.05.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 14:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43320 | WordPress WPBakery Page Builder Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43320</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Livemesh Livemesh Addons for WPBakery Page Builder addons-for-visual-composer allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Livemesh Addons for WPBakery Page Builder: from n/a through 3.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 14:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43321 | WordPress Team Showcase plugin &amp;lt;= 1.22.23 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43321</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PickPlugins Team Showcase allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Team Showcase: from n/a through 1.22.23.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 14:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43324 | WordPress Clever Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43324</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CleverSoft Clever Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Clever Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43327 | WordPress Invite Anyone plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43327</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Boone Gorges Invite Anyone allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Invite Anyone: from n/a through 1.4.7.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43329 | WordPress Allegiant theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43329</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Chill Allegiant allegiant allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Allegiant: from n/a through 1.2.7.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39666 | WordPress WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 9.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39666</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Automattic WooCommerce.This issue affects WooCommerce: from n/a through 9.1.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43238 | WordPress weMail – Email Marketing, Newsletter, Optin Forms, Subscribers WordPress Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.14.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43238</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in weDevs weMail allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects weMail: from n/a through 1.14.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43330 | WordPress PowerPack for Beaver Builder plugin &amp;lt; 2.37.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43330</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in IdeaBox Creations PowerPack for Beaver Builder allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects PowerPack for Beaver Builder: from n/a before 2.37.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43335 | WordPress Responsive Blocks – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43335</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CyberChimps Responsive Blocks – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Responsive Blocks – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks: from n/a through 1.8.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7906 | DedeBIZ Attachment Settings select_images_post.php get_mime_type unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7906</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in DedeBIZ 6.3.0. This vulnerability affects the function get_mime_type of the file /admin/dialog/select_images_post.php of the component Attachment Settings. The manipulation of the argument upload leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43276 | WordPress Child Theme Creator by Orbisius plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43276</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Svetoslav Marinov (Slavi) Child Theme Creator allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Child Theme Creator: from n/a through 1.5.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43342 | WordPress Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons, Woocommerce Builder, EDD Builder, Elementor Store Builder, Product Grid, Product Table, Woocommerce Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43342</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BdThemes Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.6.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43344 | WordPress Icegram Engage – Ultimate WP Popup Builder, Lead Generation, Optins, and CTA plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.25 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43344</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Icegram allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Icegram: from n/a through 3.1.25.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43346 | WordPress Modal Window – create popup modal window plugin &amp;lt;= 6.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43346</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wow-Company Modal Window allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Modal Window: from n/a through 6.0.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43347 | WordPress Button contact VR plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43347</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VirusTran Button contact VR allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Button contact VR: from n/a through 4.7.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43348 | WordPress Purity Of Soul theme &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43348</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Iznyn Purity Of Soul allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Purity Of Soul: from n/a through 1.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43349 | WordPress All Bootstrap Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.19 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43349</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AREOI All Bootstrap Blocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects All Bootstrap Blocks: from n/a through 1.3.19.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43351 | WordPress Bravada theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43351</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CryoutCreations Bravada bravada allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Bravada: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43352 | WordPress GivingPress Lite theme &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43352</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Organic Themes GivingPress Lite allows Stored XSS.This issue affects GivingPress Lite: from n/a through 1.8.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43353 | WordPress myCred plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43353</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in myCred allows Stored XSS.This issue affects myCred: from n/a through 2.7.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7905 | DedeBIZ archives_do.php AdminUpload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7905</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in DedeBIZ 6.3.0. This affects the function AdminUpload of the file admin/archives_do.php. The manipulation of the argument litpic leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 11:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7904 | DedeBIZ File Extension file_manage_control.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7904</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeBIZ 6.3.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/file_manage_control.php of the component File Extension Handler. The manipulation of the argument upfile1 leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 08:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7903 | DedeBIZ File Extension media_add.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7903</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeBIZ 6.3.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/media_add.php of the component File Extension Handler. The manipulation of the argument upfile1 leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 07:07:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>