<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 12:51:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-25610 | In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.12, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 9, 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 befo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25610</link><description>In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.12, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 9, 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 before fix pack 19, and older unsupported versions, the default configuration does not sanitize blog entries of JavaScript, which allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML (XSS) via a crafted payload injected into a blog entry’s content text field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 12:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1661 | Totolink X6000R shadow hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1661</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_B20230719. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /etc/shadow. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254179. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 12:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7245 | The nodejs framework in OpenVPN Connect 3.0 through 3.4.3 (Windows)/3.4.7 (macOS) was not properly configured, which allows a local user to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7245</link><description>The nodejs framework in OpenVPN Connect 3.0 through 3.4.3 (Windows)/3.4.7 (macOS) was not properly configured, which allows a local user to execute arbitrary code within the nodejs process context via the ELECTRON_RUN_AS_NODE environment variable</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 11:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24793 | A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the DICOM Element Parsing as implemented in Imaging Data Commons libdicom 1.0.5. A specially crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24793</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the DICOM Element Parsing as implemented in Imaging Data Commons libdicom 1.0.5. A specially crafted DICOM file can cause premature freeing of memory that is used later. To trigger this vulnerability, an attacker would need to induce the vulnerable application to process a malicious DICOM image.The Use-After-Free happens in the `parse_meta_element_create()` parsing the elements in the File Meta Information header.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24794 | A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the DICOM Element Parsing as implemented in Imaging Data Commons libdicom 1.0.5. A specially crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24794</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the DICOM Element Parsing as implemented in Imaging Data Commons libdicom 1.0.5. A specially crafted DICOM file can cause premature freeing of memory that is used later. To trigger this vulnerability, an attacker would need to induce the vulnerable application to process a malicious DICOM image.The Use-After-Free happens in the `parse_meta_sequence_end()` parsing the Sequence Value Represenations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50270 | Apache DolphinScheduler: Session do not expire after password change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50270</link><description>Session Fixation Apache DolphinScheduler before version 3.2.0, which session is still valid after the password change.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.2.1, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51770 | Apache DolphinScheduler: Arbitrary File Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51770</link><description>Arbitrary File Read Vulnerability in Apache Dolphinscheduler.

This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: before 3.2.1. 

We recommend users to upgrade Apache DolphinScheduler to version 3.2.1, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49109 | Remote Code Execution in Apache Dolphinscheduler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49109</link><description>Exposure of Remote Code Execution in Apache Dolphinscheduler.

This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: before 3.2.1. 

We recommend users to upgrade Apache DolphinScheduler to version 3.2.1, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49250 | Apache DolphinScheduler: Insecure TLS TrustManager used in HttpUtil</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49250</link><description>Because the HttpUtils class did not verify certificates, an attacker that could perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack on outgoing https connections could impersonate the server.

This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: before 3.2.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.2.1, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25609 | HtmlUtil.escapeRedirect in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.12, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 9, 7.3 s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25609</link><description>HtmlUtil.escapeRedirect in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.12, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 9, 7.3 service pack 3, 7.2 fix pack 15 through 18, and older unsupported versions can be circumvented by using two forward slashes, which allows remote attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external URLs via the (1) 'redirect` parameter (2) `FORWARD_URL` parameter, and (3) others parameters that rely on HtmlUtil.escapeRedirect. This vulnerability is the result of an incomplete fix in CVE-2022-28977.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25608 | HtmlUtil.escapeRedirect in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.18, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 19, 7.3 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25608</link><description>HtmlUtil.escapeRedirect in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.18, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 19, 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 before fix pack 19, and older unsupported versions can be circumvented by using the 'REPLACEMENT CHARACTER' (U+FFFD), which allows remote attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external URLs via the (1) 'redirect` parameter (2) `FORWARD_URL` parameter, (3) `noSuchEntryRedirect` parameter, and (4) others parameters that rely on HtmlUtil.escapeRedirect.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25607 | The default password hashing algorithm (PBKDF2-HMAC-SHA1) in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.15, and older unsupported versions, and Life...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25607</link><description>The default password hashing algorithm (PBKDF2-HMAC-SHA1) in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.15, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 16, 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions defaults to a low work factor, which allows attackers to quickly crack password hashes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:27:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1608 | OPPO Usercenter Credit sdk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1608</link><description>In OPPO Usercenter Credit SDK, there's a possible escalation of privilege due to loose permission check, This could lead to application internal information leak w/o user interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25606 | XXE vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.7, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 4, 7.3 before u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25606</link><description>XXE vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.7, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 4, 7.3 before update 12, 7.2 before fix pack 20, and older unsupported versions allows attackers with permission to deploy widgets/portlets/extensions to obtain sensitive information or consume system resources via the Java2WsddTask._format method.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25605 | The Journal module in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.4, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4.13, 7.3 before service pack ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25605</link><description>The Journal module in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.4, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4.13, 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions grants guest users view permission to web content templates by default, which allows remote attackers to view any template via the UI or API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 08:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25604 | Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.4, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4.13, 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25604</link><description>Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.4, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4.13, 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions does not properly check user permissions, which allows remote authenticated users with the VIEW user permission to edit their own permission via the User and Organizations section of the Control Panel.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 08:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25150 | Information disclosure vulnerability in the Control Panel in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25150</link><description>Information disclosure vulnerability in the Control Panel in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 before fix pack 19, and older unsupported versions allows remote authenticated users to obtain a user's full name from the page's title by enumerating user screen names.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 08:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25973 | Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25973</link><description>The Frentix GmbH OpenOlat LMS is affected by multiple stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities. An attacker with rights to create or edit groups can create a course with a name that contains an XSS payload. Furthermore, attackers with the permissions to create or rename a catalog (sub-category) can enter unfiltered input in the name field. In addition, attackers who are allowed to create curriculums can also enter unfiltered input in the name field. This allows an attacker to execute stored JavaScript code with the permissions of the victim in the context of the user's browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 08:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25974 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) within the Media Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25974</link><description>The Frentix GmbH OpenOlat LMS is affected by stored a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. It is possible to upload files within the Media Center of OpenOlat version 18.1.5 (or lower) as an authenticated user without any other rights. Although the filetypes are limited, an SVG image containing an XSS payload can be uploaded. After a successful upload the file can be shared with groups of users (including admins) who can be attacked with the JavaScript payload.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 08:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22234 | CVE-2024-22234: Broken Access Control in Spring Security With Direct Use of isFullyAuthenticated</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22234</link><description>In Spring Security, versions 6.1.x prior to 6.1.7 and versions 6.2.x prior to 6.2.2, an application is vulnerable to broken access control when it directly uses the AuthenticationTrustResolver.isFullyAuthenticated(Authentication) method.

Specifically, an application is vulnerable if:

  *  The application uses AuthenticationTrustResolver.isFullyAuthenticated(Authentication) directly and a null authentication parameter is passed to it resulting in an erroneous true return value.


An application is not vulnerable if any of the following is true:

  *  The application does not use AuthenticationTrustResolver.isFullyAuthenticated(Authentication) directly.
  *  The application does not pass null to AuthenticationTrustResolver.isFullyAuthenticated
  *  The application only uses isFullyAuthenticated via  Method Security https://docs.spring.io/spring-security/reference/servlet/authorization/method-security.html  or  HTTP Request Security https://docs.spring.io/spring-security/reference/servlet/authorization/authorize-http-requests.html</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 07:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25149 | Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 15, and o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25149</link><description>Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 15, and older unsupported versions does not properly restrict membership of a child site when the "Limit membership to members of the parent site" option is enabled, which allows remote authenticated users to add users who are not a member of the parent site to a child site. The added user may obtain permission to perform unauthorized actions in the child site.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 07:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44308 | Open redirect vulnerability in adaptive media administration page in Liferay DXP 2023.Q3 before patch 6, and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44308</link><description>Open redirect vulnerability in adaptive media administration page in Liferay DXP 2023.Q3 before patch 6, and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows remote attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external URLs via the _com_liferay_adaptive_media_web_portlet_AMPortlet_redirect parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 06:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5190 | Open redirect vulnerability in the Countries Management’s edit region page in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.45 through 7.4.3.101, and Liferay DXP 202...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5190</link><description>Open redirect vulnerability in the Countries Management’s edit region page in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.45 through 7.4.3.101, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3 before patch 6, and 7.4 update 45 through 92 allows remote attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external URLs via the _com_liferay_address_web_internal_portlet_CountriesManagementAdminPortlet_redirect parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 06:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45320 | Liferay Portal before 7.4.3.16 and Liferay DXP before 7.2 fix pack 19, 7.3 before update 6, and 7.4 before update 16 allow remote authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45320</link><description>Liferay Portal before 7.4.3.16 and Liferay DXP before 7.2 fix pack 19, 7.3 before update 6, and 7.4 before update 16 allow remote authenticated users to become the owner of a wiki page by editing the wiki page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 04:53:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1559 | The Link Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'll_reciprocal' parameter in all versions up to, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1559</link><description>The Link Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'll_reciprocal' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 7.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 03:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1510 | The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's su_tooltip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1510</link><description>The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's su_tooltip shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 7.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes and user supplied tags. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6764 | A format string vulnerability in a function of the IPSec VPN feature in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, U...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6764</link><description>A format string vulnerability in a function of the IPSec VPN feature in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1 could allow an attacker to achieve unauthorized remote code execution by sending a sequence of specially crafted payloads containing an invalid pointer; however, such an attack would require detailed knowledge of an affected device’s memory layout and configuration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6399 | A format string vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6399</link><description>A format string vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1 could allow an authenticated IPSec VPN user to cause DoS conditions against the “deviceid” daemon by sending a crafted hostname to an affected device if it has the “Device Insight” feature enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:04:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6398 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the file upload binary in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6398</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the file upload binary in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, NWA50AX firmware versions through 6.29(ABYW.3), WAC500 firmware versions through 6.65(ABVS.1), WAX300H firmware versions through 6.60(ACHF.1), and WBE660S firmware versions through 6.65(ACGG.1) could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute some operating system (OS) commands on an affected device via FTP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:04:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21890 | The Node.js Permission Model does not clarify in the documentation that wildcards should be only used as the last character of a file path. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21890</link><description>The Node.js Permission Model does not clarify in the documentation that wildcards should be only used as the last character of a file path. For example:
```
 --allow-fs-read=/home/node/.ssh/*.pub
```

will ignore `pub` and give access to everything after `.ssh/`.

This misleading documentation affects all users using the experimental permission model in Node.js 20 and Node.js 21.

Please note that at the time this CVE was issued, the permission model is an experimental feature of Node.js.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:04:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21891 | Node.js depends on multiple built-in utility functions to normalize paths provided to node:fs functions, which can be overwitten with user-d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21891</link><description>Node.js depends on multiple built-in utility functions to normalize paths provided to node:fs functions, which can be overwitten with user-defined implementations leading to filesystem permission model bypass through path traversal attack.
This vulnerability affects all users using the experimental permission model in Node.js 20 and Node.js 21.
Please note that at the time this CVE was issued, the permission model is an experimental feature of Node.js.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:04:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21892 | On Linux, Node.js ignores certain environment variables if those may have been set by an unprivileged user while the process is running with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21892</link><description>On Linux, Node.js ignores certain environment variables if those may have been set by an unprivileged user while the process is running with elevated privileges with the only exception of CAP_NET_BIND_SERVICE.
Due to a bug in the implementation of this exception, Node.js incorrectly applies this exception even when certain other capabilities have been set.
This allows unprivileged users to inject code that inherits the process's elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21896 | The permission model protects itself against path traversal attacks by calling path.resolve() on any paths given by the user. If the path is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21896</link><description>The permission model protects itself against path traversal attacks by calling path.resolve() on any paths given by the user. If the path is to be treated as a Buffer, the implementation uses Buffer.from() to obtain a Buffer from the result of path.resolve(). By monkey-patching Buffer internals, namely, Buffer.prototype.utf8Write, the application can modify the result of path.resolve(), which leads to a path traversal vulnerability.
This vulnerability affects all users using the experimental permission model in Node.js 20 and Node.js 21.
Please note that at the time this CVE was issued, the permission model is an experimental feature of Node.js.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22019 | A vulnerability in Node.js HTTP servers allows an attacker to send a specially crafted HTTP request with chunked encoding, leading to resour...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22019</link><description>A vulnerability in Node.js HTTP servers allows an attacker to send a specially crafted HTTP request with chunked encoding, leading to resource exhaustion and denial of service (DoS). The server reads an unbounded number of bytes from a single connection, exploiting the lack of limitations on chunk extension bytes. The issue can cause CPU and network bandwidth exhaustion, bypassing standard safeguards like timeouts and body size limits.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6397 | A null pointer dereference vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1 and USG FLEX series firmware v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6397</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1 and USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1 could allow a LAN-based attacker to cause denial-of-service (DoS) conditions by downloading a crafted RAR compressed file onto a LAN-side host if the firewall has the “Anti-Malware” feature enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 01:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0715 | EL Injection Vulnerability in Hitachi Global Link Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0715</link><description>Expression Language Injection vulnerability in Hitachi Global Link Manager on Windows allows Code Injection.This issue affects Hitachi Global Link Manager: before 8.8.7-03.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 01:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1647 | pyhtml2pdf 0.0.6 - Local File Read via Server Side XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1647</link><description>Pyhtml2pdf version 0.0.6 allows an external attacker to remotely obtain

arbitrary local files. This is possible because the application does not

validate the HTML content entered by the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1648 | electron-pdf 20.0.0 - Local File Read via Server Side XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1648</link><description>electron-pdf version 20.0.0 allows an external attacker to remotely obtain

arbitrary local files. This is possible because the application does not

validate the HTML content entered by the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48625 | Yealink Config Encrypt Tool add RSA before 1.2 has a built-in RSA key pair, and thus there is a risk of decryption by an adversary.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48625</link><description>Yealink Config Encrypt Tool add RSA before 1.2 has a built-in RSA key pair, and thus there is a risk of decryption by an adversary.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:52:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1644 | Suite CRM v7.14.2 - RCE via Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1644</link><description>Suite CRM version 7.14.2 allows including local php files. This is possible

because the application is vulnerable to LFI.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:52:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1651 | Torrentpier 2.4.1 - RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1651</link><description>Torrentpier version 2.4.1 allows executing arbitrary commands on the server.

This is possible because the application is vulnerable to insecure deserialization.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 23:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1297 | Loomio 2.22.0 - Code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1297</link><description>Loomio version 2.22.0 allows executing arbitrary commands on the server.

This is possible because the application is vulnerable to OS Command Injection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 23:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26134 | CBOR2 decoder has potential buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26134</link><description>cbor2 provides encoding and decoding for the Concise Binary Object Representation (CBOR) (RFC 8949) serialization format. Starting in version 5.5.1 and prior to version 5.6.2, an attacker can crash a service using cbor2 to parse a CBOR binary by sending a long enough object. Version 5.6.2 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 22:25:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26129 | Prestashop vulnerable to path disclosure in JavaScript variable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26129</link><description>PrestaShop is an open-source e-commerce platform. Starting in version 8.1.0 and prior to version 8.1.4, PrestaShop is vulnerable to path disclosure in a JavaScript variable. A patch is available in version 8.1.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 22:10:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6259 | Local Access to Sensitive Data in Brivo ACS100 and ACS300 </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6259</link><description>Insufficiently Protected Credentials, : Improper Access Control vulnerability in Brivo ACS100, ACS300 allows Password Recovery Exploitation, Bypassing Physical Security.This issue affects ACS100, ACS300: from 5.2.4 before 6.2.4.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 21:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6260 | Web UI OS Command Injection in Brivo ACS100, ACS300</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6260</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Brivo ACS100, ACS300 allows OS Command Injection, Bypassing Physical Security.This issue affects ACS100 (Network Adjacent Access), ACS300 (Physical Access): from 5.2.4 before 6.2.4.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 21:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1635 | Undertow: out-of-memory error after several closed connections with wildfly-http-client protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1635</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Undertow. This vulnerability impacts a server that supports the wildfly-http-client protocol. Whenever a malicious user opens and closes a connection with the HTTP port of the server and then closes the connection immediately, the server will end with both memory and open file limits exhausted at some point, depending on the amount of memory available. &#13;
&#13;
At HTTP upgrade to remoting, the WriteTimeoutStreamSinkConduit leaks connections if RemotingConnection is closed by Remoting ServerConnectionOpenListener. Because the remoting connection originates in Undertow as part of the HTTP upgrade, there is an external layer to the remoting connection. This connection is unaware of the outermost layer when closing the connection during the connection opening procedure. Hence, the Undertow WriteTimeoutStreamSinkConduit is not notified of the closed connection in this scenario. Because WriteTimeoutStreamSinkConduit creates a timeout task, the whole dependency tree leaks via that task, which is added to XNIO WorkerThread. So, the workerThread points to the Undertow conduit, which contains the connections and causes the leak.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 21:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1638 | Bluetooth characteristic LESC security requirement not enforced without additional flags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1638</link><description>The documentation specifies that the BT_GATT_PERM_READ_LESC and BT_GATT_PERM_WRITE_LESC defines for a Bluetooth characteristic: Attribute read/write permission with LE Secure Connection encryption. If set, requires that LE Secure Connections is used for read/write access, however this is only true when it is combined with other permissions, namely BT_GATT_PERM_READ_ENCRYPT/BT_GATT_PERM_READ_AUTHEN (for read) or BT_GATT_PERM_WRITE_ENCRYPT/BT_GATT_PERM_WRITE_AUTHEN (for write), if these additional permissions are not set (even in secure connections only mode) then the stack does not perform any permission checks on these characteristics and they can be freely written/read.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 21:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25640 | Improper Neutralization of Alternate XSS Syntax in iris-web</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25640</link><description>Iris is a web collaborative platform that helps incident responders share technical details during investigations. A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in iris-web, affecting multiple locations in versions prior to v2.4.0. The vulnerability may allow an attacker to inject malicious scripts into the application, which could then be executed when a user visits the affected locations. This could lead to unauthorized access, data theft, or other related malicious activities. An attacker need to be authenticated on the application to exploit this vulnerability. The issue is fixed in version v2.4.0 of iris-web. No workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 20:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25634 | IDOR make user can read e-mail log sent by other events</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25634</link><description>alf.io is an open source ticket reservation system. Prior to version 2.0-Mr-2402, an attacker can access data from other organizers. The attacker can use a specially crafted request to receive the e-mail log sent by other events. Version 2.0-M4-2402 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 19:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25635 | IDOR Vulnerability: Allowing Organization Owner to view the other Organizations API KEY and USERS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25635</link><description>alf.io is an open source ticket reservation system. Prior to version 2.0-Mr-2402, organization owners can view the generated API KEY and USERS of other organization owners using the `http://192.168.26.128:8080/admin/api/users/&lt;user_id&gt;` endpoint, which exposes the details of the provided user ID. This may also expose the API KEY in the username of the user. Version 2.0-M4-2402 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 19:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25636 | Lack of media type verification of Activity Streams objects allows impersonation and takeover of remote accounts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25636</link><description>Misskey is an open source, decentralized social media platform with ActivityPub support. Prior to version 2024.2.0, when fetching remote Activity Streams objects, Misskey doesn't check that the response from the remote server has a `Content-Type` header value of the Activity Streams media type, which allows a threat actor to upload a crafted Activity Streams document to a remote server and make a Misskey instance fetch it, if the remote server accepts arbitrary user uploads. The vulnerability allows a threat actor to impersonate and take over an account on a remote server that satisfies all of the following properties: allows the threat actor to register an account; accepts arbitrary user-uploaded documents and places them on the same domain as legitimate Activity Streams actors; and serves user-uploaded document in response to requests with an `Accept` header value of the Activity Streams media type. Version 2024.2.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 19:46:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25626 | Yocto Project Security Advisory - BitBake/Toaster</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25626</link><description>Yocto Project is an open source collaboration project that helps developers create custom Linux-based systems regardless of the hardware architecture. In Yocto Projects Bitbake before 2.6.2 (before and included Yocto Project 4.3.1), with the Toaster server (included in bitbake) running, missing input validation allows an attacker to perform a remote code execution in the server's shell via a crafted HTTP request. Authentication is not necessary. Toaster server execution has to be specifically run and is not the default for Bitbake command line builds, it is only used for the Toaster web based user interface to Bitbake. The fix has been backported to the bitbake included with Yocto Project 5.0, 3.1.31, 4.0.16, and 4.3.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 19:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50257 | Disconnect Vulnerability in RTPS Packets Used by SROS2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50257</link><description>eProsima Fast DDS (formerly Fast RTPS) is a C++ implementation of the Data Distribution Service standard of the Object Management Group. Even with the application of SROS2, due to the issue where the data (`p[UD]`) and `guid` values used to disconnect between nodes are not encrypted, a vulnerability has been discovered where a malicious attacker can forcibly disconnect a Subscriber and can deny a Subscriber attempting to connect. Afterwards, if the attacker sends the packet for disconnecting, which is data (`p[UD]`), to the Global Data Space (`239.255.0.1:7400`) using the said Publisher ID, all the Subscribers (Listeners) connected to the Publisher (Talker) will not receive any data and their connection will be disconnected. Moreover, if this disconnection packet is sent continuously, the Subscribers (Listeners) trying to connect will not be able to do so. Since the initial commit of the `SecurityManager.cpp` code (`init`, `on_process_handshake`) on Nov 8, 2016, the Disconnect Vulnerability in RTPS Packets Used by SROS2 has been present prior to versions 2.13.0, 2.12.2, 2.11.3, 2.10.3, and 2.6.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 19:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1633 | FIP Header Integer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1633</link><description>During the secure boot, bl2 (the second stage of
the bootloader) loops over images defined in the table “bl2_mem_params_descs”.
For each image, the bl2 reads the image length and destination from the image’s
certificate. Because of the way of reading from the image, which base on 32-bit unsigned integer value, it can result to an integer overflow. An attacker can bypass memory range restriction and write data out of buffer bounds, which could result in bypass of secure boot.

 Affected git version from c2f286820471ed276c57e603762bd831873e5a17 until (not</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 16:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25981 | Msa-24-0004: forum export did not respect activity group settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25981</link><description>Separate Groups mode restrictions were not honored when performing a forum export, which would export forum data for all groups. By default this only provided additional access to non-editing teachers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 16:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25982 | Msa-24-0005: csrf risk in language import utility</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25982</link><description>The link to update all installed language packs did not include the necessary token to prevent a CSRF risk.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 16:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25983 | Msa-24-0006: idor on dashboard comments block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25983</link><description>Insufficient checks in a web service made it possible to add comments to the comments block on another user's dashboard when it was not otherwise available (e.g., on their profile page).</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 16:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25978 | Msa-24-0001: denial of service risk in file picker unzip functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25978</link><description>Insufficient file size checks resulted in a denial of service risk in the file picker's unzip functionality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 16:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25979 | Msa-24-0002: forum search accepted random parameters in its url</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25979</link><description>The URL parameters accepted by forum search were not limited to the allowed parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 16:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25980 | Msa-24-0003: h5p attempts report did not respect activity group settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25980</link><description>Separate Groups mode restrictions were not honored in the H5P attempts report, which would display users from other groups. By default this only provided additional access to non-editing teachers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 16:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25625 | Pimcore Host Header Injection in user invitation link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25625</link><description>Pimcore's Admin Classic Bundle provides a Backend UI for Pimcore. A potential security vulnerability has been discovered in `pimcore/admin-ui-classic-bundle` prior to version 1.3.4. The vulnerability involves a Host Header Injection in the `invitationLinkAction` function of the UserController, specifically in the way `$loginUrl` trusts user input.  The host header from incoming HTTP requests is used unsafely when generating URLs. An attacker can manipulate the HTTP host header in requests to the /admin/user/invitationlink endpoint, resulting in the generation of URLs with the attacker's domain. In fact, if a host header is injected in the POST request, the $loginURL parameter is constructed with this unvalidated host header. It is then used to send an invitation email to the provided user. This vulnerability can be used to perform phishing attacks by making the URLs in the invitation links emails point to an attacker-controlled domain. Version 1.3.4 contains a patch for the vulnerability. The maintainers recommend validating the host header and ensuring it matches the application's domain. It would also be beneficial to use a default trusted host or hostname if the incoming host header is not recognized or is absent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 15:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25623 | Lack of media type verification of Activity Streams objects allows impersonation of remote accounts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25623</link><description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub. Prior to versions 4.2.7, 4.1.15, 4.0.15, and 3.5.19, when fetching remote statuses, Mastodon doesn't check that the response from the remote server has a `Content-Type` header value of the Activity Streams media type, which allows a threat actor to upload a crafted Activity Streams document to a remote server and make a Mastodon server fetch it, if the remote server accepts arbitrary user uploads. The vulnerability allows a threat actor to impersonate an account on a remote server that satisfies all of the following properties: allows the attacker to register an account; accepts arbitrary user-uploaded documents and places them on the same domain as the ActivityPub actors; and serves user-uploaded document in response to requests with an `Accept` header value of the Activity Streams media type. Versions 4.2.7, 4.1.15, 4.0.15, and 3.5.19 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1597 | pgjdbc SQL Injection via line comment generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1597</link><description>pgjdbc, the PostgreSQL JDBC Driver, allows attacker to inject SQL if using PreferQueryMode=SIMPLE. Note this is not the default. In the default mode there is no vulnerability. A placeholder for a numeric value must be immediately preceded by a minus. There must be a second placeholder for a string value after the first placeholder; both must be on the same line. By constructing a matching string payload, the attacker can inject SQL to alter the query,bypassing the protections that parameterized queries bring against SQL Injection attacks. Versions before 42.7.2, 42.6.1, 42.5.5, 42.4.4, 42.3.9, and 42.2.8 are affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 13:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1346 | Weak MySQL database root password in LaborOfficeFree</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1346</link><description>Weak MySQL database root password in LaborOfficeFree affects version 19.10. This vulnerability allows an attacker to calculate the root password of the MySQL database used by LaborOfficeFree using two constants.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 11:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1343 | Weak permission vulnerability in LaborOfficeFree</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1343</link><description>A weak permission was found in the backup directory in LaborOfficeFree affecting version 19.10. This vulnerability allows any authenticated user to read backup files in the directory '%programfiles(x86)% LaborOfficeFree BackUp'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 11:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1344 | Encrypted database credentials in LaborOfficeFree</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1344</link><description>Encrypted database credentials in LaborOfficeFree affecting version 19.10. This vulnerability allows an attacker to read and extract the username and password from the database of 'LOF_service.exe' and 'LaborOfficeFree.exe' located in the '%programfiles(x86)%\LaborOfficeFree\' directory. This user can log in remotely and has root-like privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 11:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1345 | Weak MySQL database root password in LaborOfficeFree</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1345</link><description>Weak MySQL database root password in LaborOfficeFree affects version 19.10. This vulnerability allows an attacker to perform a brute force attack and easily discover the root password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 11:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1580 | Integer overflow in VideoLAN dav1d</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1580</link><description>An integer overflow in dav1d AV1 decoder that can occur when decoding videos with large frame size. This can lead to memory corruption within the AV1 decoder. We recommend upgrading past version 1.4.0 of dav1d.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 10:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25710 | Apache Commons Compress: Denial of service caused by an infinite loop for a corrupted DUMP file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25710</link><description>Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in Apache Commons Compress.This issue affects Apache Commons Compress: from 1.3 through 1.25.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.26.0 which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 08:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26308 | Apache Commons Compress: OutOfMemoryError unpacking broken Pack200 file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26308</link><description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in Apache Commons Compress.This issue affects Apache Commons Compress: from 1.21 before 1.26.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.26, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 08:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24722 | An unquoted service path vulnerability in the 12d Synergy Server and File Replication Server components may allow an attacker to gain elevat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24722</link><description>An unquoted service path vulnerability in the 12d Synergy Server and File Replication Server components may allow an attacker to gain elevated privileges via the 12d Synergy Server and/or 12d Synergy File Replication Server executable service path. This is fixed in 4.3.10.192, 5.1.5.221, and 5.1.6.235.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 06:19:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26327 | An issue was discovered in QEMU 7.1.0 through 8.2.1. register_vfs in hw/pci/pcie_sriov.c mishandles the situation where a guest writes NumVF...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26327</link><description>An issue was discovered in QEMU 7.1.0 through 8.2.1. register_vfs in hw/pci/pcie_sriov.c mishandles the situation where a guest writes NumVFs greater than TotalVFs, leading to a buffer overflow in VF implementations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 04:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26328 | An issue was discovered in QEMU 7.1.0 through 8.2.1. register_vfs in hw/pci/pcie_sriov.c does not set NumVFs to PCI_SRIOV_TOTAL_VF, and thus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26328</link><description>An issue was discovered in QEMU 7.1.0 through 8.2.1. register_vfs in hw/pci/pcie_sriov.c does not set NumVFs to PCI_SRIOV_TOTAL_VF, and thus interaction with hw/nvme/ctrl.c is mishandled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 04:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26318 | Serenity before 6.8.0 allows XSS via an email link because LoginPage.tsx permits return URLs that do not begin with a / character.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26318</link><description>Serenity before 6.8.0 allows XSS via an email link because LoginPage.tsx permits return URLs that do not begin with a / character.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 03:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36774 | plugins/gtk+/glade-gtk-box.c in GNOME Glade before 3.38.1 and 3.39.x before 3.40.0 mishandles widget rebuilding for GladeGtkBox, leading to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36774</link><description>plugins/gtk+/glade-gtk-box.c in GNOME Glade before 3.38.1 and 3.39.x before 3.40.0 mishandles widget rebuilding for GladeGtkBox, leading to a denial of service (application crash).</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 01:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48624 | close_altfile in filename.c in less before 606 omits shell_quote calls for LESSCLOSE.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48624</link><description>close_altfile in filename.c in less before 606 omits shell_quote calls for LESSCLOSE.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 01:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5779 | can: out of bounds in remove_rx_filter function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5779</link><description>can: out of bounds in remove_rx_filter function</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 07:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6249 | ipm: signed to unsigned conversion problem in esp32_ipm_send</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6249</link><description>Signed to unsigned conversion esp32_ipm_send</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6749 | Unchecked user input length in the Zephyr Settings Shell</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6749</link><description>Unchecked length coming from user input in settings shell</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 07:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48621 | Vulnerability of missing authentication for critical functions in the Wi-Fi module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48621</link><description>Vulnerability of missing authentication for critical functions in the Wi-Fi module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 06:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52378 | Vulnerability of incorrect service logic in the WindowManagerServices module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause feature...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52378</link><description>Vulnerability of incorrect service logic in the WindowManagerServices module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perform abnormally.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 06:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52379 | Permission control vulnerability in the calendarProvider module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52379</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the calendarProvider module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 06:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52380 | Vulnerability of improper access control in the email module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentialit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52380</link><description>Vulnerability of improper access control in the email module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 06:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52381 | Script injection vulnerability in the email module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality, integri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52381</link><description>Script injection vulnerability in the email module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 06:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52375 | Permission control vulnerability in the WindowManagerServices module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52375</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the WindowManagerServices module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 06:19:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52376 | Information management vulnerability in the Gallery module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52376</link><description>Information management vulnerability in the Gallery module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 06:19:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52377 | Vulnerability of input data not being verified in the cellular data module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause out-of-bo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52377</link><description>Vulnerability of input data not being verified in the cellular data module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause out-of-bounds access.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 06:19:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52374 | Permission control vulnerability in the package management module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confident...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52374</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the package management module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 04:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52372 | Vulnerability of input parameter verification in the motor module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52372</link><description>Vulnerability of input parameter verification in the motor module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52373 | Vulnerability of permission verification in the content sharing pop-up module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause unauth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52373</link><description>Vulnerability of permission verification in the content sharing pop-up module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause unauthorized file sharing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52369 | Stack overflow vulnerability in the NFC module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service availability and integrity.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52369</link><description>Stack overflow vulnerability in the NFC module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service availability and integrity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:50:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52370 | Stack overflow vulnerability in the network acceleration module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause unauthorized file ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52370</link><description>Stack overflow vulnerability in the network acceleration module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause unauthorized file access.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:50:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52371 | Vulnerability of null references in the motor module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52371</link><description>Vulnerability of null references in the motor module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:50:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52368 | Input verification vulnerability in the account module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perform abnormall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52368</link><description>Input verification vulnerability in the account module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perform abnormally.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52366 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the smart activity recognition module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52366</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the smart activity recognition module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perform abnormally.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52367 | Vulnerability of improper access control in the media library module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service availa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52367</link><description>Vulnerability of improper access control in the media library module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service availability and integrity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52365 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the smart activity recognition module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52365</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the smart activity recognition module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perform abnormally.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:21:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52358 | Vulnerability of configuration defects in some APIs of the audio module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52358</link><description>Vulnerability of configuration defects in some APIs of the audio module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52360 | Logic vulnerabilities in the baseband.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service integrity.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52360</link><description>Logic vulnerabilities in the baseband.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service integrity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52361 | The VerifiedBoot module has a vulnerability that may cause authentication errors.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52361</link><description>The VerifiedBoot module has a vulnerability that may cause authentication errors.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect integrity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52362 | Permission management vulnerability in the lock screen module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52362</link><description>Permission management vulnerability in the lock screen module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52363 | Vulnerability of defects introduced in the design process in the Control Panel module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may caus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52363</link><description>Vulnerability of defects introduced in the design process in the Control Panel module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause app processes to be started by mistake.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52097 | Vulnerability of foreground service restrictions being bypassed in the NMS module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52097</link><description>Vulnerability of foreground service restrictions being bypassed in the NMS module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52357 | Vulnerability of serialization/deserialization mismatch in the vibration framework.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52357</link><description>Vulnerability of serialization/deserialization mismatch in the vibration framework.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52387 | Resource reuse vulnerability in the GPU module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52387</link><description>Resource reuse vulnerability in the GPU module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>