<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 14:33:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-48219 | O2 UK through 2025-05-17 allows subscribers to determine the Cell ID of other subscribers by initiating an IMS (IP Multimedia Subsystem) cal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48219</link><description>O2 UK through 2025-05-17 allows subscribers to determine the Cell ID of other subscribers by initiating an IMS (IP Multimedia Subsystem) call and then reading the utran-cell-id-3gpp field of a Cellular-Network-Info SIP header, aka an ECI (E-UTRAN Cell Identity) leak. The Cell ID might be usable to identify a cell location via crowdsourced data, and might correspond to a small physical area (e.g., if the called party is in a city centre). Removal of the Cellular-Network-Info header is mentioned in section 4.4.19 of ETSI TS 124 229.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 14:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4882 | itsourcecode Restaurant Management System team_update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4882</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Restaurant Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/team_update.php. The manipulation of the argument team leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 14:17:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4881 | itsourcecode Restaurant Management System user_save.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4881</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Restaurant Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/user_save.php. The manipulation of the argument username/name leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 13:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4880 | PHPGurukul News Portal aboutus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4880</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul News Portal 4.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/aboutus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 13:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4875 | Campcodes Online Shopping Portal forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4875</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Shopping Portal 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 12:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4874 | PHPGurukul News Portal Project contactus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4874</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul News Portal Project 4.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/contactus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 12:18:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4873 | PHPGurukul News Portal Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4873</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul News Portal 4.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 11:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4872 | FreeFloat FTP Server CCC Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4872</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component CCC Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 11:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4871 | PCMan FTP Server REST Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4871</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PCMan FTP Server 2.0.7. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component REST Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 10:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4870 | itsourcecode Restaurant Management System menu_save.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4870</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Restaurant Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/menu_save.php. The manipulation of the argument menu leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 10:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4869 | itsourcecode Restaurant Management System member_update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4869</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Restaurant Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/member_update.php. The manipulation of the argument menu leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 09:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4868 | merikbest ecommerce-spring-reactjs File Upload Endpoint admin path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4868</link><description>A vulnerability was found in merikbest ecommerce-spring-reactjs up to 464e610bb11cc2619cf6ce8212ccc2d1fd4277fd. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/v1/admin/ of the component File Upload Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument filename leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 09:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4867 | Tenda A15 ArpNerworkSet formArpNerworkSet denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4867</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda A15 15.13.07.13. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formArpNerworkSet of the file /goform/ArpNerworkSet. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 08:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4866 | weibocom rill-flow Management Console code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4866</link><description>A vulnerability was found in weibocom rill-flow 0.1.18. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the component Management Console. The manipulation leads to code injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 08:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4865 | itsourcecode Restaurant Management System member_save.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4865</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Restaurant Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/member_save.php. The manipulation of the argument last leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 07:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4864 | itsourcecode Restaurant Management System finished.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4864</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Restaurant Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/finished.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 07:09:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4863 | Advaya Softech GEMS ERP Portal studentLogin.action sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4863</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Advaya Softech GEMS ERP Portal 2.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /studentLogin/studentLogin.action. The manipulation of the argument userId leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 06:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4862 | PHPGurukul Directory Management System searchdata.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4862</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 2.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /searchdata.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 06:24:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4861 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System admin-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4861</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument contactnumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 05:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3715 | Bold Page Builder &amp;lt;= 5.3.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;data-text&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3715</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the data-text parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 05:34:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4860 | D-Link DAP-2695 Static Pool Settings Page adv_dhcps.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4860</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in D-Link DAP-2695 120b36r137_ALL_en_20210528. Affected is an unknown function of the file /adv_dhcps.php of the component Static Pool Settings Page. The manipulation of the argument f_mac leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 05:17:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4859 | D-Link DAP-2695 MAC Bypass Settings Page adv_macbypass.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4859</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DAP-2695 120b36r137_ALL_en_20210528. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /adv_macbypass.php of the component MAC Bypass Settings Page. The manipulation of the argument f_mac leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 04:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4858 | D-Link DAP-2695 ARP Spoofing Prevention Page adv_arpspoofing.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4858</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DAP-2695 120b36r137_ALL_en_20210528. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /adv_arpspoofing.php of the component ARP Spoofing Prevention Page. The manipulation of the argument harp_mac leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 04:04:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4852 | TOTOLINK A3002R VPN Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4852</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in TOTOLINK A3002R 2.1.1-B20230720.1011. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component VPN Page. The manipulation of the argument Comment leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 04:04:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4851 | TOTOLINK N300RH cstecgi.cgi setUploadUserData command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4851</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK N300RH 6.1c.1390_B20191101. This vulnerability affects the function setUploadUserData of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 03:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4849 | TOTOLINK N300RH cstecgi.cgi CloudACMunualUpdateUserdata command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4849</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK N300RH 6.1c.1390_B20191101. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function CloudACMunualUpdateUserdata of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument url leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 03:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4850 | TOTOLINK N300RH cstecgi.cgi setUnloadUserData command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4850</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK N300RH 6.1c.1390_B20191101. This affects the function setUnloadUserData of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument plugin_name leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 03:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4848 | FreeFloat FTP Server RECV Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4848</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component RECV Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 02:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4847 | FreeFloat FTP Server MLS Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4847</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component MLS Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 02:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4846 | FreeFloat FTP Server MPUT Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4846</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component MPUT Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 01:25:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4845 | FreeFloat FTP Server TRACE Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4845</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component TRACE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 01:25:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4844 | FreeFloat FTP Server CD Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4844</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component CD Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 01:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4843 | D-Link DCS-932L udev SubUPnPCSInit stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4843</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DCS-932L 2.18.01. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function SubUPnPCSInit of the file /sbin/udev. The manipulation of the argument CameraName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4842 | D-Link DCS-932L ucp isUCPCameraNameChanged stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4842</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DCS-932L 2.18.01. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function isUCPCameraNameChanged of the file /sbin/ucp. The manipulation of the argument CameraName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4841 | D-Link DCS-932L gpio sub_404780 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4841</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DCS-932L 2.18.01 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function sub_404780 of the file /bin/gpio. The manipulation of the argument CameraName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 22:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4839 | itwanger paicoding CrossUtil.java cross-domain policy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4839</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itwanger paicoding 1.0.0/1.0.1/1.0.2/1.0.3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /paicoding-core/src/main/java/com/github/paicoding/forum/core/util/CrossUtil.java. The manipulation leads to permissive cross-domain policy with untrusted domains. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4838 | kanwangzjm Funiture Login LoginServlet.java doPost redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4838</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in kanwangzjm Funiture up to 71ca0fb0658b3d839d9e049ac36429207f05329b. Affected is the function doPost of the file /funiture-master/src/main/java/com/app/mvc/acl/servlet/LoginServlet.java of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument ret leads to open redirect. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 21:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4918 | An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript `Promise` object. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 11...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4918</link><description>An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript `Promise` object. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.23.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 21:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4919 | An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript object by confusing array index sizes. This vulnerability aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4919</link><description>An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript object by confusing array index sizes. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.23.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 21:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4920 | An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript `Promise` object. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 138.0....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4920</link><description>An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript `Promise` object. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 138.0.4 and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.10.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 21:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4921 | An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript object by confusing array index sizes. This vulnerability aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4921</link><description>An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript object by confusing array index sizes. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 138.0.4 and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.10.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 21:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4837 | projectworlds Student Project Allocation System make_group_sql.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4837</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in projectworlds Student Project Allocation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /make_group_sql.php. The manipulation of the argument mem1/mem2/mem3 leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 20:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4836 | Projectworlds Life Insurance Management System deleteAgent.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4836</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Projectworlds Life Insurance Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /deleteAgent.php. The manipulation of the argument agent_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 20:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4835 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formWlanRedirect buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4835</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formWlanRedirect of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument redirect-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 19:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4834 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formSetLg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4834</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formSetLg of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 19:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47948 | Cocotais Bot has builtin .echo command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47948</link><description>Cocotais Bot is a QQ official robot framework based on qq-bot-sdk. Starting in version 1.5.0-test2-hotfix and prior to version 1.6.2, command echoing feature in the framework allows users to indirectly trigger privileged behavior by injecting special platform tags. Specifically, an unauthorized user can use the `/echo ` command to cause the bot to send a message that mentions all members in the chat, bypassing any permission controls. This can lead to spam, disruption, or abuse of notification systems. Version 1.6.2 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 18:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47945 | Donetick Has Weak Default JWT Secret</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47945</link><description>Donetick an open-source app for managing tasks and chores. Prior to version 0.1.44, the application uses JSON Web Tokens (JWT) for authentication, but the signing secret has a weak default value. While the responsibility is left to the system administrator to change it, this approach is inadequate. The vulnerability is proven by existence of the issue in the live version as well. This issue can result in full account takeover of any user. Version 0.1.44 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 18:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4833 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formNtp buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4833</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boafrm/formNtp of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 17:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4832 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formDosCfg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4832</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formDosCfg of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 17:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4831 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formSiteSurveyProfile buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4831</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. This affects an unknown part of the file /boafrm/formSiteSurveyProfile of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 16:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33103 | IBM i privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33103</link><description>IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, 7.5, and 7.6 product IBM TCP/IP Connectivity Utilities for i contains a privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with command line access to the host operating system can elevate privileges to gain root access to the host operating system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 16:19:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47931 | LibreNMS stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in poller group name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47931</link><description>LibreNMS is PHP/MySQL/SNMP based network monitoring software. LibreNMS v25.4.0 and prior suffers from a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in the `group name` parameter of the `http://localhost/poller/groups` form. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into web pages viewed by other users. LibreNMS v25.5.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47273 | setuptools has a path traversal vulnerability in PackageIndex.download that leads to Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47273</link><description>setuptools is a package that allows users to download, build, install, upgrade, and uninstall Python packages. A path traversal vulnerability in `PackageIndex` is present in setuptools prior to version 78.1.1. An attacker would be allowed to write files to arbitrary locations on the filesystem with the permissions of the process running the Python code, which could escalate to remote code execution depending on the context. Version 78.1.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:51:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4830 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formSysCmd buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4830</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formSysCmd of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4829 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formStats sub_40BE30 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4829</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_40BE30 of the file /boafrm/formStats of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4827 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formSaveConfig buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4827</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formSaveConfig of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48187 | RAGFlow through 0.18.1 allows account takeover because it is possible to conduct successful brute-force attacks against email verification c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48187</link><description>RAGFlow through 0.18.1 allows account takeover because it is possible to conduct successful brute-force attacks against email verification codes to perform arbitrary account registration, login, and password reset. Codes are six digits and there is no rate limiting.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 13:03:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4101 | MultiVendorX – WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solutions &amp;lt;= 4.2.22 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4101</link><description>The MultiVendorX – WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solutions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a misconfigured capability check on the 'delete_fpm_product' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.22. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete arbitrary posts, pages, attachments, and products. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 4.2.22.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 12:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13613 | Wise Chat &amp;lt;= 3.3.3 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13613</link><description>The Wise Chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.3 via the 'uploads' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/uploads directory which can contain file attachments included in chat messages. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 3.3.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4669 | Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 10.11.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wpbc Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4669</link><description>The WP Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wpbc shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 10.11.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3527 | EventON - WordPress Virtual Event Calendar Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3527</link><description>The EventON Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check in the 'assets/lib/settings/settings.js' file in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 4.9.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3888 | Jupiterx Core &amp;lt;= 4.8.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Inline SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3888</link><description>The Jupiter X Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the page with the included SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4826 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formWirelessTbl buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4826</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boafrm/formWirelessTbl of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4825 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formDMZ buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4825</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formDMZ of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 10:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4824 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formWsc buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4824</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. This affects an unknown part of the file /boafrm/formWsc of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 10:23:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4823 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formReflashClientTbl submit-url buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4823</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function submit-url of the file /boafrm/formReflashClientTbl of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 09:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4610 | WP-Members &amp;lt;= 3.5.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wpmem_user_memberships Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4610</link><description>The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wpmem_user_memberships shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 09:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4190 | CSV Mass Importer &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Admin+ Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4190</link><description>The CSV Mass Importer WordPress plugin through 1.2 does not properly validate uploaded files, allowing high privilege users such as admin to upload arbitrary files on the server even when they should not be allowed to (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 06:18:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4819 | y_project RuoYi Offline Logout batchForceLogout improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4819</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in y_project RuoYi 4.8.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /monitor/online/batchForceLogout of the component Offline Logout. The manipulation of the argument ids leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 06:18:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3812 | WPBot Pro Wordpress Chatbot &amp;lt;= 13.6.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3812</link><description>The WPBot Pro Wordpress Chatbot plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the qcld_openai_delete_training_file() function in all versions up to, and including, 13.6.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 05:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4389 | Crawlomatic Multipage Scraper Post Generator &amp;lt;= 2.6.8.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4389</link><description>The Crawlomatic Multipage Scraper Post Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the crawlomatic_generate_featured_image() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.8.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 05:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4391 | Echo RSS Feed Post Generator &amp;lt;= 5.4.8.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4391</link><description>The Echo RSS Feed Post Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the echo_generate_featured_image() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.8.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 05:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4818 | SourceCodester Doctor&amp;#x27;s Appointment System GET Parameter delete-doctor.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4818</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Doctor's Appointment System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/delete-doctor.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 05:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4817 | Sourcecodester Doctor&amp;#x27;s Appointment System GET Parameter delete-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4817</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Sourcecodester Doctor's Appointment System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/delete-appointment.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 04:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4189 | Audio Comments Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4189</link><description>The Audio Comments Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'audio-comments/audior-settings.php' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 03:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4194 | AlT Monitoring &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4194</link><description>The AlT Monitoring plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'ALT_Monitoring_edit' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 03:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4816 | SourceCodester Doctor&amp;#x27;s Appointment System GET Parameter appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4816</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Doctor's Appointment System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/appointment.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4815 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System supplier_update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4815</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /pages/supplier_update.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4814 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System supplier_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4814</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /pages/supplier_add.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 02:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47893 | GPU DDK - OOB read and write of the shared KMD/FW memory heap (VZ/TEE setups)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47893</link><description>Kernel software installed and running inside a Guest VM may exploit memory shared with the GPU Firmware to read and/or write data outside the Guest's virtualised GPU memory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 02:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1706 | GPU DDK - Improper locking when accessing the pvr_exp_fence  object</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1706</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to trigger use-after-free kernel exceptions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 02:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4812 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4812</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /profile.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 21:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4813 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System edit-phlebotomist.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4813</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /edit-phlebotomist.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 21:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4811 | CodeAstro Pharmacy Management System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4811</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Pharmacy Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 21:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48188 | libpspp-core.a in GNU PSPP through 2.0.1 has an incorrect call from fill_buffer (in data/encrypted-file.c) to the Gnulib rijndaelDecrypt fun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48188</link><description>libpspp-core.a in GNU PSPP through 2.0.1 has an incorrect call from fill_buffer (in data/encrypted-file.c) to the Gnulib rijndaelDecrypt function, leading to a heap-based buffer over-read.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 21:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4363 | Wholesale Market &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4363</link><description>The Wholesale Market WordPress plugin before 2.2.2, Wholesale Market for WooCommerce WordPress plugin before 2.0.1 have a flawed CSRF check when updating their settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin update them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4810 | Tenda AC7 SetRebootTimer formSetRebootTimer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4810</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC7 15.03.06.44. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetRebootTimer of the file /goform/SetRebootTimer. The manipulation of the argument reboot_time leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32407 | Samsung Internet for Galaxy Watch version 5.0.9, available up until Samsung Galaxy Watch 3, does not properly validate TLS certificates, all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32407</link><description>Samsung Internet for Galaxy Watch version 5.0.9, available up until Samsung Galaxy Watch 3, does not properly validate TLS certificates, allowing for an attacker to impersonate any and all websites visited by the user. This is a critical misconfiguration in the way the browser validates the identity of the server. It negates the use of HTTPS as a secure channel, allowing for Man-in-the-Middle attacks, stealing sensitive information or modifying incoming and outgoing traffic. NOTE: This vulnerability is in an end-of-life product that is no longer maintained by the vendor.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4804 | WatchGuard Firebox Stored Cross-Site-Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Hotpot Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4804</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WatchGuard Fireware OS allows Stored XSS via the spamBlocker module. This vulnerability requires an authenticated administrator session to a locally managed Firebox.
This issue affects Fireware OS: from 12.0 through 12.11.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4805 | WatchGuard Firebox Stored Cross-Site-Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Acces Portal Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4805</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WatchGuard Fireware OS allows Stored XSS. This vulnerability requires an authenticated administrator session to a locally managed Firebox.
This issue affects Fireware OS: from 12.0 through 12.11.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4808 | PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System add-normal-ticket.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4808</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System 2.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /add-normal-ticket.php. The manipulation of the argument noadult leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4809 | Tenda AC7 setMacFilterCfg fromSafeSetMacFilter stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4809</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC7 15.03.06.44. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function fromSafeSetMacFilter of the file /goform/setMacFilterCfg. The manipulation of the argument deviceList leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4802 | Untrusted LD_LIBRARY_PATH environment variable vulnerability in the GNU C Library version 2.27 to 2.38 allows attacker controlled loading of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4802</link><description>Untrusted LD_LIBRARY_PATH environment variable vulnerability in the GNU C Library version 2.27 to 2.38 allows attacker controlled loading of dynamically shared library in statically compiled setuid binaries that call dlopen (including internal dlopen calls after setlocale or calls to NSS functions such as getaddrinfo).</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 19:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4807 | SourceCodester Online Student Clearance System exposure of information through directory listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4807</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Online Student Clearance System 1.0. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to exposure of information through directory listing. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 19:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22233 | Spring Framework DataBinder Case Sensitive Match Exception</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22233</link><description>CVE-2024-38820 ensured Locale-independent, lowercase conversion for both the configured disallowedFields patterns and for request parameter names. However, there are still cases where it is possible to bypass the disallowedFields checks.

Affected Spring Products and Versions

Spring Framework:
  *  6.2.0 - 6.2.6

  *  6.1.0 - 6.1.19

  *  6.0.0 - 6.0.27

  *  5.3.0 - 5.3.42
  *  Older, unsupported versions are also affected



Mitigation

Users of affected versions should upgrade to the corresponding fixed version.

Affected version(s)Fix Version Availability 6.2.x
 6.2.7
OSS6.1.x
 6.1.20
OSS6.0.x
 6.0.28
 Commercial https://enterprise.spring.io/ 5.3.x
 5.3.43
 Commercial https://enterprise.spring.io/ 
No further mitigation steps are necessary.


Generally, we recommend using a dedicated model object with properties only for data binding, or using constructor binding since constructor arguments explicitly declare what to bind together with turning off setter binding through the declarativeBinding flag. See the Model Design section in the reference documentation.

For setting binding, prefer the use of allowedFields (an explicit list) over disallowedFields.

Credit

This issue was responsibly reported by the TERASOLUNA Framework Development Team from NTT DATA Group Corporation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 19:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4806 | SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System view_bo sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4806</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/?page=back_order/view_bo. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 19:07:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4795 | gongfuxiang schoolcms index.php SaveInfo sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4795</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in gongfuxiang schoolcms 2.3.1. This affects the function SaveInfo of the file /index.php?m=Admin&amp;amp;c=article&amp;amp;a=SaveInfo. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 18:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4793 | PHPGurukul Online Course Registration edit-student-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4793</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration 3.1. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /edit-student-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument cgpa leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 18:19:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4794 | PHPGurukul Online Course Registration news.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4794</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration 3.1. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /news.php. The manipulation of the argument newstitle leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 18:19:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4476 | Libsoup: null pointer dereference in libsoup may lead to denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4476</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability has been identified in the libsoup HTTP client library. This flaw can be triggered when a libsoup client receives a 401 (Unauthorized) HTTP response containing a specifically crafted domain parameter within the WWW-Authenticate header. Processing this malformed header can lead to a crash of the client application using libsoup. An attacker could exploit this by setting up a malicious HTTP server. If a user's application using the vulnerable libsoup library connects to this malicious server, it could result in a denial-of-service. Successful exploitation requires tricking a user's client application into connecting to the attacker's malicious server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 18:19:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4792 | FreeFloat FTP Server MDELETE Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4792</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component MDELETE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 17:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4790 | FreeFloat FTP Server GLOB Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4790</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component GLOB Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 17:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4791 | FreeFloat FTP Server HASH Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4791</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component HASH Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 17:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4788 | FreeFloat FTP Server DELETE Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4788</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component DELETE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4789 | FreeFloat FTP Server LCD Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4789</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component LCD Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:48:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4787 | SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System view_sale sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4787</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/?page=sales/view_sale. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31062 | WordPress Wishlist &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31062</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in redqteam Wishlist allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Wishlist: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31063 | WordPress Wishlist &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31063</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in redqteam Wishlist allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Wishlist: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31065 | WordPress Rozario &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31065</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in themeton Rozario allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Rozario: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31066 | WordPress Acerola &amp;lt;= 1.6.5 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31066</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in themeton Acerola allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Acerola: from n/a through 1.6.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31068 | WordPress Seven Stars &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31068</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in themeton Seven Stars allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Seven Stars: from n/a through 1.4.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31071 | WordPress HotStar – Multi-Purpose Business Theme &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31071</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in themeton HotStar – Multi-Purpose Business Theme allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects HotStar – Multi-Purpose Business Theme: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31630 | WordPress The Business &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31630</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in themeton The Business allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects The Business: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31637 | WordPress SHOUT &amp;lt;= 3.5.3 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31637</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup SHOUT allows SQL Injection. This issue affects SHOUT: from n/a through 3.5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31639 | WordPress Spare &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31639</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in themeton Spare allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Spare: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31640 | WordPress Magic Responsive Slider and Carousel WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.4 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31640</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Magic Responsive Slider and Carousel WordPress allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Magic Responsive Slider and Carousel WordPress: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31641 | WordPress UberSlider &amp;lt;= 2.3 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31641</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup UberSlider allows SQL Injection. This issue affects UberSlider: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31915 | WordPress Pixel WordPress Form BuilderPlugin &amp;amp; Autoresponder &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31915</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in kamleshyadav Pixel WordPress Form BuilderPlugin &amp; Autoresponder allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Pixel WordPress Form BuilderPlugin &amp; Autoresponder: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31921 | WordPress WP Ultimate Tours Builder &amp;lt;= 1.055 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31921</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in loopus WP Ultimate Tours Builder allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Ultimate Tours Builder: from n/a through 1.055.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31922 | WordPress CSS3 Accordions for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31922</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in QuanticaLabs CSS3 Accordions for WordPress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects CSS3 Accordions for WordPress: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31923 | WordPress CSS3 Accordions for WordPress &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31923</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in QuanticaLabs CSS3 Accordions for WordPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects CSS3 Accordions for WordPress: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31926 | WordPress Sticky Radio Player &amp;lt;= 3.4 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31926</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Sticky Radio Player allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Sticky Radio Player: from n/a through 3.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31928 | WordPress Multimedia Responsive Carousel with Image Video Audio Support &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31928</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Multimedia Responsive Carousel with Image Video Audio Support allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Multimedia Responsive Carousel with Image Video Audio Support: from n/a through 2.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32180 | WordPress CSS3 Tooltips for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32180</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in QuanticaLabs CSS3 Tooltips for WordPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects CSS3 Tooltips for WordPress: from n/a through 1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32245 | WordPress Apollo &amp;lt;= 3.6.3 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32245</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Apollo allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Apollo: from n/a through 3.6.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32287 | WordPress Responsive HTML5 Audio Player PRO With Playlist &amp;lt;= 3.5.7 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32287</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Responsive HTML5 Audio Player PRO With Playlist allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Responsive HTML5 Audio Player PRO With Playlist: from n/a through 3.5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32290 | WordPress Sticky HTML5 Music Player &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32290</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Sticky HTML5 Music Player allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Sticky HTML5 Music Player: from n/a through 3.1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32295 | WordPress Salon Booking Wordpress plugin &amp;lt;= 10.10.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32295</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wordpresschef Salon Booking Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Salon Booking Pro: from n/a through 10.10.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32296 | WordPress Simple Link Directory Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 14.7.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32296</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in quantumcloud Simple Link Directory Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Simple Link Directory Pro: from n/a through 14.7.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32299 | WordPress QuickCal &amp;lt;= 1.0.15 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32299</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Themovation QuickCal allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects QuickCal: from n/a through 1.0.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32301 | WordPress CountDown Pro WP Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32301</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup CountDown Pro WP Plugin allows SQL Injection. This issue affects CountDown Pro WP Plugin: from n/a through 2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32306 | WordPress Radio Player Shoutcast &amp;amp; Icecast WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.6 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32306</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Radio Player Shoutcast &amp; Icecast WordPress Plugin allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Radio Player Shoutcast &amp; Icecast WordPress Plugin: from n/a through 4.4.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32307 | WordPress Chameleon HTML5 Audio Player With/Without Playlist &amp;lt;= 3.5.6 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32307</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Chameleon HTML5 Audio Player With/Without Playlist allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Chameleon HTML5 Audio Player With/Without Playlist: from n/a through 3.5.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32310 | WordPress QuickCal plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.13 - CSRF to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32310</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ThemeMove QuickCal allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects QuickCal: from n/a through 1.0.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32643 | WordPress WPGYM Plugin &amp;lt;= 65.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32643</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in mojoomla WPGYM allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects WPGYM: from n/a through 65.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39481 | WordPress Eventer - WordPress Event &amp;amp; Booking Manager Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.6 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39481</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in imithemes Eventer allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Eventer: from n/a through 3.9.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39482 | WordPress Eventer - WordPress Event &amp;amp; Booking Manager Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39482</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in imithemes Eventer allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Eventer: from n/a through 3.9.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39491 | WordPress WHMpress plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2-revision-9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39491</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in WHMPress WHMpress allows Path Traversal. This issue affects WHMpress: from 6.2 through revision.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39492 | WordPress WHMpress plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2-revision-9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39492</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in WHMPress WHMpress allows Relative Path Traversal. This issue affects WHMpress: from 6.2 through revision.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39493 | WordPress Rankie &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39493</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ValvePress Rankie allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Rankie: from n/a through 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39507 | WordPress Nasa Core Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39507</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in NasaTheme Nasa Core allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Nasa Core: from n/a through 6.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39509 | WordPress TNC FlipBook  plugin  &amp;lt;= 12.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39509</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeNcode TNC FlipBook allows Stored XSS. This issue affects TNC FlipBook: from n/a through 12.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39511 | WordPress Pinterest Automatic Pin &amp;lt;= 4.18.2 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39511</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ValvePress Pinterest Automatic Pin allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Pinterest Automatic Pin: from n/a through 4.18.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39537 | WordPress WP JobHunt &amp;lt;= 7.1 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39537</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Chimpstudio WP JobHunt allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP JobHunt: from n/a through 7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46464 | WordPress Ads Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 4.88 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46464</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in scripteo Ads Pro Plugin allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ads Pro Plugin: from n/a through 4.88.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47534 | WordPress Wordpress Auto Spinner &amp;lt;= 3.25.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47534</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ValvePress Wordpress Auto Spinner allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Wordpress Auto Spinner: from n/a through 3.25.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47556 | WordPress CSS3 Compare Pricing Tables for WordPress &amp;lt;= 11.5 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47556</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in QuanticaLabs CSS3 Compare Pricing Tables for WordPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects CSS3 Compare Pricing Tables for WordPress: from n/a through 11.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47557 | WordPress MapSVG plugin &amp;lt;= 8.5.31 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47557</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in RomanCode MapSVG allows Stored XSS. This issue affects MapSVG: from n/a through 8.5.31.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47560 | WordPress MapSVG plugin &amp;lt;= 8.5.32 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47560</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in RomanCode MapSVG allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects MapSVG: from n/a through 8.5.32.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47562 | WordPress MapSVG &amp;lt;= 8.5.34 - Content Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47562</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in RomanCode MapSVG allows Code Injection. This issue affects MapSVG: from n/a through 8.5.34.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47563 | WordPress CURCY plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.7 - Arbitrary Shortcode Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47563</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in villatheme CURCY allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects CURCY: from n/a through 2.3.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47564 | WordPress EventON plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47564</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ashanjay EventON allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects EventON: from n/a through 4.9.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47567 | WordPress Video Player &amp;amp; FullScreen Video Background plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47567</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Video Player &amp; FullScreen Video Background allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Video Player &amp; FullScreen Video Background: from n/a through 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47693 | WordPress Fat Services Booking plugin &amp;lt;= 5.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47693</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in roninwp FAT Services Booking allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects FAT Services Booking: from n/a through 5.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48079 | WordPress ProfileGrid  &amp;lt;= 5.9.5.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48079</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Metagauss ProfileGrid  allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects ProfileGrid : from n/a through 5.9.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48080 | WordPress Uncanny Toolkit for LearnDash &amp;lt;= 3.7.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48080</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Uncanny Toolkit for LearnDash allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Uncanny Toolkit for LearnDash: from n/a through 3.7.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48112 | WordPress Dot html,php,xml etc pages plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48112</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in karimmughal Dot html,php,xml etc pages allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Dot html,php,xml etc pages: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48113 | WordPress Broadstreet &amp;lt;= 1.51.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48113</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Broadstreet Broadstreet allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Broadstreet: from n/a through 1.51.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48114 | WordPress ShayanWeb Admin FontChanger plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48114</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Shayan Farhang Pazhooh ShayanWeb Admin FontChanger allows Stored XSS. This issue affects ShayanWeb Admin FontChanger: from n/a through 1.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48115 | WordPress ValidateCertify &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48115</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Javier Revilla ValidateCertify allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects ValidateCertify: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48116 | WordPress EventON &amp;lt;= 2.4.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48116</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ashan Perera EventON allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects EventON: from n/a through 2.4.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48117 | WordPress WooCommerce POS &amp;lt;= 1.7.8 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48117</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in kilbot WooCommerce POS allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WooCommerce POS: from n/a through 1.7.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48119 | WordPress RS WP Book Showcase plugin &amp;lt;= 6.7.41 - Arbitrary Shortcode Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48119</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in RS WP THEMES RS WP Book Showcase allows Code Injection. This issue affects RS WP Book Showcase: from n/a through 6.7.41.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48120 | WordPress MapSVG Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 8.6.4 - Arbitrary Shortcode Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48120</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in RomanCode MapSVG Lite allows Code Injection. This issue affects MapSVG Lite: from n/a through 8.6.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48121 | WordPress WP Notes Widget &amp;lt;= 1.0.6  - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48121</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Steve Puddick WP Notes Widget allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects WP Notes Widget: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48127 | WordPress Push notification for Mobile and Web app &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48127</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in App Cheap Push notification for Mobile and Web app allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Push notification for Mobile and Web app: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48128 | WordPress Sharespine Woocommerce Connector &amp;lt;= 4.7.55 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48128</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Sharespine Sharespine Woocommerce Connector allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Sharespine Woocommerce Connector: from n/a through 4.7.55.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48131 | WordPress UltraAddons Elementor Lite &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48131</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Saiful Islam UltraAddons Elementor Lite allows Stored XSS. This issue affects UltraAddons Elementor Lite: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48132 | WordPress X Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48132</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in pencilwp X Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects X Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48134 | WordPress WP Tabs &amp;lt;= 2.2.11 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48134</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ShapedPlugin LLC WP Tabs allows Object Injection. This issue affects WP Tabs: from n/a through 2.2.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48135 | WordPress Aptivada for WP &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48135</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in aptivadadev Aptivada for WP allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Aptivada for WP: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48136 | WordPress Mortgage Calculator Estatik &amp;lt;= 2.0.12 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48136</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Estatik Mortgage Calculator Estatik allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Mortgage Calculator Estatik: from n/a through 2.0.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48137 | WordPress Interview &amp;lt;= 1.01 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48137</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in proxymis Interview allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Interview: from n/a through 1.01.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48138 | WordPress BERTHA AI &amp;lt;= 1.12.11 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48138</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in berthaai BERTHA AI allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects BERTHA AI: from n/a through 1.12.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48144 | WordPress Import Export For WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48144</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in sidngr Import Export For WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Import Export For WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48146 | WordPress SEO Flow by LupsOnline plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48146</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Michael Lups SEO Flow by LupsOnline allows Stored XSS. This issue affects SEO Flow by LupsOnline: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4786 | SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System view_return sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4786</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/?page=return/view_return. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40906 | BSON::XS versions 0.8.4 and earlier for Perl includes a bundled libbson 1.1.7, which has several vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40906</link><description>BSON::XS versions 0.8.4 and earlier for Perl includes a bundled libbson 1.1.7, which has several vulnerabilities.

Those include CVE-2017-14227, CVE-2018-16790, CVE-2023-0437, CVE-2024-6381, CVE-2024-6383, and CVE-2025-0755. 

BSON-XS was the official Perl XS implementation of MongoDB's BSON serialization, but this distribution has reached its end of life as of August 13, 2020 and is no longer supported.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4785 | PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker System user-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4785</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker System 1.1. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname/contactnumber leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:24:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47916 | Invision Community 5.0.0 before 5.0.7 allows remote code execution via crafted template strings to themeeditor.php. The issue lies within th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47916</link><description>Invision Community 5.0.0 before 5.0.7 allows remote code execution via crafted template strings to themeeditor.php. The issue lies within the themeeditor controller (file: /applications/core/modules/front/system/themeeditor.php), where a protected method named customCss can be invoked by unauthenticated users. This method passes the value of the content parameter to the Theme::makeProcessFunction() method; hence it is evaluated by the template engine. Accordingly, this can be exploited by unauthenticated attackers to inject and execute arbitrary PHP code by providing crafted template strings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47793 | Nextcloud Server and Groupfolders app vulnerable to bypass of group folder quota limit using attachment in text file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47793</link><description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system, and the Nextcloud Groupfolders app provides admin-configured folders shared by everyone in a group or team. In Nextcloud Server prior to 30.0.2, 29.0.9, and 28.0.1, Nextcloud Enterprise Server prior to 30.0.2 and 29.0.9, and Nextcloud Groupfolders app prior to 18.0.3, 17.0.5, and 16.0.11, the absence of quota checking on attachments allowed logged-in users to upload files exceeding the group folder quota. Nextcloud Server versions 30.0.2 and 29.0.9, Nextcloud Enterprise Server versions 30.0.2, 29.0.9, or 28.0.12, and Nextcloud Groupfolders app 18.0.3, 17.0.5, and 16.0.11 fix the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47794 | Nextcloud Server vulnerable to insecure temporary file creation, race with write access and permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47794</link><description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. In Nextcloud Server prior to 29.0.13, 30.0.7, and 31.0.1 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server prior to 26.0.13.13, 27.1.11.13, 28.0.14.4, 29.0.13, 30.0.7, and 31.0.1, an attacker on a multi-user system may read temporary files from Nextcloud running with a different user account, or run a symlink attack. Nextcloud Server versions 29.0.13, 30.0.7, and 31.0.1 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server 26.0.13.13, 27.1.11.13, 28.0.14.4, 29.0.13, 30.0.7, and 31.0.1 fix the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4781 | PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4781</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System 2.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email/contactno leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4782 | SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System view_receiving sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4782</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /sms/admin/?page=receiving/view_receiving&amp;amp;id=1. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4478 | Gnome-remote-desktop: unauthenticated rdp packet causes segfault in gnome-remote-desktop leading to denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4478</link><description>A flaw was found in the gnome-remote-desktop used by Anaconda's remote install feature, where a crafted RDP packet could trigger a segmentation fault. This issue causes the service to crash and remain defunct, resulting in a denial of service. It occurs pre-boot and is likely due to a NULL pointer dereference. Rebooting is required to recover the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:34:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47791 | Nextcloud Server&amp;#x27;s test remote endpoint is not rate limited</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47791</link><description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. In Nextcloud Server prior to 28.0.13, 29.0.10, and 30.0.3 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server prior to 28.0.13, 29.0.10, and 30.0.3, a currently unused endpoint to verify a share recipient was not protected correctly, allowing to proxy requests to another server. The endpoint was removed in Nextcloud Server 28.0.13, 29.0.10, and 30.0.3 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server 28.0.13, 29.0.10, and 30.0.3. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47792 | Nextcloud Desktop 3rdparty applications can create share links via socket API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47792</link><description>Nextcloud Desktop is the desktop sync client for Nextcloud. In versions of Nextcloud Desktop prior to 3.15, 3rdparty applications already installed on a user machine can create link shares for almost all data via the socket API. These shares can then be easily sent off to an external service. Nextcloud Desktop fixes the issue in version 3.15. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47790 | Nextcloud Server doesn&amp;#x27;t request second factor after session timeout</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47790</link><description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. Nextcloud Server prior to 29.0.15, 30.0.9, and 31.0.3 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server prior to 26.0.13.15, 27.1.11.15, 28.0.14.6, 29.0.15, 30.0.9, and 31.0.3 have a bug with session handling. The bug caused skipping the second factor confirmation after a successful login with the username and password when the server was configured with `remember_login_cookie_lifetime` set to `0`, once the session expired on the page to select the second factor and the page is reloaded. Nextcloud Server 29.0.15, 30.0.9, and 31.0.3 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 26.0.13.15, 27.1.11.15, 28.0.14.6, 29.0.15, 30.0.9 and 31.0.3 contain a patch. As a workaround, set the `remember_login_cookie_lifetime` in config.php to a value other than `0`, e.g. `900`. Beware that this is only a workaround for new sessions created after the configuration change. System administration can delete affected sessions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4780 | PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System foreigner-search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4780</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System 2.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /foreigner-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32962 | Flask-AppBuilder open redirect vulnerability using HTTP host injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32962</link><description>Flask-AppBuilder is an application development framework built on top of Flask. Versions prior to 4.6.2 would allow for a malicious unauthenticated actor to perform an open redirect by manipulating the Host header in HTTP requests. Flask-AppBuilder 4.6.2 introduced the `FAB_SAFE_REDIRECT_HOSTS` configuration variable, which allows administrators to explicitly define which domains are considered safe for redirection. As a workaround, use a reverse proxy to enforce trusted host headers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:55:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4600 | HTTP Request Smuggling in Google Cloud Classic Application Load Balancer due to Improper Chunked Encoding Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4600</link><description>A request smuggling vulnerability existed in the Google Cloud Classic Application Load Balancer due to improper handling of chunked-encoded HTTP requests. This allowed attackers to craft requests that could be misinterpreted by backend servers. The issue was fixed by disallowing stray data after a chunk, and is no longer exploitable. No action is required as Classic Application Load Balancer service after 2025-04-26 is not vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:55:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4211 | Improper Link Resolution Before File Access in QFileSystemEngine on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4211</link><description>Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following') vulnerability in QFileSystemEngine in the Qt corelib module on Windows which potentially allows Symlink Attacks and the use of Malicious Files. Issue originates from CVE-2024-38081. The vulnerability arises from the use of the GetTempPath API, which can be exploited by attackers to manipulate temporary file paths, potentially leading to unauthorized access and privilege escalation. The affected public API in the Qt Framework is QDir::tempPath() and anything that uses it, such as QStandardPaths with TempLocation, QTemporaryDir, and QTemporaryFile.This issue affects all version of Qt up to and including 5.15.18, from 6.0.0 through 6.5.8, from 6.6.0 through 6.8.1. It is fixed in Qt 5.15.19, Qt 6.5.9, Qt 6.8.2, 6.9.0</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4778 | PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System normal-search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4778</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System 2.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /normal-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37890 | net_sched: hfsc: Fix a UAF vulnerability in class with netem as child qdisc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37890</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net_sched: hfsc: Fix a UAF vulnerability in class with netem as child qdisc

As described in Gerrard's report [1], we have a UAF case when an hfsc class
has a netem child qdisc. The crux of the issue is that hfsc is assuming
that checking for cl-&gt;qdisc-&gt;q.qlen == 0 guarantees that it hasn't inserted
the class in the vttree or eltree (which is not true for the netem
duplicate case).

This patch checks the n_active class variable to make sure that the code
won't insert the class in the vttree or eltree twice, catering for the
reentrant case.

[1] https://lore.kernel.org/netdev/CAHcdcOm+03OD2j6R0=YHKqmy=VgJ8xEOKuP6c7mSgnp-TEJJbw@mail.gmail.com/</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40907 | FCGI versions 0.44 through 0.82, for Perl, include a vulnerable version of the FastCGI fcgi2 (aka fcgi) library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40907</link><description>FCGI versions 0.44 through 0.82, for Perl, include a vulnerable version of the FastCGI fcgi2 (aka fcgi) library.

The included FastCGI library is affected by  CVE-2025-23016, causing an integer overflow (and resultant heap-based buffer overflow) via crafted nameLen or valueLen values in data to the IPC socket. This occurs in ReadParams in fcgiapp.c.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4777 | PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System view-foreigner-ticket.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4777</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System 2.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /view-foreigner-ticket.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40629 | Path Traversal vulnerability in PNETLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40629</link><description>PNETLab 4.2.10 does not properly sanitize user inputs in its file access mechanisms. This allows attackers to perform directory traversal by manipulating file paths in HTTP requests. Specifically, the application is vulnerable to requests that access sensitive files outside the intended directory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4773 | PHPGurukul Online Course Registration level.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4773</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration 3.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/level.php. The manipulation of the argument level leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:03:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40120 | seaweedfs v3.68 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /abstract_sql/abstract_sql_store.go.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40120</link><description>seaweedfs v3.68 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /abstract_sql/abstract_sql_store.go.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:03:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2305 | Local file inclusion vulnerability in LIVE CONTRACT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2305</link><description>A Path traversal vulnerability in the file
download functionality was identified. This vulnerability allows
unauthenticated users to download arbitrary files, in the context of the
application server, from the Linux server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2306 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in LIVE CONTRACT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2306</link><description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability was
identified in the file download functionality. This vulnerability allows users
to download sensitive documents without authentication, if the URL is known.



The attack
requires the attacker to know the documents UUIDv4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4772 | PHPGurukul Online Course Registration department.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4772</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration 3.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/department.php. The manipulation of the argument department leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4771 | PHPGurukul Online Course Registration course.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4771</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration 3.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/course.php. The manipulation of the argument coursecode leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40630 | Open redirection vulnerability in IceWarp Mail Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40630</link><description>Open redirection vulnerability in IceWarp Mail Server affecting version 11.4.0. This vulnerability allows an attacker to redirect a user to any domain by sending a malicious URL to the victim, for example “ https://icewarp.domain.com///%2e%2e” https://icewarp.domain.com///%2e%2e” . This vulnerability has been tested in Firefox.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40631 | HTTP host header injection vulnerability in IceWarp Mail Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40631</link><description>HTTP host header injection vulnerability in Icewarp Mail Server affecting version 11.4.0. By modifying the Host header and adding a payload, arbitrary JavaScript code can be executed on page load. The user must interact with a malicious link to be redirected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40632 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in IceWarp Mail Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40632</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) in Icewarp Mail Server affecting version 11.4.0. This vulnerability allows an attacker to modify the “lastLogin” cookie with malicious JavaScript code that will be executed when the page is rendered.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:25:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4770 | PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System view-normal-ticket.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4770</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System 2.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /view-normal-ticket.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:10:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4769 | CBEWIN Anytxt Searcher ATService.exe uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4769</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in CBEWIN Anytxt Searcher 1.3.1128.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file ATService.exe. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. The attack needs to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:48:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4768 | feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp/production_ssm PictureServiceImpl.java uploadPicture unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4768</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp and production_ssm 1.0. This affects the function uploadPicture of the file PictureServiceImpl.java. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is distributed under two entirely different names.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:09:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4767 | defog-ai introspect Test Endpoint integration_routes.py test_custom_tool code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4767</link><description>A vulnerability was found in defog-ai introspect up to 0.1.4. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function test_custom_tool of the file introspect/backend/integration_routes.py of the component Test Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument input_model leads to code injection. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4766 | PHPGurukul Zoo Management System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4766</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/profile.php. The manipulation of the argument contactnumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1975 | Improper Validation of Array Index in ollama/ollama</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1975</link><description>A vulnerability in the Ollama server version 0.5.11 allows a malicious user to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) attack by customizing the manifest content and spoofing a service. This is due to improper validation of array index access when downloading a model via the /api/pull endpoint, which can lead to a server crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4679 | A vulnerability in Synology Active Backup for Microsoft 365 allows remote authenticated attackers to obtain sensitive information via unspec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4679</link><description>A vulnerability in Synology Active Backup for Microsoft 365 allows remote authenticated attackers to obtain sensitive information via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4765 | PHPGurukul Zoo Management System contactus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4765</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/contactus.php. The manipulation of the argument mobnum leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4758 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System contact.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4758</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /contact.php. The manipulation of the argument fname leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4761 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System admin-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4761</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/admin-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4756 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 restart.asp denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4756</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125). It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /H5/restart.asp. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4757 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4757</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53827 | Ericsson Packet Core Controller (PCC) - Improper Input Validation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53827</link><description>Ericsson Packet Core Controller (PCC) contains a
vulnerability where an attacker sending a large volume of specially
crafted messages may cause service degradation</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4755 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 netconfig.asp sub_497DE4 improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4755</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125). It has been classified as critical. This affects the function sub_497DE4 of the file /H5/netconfig.asp. The manipulation leads to improper authentication. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3624 | Missing Authorization Vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3624</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer (Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer detail view component).This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer: from 10.0.0-00 before 11.0.4-00.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:56:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8201 | Cross-Site WebSocket Hijacking Vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8201</link><description>Cross-Site WebSocket Hijacking vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer (RAID Agent component).This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer: from 10.8.0-00 before 11.0.4-00; Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer: from 10.9.0-00 before 11.0.4-00.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4753 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 login.data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4753</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125) and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /login.data. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1531 | Authentication credentials leakage vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer viewpoint OVF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1531</link><description>Authentication credentials leakage  vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer viewpoint.This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer viewpoint: from 10.0.0-00 before 11.0.4-00.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1245 | Bypass Connection Restriction Vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1245</link><description>Bypass Connection Restriction vulnerability in Hitachi Infrastructure Analytics Advisor (Data Center Analytics component), Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer  (Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer detail view component).This issue affects Hitachi Infrastructure Analytics Advisor:; Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer: from 10.0.0-00 before 11.0.4-00.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3201 | Kali Forms &amp;lt; 2.4.3 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3201</link><description>The Contact Form builder with drag &amp; drop for WordPress  WordPress plugin before 2.4.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributors to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3516 | Simple Lightbox &amp;lt; 2.9.4 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3516</link><description>The Simple Lightbox WordPress plugin before 2.9.4 does not validate and escape some of its attributes before outputting them back in a page/post, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4751 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 index.data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4751</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125). Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.data. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4752 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 install_base.data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4752</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125) and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /install_base.data. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4750 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 Configuration get_version.data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4750</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125). This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /H5/get_version.data of the component Configuration Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48174 | In libavif before 1.3.0, makeRoom in stream.c has an integer overflow and resultant buffer overflow in stream-&gt;offset+size.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48174</link><description>In libavif before 1.3.0, makeRoom in stream.c has an integer overflow and resultant buffer overflow in stream-&gt;offset+size.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4747 | Bohua NetDragon Firewall ip_status.php command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4747</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Bohua NetDragon Firewall 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /systemstatus/ip_status.php. The manipulation of the argument subnet leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4749 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 Factory Reset backup.asp sub_4983B0 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4749</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125). This vulnerability affects the function sub_4983B0 of the file /H5/backup.asp?opt=reset of the component Factory Reset Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4759 | Versions of the package lockfile-lint-api before 5.9.2 are vulnerable to Incorrect Behavior Order: Early Validation via the resolved attribu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4759</link><description>Versions of the package lockfile-lint-api before 5.9.2 are vulnerable to Incorrect Behavior Order: Early Validation via the resolved attribute of the package URL validation which can be bypassed by extending the package name allowing an attacker to install other npm packages than the intended one.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48175 | In libavif before 1.3.0, avifImageRGBToYUV in reformat.c has integer overflows in multiplications involving rgbRowBytes, yRowBytes, uRowByte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48175</link><description>In libavif before 1.3.0, avifImageRGBToYUV in reformat.c has integer overflows in multiplications involving rgbRowBytes, yRowBytes, uRowBytes, and vRowBytes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4746 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System purchase_delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4746</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /pages/purchase_delete.php. The manipulation of the argument pr_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4744 | code-projects Employee Record System edit_employee.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4744</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Employee Record System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file dashboard\edit_employee.php. The manipulation of the argument employeed_id/first_name/middle_name/last_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4745 | code-projects Employee Record System current_employees.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4745</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in code-projects Employee Record System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file current_employees.php. The manipulation of the argument employeed_id/first_name/middle_name/last_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4743 | code-projects Employee Record System getData.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4743</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Employee Record System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /dashboard/getData.php. The manipulation of the argument keywords leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4741 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System purchase_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4741</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /pages/purchase_add.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4742 | XU-YIJIE grpo-flat grpo_vanilla.py main deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4742</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in XU-YIJIE grpo-flat up to 9024b43f091e2eb9bac65802b120c0b35f9ba856. Affected is the function main of the file grpo_vanilla.py. The manipulation leads to deserialization. Local access is required to approach this attack. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4169 | Posts per Cat [Unmaintained] &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4169</link><description>The Posts per Cat [Unmaintained plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ppc' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4740 | BeamCtrl Airiana coef deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4740</link><description>A vulnerability was found in BeamCtrl Airiana up to 11.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file coef. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4739 | projectworlds Hospital Database Management System medicines_info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4739</link><description>A vulnerability was found in projectworlds Hospital Database Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /medicines_info.php. The manipulation of the argument Med_ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4735 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System product.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4735</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /pages/product.php. The manipulation of the argument Picture leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4736 | PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4736</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker 1.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /register.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51475 | IBM Content Navigator HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51475</link><description>IBM Content Navigator 3.0.11, 3.0.15, and 3.1.0 is vulnerable to HTML injection. A remote attacker could inject malicious HTML code, which when viewed, would be executed in the victim's Web browser within the security context of the hosting site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:03:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4734 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System ci_update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4734</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pages/ci_update.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:03:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47809 | Wibu CodeMeter before 8.30a sometimes allows privilege escalation immediately after installation (before a logoff or reboot). For exploitati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47809</link><description>Wibu CodeMeter before 8.30a sometimes allows privilege escalation immediately after installation (before a logoff or reboot). For exploitation, there must have been an unprivileged installation with UAC, and the CodeMeter Control Center component must be installed, and the CodeMeter Control Center component must not have been restarted. In this scenario, the local user can navigate from Import License to a privileged instance of Windows Explorer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:03:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4732 | TOTOLINK A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formFilter buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4732</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formFilter of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument ip6addr leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:03:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4733 | TOTOLINK A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formIpQoS buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4733</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boafrm/formIpQoS of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:03:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4730 | TOTOLINK A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formMapDel buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4730</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formMapDel of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument devicemac1 leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:03:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4731 | TOTOLINK A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formPortFw buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4731</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. This affects an unknown part of the file /boafrm/formPortFw of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument service_type leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:03:33 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>