<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 05:42:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-12209 | WP Umbrella: Update Backup Restore &amp;amp; Monitoring &amp;lt;= 2.17.0 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12209</link><description>The WP Umbrella: Update Backup Restore &amp; Monitoring plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.17.0 via the 'filename' parameter of the 'umbrella-restore' action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 05:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53473 | WeGIA 3.2.0 before 3998672 does not verify permission to change a password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53473</link><description>WeGIA 3.2.0 before 3998672 does not verify permission to change a password.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 22:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47107 | IBM QRadar SIEM cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47107</link><description>IBM QRadar SIEM 7.5 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows authenticated users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 14:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41762 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41762</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.5, 11.1, and 11.5 is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 13:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37071 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37071</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.5, 11.1, and 11.5 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service with a specially crafted query due to improper memory allocation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 13:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47115 | IBM AIX command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47115</link><description>IBM AIX 7.2, 7.3 and VIOS 3.1 and 4.1 could allow a local user to execute arbitrary commands on the system due to improper neutralization of input.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 13:15:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11380 | Mini Program API &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11380</link><description>The Mini Program API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'qvideo' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 11:16:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11457 | Feedpress Generator – External RSS Frontend Customizer &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11457</link><description>The Feedpress Generator – External RSS Frontend Customizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tab' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 11:16:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11464 | Easy Code Snippets &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11464</link><description>The Easy Code Snippets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 11:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11501 | Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11501</link><description>The Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.3 via deserialization of untrusted input from wd_gallery_$id parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 11:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11010 | FileOrganizer &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Local JavaScript File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11010</link><description>The FileOrganizer – Manage WordPress and Website Files plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.4 via the 'default_lang' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 09:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11367 | Smoove connector for Elementor forms &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11367</link><description>The Smoove connector for Elementor forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 09:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11374 | TWChat – Send or receive messages from users &amp;lt;= 4.0.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11374</link><description>The TWChat – Send or receive messages from users plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 09:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12128 | Simple Ecommerce Shopping Cart Plugin- Sell products through Paypal &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via monthly_sales_current_year Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12128</link><description>The Simple Ecommerce Shopping Cart Plugin- Sell products through Paypal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘monthly_sales_current_year’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 09:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12253 | Simple Ecommerce Shopping Cart Plugin- Sell products through Paypal &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Update / Data Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12253</link><description>The Simple Ecommerce Shopping Cart Plugin- Sell products through Paypal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the 'save_settings', 'export_csv', and 'simpleecommcart-action' actions in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugins settings and retrieve order and log data (which is also accessible to unauthenticated users).</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 09:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12270 | Beautiful Taxonomy Filters &amp;lt;= 2.4.3 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12270</link><description>The Beautiful taxonomy filters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'selects[0][term]' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 09:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53143 | fsnotify: Fix ordering of iput() and watched_objects decrement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53143</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fsnotify: Fix ordering of iput() and watched_objects decrement

Ensure the superblock is kept alive until we're done with iput().
Holding a reference to an inode is not allowed unless we ensure the
superblock stays alive, which fsnotify does by keeping the
watched_objects count elevated, so iput() must happen before the
watched_objects decrement.
This can lead to a UAF of something like sb-&gt;s_fs_info in tmpfs, but the
UAF is hard to hit because race orderings that oops are more likely, thanks
to the CHECK_DATA_CORRUPTION() block in generic_shutdown_super().

Also, ensure that fsnotify_put_sb_watched_objects() doesn't call
fsnotify_sb_watched_objects() on a superblock that may have already been
freed, which would cause a UAF read of sb-&gt;s_fsnotify_info.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 06:52:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11183 | Simple Side Tab &amp;lt; 2.2.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11183</link><description>The Simple Side Tab WordPress plugin before 2.2.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 06:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10046 | افزونه پیامک ووکامرس Persian WooCommerce SMS &amp;lt;= 7.0.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10046</link><description>The افزونه پیامک ووکامرس Persian WooCommerce SMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 7.0.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11329 | Comfino Payment Gateway &amp;lt;= 4.1.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11329</link><description>The Comfino Payment Gateway plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11353 | SMS for Lead Capture Forms &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Message Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11353</link><description>The SMS for Lead Capture Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the delete_message() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary messages.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11436 | Drag &amp;amp; Drop Builder, Human Face Detector, Pre-built Templates, Spam Protection, User Email Notifications &amp;amp; more! &amp;lt;= 1.4.19 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11436</link><description>The Drag &amp; Drop Builder, Human Face Detector, Pre-built Templates, Spam Protection, User Email Notifications &amp; more! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11451 | Zooom &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11451</link><description>The Zooom plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'zooom' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11904 | 코드엠샵 소셜톡 &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11904</link><description>The 코드엠샵 소셜톡 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'msntt_add_plus_talk' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11943 | 워드프레스 결제 심플페이 – 우커머스 결제 플러그인 &amp;lt;= 5.2.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via add_query_arg Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11943</link><description>The 워드프레스 결제 심플페이 – 우커머스 결제 플러그인 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12026 | Message Filter for Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) New Filter Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12026</link><description>The Message Filter for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the saveFilter() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create new filters.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12115 | Poll Maker &amp;lt;= 5.5.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Poll Duplication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12115</link><description>The Poll Maker – Versus Polls, Anonymous Polls, Image Polls plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the duplicate_poll() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to duplicate polls via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12165 | Mollie for Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 5.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12165</link><description>The Mollie for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12166 | Shortcodes Blocks Creator Ultimate &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;page&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12166</link><description>The Shortcodes Blocks Creator Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12167 | Shortcodes Blocks Creator Ultimate &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via _wpnonce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12167</link><description>The Shortcodes Blocks Creator Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the '_wpnonce' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12257 | CardGate Payments for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12257</link><description>The CardGate Payments for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7894 | If Menu &amp;lt;= 0.19.1 - Missing Authorization to License Key Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7894</link><description>The If Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of the plugin's license key due to a missing capability check on the 'actions' function in versions up to, and including, 0.19.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify delete or modify the license key.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8679 | Library Management System &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8679</link><description>The Library Management System – Manage e-Digital Books Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘value' parameter of the owt_lib_handler AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54138 | XSS Vulnerability in NuGetGallery&amp;#x27;s Markdown Autolinks Processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54138</link><description>NuGet Gallery is a package repository that powers nuget.org. The NuGetGallery has a security vulnerability related to its handling of autolinks in Markdown content. While the platform properly filters out JavaScript from standard links, it does not adequately sanitize autolinks. This oversight allows attackers to exploit autolinks as a vector for Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks. This vulnerability is fixed in 2024.12.06.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 22:17:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44852 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component thet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44852</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component theta_star::ThetaStar::isUnsafeToPlan().</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44853 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the component co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44853</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the component computeControl().</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44854 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the component sm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44854</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the component smoothPlan().</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44855 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the component na...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44855</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the component nav2_navfn_planner().</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44856 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the component na...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44856</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the component nav2_smac_planner().</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41645 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble allows an attacker to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41645</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the nav2__amcl.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41646 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble allows an attacker to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41646</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the nav2_dwb_controller.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41647 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble allows an attacker to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41647</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the nav2_mppi_controller.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41648 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble allows an attacker to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41648</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the nav2_regulated_pure_pursuit_controller.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41649 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble allows an attacker to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41649</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the executor_thread_.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41650 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble allows an attacker to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41650</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the nav2_costmap_2d.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38925 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a use-after-free via the nav2_amcl proce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38925</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a use-after-free via the nav2_amcl process. This vulnerability is triggered via remotely sending a request for change the value of dynamic-parameter`/amcl z_max` .</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38926 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a use-after-free via the nav2_amcl proce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38926</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a use-after-free via the nav2_amcl process. This vulnerability is triggered via remotely sending a request for change the value of dynamic-parameter `/amcl z_short`.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38927 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a use-after-free via the nav2_amcl proce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38927</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a use-after-free via the nav2_amcl process. This vulnerability is triggered via remotely sending a request to change the value of dynamic-parameter `/amcl do_beamskip`.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41644 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble allows an attacker to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41644</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 ROS2 navigation2 v.humble allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the dyn_param_handler_ component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38923 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a use-after-free via the nav2_amcl proce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38923</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a use-after-free via the nav2_amcl process. This vulnerability is triggered via remotely sending a request to change the value of dynamic-parameter`/amcl odom_frame_id` .</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38924 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a use-after-free via the nav2_amcl proce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38924</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a use-after-free via the nav2_amcl process. This vulnerability is triggered via remotely sending a request to change the value of dynamic-parameter`/amcl laser_model_type` .</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38921 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a use-after-free via the nav2_amcl proce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38921</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a use-after-free via the nav2_amcl process. This vulnerability is triggered via remotely sending a request for change the value of dynamic-parameter`/amcl z_rand ` .</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38922 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble version was discovered to contain a heap overflow in the nav2_amcl process. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38922</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating System 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble version was discovered to contain a heap overflow in the nav2_amcl process. This vulnerability is triggered via sending a crafted message to the component /initialpose.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12326 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in Jirafeau</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12326</link><description>Jirafeau normally prevents browser preview for SVG files due to the possibility that manipulated SVG files could be exploited for cross site scripting. This was done by storing the MIME type of a file and preventing the browser preview for MIME type image/svg+xml. This issue was first reported in CVE-2022-30110. However, it was still possible to do a browser preview of a SVG file by sending a manipulated MIME type during the upload, where the case of any letter in image/svg+xml had been changed (like image/svg+XML). The check for image/svg+xml has been changed to be case insensitive.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 20:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7874 | XSS in Tungsten Automation TotalAgility</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7874</link><description>Tungsten Automation (Kofax) TotalAgility in versions all through 7.9.0.25.0.954 is vulnerable to a Reflected XSS attacks through mfpConnectionId parameter manipulation in a form sent to endpoints "/TotalAgility/Kofax/BrowserDevice/ScanFront.aspx" 
and "/TotalAgility/Kofax/BrowserDevice/ScanFrontDebug.aspx"
This allows for injection of a malicious JavaScript code, leading to a possible information leak. 
Exploitation is possible only while using POST requests and also requires retrieving/generating a proper VIEWSTATE parameter, which limits the risk of a successful attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 20:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7875 | XSS in Tungsten Automation TotalAgility</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7875</link><description>Tungsten Automation (Kofax) TotalAgility in versions all through 7.9.0.25.0.954 is vulnerable to a Reflected XSS attacks through mfpScreenResolutionWidth parameter manipulation in a form sent to an endpoint /TotalAgility/Kofax/BrowserDevice/ScanFront.aspx
This allows for injection of a malicious JavaScript code, leading to a possible information leak. 
Exploitation is possible only while using POST requests and also requires retrieving/generating a proper VIEWSTATE parameter, which limits the risk of a successful attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 20:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0130 | NVIDIA UFM Enterprise, UFM Appliance, and UFM CyberAI contain a vulnerability where an attacker can cause an improper authentication issue b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0130</link><description>NVIDIA UFM Enterprise, UFM Appliance, and UFM CyberAI contain a vulnerability where an attacker can cause an improper authentication issue by sending a malformed request through the Ethernet management interface. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to escalation of privileges, data tampering, denial of service, and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 19:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0139 | NVIDIA Base Command Manager and Bright Cluster Manager for Linux contain an insecure temporary file vulnerability. A successful exploit of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0139</link><description>NVIDIA Base Command Manager and Bright Cluster Manager for Linux contain an insecure temporary file vulnerability. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 19:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47146 | Ruijie Reyee OS Resource Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47146</link><description>Ruijie Reyee OS versions 2.206.x up to but not including 2.320.x could allow an attacker to obtain the devices serial number if physically adjacent and sniffing the RAW WIFI signal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 18:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45722 | Ruijie Reyee OS Use of Weak Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45722</link><description>Ruijie Reyee OS versions 2.206.x up to but not including 2.320.x uses weak credential mechanism that could allow an attacker to easily calculate MQTT credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 18:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46874 | Ruijie Reyee OS Improper Handling of Insufficient Permissions or Privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46874</link><description>Ruijie Reyee OS versions 2.206.x up to but not including 2.320.x could allow MQTT clients connecting with device credentials to send messages to some topics. Attackers with device credentials could issue commands to other devices on behalf of Ruijie's cloud.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 18:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47791 | Ruijie Reyee OS Improper Neutralization of Wildcards or Matching Symbols</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47791</link><description>Ruijie Reyee OS versions 2.206.x up to but not including 2.320.x could allow an attacker to subscribe to partial possible topics in Ruijie MQTT broker, and receive partial messages being sent to and from devices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 18:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48874 | Ruijie Reyee OS Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48874</link><description>Ruijie Reyee OS versions 2.206.x up to but not including 2.320.x could give attackers the ability to force Ruijie's proxy servers to perform any request the attackers choose. Using this, attackers could access internal services used by Ruijie and their internal cloud infrastructure via AWS cloud metadata services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 18:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52324 | Ruijie Reyee OS Use of Inherently Dangerous Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52324</link><description>Ruijie Reyee OS versions 2.206.x up to but not including 2.320.x uses an inherently dangerous function which could allow an attacker to send a malicious MQTT message resulting in devices executing arbitrary OS commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 18:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42494 | Ruijie Reyee OS Exposure of Private Personal Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42494</link><description>Ruijie Reyee OS versions 2.206.x up to but not including 2.320.x contains a a feature that could enable sub accounts or attackers to view and exfiltrate sensitive information from all cloud accounts registered to Ruijie's services</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 18:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47043 | Ruijie Reyee OS Insecure Storage of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47043</link><description>Ruijie Reyee OS versions 2.206.x up to but not including 2.320.x could enable an attacker to correlate a device serial number and the user's phone number and part of the email address.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 18:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51727 | Ruijie Reyee OS Premature Release of Resource During Expected Lifetime</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51727</link><description>Ruijie Reyee OS versions 2.206.x up to but not including 2.320.x contains a feature that could enable attackers to invalidate a legitimate user's session and cause a denial-of-service attack on a user's account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 18:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47547 | Ruijie Reyee OS Weak Password Recovery Mechanism for Forgotten Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47547</link><description>Ruijie Reyee OS versions 2.206.x up to but not including 2.320.x contains a weak mechanism for its users to change their passwords which leaves authentication vulnerable to brute force attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 18:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11220 | Open Automation Software Incorrect Execution-Assigned Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11220</link><description>A local low-level user on the server machine with credentials to the running OAS services can create and execute a report with an rdlx file on the server system itself. Any code within the rdlx file of the report executes with SYSTEM privileges, resulting in privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 17:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48871 | Planet Technology Planet WGS-804HPT Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48871</link><description>The affected product is vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow. An unauthenticated attacker could send a malicious HTTP request that the webserver fails to properly check input size before copying data to the stack, potentially allowing remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 17:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52320 | Planet Technology Planet WGS-804HPT Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52320</link><description>The affected product is vulnerable to a command injection. An unauthenticated attacker could send commands through a malicious HTTP request which could result in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 17:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52558 | Planet Technology Planet WGS-804HPT Integer Underflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52558</link><description>The affected product is vulnerable to an integer underflow. An unauthenticated attacker could send a malformed HTTP request, which could allow the attacker to crash the program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 17:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48703 | PhpGurukul Medical Card Generation System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /admin/search-medicalcard.php via the searchda...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48703</link><description>PhpGurukul Medical Card Generation System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /admin/search-medicalcard.php via the searchdata parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 17:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55268 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /covidtms/registered-user-testing.php in PHPGurukul COVID 19 Testing Manag...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55268</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /covidtms/registered-user-testing.php in PHPGurukul COVID 19 Testing Management System 1.0 which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the regmobilenumber parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 17:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48863 | License Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48863</link><description>A command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect License Center. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
License Center 1.9.43 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:53:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48865 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48865</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow attackers with local network access to compromise the security of the system.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.9.2954 build 20241120 and later
QTS 5.2.2.2950 build 20241114 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.9.2954 build 20241120 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.2.2952 build 20241116 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:53:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48866 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48866</link><description>An improper handling of URL encoding (Hex Encoding) vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers to run the system into unexpected state.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.9.2954 build 20241120 and later
QTS 5.2.2.2950 build 20241114 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.9.2954 build 20241120 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.2.2952 build 20241116 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:53:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48867 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48867</link><description>An improper neutralization of CRLF sequences ('CRLF Injection') vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers to modify application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.9.2954 build 20241120 and later
QTS 5.2.2.2950 build 20241114 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.9.2954 build 20241120 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.2.2952 build 20241116 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48868 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48868</link><description>An improper neutralization of CRLF sequences ('CRLF Injection') vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers to modify application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.9.2954 build 20241120 and later
QTS 5.2.2.2950 build 20241114 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.9.2954 build 20241120 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.2.2952 build 20241116 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50393 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50393</link><description>A command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.9.2954 build 20241120 and later
QTS 5.2.2.2950 build 20241114 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.9.2954 build 20241120 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.2.2952 build 20241116 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50402 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50402</link><description>A use of externally-controlled format string vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained administrator access to obtain secret data or modify memory.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.9.2954 build 20241120 and later
QTS 5.2.2.2950 build 20241114 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.9.2954 build 20241120 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.2.2952 build 20241116 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50403 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50403</link><description>A use of externally-controlled format string vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained administrator access to obtain secret data or modify memory.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.2.2950 build 20241114 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.2.2952 build 20241116 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48859 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48859</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers to compromise the security of the system.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.9.2954 build 20241120 and later
QTS 5.2.2.2950 build 20241114 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.9.2954 build 20241120 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.2.2952 build 20241116 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50387 | SMB Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50387</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers to inject malicious code.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
SMB Service 4.15.002 and later
SMB Service h4.15.002 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50388 | HBS 3 Hybrid Backup Sync</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50388</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect HBS 3 Hybrid Backup Sync. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers to execute commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
HBS 3 Hybrid Backup Sync 25.1.1.673 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50389 | QuRouter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50389</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been reported to affect QuRouter. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers to inject malicious code.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuRouter 2.4.5.032 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50404 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50404</link><description>A link following vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained user access to traverse the file system to unintended locations.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
Qsync Central 4.4.0.16_20240819 ( 2024/08/19 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53691 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53691</link><description>A link following vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained user access to traverse the file system to unintended locations.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.8.2823 build 20240712 and later
QTS 5.2.0.2802 build 20240620 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.8.2823 build 20240712 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.0.2802 build 20240620 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54749 | Ubiquiti U7-Pro 7.0.35 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as root...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54749</link><description>Ubiquiti U7-Pro 7.0.35 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54143 | openwrt/asu allows build artifact poisoning via truncated SHA-256 hash and command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54143</link><description>openwrt/asu is an image on demand server for OpenWrt based distributions. The request hashing mechanism truncates SHA-256 hashes to only 12 characters. This significantly reduces entropy, making it feasible for an attacker to generate collisions. By exploiting this, a previously built malicious image can be served in place of a legitimate one, allowing the attacker to "poison" the artifact cache and deliver compromised images to unsuspecting users. This can be combined with other attacks, such as a command injection in Imagebuilder that allows malicious users to inject arbitrary commands into the build process, resulting in the production of malicious firmware images signed with the legitimate build key. This has been patched with 920c8a1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50677 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OroPlatform CMS v5.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50677</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OroPlatform CMS v5.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Search parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30129 | HCL Nomad server on Domino is affected by a host header injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30129</link><description>The HTTP host header can be manipulated and cause the application to behave in unexpected ways. Any changes made to the header would cause the request to be sent to a completely different domain/IP address.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54137 | liboqs has a correctness error in HQC decapsulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54137</link><description>liboqs is a C-language cryptographic library that provides implementations of post-quantum cryptography algorithms. A correctness error has been identified in the reference implementation of the HQC key encapsulation mechanism. Due to an indexing error, part of the secret key is incorrectly treated as non-secret data. This results in an incorrect shared secret value being returned when the decapsulation function is called with a malformed ciphertext. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.12.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:22:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54750 | Ubiquiti U6-LR 6.6.65 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as root.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54750</link><description>Ubiquiti U6-LR 6.6.65 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54745 | WAVLINK WN701AE M01AE_V240305 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54745</link><description>WAVLINK WN701AE M01AE_V240305 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:45:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54747 | WAVLINK WN531P3 202383 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as root...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54747</link><description>WAVLINK WN531P3 202383 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:45:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12254 | Unbounded memory buffering in SelectorSocketTransport.writelines()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12254</link><description>Starting in Python 3.12.0, the asyncio._SelectorSocketTransport.writelines()
 method would not "pause" writing and signal to the Protocol to drain 
the buffer to the wire once the write buffer reached the "high-water 
mark". Because of this, Protocols would not periodically drain the write
 buffer potentially leading to memory exhaustion.





This
 vulnerability likely impacts a small number of users, you must be using
 Python 3.12.0 or later, on macOS or Linux, using the asyncio module 
with protocols, and using .writelines() method which had new 
zero-copy-on-write behavior in Python 3.12.0 and later. If not all of 
these factors are true then your usage of Python is unaffected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54135 | Untrusted Deserialization in ClipBucket-v5 Version 2.0 to 5.5.1 Revision 199</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54135</link><description>ClipBucket V5 provides open source video hosting with PHP. ClipBucket-v5 Version 2.0 to Version 5.5.1 Revision 199 are vulnerable to PHP Deserialization vulnerability. The vulnerability exists in upload/photo_upload.php  within the decode_key function. User inputs were supplied to this function without sanitization via collection GET parameter and photoIDS POST parameter respectively. The decode_key function invokes PHP unserialize function as defined in upload/includes/classes/photos.class.php. As a result, it is possible for an adversary to inject maliciously crafted PHP serialized object and utilize gadget chains to cause unexpected behaviors of the application. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.5.1 Revision 200.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54136 | Untrusted Deserialization in ClipBucket-v5 Version 5.5.1 Revision 199 and Below</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54136</link><description>ClipBucket V5 provides open source video hosting with PHP. ClipBucket-v5 Version 5.5.1 Revision 199 and below is vulnerable to PHP Deserialization vulnerability. The vulnerability exists in upload/upload.php where the user supplied input via collection get parameter is directly provided to unserialize function. As a result, it is possible for an adversary to inject maliciously crafted PHP serialized object and utilize gadget chains to cause unexpected behaviors of the application. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.5.1 Revision 200.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54141 | phpMyFAQ Generates an Error Message Containing Sensitive Information if database server is not available</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54141</link><description>phpMyFAQ is an open source FAQ web application for PHP 8.1+ and MySQL, PostgreSQL and other databases. Prior to 4.0.0, phpMyFAQ exposes the database (ie postgreSQL) server's credential when connection to DB fails. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11738 | Rustls: rustls network-reachable panic in `acceptor::accept`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11738</link><description>A flaw was found in Rustls 0.23.13 and related APIs. This vulnerability allows denial of service (panic) via a fragmented TLS ClientHello message.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 14:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42196 | HCL Launch is susceptible to Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42196</link><description>HCL Launch stores potentially sensitive information in log files that could be read by a local user with access to HTTP request logs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 14:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10516 | Swift Performance Lite &amp;lt;= 2.3.7.1 - Unauthenticated Local PHP File Inclusion via &amp;#x27;ajaxify&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10516</link><description>The Swift Performance Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local PHP File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.7.1 via the 'ajaxify' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4633 | Slider &amp;amp; Popup Builder by Depicter – Add Image Slider, Carousel Slider, Exit Intent Popup, Popup Modal, Coupon Popup, Post Slider Carousel &amp;lt;= 3.2.1- Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4633</link><description>The Slider and Carousel slider by Depicter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘addExtraMimeType’ function in versions up to, and including, 3.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11321 | Reflected XSS in Hi e-learning&amp;#x27;s Learning Management System (LMS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11321</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Hi e-learning Learning Management System (LMS) allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Learning Management System (LMS): before 06.12.2024.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21571 | Snyk has identified a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in all versions of Code Agent. The vulnerability enables an attacker to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21571</link><description>Snyk has identified a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in all versions of Code Agent. The vulnerability enables an attacker to execute arbitrary code within the Code Agent container. Exploiting this vulnerability would require an attacker to have network access to the Code Agent within the deployment environment. External exploitation of this vulnerability is unlikely and depends on both misconfigurations of the cluster and/or chaining with another vulnerability. However, internal exploitation (with a cluster misconfiguration) could still be possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53826 | WordPress WPCasa plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.13 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53826</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPSight WPCasa allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects WPCasa: from n/a through 1.2.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51615 | WordPress WordPress Auction Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51615</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Owen Cutajar &amp; Hyder Jaffari WordPress Auction Plugin allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WordPress Auction Plugin: from n/a through 3.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51815 | WordPress s2Member – Excellent for All Kinds of Memberships, Content Restriction Paywalls &amp;amp; Member Access Subscriptions plugin &amp;lt;= 241114 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51815</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in WP Sharks s2Member Pro allows Code Injection.This issue affects s2Member Pro: from n/a through 241114.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52335 | A vulnerability has been identified in syngo.plaza VB30E (All versions &lt; VB30E_HF05). The affected application do not properly sanitize inpu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52335</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in syngo.plaza VB30E (All versions &lt; VB30E_HF05). The affected application do not properly sanitize input data before sending it to the SQL server. This could allow an attacker with access to the application could use this vulnerability to execute malicious SQL commands to compromise the whole database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53794 | WordPress Arkhe Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.27.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53794</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LOOS,Inc. Arkhe Blocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Arkhe Blocks: from n/a through 2.27.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53795 | WordPress Church Admin plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53795</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Andy Moyle Church Admin allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Church Admin: from n/a through 5.0.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53796 | WordPress Themesflat Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53796</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themesflat Themesflat Addons For Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Themesflat Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53797 | WordPress Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.4.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53797</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Beaver Builder Team Beaver Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Beaver Builder: from n/a through 2.8.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53799 | WordPress FloristPress plugin &amp;lt;= 7.3.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53799</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BAKKBONE Australia FloristPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects FloristPress: from n/a through 7.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53801 | WordPress Bold Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53801</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BoldThemes Bold Page Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Bold Page Builder: from n/a through 5.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53802 | WordPress Futurio Extra plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53802</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FuturioWP Futurio Extra allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Futurio Extra: from n/a through 2.0.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53803 | WordPress WP Mailster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.16.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53803</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in brandtoss WP Mailster allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Mailster: from n/a through 1.8.16.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53804 | WordPress WP Mailster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.16.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53804</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in brandtoss WP Mailster allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects WP Mailster: from n/a through 1.8.16.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53805 | WordPress WP Mailster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.16.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53805</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in brandtoss WP Mailster allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Mailster: from n/a through 1.8.16.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53806 | WordPress Maspik plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.7 - CSRF to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53806</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WpMaspik Maspik – Spam blacklist allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Maspik – Spam blacklist: from n/a through 2.2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53807 | WordPress WP Mailster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.16.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53807</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in brandtoss WP Mailster allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects WP Mailster: from n/a through 1.8.16.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53808 | WordPress NEX-Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 8.7.8 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53808</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Basix NEX-Forms – Ultimate Form Builder allows SQL Injection.This issue affects NEX-Forms – Ultimate Form Builder: from n/a through 8.7.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53809 | WordPress Namaste! LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.4.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53809</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Kiboko Labs Namaste! LMS allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Namaste! LMS: from n/a through 2.6.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53810 | WordPress Simple User Registration plugin &amp;lt;= 5.5 - Broken Access Control on User Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53810</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Najeeb Ahmad Simple User Registration allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Simple User Registration: from n/a through 5.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53811 | WordPress WDesignKit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.40 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53811</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in POSIMYTH WDesignkit allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects WDesignkit: from n/a through 1.0.40.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53812 | WordPress WP GeoNames plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53812</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jacques Malgrange WP GeoNames allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP GeoNames: from n/a through 1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53813 | WordPress wp-travel plugin &amp;lt;= 9.6.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53813</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Travel WP Travel allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Travel: from n/a through 9.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53815 | WordPress Pinpoint Booking System plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.9.5.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53815</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in PINPOINT.WORLD Pinpoint Booking System allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Pinpoint Booking System: from n/a through 2.9.9.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53817 | WordPress Acowebs Product Labels For Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.8 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53817</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Acowebs Product Labels For Woocommerce allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Product Labels For Woocommerce: from n/a through 1.5.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53820 | WordPress Captivate Sync plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.22 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53820</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Captivate Audio Ltd Captivate Sync allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Captivate Sync: from n/a through 2.0.22.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53821 | WordPress Pie Register Premium plugin &amp;lt; 3.8.3.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53821</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Pie Register Premium allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Pie Register Premium: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53823 | WordPress The Plus Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 5.6.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53823</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in POSIMYTH The Plus Addons for Elementor Page Builder Lite allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects The Plus Addons for Elementor Page Builder Lite: from n/a through 5.6.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53824 | WordPress All Bootstrap Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.20 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53824</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AREOI All Bootstrap Blocks allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects All Bootstrap Blocks: from n/a through 1.3.19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53825 | WordPress FileBird Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53825</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ninja Team Filebird allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Filebird: from n/a through 6.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54205 | WordPress Paloma Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.14 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54205</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Paloma Paloma Widget allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Paloma Widget: from n/a through 1.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54206 | WordPress Z-Downloads plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54206</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in URBAN BASE Z-Downloads allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Z-Downloads: from n/a through 1.11.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54207 | WordPress WordPress Auction Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54207</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Owen Cutajar &amp; Hyder Jaffari WordPress Auction Plugin allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WordPress Auction Plugin: from n/a through 3.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54208 | WordPress Block Controller plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54208</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Joni Halabi Block Controller allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Block Controller: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54209 | WordPress Awesome Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54209</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPFactory Awesome Shortcodes allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Awesome Shortcodes: from n/a through 1.7.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54210 | WordPress  Advanced Element Bucket Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54210</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodexShaper Advanced Element Bucket Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Advanced Element Bucket Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54211 | WordPress Borderless – Widgets, Elements, Templates and Toolkit for Elementor &amp;amp; Gutenberg plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54211</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Visualmodo Borderless allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Borderless: from n/a through 1.5.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54212 | WordPress Magical Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54212</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Noor alam Magical Addons For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Magical Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54213 | WordPress WordPress Page Builder – Zion Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.12 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54213</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in zionbuilder.io WordPress Page Builder – Zion Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WordPress Page Builder – Zion Builder: from n/a through 3.6.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54214 | WordPress Revy plugin &amp;lt;= 1.18 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54214</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in NotFound Revy allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Revy: from n/a through 1.18.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54216 | WordPress ARForms plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.1 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary File Read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54216</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in NotFound ARForms allows Path Traversal.This issue affects ARForms: from n/a through 6.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10772 | SICK InspectorP61x and SICK InspectorP62x are vulnerable for firmware modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10772</link><description>Since the firmware update is not validated, an attacker can install modified firmware on the
device. This has a high impact on the availabilty, integrity and confidentiality up to the complete compromise of the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 12:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10773 | SICK InspectorP61x, SICK InspectorP62x and SICK TiM3xx are vulnerable for pass-the-hash attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10773</link><description>The product is vulnerable to pass-the-hash attacks in combination with hardcoded credentials of hidden user levels. This means that an attacker can log in with the hidden user levels and gain
full access to the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 12:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10774 | SICK InspectorP61x and SICK InspectorP62x have unauthenticated CROWN APIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10774</link><description>Unauthenticated CROWN APIs allow access to critical functions. This leads to the accessibility of large parts of the web application without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 12:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10776 | SICK InspectorP61x and SICK InspectorP62x: missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10776</link><description>Lua apps can be deployed, removed, started, reloaded or stopped without authorization via
AppManager. This allows an attacker to remove legitimate apps creating a DoS attack, read and write
files or load apps that use all features of the product available to a customer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 12:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10771 | SICK InspectorP61x, SICK InspectorP62x and SICK TiM3xx are vulnerable for remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10771</link><description>Due to missing input validation during one step of the firmware update process, the product
is vulnerable to remote code execution. With network access and the user level ”Service”, an attacker
can execute arbitrary system commands in the root user’s contexts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 12:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11022 | SICK InspectorP61x and SICK InspectorP62x are vulnerable for a replay attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11022</link><description>The authentication process to the web server uses a challenge response procedure which
inludes the nonce and additional information. This challenge can be used several times for login and is
therefore vulnerable for a replay attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 12:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53907 | An issue was discovered in Django 5.1 before 5.1.4, 5.0 before 5.0.10, and 4.2 before 4.2.17. The strip_tags() method and striptags template...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53907</link><description>An issue was discovered in Django 5.1 before 5.1.4, 5.0 before 5.0.10, and 4.2 before 4.2.17. The strip_tags() method and striptags template filter are subject to a potential denial-of-service attack via certain inputs containing large sequences of nested incomplete HTML entities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 11:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53908 | An issue was discovered in Django 5.1 before 5.1.4, 5.0 before 5.0.10, and 4.2 before 4.2.17. Direct usage of the django.db.models.fields.js...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53908</link><description>An issue was discovered in Django 5.1 before 5.1.4, 5.0 before 5.0.10, and 4.2 before 4.2.17. Direct usage of the django.db.models.fields.json.HasKey lookup, when an Oracle database is used, is subject to SQL injection if untrusted data is used as an lhs value. (Applications that use the jsonfield.has_key lookup via __ are unaffected.)</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 11:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11729 | KiviCare – Clinic &amp;amp; Patient Management System (EHR) &amp;lt;= 3.6.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11729</link><description>The KiviCare – Clinic &amp; Patient Management System (EHR) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'service_list[0][service_id]' parameter of the get_widget_payment_options AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Custom-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 11:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11730 | KiviCare – Clinic &amp;amp; Patient Management System (EHR) &amp;lt;= 3.6.4 - Authenticated (Doctor/Receptionist+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11730</link><description>The KiviCare – Clinic &amp; Patient Management System (EHR) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'sort[]' parameter of the static_data_list AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with doctor/receptionist-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 11:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53141 | netfilter: ipset: add missing range check in bitmap_ip_uadt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53141</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: ipset: add missing range check in bitmap_ip_uadt

When tb[IPSET_ATTR_IP_TO] is not present but tb[IPSET_ATTR_CIDR] exists,
the values of ip and ip_to are slightly swapped. Therefore, the range check
for ip should be done later, but this part is missing and it seems that the
vulnerability occurs.

So we should add missing range checks and remove unnecessary range checks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 09:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53142 | initramfs: avoid filename buffer overrun</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53142</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

initramfs: avoid filename buffer overrun

The initramfs filename field is defined in
Documentation/driver-api/early-userspace/buffer-format.rst as:

 37 cpio_file := ALGN(4) + cpio_header + filename + "\0" + ALGN(4) + data
...
 55 ============= ================== =========================
 56 Field name    Field size         Meaning
 57 ============= ================== =========================
...
 70 c_namesize    8 bytes            Length of filename, including final \0

When extracting an initramfs cpio archive, the kernel's do_name() path
handler assumes a zero-terminated path at @collected, passing it
directly to filp_open() / init_mkdir() / init_mknod().

If a specially crafted cpio entry carries a non-zero-terminated filename
and is followed by uninitialized memory, then a file may be created with
trailing characters that represent the uninitialized memory. The ability
to create an initramfs entry would imply already having full control of
the system, so the buffer overrun shouldn't be considered a security
vulnerability.

Append the output of the following bash script to an existing initramfs
and observe any created /initramfs_test_fname_overrunAA* path. E.g.
  ./reproducer.sh | gzip &gt;&gt; /myinitramfs

It's easiest to observe non-zero uninitialized memory when the output is
gzipped, as it'll overflow the heap allocated @out_buf in __gunzip(),
rather than the initrd_start+initrd_size block.

---- reproducer.sh ----
nilchar="A"	# change to "\0" to properly zero terminate / pad
magic="070701"
ino=1
mode=$(( 0100777 ))
uid=0
gid=0
nlink=1
mtime=1
filesize=0
devmajor=0
devminor=1
rdevmajor=0
rdevminor=0
csum=0
fname="initramfs_test_fname_overrun"
namelen=$(( ${#fname} + 1 ))	# plus one to account for terminator

printf "%s%08x%08x%08x%08x%08x%08x%08x%08x%08x%08x%08x%08x%08x%s" \
	$magic $ino $mode $uid $gid $nlink $mtime $filesize \
	$devmajor $devminor $rdevmajor $rdevminor $namelen $csum $fname

termpadlen=$(( 1 + ((4 - ((110 + $namelen) &amp; 3)) % 4) ))
printf "%.s${nilchar}" $(seq 1 $termpadlen)
---- reproducer.sh ----

Symlink filename fields handled in do_symlink() won't overrun past the
data segment, due to the explicit zero-termination of the symlink
target.

Fix filename buffer overrun by aborting the initramfs FSM if any cpio
entry doesn't carry a zero-terminator at the expected (name_len - 1)
offset.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 09:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10681 | ARMember – Membership Plugin, Content Restriction, Member Levels, User Profile &amp;amp; User signup &amp;lt;= 4.0.51 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10681</link><description>The The ARMember – Membership Plugin, Content Restriction, Member Levels, User Profile &amp; User signup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.51. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 09:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10909 | Pojo Forms &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via form_preview_shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10909</link><description>The The Pojo Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution via form_preview_shortcode AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.7. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary shortcodes. This was partially fixed in version 1.4.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 09:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11289 | Soledad &amp;lt;= 8.5.9 - Unauthenticated Limited Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11289</link><description>The Soledad theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 8.5.9 via several functions like penci_archive_more_post_ajax_func, penci_more_post_ajax_func, and penci_more_featured_post_ajax_func. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute PHP files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where PHP files can be uploaded and included. The exploitability of this is limited to Windows.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 09:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11460 | Verowa Connect &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11460</link><description>The Verowa Connect plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'search_string' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 09:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11728 | KiviCare – Clinic &amp;amp; Patient Management System (EHR) &amp;lt;= 3.6.4 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11728</link><description>The KiviCare – Clinic &amp; Patient Management System (EHR) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'visit_type[service_id]' parameter of the tax_calculated_data AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 09:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10320 | Cookielay &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via cookielay Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10320</link><description>The Cookielay plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's cookielay shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10689 | XLTab – Accordions and Tabs for Elementor Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10689</link><description>The XLTab – Accordions and Tabs for Elementor Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.4 via the 'XLTAB_INSERT_TPL' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private or draft posts created by Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10692 | PowerPack Elementor Addons (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates) &amp;lt;= 2.8.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10692</link><description>The PowerPack Elementor Addons (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.1 via the Content Reveal widget due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10849 | NewsMash &amp;lt;= 1.0.71 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10849</link><description>The NewsMash theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a malicious display name in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.71 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10879 | ForumWP – Forum &amp;amp; Discussion Board &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10879</link><description>The ForumWP – Forum &amp; Discussion Board plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11204 | ForumWP – Forum &amp;amp; Discussion Board &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via url Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11204</link><description>The ForumWP – Forum &amp; Discussion Board plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11276 | PDF Builder for WooCommerce. Create invoices,packing slips and more &amp;lt;= 1.2.136 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11276</link><description>The PDF Builder for WooCommerce. Create invoices,packing slips and more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.136 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11292 | WP Private Content Plus &amp;lt;= 3.6.1 - Unauthenticated Content Restriction Bypass to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11292</link><description>The WP Private Content Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.1 via the WordPress core search feature. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from posts that have been restricted to higher-level roles such as administrator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11323 | AI Quiz | Quiz Maker &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11323</link><description>The AI Quiz | Quiz Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the ai_quiz_update_style() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11336 | Clickbank WordPress Plugin (Storefront) &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11336</link><description>The Clickbank WordPress Plugin (Storefront) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation via the cs_menu page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11339 | Smart PopUp Blaster &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11339</link><description>The Smart PopUp Blaster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's
'spb-button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11352 | TwentyTwenty &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11352</link><description>The TwentyTwenty plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'twentytwenty' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11368 | Splash Sync &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11368</link><description>The Splash Sync plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11444 | CLUEVO LMS, E-Learning Platform &amp;lt;= 1.13.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Module Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11444</link><description>The CLUEVO LMS, E-Learning Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the cluevo_render_module_ui() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete modules via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11450 | ONLYOFFICE Docs &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11450</link><description>The ONLYOFFICE Docs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'onlyoffice' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11687 | Next-Cart Store to WooCommerce Migration &amp;lt;= 3.9.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11687</link><description>The Next-Cart Store to WooCommerce Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11823 | Folder Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11823</link><description>The Folder Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'foldergallery' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12003 | WP System &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12003</link><description>The WP System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the generate_wp_system_page_content() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12027 | Message Filter for Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Filter Updates/Deletions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12027</link><description>The Message Filter for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the updateFilter() and deleteFilter() functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update and delete filters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12028 | Friends &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12028</link><description>The Friends plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on several REST API endpoints in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send arbitrary friend requests on behalf of another website, accept the friend request for the targeted website, and then communicate with the site as an accepted friend.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12060 | WP Media Optimizer (.webp) &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via wpmowebp-css-resources and wpmowebp-js-resources Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12060</link><description>The WP Media Optimizer (.webp) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘wpmowebp-css-resources’ and 'wpmowebp-js-resources' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12110 | Gold Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) License Activation/Deactivation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12110</link><description>The Gold Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the activate() and deactivate() functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to activate and deactivate licenses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12155 | SV100 Companion &amp;lt;= 2.0.02 - Missing Authorization to Unuathenticated Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12155</link><description>The SV100 Companion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the settings_import() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.02. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9705 | Ultimate Coming Soon &amp;amp; Maintenance &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Template Name Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9705</link><description>The Ultimate Coming Soon &amp; Maintenance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ucsm_update_template_name_lite' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change the name of the plugin's templates.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9706 | Ultimate Coming Soon &amp;amp; Maintenance &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Template Activation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9706</link><description>The Ultimate Coming Soon &amp; Maintenance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ucsm_activate_lite_template_lite function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the template used for the coming soon / maintenance page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9866 | Event Tickets with Ticket Scanner &amp;lt;= 2.4.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9866</link><description>The Event Tickets with Ticket Scanner plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'data' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping and missing authorization on the functionality to manage tickets. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This missing authorization aspect of this was patched in 2.4.1, while the Cross-Site Scripting was fully patched in 2.4.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9872 | Online Booking &amp;amp; Scheduling Calendar for WordPress by vcita &amp;lt;= 4.5.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9872</link><description>The Online Booking &amp; Scheduling Calendar for WordPress by vcita plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the vcita_save_user_data_callback() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject malicious web scripts and update settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 08:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11178 | Login With OTP &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Authentication Bypass via Weak OTP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11178</link><description>The Login With OTP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 1.4.2. This is due to the plugin generating too weak OTP, and there’s no attempt or time limit. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to generate and brute force the 6-digit numeric OTP that makes it possible to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the email.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 06:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10480 | 3DPrint Lite &amp;lt; 2.1 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10480</link><description>The 3DPrint Lite WordPress plugin before 2.1 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 06:22:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10551 | Sticky Social Icons &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10551</link><description>The Sticky Social Icons WordPress plugin through 1.2.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 06:22:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10578 | Pubnews &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10578</link><description>The Pubnews theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary plugin installation due to a missing capability check on the pubnews_importer_plugin_action_for_notice() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to install arbitrary plugins that can be leveraged to exploit other vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 05:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11201 | myCred – Loyalty Points and Rewards plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.5.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via mycred_send Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11201</link><description>The myCred – Loyalty Points and Rewards plugin for WordPress and WooCommerce – Give Points, Ranks, Badges, Cashback, WooCommerce rewards, and WooCommerce credits for Gamification plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's mycred_send shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 05:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11585 | WP Hide &amp;amp; Security Enhancer &amp;lt;= 2.5.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Contents Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11585</link><description>The WP Hide &amp; Security Enhancer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file contents deletion due to a missing authorization and insufficient file path validation in the file-process.php in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can break the site or lead to data loss.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 05:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11379 | Broadcast &amp;lt;= 51.01 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11379</link><description>The Broadcast plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'do_check' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 51.01 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This only affects multi-site installations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 04:37:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10247 | YouTube Gallery and Vimeo Gallery Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10247</link><description>The Video Gallery – Best WordPress YouTube Gallery Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the orderby parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 03:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10836 | Flixita &amp;lt;= 1.0.82 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10836</link><description>The Flixita theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.82 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 03:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9769 | Video Gallery &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9769</link><description>The Video Gallery – Best WordPress YouTube Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 03:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11149 | OpenBSD vmm GDTR limits</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11149</link><description>In OpenBSD 7.4 before errata 014, vmm(4) did not restore GDTR limits properly on Intel (VMX) CPUs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49041 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49041</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>