<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:42:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-9585 | Comfast CF-N1 webmgnt wifilith_delete_pic_file command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9585</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Comfast CF-N1 2.6.0. This affects the function wifilith_delete_pic_file of the file /usr/bin/webmgnt. This manipulation of the argument portal_delete_picname causes command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9583 | Comfast CF-N1 webmgnt ping_config command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9583</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Comfast CF-N1 2.6.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function ping_config of the file /usr/bin/webmgnt. The manipulation leads to command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9584 | Comfast CF-N1 webmgnt update_interface_png command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9584</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Comfast CF-N1 2.6.0. Affected by this issue is the function update_interface_png of the file /usr/bin/webmgnt. The manipulation of the argument interface/display_name results in command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6203 | Vault unauthenticated denial of service through complex json payload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6203</link><description>A malicious user may submit a specially-crafted complex payload that otherwise meets the default request size limit which results in excessive memory and CPU consumption of Vault. This may lead to a timeout in Vault’s auditing subroutine, potentially resulting in the Vault server to become unresponsive. This vulnerability, CVE-2025-6203, is fixed in Vault Community Edition 1.20.3 and Vault Enterprise 1.20.3, 1.19.9, 1.18.14, and 1.16.25.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9582 | Comfast CF-N1 webmgnt ntp_timezone command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9582</link><description>A flaw has been found in Comfast CF-N1 2.6.0. Affected is the function ntp_timezone of the file /usr/bin/webmgnt. Executing manipulation of the argument timestr can lead to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9580 | LB-LINK BL-X26 HTTP set_blacklist os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9580</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in LB-LINK BL-X26 1.2.8. This affects an unknown function of the file /goform/set_blacklist of the component HTTP Handler. Such manipulation of the argument mac leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9581 | Comfast CF-N1 webmgnt multi_pppoe command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9581</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Comfast CF-N1 2.6.0. This impacts the function multi_pppoe of the file /usr/bin/webmgnt. Performing manipulation of the argument phy_interface results in command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57215 | Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.20 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function get_parentControl_list_Info.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57215</link><description>Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.20 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function get_parentControl_list_Info.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57220 | An input validation flaw in the 'ate' service of Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.09_multi_TDE01 to escalate privileges to root via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57220</link><description>An input validation flaw in the 'ate' service of Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.09_multi_TDE01 to escalate privileges to root via a crafted UDP packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57219 | Incorrect access control in the endpoint /goform/ate of Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.09_multi_TDE01 allows attackers to escalate privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57219</link><description>Incorrect access control in the endpoint /goform/ate of Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.09_multi_TDE01 allows attackers to escalate privileges or access sensitive components via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9577 | TOTOLINK X2000R Administrative shadow.sample default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9577</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in TOTOLINK X2000R up to 2.0.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /etc/shadow.sample of the component Administrative Interface. The manipulation results in use of default credentials. Attacking locally is a requirement. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9579 | LB-LINK BL-X26 HTTP set_hidessid_cfg os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9579</link><description>A weakness has been identified in LB-LINK BL-X26 1.2.8. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /goform/set_hidessid_cfg of the component HTTP Handler. This manipulation of the argument enable causes os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31971 | AIML Solutions for HCL SX is susceptible to a URL validation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31971</link><description>AIML Solutions for HCL SX is vulnerable to a URL validation vulnerability.  The issue may allow attackers to launch a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack enabling unauthorized network calls from the system, potentially exposing internal services or sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9195 | Improper input validation in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker with local access to cause a Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9195</link><description>Improper input validation in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker with local access to cause a Denial of Service</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9575 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 upload.cgi cgiMain os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9575</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This issue affects the function cgiMain of the file /cgi-bin/upload.cgi. Executing manipulation of the argument filename can lead to os command injection. The attack may be performed from a remote location. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9576 | seeedstudio ReSpeaker Administrative shadow default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9576</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in seeedstudio ReSpeaker LinkIt7688. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /etc/shadow of the component Administrative Interface. The manipulation leads to use of default credentials. An attack has to be approached locally. A high degree of complexity is needed for the attack. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58059 | Valtimo scripting engine can be used to gain access to sensitive data or resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58059</link><description>Valtimo is a platform for Business Process Automation. In versions before 12.16.0.RELEASE, and from 13.0.0.RELEASE to before 13.1.2.RELEASE, any admin that can create or modify and execute process-definitions could gain access to sensitive data or resources. This includes but is not limited to: running executables on the application host, inspecting and extracting data from the host environment or application properties, spring beans (application context, database pooling). The following conditions have to be met in order to perform this attack: the user must be logged in, have the admin role, and must have some knowledge about running scripts via a the Camunda/Operator engine. Version 12.16.0 and 13.1.2 have been patched. It is strongly advised to upgrade. If no scripting is needed in any of the processes, it could be possible to disable it altogether via the ProcessEngineConfiguration. However, this workaround could lead to unexpected side-effects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58049 | XWiki PDF export jobs store sensitive cookies unencrypted in job statuses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58049</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. In versions from 14.4.2 to before 16.4.8, 16.5.0-rc-1 to before 16.10.7, and 17.0.0-rc-1 to before 17.4.0-rc-1, the PDF export jobs store sensitive cookies unencrypted in job statuses. XWiki shouldn't store passwords in plain text, and it shouldn't be possible to gain access to plain text passwords by gaining access to, e.g., a backup of the data directory. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 16.4.8, 16.10.7, and 17.4.0-rc-1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57218 | Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.09_multi_TDE01 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the security_5g parameter in the function s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57218</link><description>Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.09_multi_TDE01 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the security_5g parameter in the function sub_46284C.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58048 | Paymenter Vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via Public File Uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58048</link><description>Paymenter is a free and open-source webshop solution for hostings. Prior to version 1.2.11, the ticket attachments functionality in Paymenter allows a malicious authenticated user to upload arbitrary files. This could result in sensitive data extraction from the database, credentials being read from configuration files, and arbitrary system commands being run under the web server user context. This vulnerability was patched by commit 87c3db4 and was released under the version 1.2.11 tag without any other code modifications compared to version 1.2.10. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators can mitigate this vulnerability with one or more of the following measures: updating nginx config to download attachments instead of executing them or disallowing access to /storage/ fully using a WAF such as Cloudflare.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57217 | Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.09_multi_TDE01 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Password parameter in the function R7We...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57217</link><description>Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.09_multi_TDE01 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Password parameter in the function R7WebsSecurityHandler.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58047 | Volto affected by possible DoS by invoking specific URL by anonymous user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58047</link><description>Volto is a React based frontend for the Plone Content Management System. In versions from 19.0.0-alpha.1 to before 19.0.0-alpha.4, 18.0.0 to before 18.24.0, 17.0.0 to before 17.22.1, and prior to 16.34.0, an anonymous user could cause the NodeJS server part of Volto to quit with an error when visiting a specific URL. The problem has been patched in versions 16.34.0, 17.22.1, 18.24.0, and 19.0.0-alpha.4. To mitigate downtime, have setup automatically restart processes that quit with an error.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31977 | A cryptographic weakness has been identified in the HCL BigFix Service Management (SM)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31977</link><description>HCL BigFix SM is affected by cryptographic weakness due to weak or outdated encryption algorithms.  An attacker with network access could exploit this weakness to decrypt or manipulate encrypted communications under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31979 | A File Upload Validation Bypass vulnerability has been identified in the HCL BigFix Service Management (SM)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31979</link><description>A File Upload Validation Bypass vulnerability has been identified in the HCL BigFix SM, where the application fails to properly enforce file type restrictions during the upload process. An attacker may exploit this flaw to upload malicious or unauthorized files, such as scripts, executables, or web shells, by bypassing client-side or server-side validation mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:17:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31972 | HCL BigFix Service Management (SM) is affected by a Sensitive Information Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31972</link><description>HCL BigFix SM is affected by a Sensitive Information Exposure vulnerability where internal connections do not use TLS encryption which could allow an attacker unauthorized access to sensitive data transmitted between internal components.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58334 | In JetBrains IDE Services before 2025.5.0.1086, 
2025.4.2.2164 users without appropriate permissions could assign high-privileged role for t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58334</link><description>In JetBrains IDE Services before 2025.5.0.1086, 
2025.4.2.2164 users without appropriate permissions could assign high-privileged role for themselves</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58335 | In JetBrains Junie before 252.284.66,
251.284.66,
243.284.66,
252.284.61,
251.284.61,
243.284.61,
252.284.50,
252.284.54,
251.284.54,
251.28...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58335</link><description>In JetBrains Junie before 252.284.66,
251.284.66,
243.284.66,
252.284.61,
251.284.61,
243.284.61,
252.284.50,
252.284.54,
251.284.54,
251.284.50,
243.284.54,
243.284.50 information disclosure was possible via search_project function</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57819 | FreePBX Affected by Authentication Bypass Leading to SQL Injection and RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57819</link><description>FreePBX is an open-source web-based graphical user interface. FreePBX 15, 16, and 17 endpoints are vulnerable due to insufficiently sanitized user-supplied data allowing unauthenticated access to FreePBX Administrator leading to arbitrary database manipulation and remote code execution. This issue has been patched in endpoint versions 15.0.66, 16.0.89, and 17.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57756 | Contao discloses sensitive information in the front end search index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57756</link><description>Contao is an Open Source CMS. In versions starting from 4.9.14 and prior to 4.13.56, 5.3.38, and 5.6.1, protected content elements that are rendered as fragments are indexed and become publicly available in the front end search. This issue has been patched in versions 4.13.56, 5.3.38, and 5.6.1. A workaround involves disabling the front end search.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57757 | Contao discloses information in the news module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57757</link><description>Contao is an Open Source CMS. In versions starting from 5.0.0 and prior to 5.3.38 and 5.6.1, if a news feed contains protected news archives, their news items are not filtered and become publicly available in the RSS feed. This issue has been patched in versions 5.3.38 and 5.6.1. A workaround involves not adding protected news archives to the news feed page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57758 | Contao has improper access control in the back end voters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57758</link><description>Contao is an Open Source CMS. In versions starting from 5.0.0 and prior to 5.3.38 and 5.6.1, the table access voter in the back end doesn't check if a user is allowed to access the corresponding module. This issue has been patched in versions 5.3.38 and 5.6.1. A workaround involves not relying solely on the voter and additionally to check USER_CAN_ACCESS_MODULE.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57759 | Contao has improper privilege management for page and article fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57759</link><description>Contao is an Open Source CMS. In versions starting from 5.3.0 and prior to 5.3.38 and 5.6.1, under certain conditions, back end users may be able to edit fields of pages and articles without having the necessary permissions. This issue has been patched in versions 5.3.38 and 5.6.1. There are no workarounds.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51643 | Meitrack T366G-L GPS Tracker devices contain an SPI flash chip (Winbond 25Q64JVSIQ) that is accessible without authentication or tamper prot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51643</link><description>Meitrack T366G-L GPS Tracker devices contain an SPI flash chip (Winbond 25Q64JVSIQ) that is accessible without authentication or tamper protection. An attacker with physical access to the device can use a standard SPI programmer to extract the firmware using flashrom. This results in exposure of sensitive configuration data such as APN credentials, backend server information, and network parameter</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13986 | Nagios XI Authenticated Arbitrary File Upload Path Traversal RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13986</link><description>Nagios XI &lt; 2024R1.3.2 contains a remote code execution vulnerability by chaining two flaws: an arbitrary file upload and a path traversal in the Core Config Snapshots interface. The issue arises from insufficient validation of file paths and extensions during MIB upload and snapshot rename operations. Exploitation results in the placement of attacker-controlled PHP files in a web-accessible directory, executed as the www-data user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25010 | Kibana privilege escalation via reporting_user role</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25010</link><description>Incorrect authorization in Kibana can lead to privilege escalation via the built-in reporting_user role which incorrectly has the ability to access all Kibana Spaces.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57767 | Asterisk can crash from a specifically malformed Authorization header in an incoming SIP request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57767</link><description>Asterisk is an open source private branch exchange and telephony toolkit. Prior to versions 20.15.2, 21.10.2, and 22.5.2, if a SIP request is received with an Authorization header that contains a realm that wasn't in a previous 401 response's WWW-Authenticate header, or an Authorization header with an incorrect realm was received without a previous 401 response being sent, the get_authorization_header() function in res_pjsip_authenticator_digest will return a NULL. This wasn't being checked before attempting to get the digest algorithm from the header which causes a SEGV. This issue has been patched in versions 20.15.2, 21.10.2, and 22.5.2. There are no workarounds.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29364 | spimsimulator spim v9.1.24 and before is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the READ_SYSCALL and WRITE_SYSCALL system calls. The application v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29364</link><description>spimsimulator spim v9.1.24 and before is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the READ_SYSCALL and WRITE_SYSCALL system calls. The application verifies the legitimacy of the starting and ending addresses for memory read/write operations. By configuring the starting and ending addresses for memory read/write to point to distinct memory segments within the virtual machine, it is possible to circumvent these checks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54995 | Asterisk remotely exploitable leak of RTP UDP ports and internal resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54995</link><description>Asterisk is an open source private branch exchange and telephony toolkit. Prior to versions 18.26.4 and 18.9-cert17, RTP UDP ports and internal resources can leak due to a lack of session termination. This could result in leaks and resource exhaustion. This issue has been patched in versions 18.26.4 and 18.9-cert17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56236 | FormCms v0.5.5 contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the avatar upload feature. Authenticated users can upload .html...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56236</link><description>FormCms v0.5.5 contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the avatar upload feature. Authenticated users can upload .html files containing malicious JavaScript, which are accessible via a public URL. When a privileged user accesses the file, the script executes in their browser context.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48908 | lychee-action vulnerable to arbitrary code injection in composite action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48908</link><description>lychee link checking action checks links in Markdown, HTML, and text files using lychee. Prior to version 2.0.2, there is a potential attack of arbitrary code injection vulnerability in lychee-setup of the composite action at action.yml. This issue has been patched in version 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8067 | Udisks: out-of-bounds read in udisks daemon</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8067</link><description>A flaw was found in the Udisks daemon, where it allows unprivileged users to create loop devices using the D-BUS system. This is achieved via the loop device handler, which handles requests sent through the D-BUS interface. As two of the parameters of this handle, it receives the file descriptor list and index specifying the file where the loop device should be backed. The function itself validates the index value to ensure it isn't bigger than the maximum value allowed. However, it fails to validate the lower bound, allowing the index parameter to be a negative value. Under these circumstances, an attacker can cause the UDisks daemon to crash or perform a local privilege escalation by gaining access to files owned by privileged users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:00:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52054 | An issue was discovered in Tenda AC8 v4.0 AC1200 Dual-band Gigabit Wireless Router AC8v4.0 Firmware 16.03.33.05. The root password of the de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52054</link><description>An issue was discovered in Tenda AC8 v4.0 AC1200 Dual-band Gigabit Wireless Router AC8v4.0 Firmware 16.03.33.05. The root password of the device is calculated with a static string and the last two octets of the MAC address of the device. This allows an unauthenticated attacker to authenticate with network services on the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55583 | D-Link DIR-868L B1 router firmware version FW2.05WWB02 contains an unauthenticated OS command injection vulnerability in the fileaccess.cgi ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55583</link><description>D-Link DIR-868L B1 router firmware version FW2.05WWB02 contains an unauthenticated OS command injection vulnerability in the fileaccess.cgi component. The endpoint /dws/api/UploadFile accepts a pre_api_arg parameter that is passed directly to system-level shell execution functions without sanitization or authentication. Remote attackers can exploit this to execute arbitrary commands as root via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49790 | IBM Watson Studio on Cloud Pak for Data cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49790</link><description>IBM Watson Studio on Cloud Pak for Data 4.0 and 5.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9578 | Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9578</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windows) before build 40734.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51971 | A reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in register.php of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0. Unsanitiz...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51971</link><description>A reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in register.php of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0. Unsanitized user input in the f_name parameter is reflected in the server response without proper HTML encoding or output escaping. This allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary JavaScript code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51972 | A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the login.php of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0 due to improper sanitization of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51972</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the login.php of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0 due to improper sanitization of user-supplied input in the keyword POST parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51967 | A Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the themeSet.php file of ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System 1.0. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51967</link><description>A Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the themeSet.php file of ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System 1.0. The application fails to sanitize user-supplied input in the theme POST parameter, allowing an attacker to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript in a victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51968 | A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the action.php file of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0. The application fails to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51968</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the action.php file of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0. The application fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input in the proId POST parameter, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary SQL expressions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51969 | A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the product.php page of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0. This flaw is present in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51969</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the product.php page of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0. This flaw is present in the product_id GET parameter, which is not properly validated before being included in a SQL statement.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58123 | Lack of TLS validation in plugin BGP Monitoring on Checkmk Exchange</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58123</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation in Checkmk Exchange plugin BGP Monitoring allows attackers in MitM position to intercept traffic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58124 | Lack of TLS validation in plugin check-mk-api on Checkmk Exchange</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58124</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation in Checkmk Exchange plugin check-mk-api allows attackers in MitM position to intercept traffic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58125 | Lack of TLS validation in plugin Freebox v6 agent on Checkmk Exchange</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58125</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation in Checkmk Exchange plugin Freebox v6 agent allows attackers in MitM position to intercept traffic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58126 | Lack of TLS validation in plugin VMware vSAN on Checkmk Exchange</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58126</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation in Checkmk Exchange plugin VMware vSAN allows attackers in MitM position to intercept traffic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58127 | Lack of TLS validation in plugin Dell Powerscale on Checkmk Exchange</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58127</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation in Checkmk Exchange plugin Dell Powerscale allows attackers in MitM position to intercept traffic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48100 | WordPress bidorbuy Store Integrator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.12.0 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48100</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in extremeidea bidorbuy Store Integrator allows Remote Code Inclusion. This issue affects bidorbuy Store Integrator: from n/a through 2.12.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48109 | WordPress XM-Backup plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48109</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Xavier Media XM-Backup allows Stored XSS. This issue affects XM-Backup: from n/a through 0.9.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48110 | WordPress Link View plugin &amp;lt;= 0.8.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48110</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in mibuthu Link View allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Link View: from n/a through 0.8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48304 | WordPress Google XML News Sitemap plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 0.02 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48304</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Gary Illyes Google XML News Sitemap plugin allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Google XML News Sitemap plugin: from n/a through 0.02.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48305 | WordPress Goal Tracker for Patreon plugin &amp;lt;= 0.4.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48305</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in vikingjs Goal Tracker for Patreon allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Goal Tracker for Patreon: from n/a through 0.4.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48306 | WordPress Savyour Affiliate Partner plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48306</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in developers savyour Savyour Affiliate Partner allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Savyour Affiliate Partner: from n/a through 2.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48307 | WordPress SEO For Images plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48307</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in kasonzhao SEO For Images allows Stored XSS. This issue affects SEO For Images: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48308 | WordPress Newsletter subscription optin module plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48308</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in nonletter Newsletter subscription optin module allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Newsletter subscription optin module: from n/a through 1.2.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48309 | WordPress BetPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 Lite - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48309</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in web-able BetPress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects BetPress: from n/a through 1.0.1 Lite.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48310 | WordPress Table Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48310</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wptableeditor Table Editor allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Table Editor: from n/a through 1.6.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48311 | WordPress Invisible Optin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48311</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in OffClicks Invisible Optin allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Invisible Optin: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48312 | WordPress WPAvatar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48312</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 文派翻译（WP Chinese Translation） WPAvatar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WPAvatar: from n/a through 1.9.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48313 | WordPress Tripadvisor Shortcode plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48313</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in kevin heath Tripadvisor Shortcode allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Tripadvisor Shortcode: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48314 | WordPress Add Code To Head plugin &amp;lt;= 1.17 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48314</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in salubrio Add Code To Head allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Add Code To Head: from n/a through 1.17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48315 | WordPress WordPress HTML plugin &amp;lt;= 0.51 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48315</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in stanton119 WordPress HTML allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WordPress HTML: from n/a through 0.51.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48316 | WordPress Responsive Mobile-Friendly Tooltip plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48316</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ItayXD Responsive Mobile-Friendly Tooltip allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Responsive Mobile-Friendly Tooltip: from n/a through 1.6.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48318 | WordPress 多说社会化评论框 plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48318</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in shen2 多说社会化评论框 allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects 多说社会化评论框: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48319 | WordPress Mesa Mesa Reservation Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48319</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in gslauraspeck Mesa Mesa Reservation Widget allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Mesa Mesa Reservation Widget: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48320 | WordPress 百度分享按钮 plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48320</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in cuckoohello 百度分享按钮 allows Stored XSS. This issue affects 百度分享按钮: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48321 | WordPress Ultimate twitter profile widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48321</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in dyiosah Ultimate twitter profile widget allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ultimate twitter profile widget: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48322 | WordPress Statify Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48322</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Finn Dohrn Statify Widget allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Statify Widget: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48323 | WordPress Advance Food Menu plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48323</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Md Abunaser Khan Advance Food Menu allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Advance Food Menu: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48324 | WordPress tli.tl auto Twitter poster plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48324</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in khashabawy tli.tl auto Twitter poster allows Stored XSS. This issue affects tli.tl auto Twitter poster: from n/a through 3.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48325 | WordPress WP Admin Theme plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48325</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in shmish111 WP Admin Theme allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Admin Theme: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48327 | WordPress WP Mailgun SMTP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48327</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in inkthemes WP Mailgun SMTP allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects WP Mailgun SMTP: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48343 | WordPress WPMU Ldap Authentication plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48343</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Aaron Axelsen WPMU Ldap Authentication allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WPMU Ldap Authentication: from n/a through 5.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48347 | WordPress bxSlider integration for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48347</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Vincent Mimoun-Prat bxSlider integration for WordPress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects bxSlider integration for WordPress: from n/a through 1.7.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48348 | WordPress Site Offline plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48348</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in chandrashekharsahu Site Offline allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Site Offline: from n/a through 1.5.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48349 | WordPress Video Gallery – Vimeo and YouTube Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48349</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in origincode Video Gallery – Vimeo and YouTube Gallery allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Video Gallery – Vimeo and YouTube Gallery: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48350 | WordPress AutoWP plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48350</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Neuralabz LTD AutoWP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects AutoWP: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48351 | WordPress Kento Splash Screen plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48351</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PluginsPoint Kento Splash Screen allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Kento Splash Screen: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48352 | WordPress Yandex Site search pinger plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48352</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sitesearch-yandex Yandex Site search pinger allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Yandex Site search pinger: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48353 | WordPress Clickbank WordPress Plugin (Niche Storefront) plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48353</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in dactum Clickbank WordPress Plugin (Niche Storefront) allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Clickbank WordPress Plugin (Niche Storefront): from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48354 | WordPress Better Post &amp;amp; Filter Widgets for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48354</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Smart Widgets Better Post &amp;amp; Filter Widgets for Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Better Post &amp;amp; Filter Widgets for Elementor: from n/a through 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48356 | WordPress Kanpress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1   - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48356</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Isra Kanpress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Kanpress: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48357 | WordPress Century ToolKit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Arbitrary Plugin Activation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48357</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Theme Century Century ToolKit allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Century ToolKit: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48358 | WordPress Risk Free Cash On Delivery (COD) – WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48358</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in everythingwp Risk Free Cash On Delivery (COD) &amp;#8211; WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Risk Free Cash On Delivery (COD) &amp;#8211; WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48359 | WordPress ATT YouTube Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48359</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in thaihavnn07 ATT YouTube Widget allows Stored XSS. This issue affects ATT YouTube Widget: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48360 | WordPress Varnish/Nginx Proxy Caching plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48360</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Razvan Stanga Varnish/Nginx Proxy Caching allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Varnish/Nginx Proxy Caching: from n/a through 1.8.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48361 | WordPress Hesabfa Accounting plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.4 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Log File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48361</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Saeed Sattar Beglou Hesabfa Accounting allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Hesabfa Accounting: from n/a through 2.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48362 | WordPress Hesabfa Accounting plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48362</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Saeed Sattar Beglou Hesabfa Accounting allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Hesabfa Accounting: from n/a through 2.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48363 | WordPress Popup for CF7 with Sweet Alert plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48363</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Metin Saraç Popup for CF7 with Sweet Alert allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Popup for CF7 with Sweet Alert: from n/a through 1.6.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48364 | WordPress rajce plugin &amp;lt;= 0.4.2 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48364</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in vEnCa-X rajce allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects rajce: from n/a through 0.4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48365 | WordPress Custom Comment plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48365</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in imaprogrammer Custom Comment allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Custom Comment: from n/a through 2.1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49383 | WordPress Neresa Theme &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49383</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in CocoBasic Neresa allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Neresa: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49387 | WordPress Drag and Drop File Upload for Elementor Forms Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49387</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in add-ons.org Drag and Drop File Upload for Elementor Forms allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Drag and Drop File Upload for Elementor Forms: from n/a through 1.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49388 | WordPress Miraculous Core Plugin Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49388</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in kamleshyadav Miraculous Core Plugin allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Miraculous Core Plugin: from n/a through 2.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49402 | WordPress Houzez CRM Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49402</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in favethemes Houzez CRM allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Houzez CRM: from n/a through 1.4.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49404 | WordPress Listeo-Core Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.32 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49404</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in purethemes Listeo-Core allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Listeo-Core: from n/a through 1.9.32.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49405 | WordPress Houzez Theme &amp;lt;= 4.1.1 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49405</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in favethemes Houzez allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Houzez: from n/a through 4.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49407 | WordPress Houzez Theme &amp;lt;= 4.1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49407</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in favethemes Houzez allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Houzez: from n/a through 4.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52761 | WordPress WP Funnel Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52761</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in manfcarlo WP Funnel Manager allows Object Injection. This issue affects WP Funnel Manager: from n/a through 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53215 | WordPress Yahoo! WebPlayer Plugin &amp;lt;=  2.0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53215</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 8bitkid Yahoo! WebPlayer allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Yahoo! WebPlayer: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53216 | WordPress Glamer Theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53216</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ThemeUniver Glamer allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Glamer: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53220 | WordPress XmasB Quotes Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53220</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in XmasB XmasB Quotes allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects XmasB Quotes: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53223 | WordPress Theme Switcher Reloaded Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53223</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in undoIT Theme Switcher Reloaded allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Theme Switcher Reloaded: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53224 | WordPress NextGEN Gallery Search Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.12 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53224</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Koen Schuit NextGEN Gallery Search allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects NextGEN Gallery Search: from n/a through 2.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53225 | WordPress e-Boekhouden.nl Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53225</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in eboekhouden e-Boekhouden.nl allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects e-Boekhouden.nl: from n/a through 1.9.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53227 | WordPress Magazine Saga Theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53227</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Unfoldwp Magazine Saga allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Magazine Saga: from n/a through 1.2.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53230 | WordPress Page Manager for Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53230</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in honzat Page Manager for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Page Manager for Elementor: from n/a through 2.0.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53243 | WordPress Employee Directory – Staff Listing &amp;amp; Team Directory Plugin for WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.3 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53243</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in emarket-design Employee Directory – Staff Listing &amp;amp; Team Directory Plugin for WordPress allows Object Injection. This issue affects Employee Directory – Staff Listing &amp;amp; Team Directory Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 4.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53244 | WordPress Magazine Elite Theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53244</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Unfoldwp Magazine Elite allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Magazine Elite: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53247 | WordPress BlogMarks Theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53247</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in WPInterface BlogMarks allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects BlogMarks: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53248 | WordPress Magazine Theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53248</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Unfoldwp Magazine allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Magazine: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53250 | WordPress Chartbeat Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53250</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Chartbeat Chartbeat allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects Chartbeat: from n/a through 2.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53289 | WordPress Theme Blvd Widget Areas Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53289</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jason Theme Blvd Widget Areas allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Theme Blvd Widget Areas: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53326 | WordPress Gutenify Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53326</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in CodeYatri Gutenify allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Gutenify: from n/a through 1.5.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53328 | WordPress Poll, Survey &amp;amp; Quiz Maker Plugin by Opinion Stage Plugin &amp;lt;= 19.11.0 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53328</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Assaf Parag Poll, Survey &amp; Quiz Maker Plugin by Opinion Stage allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Poll, Survey &amp; Quiz Maker Plugin by Opinion Stage: from n/a through 19.11.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53334 | WordPress Jannah Theme &amp;lt;= 7.4.1 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53334</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in TieLabs Jannah allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Jannah: from n/a through 7.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53337 | WordPress LifePress Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53337</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ashan Perera LifePress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects LifePress: from n/a through 2.1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53572 | WordPress WP Easy Contact Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53572</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in emarket-design WP Easy Contact allows Object Injection. This issue affects WP Easy Contact: from n/a through 4.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53576 | WordPress Ovatheme Events Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53576</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ovatheme Ovatheme Events allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Ovatheme Events: from n/a through 1.2.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53578 | WordPress Kipso Theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53578</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in gavias Kipso allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Kipso: from n/a through 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53579 | WordPress Captcha.eu Plugin &amp;lt; 1.0.61 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53579</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in captcha.eu Captcha.eu allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Captcha.eu: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53583 | WordPress Employee Spotlight Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.1 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53583</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in emarket-design Employee Spotlight allows Object Injection. This issue affects Employee Spotlight: from n/a through 5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53584 | WordPress WP Ticket Customer Service Software &amp;amp; Support Ticket System Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.0.2 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53584</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in emarket-design WP Ticket Customer Service Software &amp; Support Ticket System allows Object Injection. This issue affects WP Ticket Customer Service Software &amp; Support Ticket System: from n/a through 6.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53588 | WordPress UPC/EAN/GTIN Code Generator Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53588</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Dmitry V. (CEO of "UKR Solution") UPC/EAN/GTIN Code Generator allows Path Traversal. This issue affects UPC/EAN/GTIN Code Generator: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54029 | WordPress WooCommerce csv import export Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54029</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in extendons WooCommerce csv import export allows Path Traversal. This issue affects WooCommerce csv import export: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54710 | WordPress Tiktok Feed Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.21 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54710</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in bPlugins Tiktok Feed allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Tiktok Feed: from n/a through 1.0.21.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54714 | WordPress Zephyr Project Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.201 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54714</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Dylan James Zephyr Project Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Zephyr Project Manager: from n/a through 3.3.201.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54716 | WordPress Ireca Theme &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54716</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ovatheme Ireca allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Ireca: from n/a through 1.8.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54720 | WordPress Nest Addons Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54720</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in SteelThemes Nest Addons allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Nest Addons: from n/a through 1.6.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54724 | WordPress Golo Theme &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54724</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in uxper Golo allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Golo: from n/a through 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54725 | WordPress Golo Theme &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Broken Authentication Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54725</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in uxper Golo allows Authentication Abuse. This issue affects Golo: from n/a through 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54731 | WordPress YouTube Showcase Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54731</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in emarket-design YouTube Showcase allows Object Injection. This issue affects YouTube Showcase: from n/a through 3.5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54733 | WordPress All Bootstrap Blocks Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.28 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54733</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Miles All Bootstrap Blocks allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects All Bootstrap Blocks: from n/a through 1.3.28.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54734 | WordPress B Slider Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.30 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54734</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in bPlugins B Slider allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects B Slider: from n/a through 1.1.30.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54738 | WordPress Jobmonster Theme &amp;lt;= 4.7.9 - Broken Authentication Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54738</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in NooTheme Jobmonster allows Authentication Abuse. This issue affects Jobmonster: from n/a through 4.7.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54742 | WordPress WpEvently Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.8 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54742</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in magepeopleteam WpEvently allows Object Injection. This issue affects WpEvently: from n/a through 4.4.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39496 | WordPress WooBeWoo Product Filter Pro plugin &amp;lt; 2.9.6 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39496</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WBW WooBeWoo Product Filter Pro allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WooBeWoo Product Filter Pro: from n/a before 2.9.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:48:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9376 | Block Bad Bots and Stop Bad Bots Crawlers and Spiders and Anti Spam Protection &amp;lt;= 11.58 - Insufficient Authorization to Unauthenticated Blocklist Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9376</link><description>The Block Bad Bots and Stop Bad Bots Crawlers and Spiders and Anti Spam Protection plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to an insufficient capability check on the 'stopbadbots_check_wordpress_logged_in_cookie' function in all versions up to, and including, 11.58. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass blocklists, rate limits, and other plugin functionality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54540 | Reflected XSS in QuickCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54540</link><description>QuickCMS is vulnerable to Reflected XSS via sSort parameter in admin's panel functionality. A malicious attacker can craft a specially crafted URL that, when opened, results in arbitrary JavaScript execution in the victim's browser.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 6.8 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:36:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54541 | Cross-Site Request Forgery in QuickCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54541</link><description>QuickCMS is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in page deletion functionality. Malicious attacker can craft special website, which when visited by the admin, will automatically send a POST request deleting an article.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 6.8 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54542 | Sending Password in GET Request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54542</link><description>QuickCMS sends password and login via GET Request. This allows a local attacker with access to the victim's browser history to obtain the necessary credentials to log in as the user.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 6.8 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54543 | Stored XSS in QuickCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54543</link><description>QuickCMS is vulnerable to Stored XSS via sDescriptionMeta parameter in page editor SEO functionality. Malicious attacker with admin privileges can inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed when visiting edited page. By default admin user is not able to add JavaScript into the website.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 6.8 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54544 | Stored XSS in QuickCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54544</link><description>QuickCMS is vulnerable to Stored XSS via aDirFilesDescriptions parameter in files editor functionality. Malicious attacker with admin privileges can inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed when visiting edited page. By default admin user is not able to add JavaScript into the website.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 6.8 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55175 | Reflected XSS in QuickCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55175</link><description>QuickCMS is vulnerable to Reflected XSS via sLangEdit parameter in admin's panel functionality. A malicious attacker can craft a specially crafted URL that, when opened, results in arbitrary JavaScript execution in the victim's browser.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 6.8 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48963 | Local privilege escalation due to improper soft link handling. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Linux...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48963</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to improper soft link handling. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Linux, macOS, Windows) before build 40296.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58240 | tls: separate no-async decryption request handling from async</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58240</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tls: separate no-async decryption request handling from async

If we're not doing async, the handling is much simpler. There's no
reference counting, we just need to wait for the completion to wake us
up and return its result.

We should preferably also use a separate crypto_wait. I'm not seeing a
UAF as I did in the past, I think aec7961916f3 ("tls: fix race between
async notify and socket close") took care of it.

This will make the next fix easier.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46409 | Inadequate encryption strength issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier). If this vulnerability is e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46409</link><description>Inadequate encryption strength issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier). If this vulnerability is exploited, a function that requires authentication may be accessed by a remote unauthenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52460 | Files or directories accessible to external parties issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier). If ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52460</link><description>Files or directories accessible to external parties issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier). If exploited, uploaded files and SS1 configuration files may be accessed by a remote unauthenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53396 | Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier), whi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53396</link><description>Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier), which may allow users who can log in to a client terminal to obtain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53970 | SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files and exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53970</link><description>SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files and execute OS commands with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54762 | SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files and exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54762</link><description>SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files and execute OS commands with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54819 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54819</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier). If this vulnerability is exploited, legitimate files may be overwritten by a remote authenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58072 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58072</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier). If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary files may be viewed by a remote unauthenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58081 | Use of hard-coded password issue/vulnerability in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier) allows a remote unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58081</link><description>Use of hard-coded password issue/vulnerability in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to view arbitrary files with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58322 | NAVER MYBOX Explorer for Windows before 3.0.8.133 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges to NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM by executing arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58322</link><description>NAVER MYBOX Explorer for Windows before 3.0.8.133 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges to NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM by executing arbitrary commands due to improper privilege checks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:18:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6255 | Dynamic AJAX Product Filters for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via className Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6255</link><description>The Dynamic AJAX Product Filters for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘className’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 06:51:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8073 | Dynamic AJAX Product Filters for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via name Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8073</link><description>The Dynamic AJAX Product Filters for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘name’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 06:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13807 | Xagio SEO &amp;lt;= 7.1.0.5 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via Unprotected Back-Up Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13807</link><description>The Xagio SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 7.1.0.5 via the backup functionality due to weak filename structure and lack of protection in the directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from backups which can include the entire database and site's files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 05:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7955 | RingCentral Communications 1.5 - 1.6.8 - Missing Server‑Side Verification to Authentication Bypass via ringcentral_admin_login_2fa_verify Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7955</link><description>The RingCentral Communications plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to improper validation within the ringcentral_admin_login_2fa_verify() function in versions 1.5 to 1.6.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any user simply by supplying identical bogus codes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 05:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7956 | Ajax Search Lite &amp;lt;= 4.13.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Basic Information Exposure via ASL_Query in AJAX Search Handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7956</link><description>The Ajax Search Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Basic Information Exposure due to missing authorization in its AJAX search handler in all versions up to, and including, 4.13.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to issue repeated AJAX requests to leak the content of any protected post in rolling 100‑character windows.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 05:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8977 | Simple Download Monitor &amp;lt;= 3.9.33 - Simple Download Monitor &amp;lt;= 3.9.33 – Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via order parameter in Log Export functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8977</link><description>The Simple Download Monitor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the order parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.33 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, and permissions granted by an Administrator, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 04:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9648 | WP ULike Pro &amp;lt;= 1.9.3 - Unauthenticated Limited Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9648</link><description>The WP ULike Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the WP_Ulike_Pro_File_Uploader class in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload limited arbitrary files like .php2, .php6, .php7, .phps, .pht, .phtm, .pgif, .shtml, .phar, .inc, .hphp, .ctp, .module, .html, .svg on the affected site's server which may make make other attacks like Cross-Site Scripting possible. Only versions up to 1.8.7 were confirmed vulnerable, however, the earliest tested version for a patch we have access to is 1.9.4, so we are considering 1.9.4 the patched version.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0951 | LiquidThemes Themes &amp;lt;= Various Versions - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) All Plugins Deactivated</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0951</link><description>Multiple plugins and/or themes for WordPress by LiquidThemes are vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the liquid_reset_wordpress_before AJAX in various versions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to deactivate all of a site's plugins. While we escalated this to Envato after not being able to establish contact, it appears the developer added a nonce check, however that is not sufficient protection as the nonce is exposed to all users with access to the dashboard.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8603 | Unlimited Elements For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.5.148 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8603</link><description>The Unlimited Elements For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.148 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9345 | File Manager, Code Editor, and Backup by Managefy &amp;lt;= 1.4.8 - Authenticated (Admin+) Path Traversal to Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9345</link><description>The File Manager, Code Editor, and Backup by Managefy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.8 via the ajax_downloadfile() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to perform actions on files outside of the originally intended directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9346 | Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 10.14.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9346</link><description>The Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via settings in all versions up to, and including, 10.14.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36003 | IBM Security Verify Governance Identity Manager information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36003</link><description>IBM Security Verify Governance Identity Manager 10.0.2 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when detailed technical error messages are returned. This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 02:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7812 | Video Share VOD – Turnkey Video Site Builder Script &amp;lt;= 2.7.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7812</link><description>The Video Share VOD – Turnkey Video Site Builder Script plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the adminExport() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and execute remote code when the Server command execution setting is enabled via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 02:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8897 | Beaver Builder Plugin (Lite Version) &amp;lt;= 2.9.2.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8897</link><description>The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘'fl_builder' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 02:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9344 | UsersWP &amp;lt;= 1.2.42 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9344</link><description>The UsersWP – Front-end login form, User Registration, User Profile &amp; Members Directory plugin for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'uwp_profile' and 'uwp_profile_header' shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.42 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 02:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9352 | Pronamic Google Maps &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9352</link><description>The Pronamic Google Maps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the description field in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 02:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7307 | Sangfor Behavior Management System XML External Entity Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7307</link><description>Sangfor Behavior Management System (also referred to as DC Management System in Chinese-language documentation) contains an XML external entity (XXE) injection vulnerability in the /src/sangforindex endpoint. A remote unauthenticated attacker can submit crafted XML data containing external entity definitions, leading to potential disclosure of internal files, server-side request forgery (SSRF), or other impacts depending on parser behavior. The vulnerability is due to improper configuration of the XML parser, which allows resolution of external entities without restriction. This product is now integrated into their IAM (Internet Access Management) platform and an affected version range is undefined.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7308 | SecGate3600 Firewall Information Disclosure via authManageSet.cgi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7308</link><description>SecGate3600, a network firewall product developed by NSFOCUS, contains a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability in the /cgi-bin/authUser/authManageSet.cgi endpoint. The affected component fails to enforce authentication checks on POST requests to retrieve user data. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this flaw to obtain sensitive information, including user identifiers and configuration details, by sending crafted requests to the vulnerable endpoint. An affected version range is undefined.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13979 | St. Joe ERP System SingleRowQueryConverter SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13979</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the St. Joe ERP system ("圣乔ERP系统") that allows unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via crafted HTTP POST requests to the login endpoint. The application fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input before incorporating it into SQL queries, enabling direct manipulation of the backend database. Successful exploitation may result in unauthorized data access, modification of records, or limited disruption of service. An affected version range is undefined.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13982 | SPON IP Network Intercom System rj_get_token.php Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13982</link><description>SPON IP Network Broadcast System, a digital audio transmission platform developed by SPON Communications, contains an arbitrary file read vulnerability in the rj_get_token.php endpoint. The flaw arises from insufficient input validation on the jsondata[url] parameter, which allows attackers to perform directory traversal and access sensitive files on the server. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted POST request to read arbitrary files, potentially exposing system configuration, credentials, or internal logic. An affected version range is undefined.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25115 | D-Link DIR-110/412/600/615/645/815 RCE via service.cgi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25115</link><description>Multiple D-Link DIR-series routers, including DIR-110, DIR-412, DIR-600, DIR-610, DIR-615, DIR-645, and DIR-815 firmware version 1.03, contain a vulnerability in the service.cgi endpoint that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary system commands without authentication. The flaw stems from improper input handling in the EVENT=CHECKFW parameter, which is passed directly to the system shell without sanitization. A crafted HTTP POST request can inject commands that are executed with root privileges, resulting in full device compromise. These router models are no longer supported at the time of assignment and affected version ranges may vary.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7309 | Dahua Smart Park Integrated Management Platform Front-End Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7309</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Dahua Smart Park Integrated Management Platform (also referred to as the Dahua Smart Campus Integrated Management Platform), affecting the SOAP-based GIS bitmap upload interface. The flaw allows unauthenticated remote attackers to upload arbitrary files to the server via crafted SOAP requests, including executable JSP payloads. Successful exploitation may lead to remote code execution (RCE) and full compromise of the affected system. The vulnerability is presumed to affect builds released prior to September 2023 and is said to be remediated in newer versions of the product, though the exact affected range remains undefined.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13980 | H3C Intelligent Management Center (iMC) /byod/index.xhtml RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13980</link><description>H3C Intelligent Management Center (IMC) versions up to and including E0632H07 contains a remote command execution vulnerability in the /byod/index.xhtml endpoint. Improper handling of JSF ViewState allows unauthenticated attackers to craft POST requests with forged javax.faces.ViewState parameters, potentially leading to arbitrary command execution. This flaw does not require authentication and may be exploited without session cookies. An affected version range is undefined.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13981 | LiveBos UploadFile.do Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13981</link><description>LiveBOS, an object-oriented business architecture middleware suite developed by Apex Software Co., Ltd., contains an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in its UploadFile.do;.js.jsp endpoint. This flaw affects the LiveBOS Server component and allows unauthenticated remote attackers to upload crafted files outside the intended directory structure via path traversal in the filename parameter. Successful exploitation may lead to remote code execution on the server, enabling full system compromise. The vulnerability is presumed to affect builds released prior to August 2024 and is said to be remediated in newer versions of the product, though the exact affected range remains undefined.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13984 | Qi&amp;#x27;anxin TianQing Management Center rptsvr Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13984</link><description>QiAnXin TianQing Management Center versions up to and including 6.7.0.4130 contain a path traversal vulnerability in the rptsvr component that allows unauthenticated attackers to upload files to arbitrary locations on the server. The /rptsvr/upload endpoint fails to sanitize the filename parameter in multipart form-data requests, enabling path traversal. This allows attackers to place executable files in web-accessible directories, potentially leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13985 | Dahua EIMS capture_handle.action RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13985</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in Dahua EIMS versions prior to 2240008 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary system commands via the capture_handle.action interface. The flaw stems from improper input validation in the captureCommand parameter, which is processed without sanitization or authentication. By sending crafted HTTP requests, attackers can inject OS-level commands that are executed on the server, leading to full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34160 | AnyShare ServiceAgent API Unauthenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34160</link><description>AnyShare contains a critical unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability in the ServiceAgent API exposed on port 10250. The endpoint /api/ServiceAgent/start_service accepts user-supplied input via POST and fails to sanitize command-like payloads. An attacker can inject shell syntax that is interpreted by the backend, enabling arbitrary command execution. The vulnerability is presumed to affect builds released prior to August 2025 and is said to be remediated in newer versions of the product, though the exact affected range remains undefined.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34162 | Bian Que Feijiu Intelligent Emergency and Quality Control System SQL Injection via GetLyfsByParams</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34162</link><description>An unauthenticated SQL injection vulnerability exists in the GetLyfsByParams endpoint of Bian Que Feijiu Intelligent Emergency and Quality Control System, accessible via the /AppService/BQMedical/WebServiceForFirstaidApp.asmx interface. The backend fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input in the strOpid parameter, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary SQL statements. This can lead to data exfiltration, authentication bypass, and potentially remote code execution, depending on backend configuration. The vulnerability is presumed to affect builds released prior to June 2025 and is said to be remediated in newer versions of the product, though the exact affected range remains undefined.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34163 | Dongsheng Logistics Software Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34163</link><description>Dongsheng Logistics Software exposes an unauthenticated endpoint at /CommMng/Print/UploadMailFile that fails to enforce proper file type validation and access control. An attacker can upload arbitrary files, including executable scripts such as .ashx, via a crafted multipart/form-data POST request. This allows remote code execution on the server, potentially leading to full system compromise. The vulnerability is presumed to affect builds released prior to July 2025 and is said to be remediated in newer versions of the product, though the exact affected range remains undefined.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34520 | Arcserve UDP &amp;lt; 10.2 Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34520</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability in Arcserve Unified Data Protection (UDP) allows unauthenticated attackers to gain unauthorized access to protected functionality or user accounts. By manipulating specific request parameters or exploiting a logic flaw, an attacker can bypass login mechanisms without valid credentials and access administrator-level features. This vulnerability affects all UDP versions prior to 10.2. UDP 10.2 includes the necessary patches and requires no action. Versions 8.0 through 10.1 are supported and require either patch application or upgrade to 10.2. Versions 7.x and earlier are unsupported or out of maintenance and must be upgraded to 10.2 to remediate the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34521 | Arcserve UDP &amp;lt; 10.2 Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34521</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the web interface of the Arcserve Unified Data Protection (UDP), where unsanitized user input is improperly reflected in HTTP responses. This flaw allows remote attackers with low privileges to craft malicious links that, when visited by another user, execute arbitrary JavaScript in the victim’s browser. Successful exploitation may lead to session hijacking, credential theft, or other client-side impacts. The vulnerability requires user interaction and occurs within a shared browser context. This vulnerability affects all UDP versions prior to 10.2. UDP 10.2 includes the necessary patches and requires no action. Versions 8.0 through 10.1 are supported and require either patch application or upgrade to 10.2. Versions 7.x and earlier are unsupported or out of maintenance and must be upgraded to 10.2 to remediate the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34522 | Arcserve UDP &amp;lt; 10.2 Pre-Authentication Heap Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34522</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the input parsing logic of Arcserve Unified Data Protection (UDP). This flaw can be triggered without authentication by sending specially crafted input to the target system. Improper bounds checking allows an attacker to overwrite heap memory, potentially leading to application crashes or remote code execution. Exploitation occurs in the context of the affected process and does not require user interaction. The vulnerability poses a high risk due to its pre-authentication nature and potential for full compromise. This vulnerability affects all UDP versions prior to 10.2. UDP 10.2 includes the necessary patches and requires no action. Versions 8.0 through 10.1 are supported and require either patch application or upgrade to 10.2. Versions 7.x and earlier are unsupported or out of maintenance and must be upgraded to 10.2 to remediate the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34523 | Arcserve UDP &amp;lt; 10.2 Pre-Authentication Heap Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34523</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the exists in the network-facing input handling routines of Arcserve Unified Data Protection (UDP). This flaw is reachable without authentication and results from improper bounds checking when processing attacker-controlled input. By sending specially crafted data, a remote attacker can corrupt heap memory, potentially causing a denial of service or enabling arbitrary code execution depending on the memory layout and exploitation techniques used. This vulnerability is similar in nature to CVE-2025-34522 but affects a separate code path or component. No user interaction is required, and exploitation occurs in the context of the vulnerable process. This vulnerability affects all UDP versions prior to 10.2. UDP 10.2 includes the necessary patches and requires no action. Versions 8.0 through 10.1 are supported and require either patch application or upgrade to 10.2. Versions 7.x and earlier are unsupported or out of maintenance and must be upgraded to 10.2 to remediate the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40779 | Kea crash upon interaction between specific client options and subnet selection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40779</link><description>If a DHCPv4 client sends a request with some specific options, and Kea fails to find an appropriate subnet for the client, the `kea-dhcp4` process will abort with an assertion failure.  This happens only if the client request is unicast directly to Kea; broadcast messages do not cause the problem.
This issue affects Kea versions 2.7.1 through 2.7.9, 3.0.0, and 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 20:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55582 | D-Link DCS-825L firmware v1.08.01 contains a vulnerability in the watchdog script `mydlink-watch-dog.sh`, which blindly respawns binaries su...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55582</link><description>D-Link DCS-825L firmware v1.08.01 contains a vulnerability in the watchdog script `mydlink-watch-dog.sh`, which blindly respawns binaries such as `dcp` and `signalc` without verifying integrity, authenticity, or permissions. An attacker with local filesystem access (via physical access, firmware modification, or debug interfaces) can replace these binaries with malicious payloads. The script executes these binaries as root in an infinite loop, leading to persistent privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution. This issue is mitigated in v1.09.02, but the product is officially End-of-Life and unsupported.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 20:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55618 | In Hyundai Navigation App STD5W.EUR.HMC.230516.afa908d, an attacker can inject HTML payloads in the profile name field in navigation app whi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55618</link><description>In Hyundai Navigation App STD5W.EUR.HMC.230516.afa908d, an attacker can inject HTML payloads in the profile name field in navigation app which then get rendered.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 20:19:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2246 | Missing Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2246</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 18.1.5, 18.2 before 18.2.5, and 18.3 before 18.3.1 that could have allowed unauthenticated users to access sensitive manual CI/CD variables by querying the GraphQL API.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 19:39:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3601 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3601</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 8.15 before 18.1.5, 18.2 before 18.2.5, and 18.3 before 18.3.1 that could have could have allowed an authenticated user to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) condition by submitting URLs that generate excessively large responses.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 19:39:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4225 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4225</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 14.1 before 18.1.5, 18.2 before 18.2.5, and 18.3 before 18.3.1 that that under certain conditions could have allowed an unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial-of-service condition affecting all users by sending specially crafted GraphQL requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 19:39:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5101 | Improper Control of Generation of Code (&amp;#x27;Code Injection&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5101</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 18.1.5, 18.2 before 18.2.5, and 18.3 before 18.3.1 that under certain conditions could have allowed an authenticated attacker to distribute malicious code that appears harmless in the web interface by taking advantage of ambiguity between branches and tags during repository imports.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 19:39:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37777 | O2OA v9.0.3 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the mainOutput() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37777</link><description>O2OA v9.0.3 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the mainOutput() function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 19:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55495 | Tenda AC6 V15.03.06.23_multi was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the list parameter in the fromSetIpMacBind function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55495</link><description>Tenda AC6 V15.03.06.23_multi was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the list parameter in the fromSetIpMacBind function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 19:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58050 | PCRE2: heap-buffer-overflow read in match_ref due to missing boundary restoration in SCS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58050</link><description>The PCRE2 library is a set of C functions that implement regular expression pattern matching. In version 10.45, a heap-buffer-overflow read vulnerability exists in the PCRE2 regular expression matching engine, specifically within the handling of the (*scs:...) (Scan SubString) verb when combined with (*ACCEPT) in src/pcre2_match.c. This vulnerability may potentially lead to information disclosure if the out-of-bounds data read during the memcmp affects the final match result in a way observable by the attacker. This issue has been resolved in version 10.46.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50979 | NodeBB v4.3.0 is vulnerable to SQL injection in its search-categories API endpoint (/api/v3/search/categories). The search query parameter i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50979</link><description>NodeBB v4.3.0 is vulnerable to SQL injection in its search-categories API endpoint (/api/v3/search/categories). The search query parameter is not properly sanitized, allowing unauthenticated, remote attackers to inject boolean-based blind and PostgreSQL error-based payloads.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58192 | WordPress WP Bulk Delete Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58192</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Xylus Themes WP Bulk Delete allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP Bulk Delete: from n/a through 1.3.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58193 | WordPress Uncanny Automator Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.7.0.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58193</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Uncanny Automator allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Uncanny Automator: from n/a through 6.7.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58194 | WordPress Bold Page Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.4.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58194</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in boldthemes Bold Page Builder allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Bold Page Builder: from n/a through 5.4.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58195 | WordPress Xpro Elementor Addons Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.17 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58195</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Xpro Xpro Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Xpro Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.4.17.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58196 | WordPress UiCore Elements Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58196</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in uicore UiCore Elements allows Stored XSS. This issue affects UiCore Elements: from n/a through 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58197 | WordPress Simple Download Monitor Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.34 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58197</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in mra13 / Team Tips and Tricks HQ Simple Download Monitor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Simple Download Monitor: from n/a through 3.9.34.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58198 | WordPress Xpro Theme Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58198</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Xpro Xpro Theme Builder allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Xpro Theme Builder: from n/a through 1.2.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58201 | WordPress AfterShip Tracking Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.17.17 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58201</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AfterShip &amp; Automizely AfterShip Tracking allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects AfterShip Tracking: from n/a through 1.17.17.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58202 | WordPress Simple Page Access Restriction Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.32 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58202</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Plugins and Snippets Simple Page Access Restriction allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Simple Page Access Restriction: from n/a through 1.0.32.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58203 | WordPress Solace Extra Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58203</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in solacewp Solace Extra allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects Solace Extra: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58204 | WordPress Podlove Podcast Publisher Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.5 - Open Redirection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58204</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Eric Teubert Podlove Podcast Publisher allows Phishing. This issue affects Podlove Podcast Publisher: from n/a through 4.2.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58205 | WordPress ElementInvader Addons for Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58205</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Element Invader ElementInvader Addons for Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects ElementInvader Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58208 | WordPress PDF for Elementor Forms + Drag And Drop Template Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58208</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in add-ons.org PDF for Elementor Forms + Drag And Drop Template Builder allows Stored XSS. This issue affects PDF for Elementor Forms + Drag And Drop Template Builder: from n/a through 6.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58209 | WordPress Transcoder Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58209</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in rtCamp Transcoder allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Transcoder: from n/a through 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58211 | WordPress Chatbox Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58211</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in alexvtn Chatbox Manager allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Chatbox Manager: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58212 | WordPress Epeken All Kurir Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58212</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in epeken Epeken All Kurir allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Epeken All Kurir: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58213 | WordPress Booking System Trafft Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58213</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ameliabooking Booking System Trafft allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Booking System Trafft: from n/a through 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58216 | WordPress WP Thumbtack Review Slider Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58216</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in jgwhite33 WP Thumbtack Review Slider allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Thumbtack Review Slider: from n/a through 2.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58217 | WordPress Instant Breaking News Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58217</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in GeroNikolov Instant Breaking News allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Instant Breaking News: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58218 | WordPress Small Package Quotes – USPS Edition Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.9 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58218</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in enituretechnology Small Package Quotes – USPS Edition allows Object Injection. This issue affects Small Package Quotes – USPS Edition: from n/a through 1.3.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55422 | In FoxCMS 1.2.6, there is a reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /index.php/plus.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55422</link><description>In FoxCMS 1.2.6, there is a reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /index.php/plus.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51667 | An issue was discovered in simple-admin-core v1.2.0 thru v1.6.7. The /sys-api/role/update interface in the simple-admin-core system has a li...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51667</link><description>An issue was discovered in simple-admin-core v1.2.0 thru v1.6.7. The /sys-api/role/update interface in the simple-admin-core system has a limited SQL injection vulnerability, which may lead to partial data leakage or disruption of normal system operations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:43:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50428 | In RaspAP raspap-webgui 3.3.2 and earlier, a command injection vulnerability exists in the includes/hostapd.php script. The vulnerability is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50428</link><description>In RaspAP raspap-webgui 3.3.2 and earlier, a command injection vulnerability exists in the includes/hostapd.php script. The vulnerability is due to improper sanitizing of user input passed via the interface parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34157 | Coolify Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Project Name Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34157</link><description>Coolify versions prior to v4.0.0-beta.420.6 are vulnerable to a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack in the project creation workflow. An authenticated user with low privileges can create a project with a maliciously crafted name containing embedded JavaScript. When an administrator attempts to delete the project or its associated resource, the payload executes in the admin’s browser context. This results in full compromise of the Coolify instance, including theft of API tokens, session cookies, and access to WebSocket-based terminal sessions on managed servers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34159 | Coolify Docker Compose Directive Injection in Application Deployment Workflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34159</link><description>Coolify versions prior to v4.0.0-beta.420.6 are vulnerable to a remote code execution vulnerability in the application deployment workflow. The platform allows authenticated users, with low-level member privileges, to inject arbitrary Docker Compose directives during project creation. By crafting a malicious service definition that mounts the host root filesystem, an attacker can gain full root access to the underlying server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34161 | Coolify Git Repository Field Command Injection in Project Deployment Workflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34161</link><description>Coolify versions prior to v4.0.0-beta.420.7 are vulnerable to a remote code execution vulnerability in the project deployment workflow. The platform allows authenticated users, with low-level member privileges, to inject arbitrary shell commands via the Git Repository field during project creation. By submitting a crafted repository string containing command injection syntax, an attacker can execute arbitrary commands on the underlying host system, resulting in full server compromise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:55:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50977 | A template injection vulnerability leading to reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) has been identified in version 1.7.1, requiring authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50977</link><description>A template injection vulnerability leading to reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) has been identified in version 1.7.1, requiring authenticated admin access for exploitation. The vulnerability exists in the 'r' parameter and allows attackers to inject malicious Angular expressions that execute JavaScript code in the context of the application. The flaw can be exploited through GET requests to the summary endpoint as well as POST requests to specific Wicket interface endpoints, though the GET method provides easier weaponization. This vulnerability enables authenticated administrators to execute arbitrary client-side code, potentially leading to session hijacking, data theft, or further privilege escalation attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:55:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57821 | Basecamp&amp;#x27;s Google Sign-In for Rails allowed redirects to a malformed URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57821</link><description>Basecamp's Google Sign-In adds Google sign-in to Rails applications. Prior to version 1.3.0, it is possible to craft a malformed URL that passes the "same origin" check, resulting in the user being redirected to another origin. Rails applications configured to store the flash information in a session cookie may be vulnerable, if this can be chained with an attack that allows injection of arbitrary data into the session cookie. This issue has been patched in version 1.3.0. If upgrading is not possible at this time, a way to mitigate the chained attack can be done by explicitly setting SameSite=Lax or SameSite=Strict on the application session cookie.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20241 | Cisco Nexus 3000 and 9000 Series Switches IS-IS Protocol &amp;lt;TBD&amp;gt; Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20241</link><description>A vulnerability in the Intermediate System-to-Intermediate System (IS-IS) feature of Cisco NX-OS Software for Cisco Nexus 3000 Series Switches and Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Switches in standalone NX-OS mode could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the IS-IS process to unexpectedly restart, which could cause an affected device to reload.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation when parsing an ingress IS-IS packet. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IS-IS packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the unexpected restart of the IS-IS process, which could cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
Note: The IS-IS protocol is a routing protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must be Layer 2-adjacent to the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20262 | Cisco Nexus 3000 and 9000 Series Switches Protocol Independent Multicast Version 6 Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20262</link><description>A vulnerability in the Protocol Independent Multicast Version 6 (PIM6) feature of Cisco Nexus 3000 Series Switches and Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Switches in standalone NX-OS mode could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, remote attacker to trigger a crash of the PIM6 process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.

This vulnerability is due to improper processing of PIM6 ephemeral data queries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted ephemeral query to an affected device through one of the following methods: NX-API REST, NETCONF, RESTConf, gRPC, or Model Driven Telemetry. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the PIM6 process to crash and restart, causing potential adjacency flaps and resulting in a DoS of the PIM6 and ephemeral query processes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20290 | Cisco NXOS Software Sensitive Log Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20290</link><description>A vulnerability in the logging feature of Cisco NX-OS Software for Cisco Nexus 3000 Series Switches, Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Switches in standalone NX-OS mode, Cisco UCS 6400 Fabric Interconnects, Cisco UCS 6500 Series Fabric Interconnects, and Cisco UCS 9108 100G Fabric Interconnects could allow an authenticated, local attacker access to sensitive information.

This vulnerability is due to improper logging of sensitive information. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing log files on the file system where they are stored. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access sensitive information, such as stored credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:44:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20292 | Cisco NXOS Software Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20292</link><description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute a command injection attack on the underlying operating system of an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid user credentials on the affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by entering crafted input as the argument of an affected CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read and write files on the underlying operating system with the privileges of a non-root user account. File system access is limited to the permissions that are granted to that non-root user account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:44:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20294 | Cisco UCS Manager Software Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20294</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI and web-based management interface of Cisco UCS Manager Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative privileges to perform command injection attacks on an affected system and elevate privileges to root.
&amp;nbsp;
These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient input validation of command arguments supplied by the user. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by authenticating to a device and submitting crafted input to the affected commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of the affected device with root-level privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:44:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20295 | Cisco UCS Manager Software Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20295</link><description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco UCS Manager Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrative privileges to read or create a file or overwrite any file on the file system of the underlying operating system of an affected device, including system files.
&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of command arguments supplied by the user. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to a device and submitting crafted input to the affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read or create a file or overwrite any file on the file system of the underlying operating system of the affected device, including system files. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20296 | Cisco UCS Manager Software Stored Software Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20296</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco UCS Manager Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious data into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must be a member of the Administrator or AAA Administrator role.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20317 | Cisco UCS Virtual Keyboard Video Monitor (vKVM) Open Redirect Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20317</link><description>A vulnerability in the Virtual Keyboard Video Monitor (vKVM) connection handling of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to redirect a user to a malicious website.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient verification of vKVM endpoints. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to redirect a user to a malicious webpage and potentially capture user credentials.
Note: The affected vKVM client is also included in Cisco UCS Manager.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20342 | Cisco Integrated Management Controller Virtual Keyboard Video Monitor (vKVM) Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20342</link><description>A vulnerability in the Virtual Keyboard Video Monitor (vKVM) connection handling of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with low privileges to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into a specific data field in the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid user credentials with privileges that allow for vKVM access on the affected device.
Note: The affected vKVM client is also included in Cisco UCS Manager.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20344 | Cisco Nexus Dashboard Path Traversal Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20344</link><description>A vulnerability in the backup restore functionality of Cisco Nexus Dashboard could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a path traversal attack on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of the contents of a backup file. An attacker with valid Administrator credentials could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root privileges on the underlying shell on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20347 | Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller Unauthorized REST API Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20347</link><description>A vulnerability in the REST API endpoints of Cisco Nexus Dashboard and Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC) could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, remote attacker to view sensitive information or upload and modify files on an affected device.

This vulnerability exists because of missing authorization controls on some REST API endpoints. An attacker could exploit th vulnerability by sending crafted API requests to an affected endpoint. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform limited Administrator functions, such as accessing sensitive information regarding HTTP Proxy and NTP configurations, uploading images, and damaging image files on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:44:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20348 | Cisco Nexus Dashboard Unauthorized REST API Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20348</link><description>A vulnerability in the REST API endpoints of Cisco Nexus Dashboard and Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC) could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, remote attacker to view sensitive information or upload and modify files on an affected device.

This vulnerability exists because of missing authorization controls on some REST API endpoints. An attacker could exploit th vulnerability by sending crafted API requests to an affected endpoint. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform limited Administrator functions, such as accessing sensitive information regarding HTTP Proxy and NTP configurations, uploading images, and damaging image files on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:44:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5187 | Nodes can delete themselves by adding an OwnerReference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5187</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the NodeRestriction admission controller in Kubernetes clusters where node users can delete their corresponding node object by patching themselves with an OwnerReference to a cluster-scoped resource. If the OwnerReference resource does not exist or is subsequently deleted, the given node object will be deleted via garbage collection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:44:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54598 | The Bevy Event service through 2025-07-22, as used for eBay Seller Events and other activities, allows CSRF to delete all notifications via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54598</link><description>The Bevy Event service through 2025-07-22, as used for eBay Seller Events and other activities, allows CSRF to delete all notifications via the /notifications/delete/ URI.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50984 | diskover-web v2.3.0 Community Edition is vulnerable to multiple boolean-based blind SQL injection flaws in its Elasticsearch configuration f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50984</link><description>diskover-web v2.3.0 Community Edition is vulnerable to multiple boolean-based blind SQL injection flaws in its Elasticsearch configuration form. Unsanitized user input in POST parameters such as ES_PASS, ES_MAXSIZE, ES_TRANSLOGSIZE, ES_TIMEOUT, ES_USER, ES_HOST, ES_PORT, ES_SCROLLSIZE, ES_CHUNKSIZE and others can be crafted to inject arbitrary SQLite expressions wrapped in JSON functions. By exploiting these injection points, an attacker can infer or extract sensitive information from the underlying database without authentication. This issue stems from improper input validation and parameterization in the application's JSON-based query construction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50978 | In Gitblit v1.7.1, a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the way repository path names are handled. By injecting a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50978</link><description>In Gitblit v1.7.1, a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the way repository path names are handled. By injecting a specially crafted path payload an attacker can cause arbitrary JavaScript to execute when a victim views the manipulated URL. This flaw stems from insufficient input sanitization of filename elements.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50983 | SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the sortKey parameter of the GET /api/v1/wanted/cutoff API endpoint in readarr 0.4.15.2787. The endpoi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50983</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the sortKey parameter of the GET /api/v1/wanted/cutoff API endpoint in readarr 0.4.15.2787. The endpoint fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input, allowing attackers to inject and execute arbitrary SQL commands against the backend SQLite database. Sqlmap confirmed exploitation via stacked queries, demonstrating that the parameter can be abused to run arbitrary SQL statements. A heavy query was executed using SQLite's RANDOMBLOB() and HEX() functions to simulate a time-based payload, indicating deep control over database interactions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:23:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50972 | SQL Injection vulnerability in AbanteCart 1.4.2, allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the tmpl_id paramete...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50972</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in AbanteCart 1.4.2, allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the tmpl_id parameter to index.php. Three techniques have been demonstrated: error-based injection using a crafted FLOOR-based payload, time-based blind injection via SLEEP(), and UNION-based injection to extract arbitrary data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50985 | diskover-web v2.3.0 Community Edition is vulnerable to multiple reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) flaws in its web interface. Unsanitized...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50985</link><description>diskover-web v2.3.0 Community Edition is vulnerable to multiple reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) flaws in its web interface. Unsanitized GET parameters including maxage, maxindex, index, path, q (query), and doctype are directly echoed into the HTML response, allowing attackers to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript when a victim visits a maliciously crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:24:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50986 | diskover-web v2.3.0 Community Edition suffers from multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in its administrative settings...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50986</link><description>diskover-web v2.3.0 Community Edition suffers from multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in its administrative settings interface. Various configuration fields such as ES_HOST, ES_INDEXREFRESH, ES_PORT, ES_SCROLLSIZE, ES_TRANSLOGSIZE, ES_TRANSLOGSYNCINT, EXCLUDES_FILES, FILE_TYPES[], INCLUDES_DIRS, INCLUDES_FILES, and TIMEZONE do not properly sanitize user-supplied input. Malicious payloads submitted via these parameters are persisted in the application and executed whenever an administrator views or edits the settings page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53105 | GLPI permits unauthorized rules execution order</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53105</link><description>GLPI, which stands for Gestionnaire Libre de Parc Informatique, is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. In versions 10.0.0 to before 10.0.19, a connected user without administration rights can change the rules execution order. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.19.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9533 | TOTOLINK T10 formLoginAuth.htm improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9533</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK T10 4.1.8cu.5241_B20210927. Affected is an unknown function of the file /formLoginAuth.htm. The manipulation of the argument authCode with the input 1 leads to improper authentication. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50989 | OPNsense 25.1 contains an authenticated command injection vulnerability in its Bridge Interface Edit endpoint (interfaces_bridge_edit.php). ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50989</link><description>OPNsense 25.1 contains an authenticated command injection vulnerability in its Bridge Interface Edit endpoint (interfaces_bridge_edit.php). The span POST parameter is concatenated into a system-level command without proper sanitization or escaping, allowing an administrator to inject arbitrary shell operators and payloads. Successful exploitation grants RCE with the privileges of the web service (typically root), potentially leading to full system compromise or lateral movement. This vulnerability arises from inadequate input validation and improper handling of user-supplied data in backend command invocations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52122 | Freeform 5.0.0 to before 5.10.16, a plugin for CraftCMS, contains an Server-side template injection (SSTI) vulnerability, resulting in arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52122</link><description>Freeform 5.0.0 to before 5.10.16, a plugin for CraftCMS, contains an Server-side template injection (SSTI) vulnerability, resulting in arbitrary code injection for all users that have access to editing a form (submission title).</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43729 | Dell ThinOS 10, versions prior to 2508_10.0127, contains an Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability. A local low...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43729</link><description>Dell ThinOS 10, versions prior to 2508_10.0127, contains an Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability. A local low-privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability leading to Elevation of Privileges and Unauthorized Access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56694 | Client-side password validation (CWE-602) in lumasoft fotoShare Cloud 2025-03-13 allowing unauthenticated attackers to view password-protect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56694</link><description>Client-side password validation (CWE-602) in lumasoft fotoShare Cloud 2025-03-13 allowing unauthenticated attackers to view password-protected photo albums.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9532 | Portabilis i-Educar view sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9532</link><description>A flaw has been found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This impacts an unknown function of the file /RegraAvaliacao/view. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43730 | Dell ThinOS 10, versions prior to 2508_10.0127, contains an Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43730</link><description>Dell ThinOS 10, versions prior to 2508_10.0127, contains an Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection') vulnerability. A local unauthenticated user could potentially exploit this vulnerability leading to Elevation of Privileges and Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43882 | Dell ThinOS 10, versions prior to 2508_10.0127, contains an Unverified Ownership vulnerability. A local low-privileged attacker could potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43882</link><description>Dell ThinOS 10, versions prior to 2508_10.0127, contains an Unverified Ownership vulnerability. A local low-privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability leading to Unauthorized Access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43728 | Dell ThinOS 10, versions prior to 2508_10.0127, contain a Protection Mechanism Failure vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43728</link><description>Dell ThinOS 10, versions prior to 2508_10.0127, contain a Protection Mechanism Failure vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Protection mechanism bypass.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9529 | Campcodes Payroll Management System index.php include file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9529</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Payroll Management System 1.0. The affected element is the function include of the file /index.php. This manipulation of the argument page causes file inclusion. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9531 | Portabilis i-Educar Agenda agenda.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9531</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This affects an unknown function of the file /intranet/agenda.php of the component Agenda Module. Performing manipulation of the argument cod_agenda results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9527 | Linksys E1700 QoSSetup stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9527</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Linksys E1700 1.0.0.4.003. This affects the function QoSSetup of the file /goform/QoSSetup. Performing manipulation of the argument ack_policy results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9528 | Linksys E1700 systemCommand os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9528</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Linksys E1700 1.0.0.4.003. This vulnerability affects the function systemCommand of the file /goform/systemCommand. Executing manipulation of the argument command can lead to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9525 | Linksys E1700 setWan stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9525</link><description>A flaw has been found in Linksys E1700 1.0.0.4.003. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setWan of the file /goform/setWan. This manipulation of the argument DeviceName/lanIp causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9526 | Linksys E1700 setSysAdm stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9526</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Linksys E1700 1.0.0.4.003. Affected by this issue is the function setSysAdm of the file /goform/setSysAdm. Such manipulation of the argument rm_port leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9523 | Tenda AC1206 GetParentControlInfo stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9523</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda AC1206 15.03.06.23. Affected is the function GetParentControlInfo of the file /goform/GetParentControlInfo. The manipulation of the argument mac results in stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2313 | RCE via Print.pl in uhcPrintServerPrint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2313</link><description>In the Print.pl service, the "uhcPrintServerPrint" function allows execution of arbitrary code via the "CopyCounter" parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30036 | Stored XSS permitting session takeover of arbitrary user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30036</link><description>Stored XSS vulnerability exists in the "Oddział" (Ward) module, in the death diagnosis description field, and allows the execution of arbitrary JavaScript code. This can lead to session hijacking of other users and potentially to privilege escalation up to full administrative rights.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30037 | Missing authentication in APIs allowing data retrieval and modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30037</link><description>The system exposes several endpoints, typically including "/int/" in their path, that should be restricted to internal services, but are instead publicly accessible without authentication to any host able to reach the application server on port 443/tcp.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30038 | Session ID leakage in Zone.Identifier of downloaded files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30038</link><description>The vulnerability consists of a session ID leak when saving a file downloaded from CGM CLININET. The identifier is exposed through a built-in Windows security feature that stores additional metadata in an NTFS alternate data stream (ADS) for all files downloaded from potentially untrusted sources.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30039 | Missing authentication in API returning a list of all active sessions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30039</link><description>Unauthenticated access to the "/cgi-bin/CliniNET.prd/GetActiveSessions.pl" endpoint allows takeover of any user session logged into the system, including users with admin privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30040 | Missing authentication in API returning request logs containing session IDs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30040</link><description>The vulnerability allows unauthenticated users to download a file containing session ID data by directly accessing the "/cgi-bin/CliniNET.prd/utils/userlogxls.pl" endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30041 | Missing authentication in APIs returning statistical data along with session IDs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30041</link><description>The paths "/cgi-bin/CliniNET.prd/utils/userlogstat.pl", "/cgi-bin/CliniNET.prd/utils/usrlogstat.pl", and "/cgi-bin/CliniNET.prd/utils/dblogstat.pl" expose data containing session IDs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30048 | Unauthenticated access to module configuration endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30048</link><description>The "serverConfig" endpoint, which returns the module configuration including credentials, is accessible without authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30055 | Conditional RCE via the &amp;quot;system&amp;quot; function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30055</link><description>The "system" function receives untrusted input from the user. If the "EnableJSCaching" option is enabled, it is possible to execute arbitrary code provided as the "Module" parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30056 | Calling system commands via RunCommand</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30056</link><description>The RunCommand function accepts any parameter, which is then passed for execution in the shell. This allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30057 | Authenticated RCE with uhcapache privileges in ConvertToPDF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30057</link><description>In UHCRTFDoc, the filename parameter can be exploited to execute arbitrary code via command injection into the system() call in the ConvertToPDF function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30058 | SQL injection in getPatientIdentifier function of PatientService.pl</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30058</link><description>In the PatientService.pl service, the "getPatientIdentifier" function is vulnerable to SQL injection through the "pesel" parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30059 | Authenticated SQL injection in PrepareCDExportJSON.pl</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30059</link><description>In the PrepareCDExportJSON.pl service, the "getPerfServiceIds" function is vulnerable to SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30060 | SQL injection in ReturnUserUnitsXML.pl via the UserID parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30060</link><description>In the ReturnUserUnitsXML.pl service, the "getUserInfo" function is vulnerable to SQL injection through the "UserID" parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30061 | SQL injection in utils/Reporter/OpenReportWindow.pl via the UserID parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30061</link><description>In the "utils/Reporter/OpenReportWindow.pl" service, there is an SQL injection vulnerability through the "UserID" parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30063 | Excessive permissions on configuration files containing database logins and passwords</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30063</link><description>The configuration file containing database logins and passwords is readable by any local user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30064 | Possibility to generate a session for any user via the &amp;quot;ex:action&amp;quot; parameter after obtaining access to the JWT key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30064</link><description>An insufficiently secured internal function allows session generation for arbitrary users. The decodeParam function checks the JWT but does not verify which signing algorithm was used. As a result, an attacker can use the "ex:action" parameter in the VerifyUserByThrustedService function to generate a session for any user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4459 | SMA: Directory Traversal in Sunny Boy &amp;lt;3.10.27.R</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4459</link><description>An authorized remote attacker can access files and directories outside the intended web root, potentially exposing sensitive system information of the affected Sunny Boy devices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 08:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9514 | macrozheng mall Registration weak password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9514</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in macrozheng mall up to 1.0.3. This impacts an unknown function of the component Registration. Such manipulation leads to weak password requirements. The attack can be executed remotely. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is said to be difficult. The vendor deleted the GitHub issue for this vulnerability without and explanation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 06:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57797 | Incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability exists in ScanSnap Manager installers versions prior to V6.5L61. If this vulnerability is explo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57797</link><description>Incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability exists in ScanSnap Manager installers versions prior to V6.5L61. If this vulnerability is exploited, an authenticated local attacker may escalate privileges and execute an arbitrary command.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 05:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9511 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System addvisitor.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9511</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /visitor/addvisitor.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 05:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9513 | editso fuso mod.rs PenetrateRsaAndAesHandshake inadequate encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9513</link><description>A flaw has been found in editso fuso up to 1.0.4-beta.7. This affects the function PenetrateRsaAndAesHandshake of the file src/net/penetrate/handshake/mod.rs. This manipulation of the argument priv_key causes inadequate encryption strength. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. A high degree of complexity is needed for the attack. The exploitability is reported as difficult.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 05:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57846 | Multiple i-フィルター products contain an issue with incorrect default permissions. If this vulnerability is exploited, a local authenticated att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57846</link><description>Multiple i-フィルター products contain an issue with incorrect default permissions. If this vulnerability is exploited, a local authenticated attacker may replace a service executable on the system where the product is running, potentially allowing arbitrary code execution with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 05:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48081 | WordPress Printeers Print &amp;amp; Ship plugin &amp;lt;= 1.17.0 - Directory Traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48081</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in Printeers Printeers Print &amp; Ship allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Printeers Print &amp; Ship: from n/a through 1.17.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 05:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9510 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System addbranch.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9510</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /branch/addbranch.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 05:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9508 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System rented_info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9508</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /report/rented_info.php. The manipulation of the argument rsid results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 04:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9509 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System fair_info_all.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9509</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /report/fair_info_all.php. Performing manipulation of the argument fid results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 04:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9506 | Campcodes Online Loan Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9506</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Online Loan Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_plan. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from a remote location. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 04:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9507 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System visitor_info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9507</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /report/visitor_info.php. Executing manipulation of the argument vid can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 04:23:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9504 | Campcodes Online Loan Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9504</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Campcodes Online Loan Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /ajax.php?action=save_plan. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:48:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9505 | Campcodes Online Loan Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9505</link><description>A flaw has been found in Campcodes Online Loan Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /ajax.php?action=save_loan_type. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:48:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49035 | WordPress Admin Menu Groups plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49035</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in chaimchaikin Admin Menu Groups allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Admin Menu Groups: from n/a through 0.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49039 | WordPress Link View plugin &amp;lt;= 0.8.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49039</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in mibuthu Link View allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Link View: from n/a through 0.8.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49040 | WordPress Backup Bolt plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49040</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Backup Bolt allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Backup Bolt: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9503 | Campcodes Online Loan Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9503</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Campcodes Online Loan Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /ajax.php?action=save_borrower. The manipulation of the argument lastname leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:25:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9502 | Campcodes Online Loan Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9502</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Online Loan Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /ajax.php?action=save_payment. Executing manipulation of the argument loan_id can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7732 | Lazy Load for Videos &amp;lt;= 2.18.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via data-video-title and href Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7732</link><description>The Lazy Load for Videos plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via its lazy‑loading handlers in all versions up to, and including, 2.18.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. The plugin’s JavaScript registration handlers read the client‑supplied 'data-video-title' and 'href' attributes, decode HTML entities by default, and pass them directly into DOM sinks without any escaping or validation. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 02:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8490 | All-in-One WP Migration and Backup &amp;lt;= 7.97 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8490</link><description>The All-in-One WP Migration and Backup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Import in all versions up to, and including, 7.97 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 23:27:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21125 | In btif_hh_hsdata_rpt_copy_cb of bta_hh.cc, there is a possible way to corrupt memory due to a use after free. This could lead to local esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21125</link><description>In btif_hh_hsdata_rpt_copy_cb of bta_hh.cc, there is a possible way to corrupt memory due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege over Bluetooth with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49740 | In multiple locations, there is a possible crash loop due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local denial of service with no additio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49740</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible crash loop due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0074 | In process_service_attr_rsp of sdp_discovery.cc, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0074</link><description>In process_service_attr_rsp of sdp_discovery.cc, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0075 | In process_service_search_attr_req of sdp_server.cc, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0075</link><description>In process_service_search_attr_req of sdp_server.cc, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0078 | In main of main.cpp, there is a possible way to bypass SELinux due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0078</link><description>In main of main.cpp, there is a possible way to bypass SELinux due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0079 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way that avdtp and avctp channels could be unencrypted due to a logic error in the code. This cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0079</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way that avdtp and avctp channels could be unencrypted due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0080 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to overlay the installation confirmation dialog due to a tapjacking/overlay attack. This coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0080</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to overlay the installation confirmation dialog due to a tapjacking/overlay attack. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0081 | In dng_lossless_decoder::HuffDecode of dng_lossless_jpeg.cpp, there is a possible way to cause a crash due to uninitialized data. This could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0081</link><description>In dng_lossless_decoder::HuffDecode of dng_lossless_jpeg.cpp, there is a possible way to cause a crash due to uninitialized data. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0082 | In multiple functions of StatusHint.java and TelecomServiceImpl.java, there is a possible way to reveal images across users due to a confuse...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0082</link><description>In multiple functions of StatusHint.java and TelecomServiceImpl.java, there is a possible way to reveal images across users due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0083 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to access content across user profiles due to URI double encoding. This could lead to local i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0083</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to access content across user profiles due to URI double encoding. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0084 | In multiple locations, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a use after free. This could lead to remote code execution over Blueto...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0084</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a use after free. This could lead to remote code execution over Bluetooth, if HFP support is enabled, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0086 | In onResult of AccountManagerService.java, there is a possible way to overwrite auth token due to a missing permission check. This could lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0086</link><description>In onResult of AccountManagerService.java, there is a possible way to overwrite auth token due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0092 | In handleBondStateChanged of AdapterService.java, there is a possible permission bypass due to misleading or insufficient UI. This could lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0092</link><description>In handleBondStateChanged of AdapterService.java, there is a possible permission bypass due to misleading or insufficient UI. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0093 | In handleBondStateChanged of AdapterService.java, there is a possible unapproved data access due to a missing permission check. This could l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0093</link><description>In handleBondStateChanged of AdapterService.java, there is a possible unapproved data access due to a missing permission check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22403 | In sdp_snd_service_search_req of sdp_discovery.cc, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22403</link><description>In sdp_snd_service_search_req of sdp_discovery.cc, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22404 | In avct_lcb_msg_ind of avct_lcb_act.cc, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lead to local ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22404</link><description>In avct_lcb_msg_ind of avct_lcb_act.cc, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22405 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22405</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22406 | In bnepu_check_send_packet of bnep_utils.cc, there is a possible way to achieve code execution due to a use after free. This could lead to l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22406</link><description>In bnepu_check_send_packet of bnep_utils.cc, there is a possible way to achieve code execution due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22407 | In hidd_check_config_done of hidd_conn.cc, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22407</link><description>In hidd_check_config_done of hidd_conn.cc, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22408 | In rfc_check_send_cmd of rfc_utils.cc, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lead to remote ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22408</link><description>In rfc_check_send_cmd of rfc_utils.cc, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22409 | In rfc_send_buf_uih of rfc_ts_frames.cc, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lead to local...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22409</link><description>In rfc_send_buf_uih of rfc_ts_frames.cc, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22410 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22410</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22411 | In process_service_attr_rsp of sdp_discovery.cc, there is a possible use after free due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22411</link><description>In process_service_attr_rsp of sdp_discovery.cc, there is a possible use after free due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22412 | In multiple functions of sdp_server.cc, there is a possible use after free due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to remote (prox...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22412</link><description>In multiple functions of sdp_server.cc, there is a possible use after free due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22413 | In multiple functions of hyp-main.c, there is a possible privilege escalation due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local inf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22413</link><description>In multiple functions of hyp-main.c, there is a possible privilege escalation due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26417 | In checkWhetherCallingAppHasAccess of DownloadProvider.java, there is a possible bypass of user consent when opening files in shared storage...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26417</link><description>In checkWhetherCallingAppHasAccess of DownloadProvider.java, there is a possible bypass of user consent when opening files in shared storage due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57820 | Svelte devalue vulnerable to prototype pollution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57820</link><description>Svelte devalue is a utility library. Prior to version 5.3.2, a string passed to devalue.parse could represent an object with a __proto__ property and devalue.parse does not check that an index is numeric. This could result in assigning prototypes to objects and properties, leading to prototype pollution. This issue has been fixed in version 5.3.2</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35112 | Agiloft XML external entity local path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35112</link><description>Agiloft Release 28 contains an XML External Entities vulnerability in any table that allows 'import/export', allowing an authenticated attacker to import the template file and perform path traversal on the local system files. Users should upgrade to Agiloft Release 31.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:32:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9277 | SiteSEO – SEO Simplified &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Broken Regex Expression</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9277</link><description>The SiteSEO – SEO Simplified plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the broken preg_replace expression in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:32:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35113 | Agiloft improper neutralization in EUI template engine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35113</link><description>Agiloft Release 28 does not properly neutralize special elements used in an EUI template engine, allowing an authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution by loading a specially crafted payload. Users should upgrade to Agiloft Release 31.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35114 | Agiloft local privilege escalation via default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35114</link><description>Agiloft Release 28 contains several accounts with default credentials that could allow local privilege escalation. The password hash is known for at least one of the accounts and the credentials could be cracked offline. Users should upgrade to Agiloft Release 30.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35115 | Agiloft insecure download of system packages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35115</link><description>Agiloft Release 28 downloads critical system packages over an insecure HTTP connection. An attacker in a Man-In-the-Middle position could replace or modify the contents of the download URL. Users should upgrade to Agiloft Release 30.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9492 | Campcodes Online Water Billing System addclient1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9492</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Campcodes Online Water Billing System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /addclient1.php. Executing manipulation of the argument lname can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35203 | Mahara before 22.10.6, 23.04.6, and 24.04.1 allows cross-site scripting (XSS) via a file, with JavaScript code as part of its name, that is ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35203</link><description>Mahara before 22.10.6, 23.04.6, and 24.04.1 allows cross-site scripting (XSS) via a file, with JavaScript code as part of its name, that is uploaded via the Mahara filebrowser system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47192 | An issue was discovered in Mahara 23.04.8 and 24.04.4. The use of a malicious export download URL can allow an attacker to download files th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47192</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mahara 23.04.8 and 24.04.4. The use of a malicious export download URL can allow an attacker to download files that they do not have permission to download.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52353 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability in Badaso CMS 2.9.11. The Media Manager allows authenticated users to upload files containing embe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52353</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability in Badaso CMS 2.9.11. The Media Manager allows authenticated users to upload files containing embedded PHP code via the file-upload endpoint, bypassing content-type validation. When such a file is accessed via its URL, the server executes the PHP payload, enabling an attacker to run arbitrary system commands and achieve full compromise of the underlying host. This has been demonstrated by embedding a backdoor within a PDF and renaming it with a .php extension.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55443 | Telpo MDM 1.4.6 thru 1.4.9 for Android contains sensitive administrator credentials and MQTT server connection details (IP/port) that are st...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55443</link><description>Telpo MDM 1.4.6 thru 1.4.9 for Android contains sensitive administrator credentials and MQTT server connection details (IP/port) that are stored in plaintext within log files on the device's external storage. This allows attackers with access to these logs to: 1. Authenticate to the MDM web platform to execute administrative operations (device shutdown/factory reset/software installation); 2. Connect to the MQTT server to intercept/publish device data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50971 | Directory traversal vulnerability in AbanteCart version 1.4.2 allows unauthenticated attackers to gain access to sensitive system files via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50971</link><description>Directory traversal vulnerability in AbanteCart version 1.4.2 allows unauthenticated attackers to gain access to sensitive system files via the template parameter to index.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50975 | IPFire 2.29 web-based firewall interface (firewall.cgi) fails to sanitize several rule parameters such as PROT, SRC_PORT, TGT_PORT, dnatport...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50975</link><description>IPFire 2.29 web-based firewall interface (firewall.cgi) fails to sanitize several rule parameters such as PROT, SRC_PORT, TGT_PORT, dnatport, key, ruleremark, src_addr, std_net_tgt, and tgt_addr, allowing an authenticated administrator to inject persistent JavaScript. This stored XSS payload is executed whenever another admin views the firewall rules page, enabling session hijacking, unauthorized actions within the interface, or further internal pivoting. Exploitation requires only high-privilege GUI access, and the complexity of the attack is low.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:11:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9478 | Use after free in ANGLE in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.154 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9478</link><description>Use after free in ANGLE in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.154 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Critical)</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23307 | NVIDIA NeMo Curator for all platforms contains a vulnerability where a malicious file created by an attacker could allow code injection. A s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23307</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Curator for all platforms contains a vulnerability where a malicious file created by an attacker could allow code injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 18:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23312 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the retrieval services component, where malicious data created by an att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23312</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the retrieval services component, where malicious data created by an attacker could cause a code injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 18:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23313 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the NLP component, where malicious data created by an attacker could cau...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23313</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the NLP component, where malicious data created by an attacker could cause a code injection issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 18:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23314 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the NLP component, where malicious data created by an attacker could cau...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23314</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the NLP component, where malicious data created by an attacker could cause a code injection issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 18:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23315 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the export and deploy component, where malicious data created by an atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23315</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the export and deploy component, where malicious data created by an attacker could cause a code injection issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 18:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57818 | Firecrawl SSRF Vulnerability via malicious webhook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57818</link><description>Firecrawl turns entire websites into LLM-ready markdown or structured data. Prior to version 2.0.1, a server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability was discovered in Firecrawl's webhook functionality. Authenticated users could configure a webhook to an internal URL and send POST requests with arbitrary headers, which may have allowed access to internal systems. This has been fixed in version 2.0.1. If upgrading is not possible, it is recommend to isolate Firecrawl from any sensitive internal systems.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 18:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50976 | IPFire 2.29 DNS management interface (dns.cgi) fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input in the NAMESERVER, REMARK, and TLS_HOSTNAME qu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50976</link><description>IPFire 2.29 DNS management interface (dns.cgi) fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input in the NAMESERVER, REMARK, and TLS_HOSTNAME query parameters, resulting in a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55298 | ImageMagick Format String Bug in InterpretImageFilename leads to arbitrary code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55298</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to ImageMagick versions 6.9.13-28 and 7.1.2-2, a format string bug vulnerability exists in InterpretImageFilename function where user input is directly passed to FormatLocaleString without proper sanitization. An attacker can overwrite arbitrary memory regions, enabling a wide range of attacks from heap overflow to remote code execution. This issue has been patched in versions 6.9.13-28 and 7.1.2-2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57803 | ImageMagick (WriteBMPImage): 32-bit integer overflow when writing BMP scanline stride → heap buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57803</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 6.9.13-28 and 7.1.2-2 for ImageMagick's 32-bit build, a 32-bit integer overflow in the BMP encoder’s scanline-stride computation collapses bytes_per_line (stride) to a tiny value while the per-row writer still emits 3 × width bytes for 24-bpp images. The row base pointer advances using the (overflowed) stride, so the first row immediately writes past its slot and into adjacent heap memory with attacker-controlled bytes. This is a classic, powerful primitive for heap corruption in common auto-convert pipelines. This issue has been patched in versions 6.9.13-28 and 7.1.2-2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50974 | The Calamaris log exporter CGI (/cgi-bin/logs.cgi/calamaris.dat) in IPFire 2.29 does not properly sanitize user-supplied input before incorp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50974</link><description>The Calamaris log exporter CGI (/cgi-bin/logs.cgi/calamaris.dat) in IPFire 2.29 does not properly sanitize user-supplied input before incorporating parameter values into a shell command. An unauthenticated remote attacker can inject arbitrary OS commands by embedding shell metacharacters in any of the following parameters BYTE_UNIT, DAY_BEGIN, DAY_END, HIST_LEVEL, MONTH_BEGIN, MONTH_END, NUM_CONTENT, NUM_DOMAINS, NUM_HOSTS, NUM_URLS, PERF_INTERVAL, YEAR_BEGIN, YEAR_END.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1494 | IBM Cognos Command Center clickjacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1494</link><description>IBM Cognos Command Center 10.2.4.1 and 10.2.5 could allow a remote attacker to hijack the clicking action of the victim. By persuading a victim to visit a malicious Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to hijack the victim's click actions and possibly launch further attacks against the victim.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1994 | IBM Cognos Command Center code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1994</link><description>IBM Cognos Command Center 10.2.4.1 and 10.2.5 



could allow a local user to execute arbitrary code on the system due to the use of unsafe use of the BinaryFormatter function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2697 | IBM Cognos Command Center HTTP Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2697</link><description>IBM Cognos Command Center 10.2.4.1 and 10.2.5 

could allow a remote attacker to conduct phishing attacks, using an open redirect attack. By persuading a victim to visit a specially crafted Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to spoof the URL displayed to redirect a user to a malicious Web site that would appear to be trusted. This could allow the attacker to obtain highly sensitive information or conduct further attacks against the victim.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52184 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Helpy.io v.2.8.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the New Topic Ticket funtion.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52184</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Helpy.io v.2.8.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the New Topic Ticket funtion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55212 | ImageMagick affected by divide-by-zero in ThumbnailImage via montage -geometry &amp;quot;:&amp;quot; leads to crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55212</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 6.9.13-28 and 7.1.2-2, passing a geometry string containing only a colon (":") to montage -geometry leads GetGeometry() to set width/height to 0. Later, ThumbnailImage() divides by these zero dimensions, triggering a crash (SIGFPE/abort), resulting in a denial of service. This issue has been patched in versions 6.9.13-28 and 7.1.2-2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36729 | RACOM M!DGE2 Privilege Escalation via SDK Testing Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36729</link><description>A non-primary administrator user with admin rights to the web interface but without shell access permissions can display configuration of the device including the master admin password. This vulnerability also allows the user to give themselves shell access with the root gid.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9491 | Microsoft Windows LNK File UI Misrepresentation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9491</link><description>Microsoft Windows LNK File UI Misrepresentation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Microsoft Windows. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of .LNK files. Crafted data in an .LNK file can cause hazardous content in the file to be invisible to a user who inspects the file via the Windows-provided user interface. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-25373.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57425 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SourceCodester FAQ Management System 1.0 allows an authenticated attacker to inject mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57425</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SourceCodester FAQ Management System 1.0 allows an authenticated attacker to inject malicious JavaScript into the 'question' and 'answer' fields via the update-faq.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57813 | Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File in github.com/traPtitech/traQ</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57813</link><description>traQ is a messenger application built for Digital Creators Club traP. Prior to version 3.25.0, a vulnerability exists where sensitive information, such as OAuth tokens, are recorded in log files when an error occurs during the execution of an SQL query. An attacker could intentionally trigger an SQL error by methods such as placing a high load on the database. This could allow an attacker who has the authority to view the log files to illicitly acquire the recorded sensitive information. This vulnerability has been patched in version 3.25.0. If upgrading is not possible, a temporary workaround involves reviewing access permissions for SQL error logs and strictly limiting access to prevent unauthorized users from viewing them.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57810 | jsPDF Parsing of Corrupt PNGs Leads to Potential Denial of Service (DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57810</link><description>jsPDF is a library to generate PDFs in JavaScript. Prior to 3.0.2, user control of the first argument of the addImage method results in CPU utilization and denial of service. If given the possibility to pass unsanitized image data or URLs to the addImage method, a user can provide a harmful PNG file that results in high CPU utilization and denial of service. The vulnerability was fixed in jsPDF 3.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56432 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Nagios XI 2024R2. The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaSc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56432</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Nagios XI 2024R2. The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of a logged-in user's session via a specially crafted URL. The issue resides in a web component responsible for rendering performance-related data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:37:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25732 | Incorrect access control in the EEPROM component of Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25732</link><description>Incorrect access control in the EEPROM component of Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 allows attackers to replace password hashes stored in the EEPROM with hashes of their own, leading to the escalation of privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:57:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25733 | Incorrect access control in the SPI Flash Chip of Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25733</link><description>Incorrect access control in the SPI Flash Chip of Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 allows physically proximate attackers to arbitrarily modify SPI flash regions, leading to a degradation of the security posture of the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:57:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25734 | Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 was discovered to contain an u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25734</link><description>Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 was discovered to contain an unauthenticated EFI shell which allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or escalate privileges during the boot process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25735 | Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 were discovered to lack SPI Pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25735</link><description>Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 were discovered to lack SPI Protected Range Registers (PRRs), allowing attackers with software running on the system to modify SPI flash in real-time.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25736 | Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9260 RSU LEO v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 were discovered to contain Android Debug Bridge (ADB) p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25736</link><description>Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9260 RSU LEO v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 were discovered to contain Android Debug Bridge (ADB) pre-installed (/mnt/c3platpersistent/opt/platform-tools/adb) and enabled by default, allowing unauthenticated root shell access to the cellular modem via the default 'kapsch' user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25737 | Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 were discovered to lack secure...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25737</link><description>Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 were discovered to lack secure password requirements for its BIOS Supervisor and User accounts, allowing attackers to bypass authentication via a bruteforce attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52037 | A vulnerability has been found in NotesCMS and classified as medium. Affected by this vulnerability is the page /index.php?route=sites. The ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52037</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in NotesCMS and classified as medium. Affected by this vulnerability is the page /index.php?route=sites. The manipulation of the title of the service descriptions leads to a stored XSS vulnerability. The issue was confirmed to be present in the source code as of commit 7d821a0f028b0778b245b99ab3d3bff1ac10e2d3 (dated 2024-05-08), and was fixed in commit 95322c5121dbd7070f3bd54f2848079654a0a8ea (dated 2025-03-31). The attack can be launched remotely. CWE Definition of the Vulnerability: CWE-79.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:49:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52035 | A vulnerability in NotesCMS and specifically in the page /index.php?route=notes. The manipulation of the title of the service descriptions l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52035</link><description>A vulnerability in NotesCMS and specifically in the page /index.php?route=notes. The manipulation of the title of the service descriptions leads to a stored XSS vulnerability. The issue was confirmed to be present in the source code as of commit 7d821a0f028b0778b245b99ab3d3bff1ac10e2d3 (dated 2024-05-08) and was fixed in commit 95322c5121dbd7070f3bd54f2848079654a0a8ea (dated 2025-03-31). The attack can be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52036 | A vulnerability has been found in NotesCMS and classified as medium. Affected by this vulnerability is the page /index.php?route=categories....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52036</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in NotesCMS and classified as medium. Affected by this vulnerability is the page /index.php?route=categories. The manipulation of the title of the service descriptions leads to a stored XSS vulnerability. The issue was confirmed to be present in the source code as of commit 7d821a0f028b0778b245b99ab3d3bff1ac10e2d3 (dated 2024-05-08), and was fixed in commit 95322c5121dbd7070f3bd54f2848079654a0a8ea (dated 2025-03-31). The attack can be launched remotely. CWE Definition of the Vulnerability: CWE-79.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6366 | Event List &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6366</link><description>The Event List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.4. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's capabilities prior to updating their profile in the el_update_profile() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change their capabilities to those of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39335 | Supported versions of Mahara 24.04 before 24.04.1 and 23.04 before 23.04.6 are vulnerable to information being disclosed to an institution a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39335</link><description>Supported versions of Mahara 24.04 before 24.04.1 and 23.04 before 23.04.6 are vulnerable to information being disclosed to an institution administrator under certain conditions via the 'Current submissions' page: Administration -&gt; Groups -&gt; Submissions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52217 | SelectZero Data Observability Platform before 2025.5.2 is vulnerable to HTML Injection. Legacy UI fields improperly handle user-supplied inp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52217</link><description>SelectZero Data Observability Platform before 2025.5.2 is vulnerable to HTML Injection. Legacy UI fields improperly handle user-supplied input, allowing injection of arbitrary HTML.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52218 | SelectZero Data Observability Platform before 2025.5.2 is vulnerable to Content Spoofing / Text Injection. Improper sanitization of unspecif...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52218</link><description>SelectZero Data Observability Platform before 2025.5.2 is vulnerable to Content Spoofing / Text Injection. Improper sanitization of unspecified parameters allows attackers to inject arbitrary text or limited HTML into the login page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52219 | SelectZero SelectZero Data Observability Platform before 2025.5.2 contains an Open Redirect vulnerability. Legacy UI fields can be used to c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52219</link><description>SelectZero SelectZero Data Observability Platform before 2025.5.2 contains an Open Redirect vulnerability. Legacy UI fields can be used to create arbitrary external links via HTML Injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29992 | Mahara before 24.04.9 exposes database connection information if the database becomes unreachable, e.g., due to the database server being te...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29992</link><description>Mahara before 24.04.9 exposes database connection information if the database becomes unreachable, e.g., due to the database server being temporarily down or too busy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45753 | In Mahara 23.04.8 and 24.04.4, the external RSS feed block can cause XSS if the external feed XML has a malicious value for the link attribu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45753</link><description>In Mahara 23.04.8 and 24.04.4, the external RSS feed block can cause XSS if the external feed XML has a malicious value for the link attribute.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:16:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47853 | An issue was discovered in Mahara 23.04.8 and 24.04.4. Attackers may utilize escalation of privileges in certain cases when logging into Mah...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47853</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mahara 23.04.8 and 24.04.4. Attackers may utilize escalation of privileges in certain cases when logging into Mahara with Learning Tools Interoperability (LTI).</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9483 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 singlePortForwardAdd stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9483</link><description>A flaw has been found in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. Affected is the function singlePortForwardAdd of the file /goform/singlePortForwardAdd. This manipulation of the argument ruleName/schedule/inboundFilter causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55526 | n8n-workflows Main Commit ee25413 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal via the download_workflow function within api_server.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55526</link><description>n8n-workflows Main Commit ee25413 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal via the download_workflow function within api_server.py</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50753 | Mitrastar GPT-2741GNAC-N2 devices are provided with access through ssh into a restricted default shell.The command "deviceinfo show file" is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50753</link><description>Mitrastar GPT-2741GNAC-N2 devices are provided with access through ssh into a restricted default shell.The command "deviceinfo show file" is supposed to be used from restricted shell to show files and directories. By providing " /bin/sh" (quotes included) to the argument of this command will drop a root shell.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9481 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 setIpv6 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9481</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This affects the function setIpv6 of the file /goform/setIpv6. The manipulation of the argument tunrd_Prefix leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9482 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 portRangeForwardAdd stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9482</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This impacts the function portRangeForwardAdd of the file /goform/portRangeForwardAdd. The manipulation of the argument ruleName/schedule/inboundFilter/TCPPorts/UDPPorts results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8424 | Improper access control on the NetScaler Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8424</link><description>Improper access control on the NetScaler Management Interface in NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway when an attacker can get access to the appliance NSIP, Cluster Management IP or local GSLB Site IP or SNIP with Management Access</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38676 | iommu/amd: Avoid stack buffer overflow from kernel cmdline</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38676</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

iommu/amd: Avoid stack buffer overflow from kernel cmdline

While the kernel command line is considered trusted in most environments,
avoid writing 1 byte past the end of "acpiid" if the "str" argument is
maximum length.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7775 | Memory overflow vulnerability leading to Remote Code Execution and/or Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7775</link><description>Memory overflow vulnerability leading to Remote Code Execution and/or Denial of Service in NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway when NetScaler is configured as Gateway (VPN virtual server, ICA Proxy, CVPN, RDP Proxy) or AAA virtual server

(OR)

NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway 13.1, 14.1, 13.1-FIPS and NDcPP: LB virtual servers of type (HTTP, SSL or HTTP_QUIC) bound with IPv6 services or servicegroups bound with IPv6 servers 

(OR)

NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway 13.1, 14.1, 13.1-FIPS and NDcPP: LB virtual servers of type (HTTP, SSL or HTTP_QUIC) bound with DBS IPv6 services or servicegroups bound with IPv6 DBS servers

(OR)

CR virtual server with type HDX</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7776 | Memory overflow vulnerability leading to unpredictable or erroneous behavior and Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7776</link><description>Memory overflow vulnerability leading to unpredictable or erroneous behavior and Denial of Service in NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway when NetScaler is configured as a Gateway (VPN virtual server, ICA Proxy, CVPN, RDP Proxy) with PCoIP Profile bounded to it</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53811 | TCC Bypass via misconfigured Node fuses in Mosh-Pro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53811</link><description>The configuration of Mosh-Pro on macOS, specifically the "RunAsNode" fuse enabled, allows a local attacker with unprivileged access to execute arbitrary code that inherits Mosh-Pro TCC (Transparency, Consent, and Control) permissions. 
Acquired resource access is limited to previously granted permissions by the user. Accessing other resources beyond previously granted TCC permissions will prompt the user for approval in the name of Mosh-Pro, potentially disguising attacker's malicious intent. 

This issue was detected in 1.3.2 version of Mosh-Pro. Since authors did not respond to messages from CNA, patching status is unknown.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53813 | TCC Bypass via misconfigured Node fuses in Nozbe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53813</link><description>The configuration of Nozbe on macOS, specifically the "RunAsNode" fuse enabled, allows a local attacker with unprivileged access to execute arbitrary code that inherits Nozbe TCC (Transparency, Consent, and Control) permissions. 
Acquired resource access is limited to previously granted permissions by the user. Access to other resources beyond granted-permissions requires user interaction with a system prompt asking for permission.

This issue was fixed in version 2025.11 of Nozbe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8597 | Privilege Escalation via get-task-allow entitlement in MacVim.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8597</link><description>MacVim's configuration on macOS, specifically the presence of entitlement "com.apple.security.get-task-allow", allows local attackers with unprivileged access (e.g. via a malicious application) to attach a debugger, read or modify the process memory, inject code in the application's context despite being signed with Hardened Runtime and bypass Transparency, Consent, and Control (TCC). Acquired resource access is limited to previously granted permissions by the user. Access to other resources beyond granted permissions requires user interaction with a system prompt asking for permission.

According to Apple documentation, when a non-root user runs an app with the debugging tool entitlement, the system presents an authorization dialog asking for a system administrator's credentials. Since there is no prompt when the target process has "get-task-allow" entitlement, the presence of this entitlement was decided to be treated as a vulnerability because it removes one step needed to perform an attack.


This issue was fixed in build r181.2</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8700 | Privilege Escalation via get-task-allow entitlement in Invoice Ninja</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8700</link><description>Invoice Ninja's configuration on macOS, specifically the presence of entitlement "com.apple.security.get-task-allow", allows local attackers with unprivileged access (e.g. via a malicious application) to attach a debugger, read or modify the process memory, inject code in the application's context despite being signed with Hardened Runtime and bypass Transparency, Consent, and Control (TCC). Acquired resource access is limited to previously granted permissions by the user. Access to other resources beyond granted permissions requires user interaction with a system prompt asking for permission.

According to Apple documentation, when a non-root user runs an app with the debugging tool entitlement, the system presents an authorization dialog asking for a system administrator's credentials. Since there is no prompt when the target process has "get-task-allow" entitlement, the presence of this entitlement was decided to be treated as a vulnerability because it removes one step needed to perform an attack.


This issue was fixed in version 5.0.175</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9190 | TCC Bypass via misconfigured Node fuses in Cursor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9190</link><description>The configuration of Cursor on macOS, specifically the "RunAsNode" fuse enabled, allows a local attacker with unprivileged access to execute arbitrary code that inherits Cursor TCC (Transparency, Consent, and Control) permissions. 
Acquired resource access is limited to previously granted permissions by the user. Accessing other resources beyond previously granted TCC permissions will prompt the user for approval in the name of Cursor, potentially disguising attacker's malicious intent. 

This issue was detected in 15.4.1 version of Cursor. Project maintainers decided not to fix this issue, because a scenario including a local attacker falls outside their defined threat model.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44002 | Arbitrary File Creation via Symbolic Link leading to Denial-of-Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44002</link><description>Race Condition in the Directory Validation Logic in the TeamViewer Full Client and Host prior version 15.69 on Windows allows a local non-admin user to create arbitrary files with SYSTEM privileges, potentially leading to a denial-of-service condition, via symbolic link manipulation during directory verification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 11:29:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1501 | Incorrect authorization for traces request/download in CMC before 25.1.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1501</link><description>An access control vulnerability was discovered in the Request Trace and Download Trace functionalities of CMC before 25.1.0 due to a specific access restriction not being properly enforced for users with limited privileges. An authenticated user with limited privileges can request and download trace files due to improper access restrictions, potentially exposing unauthorized network data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48108 | WordPress School Management Plugin &amp;lt;= 93.2.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48108</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mojoomla School Management allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects School Management: from n/a through 93.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 09:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29901 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29901</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4933 and later</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 09:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6247 | WordPress Automatic Plugin - AI content generator and auto poster plugin &amp;lt;= 3.118.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6247</link><description>The WordPress Automatic Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.118.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on one of its functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update campaigns and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 09:23:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8860 | Tourfic &amp;lt;= 2.14.5 - Missing Authorization in Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8860</link><description>The Tourfic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the tf_order_status_email_resend_function,  tf_visitor_details_edit_function, tf_checkinout_details_edit_function, tf_order_status_edit_function, tf_order_bulk_action_edit_function, tf_remove_room_order_ids, and tf_delete_old_review_fields functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.14.5. This makes it possible for authenticated  attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to resend order status emails, update visitor/order details, edit check-in/out details, edit order status, perform bulk order status updates, remove room order IDs, and delete old review fields, respectively.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 07:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53419 | COMMGR Code Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53419</link><description>Delta Electronics COMMGR has Code Injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 07:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53418 | COMMGR Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53418</link><description>Delta Electronics COMMGR has Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 07:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57704 | EIP Builder XML External Entity Processing Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57704</link><description>Delta Electronics EIP Builder version 1.11 is vulnerable to a File Parsing XML External Entity Processing Information Disclosure Vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 06:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41702 | egOS WebGUI Hard-Coded JWT Secret Enables Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41702</link><description>The JWT secret key is embedded in the egOS WebGUI backend and is readable to the default user. An unauthenticated remote attacker can generate valid HS256 tokens and bypass authentication/authorization due to the use of hard-coded cryptographic key.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 06:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9476 | SourceCodester Human Resource Information System editemployee_process.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9476</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Human Resource Information System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Superadmin_Dashboard/process/editemployee_process.php. Such manipulation of the argument employee_file201 leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 06:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9475 | SourceCodester Human Resource Information System editemployee_process.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9475</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Human Resource Information System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Admin_Dashboard/process/editemployee_process.php. This manipulation of the argument employee_file201 causes unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5931 | Dokan Pro &amp;lt;= 4.0.5 - Authenticated (Vendor+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5931</link><description>The Dokan Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.5. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their password during a staff password reset. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with vendor-level access and above, to elevate their privilege to the level of a staff member and then change arbitrary user passwords, including those of administrators in order to gain access to their accounts. By default, the plugin allows customers to become vendors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9473 | SourceCodester Online Bank Management System feedback.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9473</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SourceCodester Online Bank Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /feedback.php. The manipulation of the argument msg leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9474 | Mihomo Party Socket sysproxy.ts enableSysProxy temp file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9474</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Mihomo Party up to 1.8.1 on macOS. Affected is the function enableSysProxy of the file src/main/sys/sysproxy.ts of the component Socket Handler. The manipulation results in creation of temporary file with insecure permissions. The attack requires a local approach. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9472 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System add_owner_utility.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9472</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /owner_utility/add_owner_utility.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9470 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System add_m_committee.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9470</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /management/add_m_committee.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:17:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9471 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System add_maintenance_cost.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9471</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /maintenance/add_maintenance_cost.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:17:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9172 | Vibes &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via `resource` Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9172</link><description>The Vibes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘resource’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9468 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System add_bill.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9468</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /bill/add_bill.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9469 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System add_fund.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9469</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /fund/add_fund.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9444 | 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System delete_group_student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9444</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/controller/delete_group_student.php. The manipulation of the argument batch_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9461 | diyhi bbs File Compression FilePackageManageAction.java information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9461</link><description>A weakness has been identified in diyhi bbs up to 6.8. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file src/main/java/cms/web/action/filePackage/FilePackageManageAction.java of the component File Compression Handler. This manipulation of the argument idGroup causes information disclosure. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9443 | Tenda CH22 editUserName formeditUserName buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9443</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda CH22 1.0.0.1. This vulnerability affects the function formeditUserName of the file /goform/editUserName. Executing manipulation of the argument new_account can lead to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8447 | Incorrect authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed read-only access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8447</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed users with access to any repository to retrieve limited code content from another repository by creating a diff between the repositories. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker needed to know the name of a private repository along with its branches, tags, or commit SHAs that they could use to trigger compare/diff functionality and retrieve limited code without proper authorization. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.18, and was fixed in versions 3.14.17, 3.15.12, 3.16.8 and 3.17.5. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9438 | 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System add_student.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9438</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/add_student.php. The manipulation of the argument address results in cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9439 | 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System edit_faculty.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9439</link><description>A weakness has been identified in 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /rse/admin/edit_faculty.php?id=2. This manipulation of the argument Name causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9440 | 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System add_title.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9440</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/add_title.php. Such manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from a remote location. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9433 | mtons mblog Admin Panel list cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9433</link><description>A vulnerability was found in mtons mblog up to 3.5.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/user/list of the component Admin Panel. Performing manipulation of the argument Name results in cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:23:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9434 | 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System edit_title.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9434</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_title.php?id=1. Executing manipulation of the argument desc can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9432 | mtons mblog Admin Panel list cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9432</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in mtons mblog up to 3.5.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/post/list of the component Admin Panel. Such manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9430 | mtons mblog update cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9430</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in mtons mblog up to 3.5.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/options/update. The manipulation of the argument input results in cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9431 | mtons mblog search cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9431</link><description>A flaw has been found in mtons mblog up to 3.5.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /search. This manipulation of the argument kw causes cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>