<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 06:58:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-10786 | Campcodes Grocery Sales and Inventory System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10786</link><description>A flaw has been found in Campcodes Grocery Sales and Inventory System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_user. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 06:58:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10785 | Campcodes Grocery Sales and Inventory System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10785</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Campcodes Grocery Sales and Inventory System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 06:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9115 | Etsy Shop &amp;lt; 3.0.7 - Reflected XSS via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;REQUEST_URI&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9115</link><description>The Etsy Shop WordPress plugin before 3.0.7 does not escape the $_SERVER['REQUEST_URI'] parameter before outputting it back in an attribute, which could lead to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in old web browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 06:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9487 | Admin and Site Enhancements &amp;lt; 7.9.8 - Authenticated Stored XSS via SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9487</link><description>The Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) WordPress plugin before 7.9.8 does not sanitise SVG files when uploaded via xmlrpc.php when such uploads are enabled, which could allow users to upload a malicious SVG containing XSS payloads</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 06:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9540 | Markup Markdown &amp;lt; 3.20.10 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9540</link><description>The Markup Markdown WordPress plugin before 3.20.10 allows links to contain JavaScript which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 06:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9541 | Markup Markdown &amp;lt; 3.20.10 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9541</link><description>The Markup Markdown WordPress plugin before 3.20.10 allows links to contain JavaScript which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 06:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10784 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System edit_subject.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10784</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit_subject.php. The manipulation of the argument subject_code leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 05:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10783 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System add_subject.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10783</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/add_subject.php. Executing manipulation of the argument subject_code can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 05:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10782 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System class.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10782</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/class.php. Performing manipulation of the argument class_name results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 04:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10781 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System edit_class.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10781</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_class.php. Such manipulation of the argument class_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 04:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10780 | CodeAstro Simple Pharmacy Management view.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10780</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in CodeAstro Simple Pharmacy Management 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /view.php. This manipulation of the argument bar_code causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 03:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59798 | Artifex Ghostscript through 10.05.1 has a stack-based buffer overflow in pdf_write_cmap in devices/vector/gdevpdtw.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59798</link><description>Artifex Ghostscript through 10.05.1 has a stack-based buffer overflow in pdf_write_cmap in devices/vector/gdevpdtw.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 03:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10779 | D-Link DCS-935L HNAP1 sub_402280 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10779</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DCS-935L up to 1.13.01. The impacted element is the function sub_402280 of the file /HNAP1/. The manipulation of the argument HNAP_AUTH/SOAPAction results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 03:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59799 | Artifex Ghostscript through 10.05.1 has a stack-based buffer overflow in pdfmark_coerce_dest in devices/vector/gdevpdfm.c via a large size v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59799</link><description>Artifex Ghostscript through 10.05.1 has a stack-based buffer overflow in pdfmark_coerce_dest in devices/vector/gdevpdfm.c via a large size value.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 03:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59800 | In Artifex Ghostscript through 10.05.1, ocr_begin_page in devices/gdevpdfocr.c has an integer overflow that leads to a heap-based buffer ove...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59800</link><description>In Artifex Ghostscript through 10.05.1, ocr_begin_page in devices/gdevpdfocr.c has an integer overflow that leads to a heap-based buffer overflow in ocr_line8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 03:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59801 | In Artifex GhostXPS before 10.06.0, there is a stack-based buffer overflow in xps_unpredict_tiff in xpstiff.c because the samplesperpixel va...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59801</link><description>In Artifex GhostXPS before 10.06.0, there is a stack-based buffer overflow in xps_unpredict_tiff in xpstiff.c because the samplesperpixel value is not checked.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 03:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10778 | Smartstore Gift Voucher confirm race condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10778</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Smartstore up to 6.2.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /checkout/confirm/ of the component Gift Voucher Handler. The manipulation leads to race condition. The attack may be initiated remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is described as difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 03:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10777 | JSC R7 R7-Office Document Server downloadas path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10777</link><description>A flaw has been found in JSC R7 R7-Office Document Server up to 20250820. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /downloadas/. Executing manipulation of the argument cmd can lead to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 2025.3.1.923 is recommended to address this issue. The affected component should be upgraded. R7-Office is a fork of OpenOffice and at the moment it remains unclear if OpenOffice is affected as well. The OpenOffice team was not able to reproduce the issue in their codebase. The vendor replied: "We confirm that this vulnerability has been verified and patched in release 2025.3.1.923. During our security testing, it was not possible to exploit the issue - the server consistently returns proper error responses to the provided scenarios."</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 03:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10776 | LionCoders SalePro POS Login cleartext transmission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10776</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in LionCoders SalePro POS up to 5.5.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Login. Performing manipulation results in cleartext transmission of sensitive information. The attack can be initiated remotely. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 01:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10775 | Wavlink WL-NU516U1 login.cgi sub_4012A0 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10775</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Wavlink WL-NU516U1 240425. This vulnerability affects the function sub_4012A0 of the file /cgi-bin/login.cgi. Such manipulation of the argument ipaddr leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 01:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10773 | B-Link BL-AC2100 Web Management set_delshrpath_cfg delshrpath stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10773</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in B-Link BL-AC2100 up to 1.0.3. Affected by this issue is the function delshrpath of the file /goform/set_delshrpath_cfg of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument Type results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 01:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10774 | Ruijie 6000-E10 sub_commit.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10774</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Ruijie 6000-E10 up to 2.4.3.6-20171117. This affects an unknown part of the file /view/vpn/autovpn/sub_commit.php. This manipulation of the argument key causes os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 01:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10772 | huggingface LeRobot ZeroMQ Socket lekiwi_remote.py missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10772</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in huggingface LeRobot up to 0.3.3. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file lerobot/common/robot_devices/robots/lekiwi_remote.py of the component ZeroMQ Socket Handler. The manipulation leads to missing authentication. The attack can only be initiated within the local network. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10771 | jeecgboot JimuReport DB2 JDBC testConnection deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10771</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in jeecgboot JimuReport up to 2.1.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file /drag/onlDragDataSource/testConnection of the component DB2 JDBC Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument clientRerouteServerListJNDIName can lead to deserialization. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10770 | jeecgboot JimuReport MySQL JDBC testConnection deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10770</link><description>A vulnerability was found in jeecgboot JimuReport up to 2.1.2. This impacts an unknown function of the file /drag/onlDragDataSource/testConnection of the component MySQL JDBC Handler. Performing manipulation results in deserialization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 22:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10767 | CosmodiumCS OnlyRAT Configuration File main.py remote_download os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10767</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in CosmodiumCS OnlyRAT up to 3.2. The affected element is the function connect/remote_upload/remote_download of the file main.py of the component Configuration File Handler. The manipulation of the argument configuration["PASSWORD"] results in os command injection. The attack requires a local approach. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 22:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53692 | Sitecore Experience Platform Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53692</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sitecore Sitecore Experience Manager (XM), Sitecore Experience Platform (XP) allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Sitecore Experience Manager (XM): from 9.2 through 10.4; Experience Platform (XP): from 9.2 through 10.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10768 | h2oai h2o-3 IBMDB2 JDBC Driver ImportSQLTable deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10768</link><description>A flaw has been found in h2oai h2o-3 up to 3.46.08. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /99/ImportSQLTable of the component IBMDB2 JDBC Driver. This manipulation of the argument connection_url causes deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 09:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10769 | h2oai h2o-3 H2 JDBC Driver ImportSQLTable deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10769</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in h2oai h2o-3 up to 3.46.08. This affects an unknown function of the file /99/ImportSQLTable of the component H2 JDBC Driver. Such manipulation of the argument connection_url leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 09:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6544 | Deserialization Vulnerability in h2oai/h2o-3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6544</link><description>A deserialization vulnerability exists in h2oai/h2o-3 versions &lt;= 3.46.0.8, allowing attackers to read arbitrary system files and execute arbitrary code. The vulnerability arises from improper handling of JDBC connection parameters, which can be exploited by bypassing regular expression checks and using double URL encoding. This issue impacts all users of the affected versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 09:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10766 | SeriaWei ZKEACMS EventViewerController.cs Download path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10766</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SeriaWei ZKEACMS up to 4.3. This issue affects the function Download of the file EventViewerController.cs. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 07:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10765 | SeriaWei ZKEACMS SEOSuggestions ZKEACMS.SEOSuggestions.dll server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10765</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in SeriaWei ZKEACMS up to 4.3. This vulnerability affects the function CheckPage/Suggestions in the library cms-v4.3\wwwroot\Plugins\ZKEACMS.SEOSuggestions\ZKEACMS.SEOSuggestions.dll of the component SEOSuggestions. Performing manipulation results in server-side request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 06:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10764 | SeriaWei ZKEACMS Event Action System PendingTaskController.cs Edit server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10764</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SeriaWei ZKEACMS up to 4.3. This affects the function Edit of the file src/ZKEACMS.EventAction/Controllers/PendingTaskController.cs of the component Event Action System. Such manipulation of the argument Data leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 05:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10763 | academico-sis academico Profile Picture edit-photo unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10763</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in academico-sis academico up to d9a9e2636fbf7e5845ee086bcb03ca62faceb6ab. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /edit-photo of the component Profile Picture Handler. This manipulation causes unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 05:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10762 | kuaifan DooTask UsersController.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10762</link><description>A vulnerability was found in kuaifan DooTask up to 1.2.49. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file app/Http/Controllers/Api/UsersController.php. The manipulation of the argument keys[department] results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 04:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10761 | Harness Login Endpoint login excessive authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10761</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Harness 3.3.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/v1/login of the component Login Endpoint. The manipulation leads to improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 03:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10760 | Harness lookup_repo.go LookupRepo server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10760</link><description>A flaw has been found in Harness 3.3.0. This impacts the function LookupRepo of the file app/api/controller/gitspace/lookup_repo.go. Executing manipulation of the argument url can lead to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 03:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10759 | Webkul QloApps CSRF Token authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10759</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Webkul QloApps up to 1.7.0. This affects an unknown function of the component CSRF Token Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument token results in authorization bypass. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor explains: "As We are already aware about this vulnerability and our Internal team are already working on this issue. (...) We'll implement the fix for this vulnerability in our next major release."</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 01:07:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10758 | htmly Custom Field post cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10758</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in htmly up to 3.1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /htmly/admin/field/post of the component Custom Field Handler. Such manipulation of the argument label leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 01:07:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10757 | UTT 1200GW formConfigDnsFilterGlobal buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10757</link><description>A weakness has been identified in UTT 1200GW up to 3.0.0-170831. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /goform/formConfigDnsFilterGlobal. This manipulation of the argument GroupName causes buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 23:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10756 | UTT HiPER 840G getOneApConfTempEntry buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10756</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in UTT HiPER 840G up to 3.1.1-190328. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /goform/getOneApConfTempEntry. The manipulation of the argument tempName results in buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 22:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10755 | Selleo Mentingo Content-Type unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10755</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Selleo Mentingo 2025.08.27. The impacted element is an unknown function of the component Content-Type Handler. The manipulation of the argument userAvatar results in unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 21:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40925 | Starch versions 0.14 and earlier generate session ids insecurely</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40925</link><description>Starch versions 0.14 and earlier generate session ids insecurely.

The default session id generator returns a SHA-1 hash seeded with a counter, the epoch time, the built-in rand function, the PID, and internal Perl reference addresses. The PID will come from a small set of numbers, and the epoch time may be guessed, if it is not leaked from the HTTP Date header. The built-in rand function is unsuitable for cryptographic usage.

Predicable session ids could allow an attacker to gain access to systems.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 12:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10741 | Selleo Mentingo Profile Picture unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10741</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Selleo Mentingo up to 2025.08.27. The affected element is an unknown function of the component Profile Picture Handler. The manipulation of the argument userAvatar leads to unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 12:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10658 | SupportCandy – Helpdesk &amp;amp; Customer Support Ticket System &amp;lt;= 3.3.7 - Authentication Bypass to Support Session Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10658</link><description>The SupportCandy – Helpdesk &amp; Customer Support Ticket System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.7. This is due to missing rate limiting on the OTP verification for guest login. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass authentication and gain unauthorized access to customer support tickets by brute forcing the 6-digit OTP code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9882 | osTicket WP Bridge &amp;lt;= 1.9.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9882</link><description>The osTicket WP Bridge plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9883 | Browser Sniff &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9883</link><description>The Browser Sniff plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 06:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9887 | Custom Login And Signup Widget &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9887</link><description>The Custom Login And Signup Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation in the /frndzk_adminclsw.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the email and username settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 06:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10002 | ClickWhale &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10002</link><description>The ClickWhale – Link Manager, Link Shortener and Click Tracker for Affiliate Links &amp; Link Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the export_csv() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. This may be exploitable by lower level users if access to the plugin is granted.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 04:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10181 | Draft List &amp;lt;= 2.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10181</link><description>The Draft List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'drafts' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 04:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10305 | Secure Passkeys &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Passkey Exposure and Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10305</link><description>The Secure Passkeys plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the delete_passkey() and passkeys_list() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view and delete passkeys.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 04:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10489 | SureForms – Drag and Drop Form Builder for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.12.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Form Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10489</link><description>The SureForms – Drag and Drop Contact Form Builder – Multi-step Forms, Conversational Forms and more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized creation of forms due to a missing capability check on the register_post_types() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to create forms when the user interface specifically prohibits it.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 04:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9949 | Internal Links Manager &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9949</link><description>The Internal Links Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the link deletion functionality in the process_bulk_action() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete SEO links via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 04:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10652 | Robcore Netatmo &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via robcore-netatmo Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10652</link><description>The Robcore Netatmo plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘module_id’ attribute of the robcore-netatmo shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 02:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>