<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:18:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-46448 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in dmpop Mejiro Commit Versions Prior To 3096393 allows attackers to run arbitrary code v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46448</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in dmpop Mejiro Commit Versions Prior To 3096393 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted string in metadata of uploaded images.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46428 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in HadSky v7.12.10 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46428</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in HadSky v7.12.10 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 20:57:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1193 | Use-after-free in setup_async_work()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1193</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in setup_async_work in the KSMBD implementation of the in-kernel samba server and CIFS in the Linux kernel. This issue could allow an attacker to crash the system by accessing freed work.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46724 | SQUID-2023:4 Denial of Service in SSL Certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46724</link><description>Squid is a caching proxy for the Web. Due to an Improper Validation of Specified Index bug, Squid versions 3.3.0.1 through 5.9 and 6.0 prior to 6.4 compiled using `--with-openssl` are vulnerable to a Denial of Service attack against SSL Certificate validation. This problem allows a remote server to perform Denial of Service against Squid Proxy by initiating a TLS Handshake with a specially crafted SSL Certificate in a server certificate chain. This attack is limited to HTTPS and SSL-Bump. This bug is fixed in Squid version 6.4. In addition, patches addressing this problem for the stable releases can be found in Squid's patch archives. Those who you use a prepackaged version of Squid should refer to the package vendor for availability information on updated packages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1192 | Use-after-free in smb2_is_status_io_timeout()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1192</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in smb2_is_status_io_timeout() in CIFS in the Linux Kernel. After CIFS transfers response data to a system call, there are still local variable points to the memory region, and if the system call frees it faster than CIFS uses it, CIFS will access a free memory region, leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3397 | Slab-use-after-free write in txend due to race condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3397</link><description>A race condition occurred between the functions lmLogClose and txEnd in JFS, in the Linux Kernel, executed in different threads. This flaw allows a local attacker with normal user privileges to crash the system or leak internal kernel information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46482 | SQL injection vulnerability in wuzhicms v.4.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Database Backup Functionality in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46482</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in wuzhicms v.4.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Database Backup Functionality in the coreframe/app/database/admin/index.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 18:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20083 | A vulnerability in ICMPv6 inspection when configured with the Snort 2 detection engine for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20083</link><description>A vulnerability in ICMPv6 inspection when configured with the Snort 2 detection engine for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the CPU of an affected device to spike to 100 percent, which could stop all traffic processing and result in a denial of service (DoS) condition. FTD management traffic is not affected by this vulnerability. This vulnerability is due to improper error checking when parsing fields within the ICMPv6 header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted ICMPv6 packet through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition. Note: To recover from the DoS condition, the Snort 2 Detection Engine or the Cisco FTD device may need to be restarted.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5358 | Improper access control in Report log filters feature in Devolutions Server 2023.2.10.0 and earlier allows attackers to retrieve logs from v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5358</link><description>Improper access control in Report log filters feature in Devolutions Server 2023.2.10.0 and earlier allows attackers to retrieve logs from vaults or entries they are not allowed to access via the report request url query parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20042 | A vulnerability in the AnyConnect SSL VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FT...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20042</link><description>A vulnerability in the AnyConnect SSL VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to an implementation error within the SSL/TLS session handling process that can prevent the release of a session handler under specific conditions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted SSL/TLS traffic to an affected device, increasing the probability of session handler leaks. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to eventually deplete the available session handler pool, preventing new sessions from being established and causing a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20063 | A vulnerability in the inter-device communication mechanisms between devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20063</link><description>A vulnerability in the inter-device communication mechanisms between devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software and devices that are running Cisco Firepower Management (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root permissions on the underlying operating system of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the expert mode of an affected device and submitting specific commands to a connected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code in the context of an FMC device if the attacker has administrative privileges on an associated FTD device. Alternatively, a successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code in the context of an FTD device if the attacker has administrative privileges on an associated FMC device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20070 | A vulnerability in the TLS 1.3 implementation of the Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20070</link><description>A vulnerability in the TLS 1.3 implementation of the Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the Snort 3 detection engine to unexpectedly restart. This vulnerability is due to a logic error in how memory allocations are handled during a TLS 1.3 session. Under specific, time-based constraints, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted TLS 1.3 message sequence through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Snort 3 detection engine to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. While the Snort detection engine reloads, packets going through the FTD device that are sent to the Snort detection engine will be dropped. The Snort detection engine will restart automatically. No manual intervention is required.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20071 | Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort detection engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20071</link><description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort detection engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured policies on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to a flaw in the FTP module of the Snort detection engine. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted FTP traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass FTP inspection and deliver a malicious payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20095 | A vulnerability in the remote access VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20095</link><description>A vulnerability in the remote access VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of HTTPS requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTPS requests to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause resource exhaustion, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20170 | A vulnerability in a specific Cisco ISE CLI command could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20170</link><description>A vulnerability in a specific Cisco ISE CLI command could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have valid Administrator-level privileges on the affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20175 | A vulnerability in a specific Cisco ISE CLI command could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20175</link><description>A vulnerability in a specific Cisco ISE CLI command could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have valid Read-only-level privileges or higher on the affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20219 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20219</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system. The attacker would need valid device credentials but does not require administrator privileges to exploit this vulnerability. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input for certain configuration options. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by using crafted input within the device configuration GUI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the device including the underlying operating system which could also affect the availability of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20220 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20220</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker must have valid device credentials, but does not need Administrator privileges. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input for certain configuration options. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by using crafted input within the device configuration GUI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the device, including on the underlying operating system, which could also affect the availability of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20246 | Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in Snort access control policies that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20246</link><description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in Snort access control policies that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured policies on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when the access control policies are being populated. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing a connection to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access control rules on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20247 | A vulnerability in the remote access SSL VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20247</link><description>A vulnerability in the remote access SSL VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured multiple certificate authentication policy and connect using only a valid username and password. This vulnerability is due to improper error handling during remote access VPN authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted requests during remote access VPN session establishment. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the configured multiple certificate authentication policy while retaining the privileges and permissions associated with the original connection profile.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20264 | A vulnerability in the implementation of Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) 2.0 single sign-on (SSO) for remote access VPN in Cisco A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20264</link><description>A vulnerability in the implementation of Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) 2.0 single sign-on (SSO) for remote access VPN in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to intercept the SAML assertion of a user who is authenticating to a remote access VPN session. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of the login URL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to access a site that is under the control of the attacker, allowing the attacker to modify the login URL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to intercept a successful SAML assertion and use that assertion to establish a remote access VPN session toward the affected device with the identity and permissions of the hijacked user, resulting in access to the protected network.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20267 | A vulnerability in the IP geolocation rules of Snort 3 could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to potentially bypass IP address rest...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20267</link><description>A vulnerability in the IP geolocation rules of Snort 3 could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to potentially bypass IP address restrictions. This vulnerability exists because the configuration for IP geolocation rules is not parsed properly. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by spoofing an IP address until they bypass the restriction. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass location-based IP address restrictions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5480 | Inappropriate implementation in Payments in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to bypass XSS preventions via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5480</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Payments in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to bypass XSS preventions via a malicious file. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5482 | Insufficient data validation in USB in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory acces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5482</link><description>Insufficient data validation in USB in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5765 | Improper access control in the password analyzer feature in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2023.2.33 and earlier on Windows allows an at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5765</link><description>Improper access control in the password analyzer feature in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2023.2.33 and earlier on Windows allows an attacker to bypass permissions via data source switching.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5766 | A remote code execution vulnerability in Remote Desktop Manager 2023.2.33 and earlier on Windows allows an attacker to remotely execute code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5766</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability in Remote Desktop Manager 2023.2.33 and earlier on Windows allows an attacker to remotely execute code from another windows user session on the same host via a specially crafted TCP packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5849 | Integer overflow in USB in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5849</link><description>Integer overflow in USB in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5850 | Incorrect security UI in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform domain spoofing via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5850</link><description>Incorrect security UI in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform domain spoofing via a crafted domain name. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5851 | Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to obfuscate security UI via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5851</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to obfuscate security UI via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5852 | Use after free in Printing in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5852</link><description>Use after free in Printing in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to potentially exploit heap corruption via specific UI gestures. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5853 | Incorrect security UI in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to obfuscate security UI via a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5853</link><description>Incorrect security UI in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to obfuscate security UI via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5854 | Use after free in Profiles in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5854</link><description>Use after free in Profiles in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to potentially exploit heap corruption via specific UI gestures. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5855 | Use after free in Reading Mode in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5855</link><description>Use after free in Reading Mode in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to potentially exploit heap corruption via specific UI gestures. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5856 | Use after free in Side Panel in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific U...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5856</link><description>Use after free in Side Panel in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5857 | Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5857</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially execute arbitrary code via a malicious file. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5858 | Inappropriate implementation in WebApp Provider in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to obfuscate security UI ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5858</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in WebApp Provider in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to obfuscate security UI via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5859 | Incorrect security UI in Picture In Picture in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform domain spoofing vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5859</link><description>Incorrect security UI in Picture In Picture in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform domain spoofing via a crafted local HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20031 | A vulnerability in the SSL/TLS certificate handling of Snort 3 Detection Engine integration with Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Softwa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20031</link><description>A vulnerability in the SSL/TLS certificate handling of Snort 3 Detection Engine integration with Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the Snort 3 detection engine to restart. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an SSL/TLS certificate that is under load is accessed when it is initiating an SSL connection. Under specific, time-based constraints, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high rate of SSL/TLS connection requests to be inspected by the Snort 3 detection engine on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Snort 3 detection engine to reload, resulting in either a bypass or a denial of service (DoS) condition, depending on device configuration. The Snort detection engine will restart automatically. No manual intervention is required.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20048 | A vulnerability in the web services interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20048</link><description>A vulnerability in the web services interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute certain unauthorized configuration commands on a Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) device that is managed by the FMC Software. This vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization of configuration commands that are sent through the web service interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the FMC web services interface and sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute certain configuration commands on the targeted FTD device. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid credentials on the FMC Software.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20196 | Two vulnerabilities in Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20196</link><description>Two vulnerabilities in Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by uploading a crafted file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files in specific directories on the device. The attacker could later use those files to conduct additional attacks, including executing arbitrary code on the affected device with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20255 | A vulnerability in an API of the Web Bridge feature of Cisco Meeting Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20255</link><description>A vulnerability in an API of the Web Bridge feature of Cisco Meeting Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a partial availability condition, which could cause ongoing video calls to be dropped due to the invalid packets reaching the Web Bridge.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20195 | Two vulnerabilities in Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20195</link><description>Two vulnerabilities in Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by uploading a crafted file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files in specific directories on the device. The attacker could later use those files to conduct additional attacks, including executing arbitrary code on the affected device with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20213 | A vulnerability in the CDP processing feature of Cisco ISE could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (D...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20213</link><description>A vulnerability in the CDP processing feature of Cisco ISE could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of the CDP process on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient bounds checking when an affected device processes CDP traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted CDP traffic to the device. A successful exploit could cause the CDP process to crash, impacting neighbor discovery and the ability of Cisco ISE to determine the reachability of remote devices. After a crash, the CDP process must be manually restarted using the cdp enable command in interface configuration mode.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20245 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the per-user-override feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Def...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20245</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the per-user-override feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured access control list (ACL) and allow traffic that should be denied to flow through an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to a logic error that could occur when the affected software constructs and applies per-user-override rules. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by connecting to a network through an affected device that has a vulnerable configuration. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the interface ACL and access resources that would should be protected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20256 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the per-user-override feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Def...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20256</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the per-user-override feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured access control list (ACL) and allow traffic that should be denied to flow through an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to a logic error that could occur when the affected software constructs and applies per-user-override rules. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by connecting to a network through an affected device that has a vulnerable configuration. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the interface ACL and access resources that would should be protected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20005 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20005</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information. In some cases, it is also possible to cause a temporary availability impact to portions of the FMC Dashboard.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20041 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20041</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information. In some cases, it is also possible to cause a temporary availability impact to portions of the FMC Dashboard.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20074 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20074</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information. In some cases, it is also possible to cause a temporary availability impact to portions of the FMC Dashboard.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20206 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20206</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information. In some cases, it is also possible to cause a temporary availability impact to portions of the FMC Dashboard.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20244 | A vulnerability in the internal packet processing of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software for Cisco Firepower 2100 Series Firewalls...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20244</link><description>A vulnerability in the internal packet processing of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software for Cisco Firepower 2100 Series Firewalls could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain packets when they are sent to the inspection engine. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of crafted packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to deplete all 9,472 byte blocks on the device, resulting in traffic loss across the device or an unexpected reload of the device. If the device does not reload on its own, a manual reload of the device would be required to recover from this state.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20270 | A vulnerability in the interaction between the Server Message Block (SMB) protocol preprocessor and the Snort 3 detection engine for Cisco F...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20270</link><description>A vulnerability in the interaction between the Server Message Block (SMB) protocol preprocessor and the Snort 3 detection engine for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured policies or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper error-checking when the Snort 3 detection engine is processing SMB traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SMB packet stream through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Snort process to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20114 | A vulnerability in the file download feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20114</link><description>A vulnerability in the file download feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to download arbitrary files from an affected system. This vulnerability is due to a lack of input sanitation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTPS request. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to download arbitrary files from the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20155 | A vulnerability in a logging API in Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to caus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20155</link><description>A vulnerability in a logging API in Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to become unresponsive or trigger an unexpected reload. This vulnerability could also allow an attacker with valid user credentials, but not Administrator privileges, to view a system log file that they would not normally have access to. This vulnerability is due to a lack of rate-limiting of requests that are sent to a specific API that is related to an FMC log. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high rate of HTTP requests to the API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition due to the FMC CPU spiking to 100 percent utilization or to the device reloading. CPU utilization would return to normal if the attack traffic was stopped before an unexpected reload was triggered.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20086 | A vulnerability in ICMPv6 processing of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20086</link><description>A vulnerability in ICMPv6 processing of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper processing of ICMPv6 messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted ICMPv6 messages to a targeted Cisco ASA or FTD system with IPv6 enabled. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20177 | A vulnerability in the SSL file policy implementation of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software that occurs when the SSL/TLS connecti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20177</link><description>A vulnerability in the SSL file policy implementation of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software that occurs when the SSL/TLS connection is configured with a URL Category and the Snort 3 detection engine could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the Snort 3 detection engine to unexpectedly restart. This vulnerability exists because a logic error occurs when a Snort 3 detection engine inspects an SSL/TLS connection that has either a URL Category configured on the SSL file policy or a URL Category configured on an access control policy with TLS server identity discovery enabled. Under specific, time-based constraints, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SSL/TLS connection through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to trigger an unexpected reload of the Snort 3 detection engine, resulting in either a bypass or denial of service (DoS) condition, depending on device configuration. The Snort 3 detection engine will restart automatically. No manual intervention is required.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5178 | Use after free in nvmet_tcp_free_crypto in nvme</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5178</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability was found in drivers/nvme/target/tcp.c` in `nvmet_tcp_free_crypto` due to a logical bug in the NVMe-oF/TCP subsystem in the Linux kernel. This issue may allow a malicious user to cause a use-after-free and double-free problem, which may permit remote code execution or lead to local privilege escalation in case that the attacker already has local privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46911 | There is a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the choose_style_tree.do interface of Jspxcms v10.2.0 backend.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46911</link><description>There is a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the choose_style_tree.do interface of Jspxcms v10.2.0 backend.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3972 | Unsafe handling of temporary files and directories</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3972</link><description>A vulnerability was found in insights-client. This security issue occurs because of insecure file operations or unsafe handling of temporary files and directories that lead to local privilege escalation. Before the insights-client has been registered on the system by root, an unprivileged local user or attacker could create the /var/tmp/insights-client directory (owning the directory with read, write, and execute permissions) on the system. After the insights-client is registered by root, an attacker could then control the directory content that insights are using by putting malicious scripts into it and executing arbitrary code as root (trivially bypassing SELinux protections because insights processes are allowed to disable SELinux system-wide).</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33228 | SolarWinds Network Configuration Manager Sensitive Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33228</link><description>The SolarWinds Network Configuration Manager was susceptible to the Exposure of Sensitive Information Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows users with administrative access to SolarWinds Web Console to obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33226 | Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33226</link><description>The Network Configuration Manager was susceptible to a Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability.  This vulnerability allows a low-level user to perform the actions with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33227 | Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33227</link><description>The Network Configuration Manager was susceptible to a Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability This vulnerability allows a low level user to perform the actions with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40061 | Insecure Job Execution Mechanism Vulnerability </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40061</link><description>Insecure
job execution mechanism vulnerability.  This
vulnerability can lead to other attacks as a result.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40062 | Incomplete List of Disallowed Inputs Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40062</link><description>SolarWinds Platform Incomplete List of Disallowed Inputs Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. If executed, this vulnerability would allow a low-privileged user to execute commands with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5847 | Under certain conditions, a low privileged attacker could load a specially crafted file during installation or upgrade to escalate privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5847</link><description>Under certain conditions, a low privileged attacker could load a specially crafted file during installation or upgrade to escalate privileges on Windows and Linux hosts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5627 | Incorrect Implementation of Authentication Algorithm Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5627</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in NPort 6000 Series, making the authentication mechanism vulnerable. This vulnerability arises from the incorrect implementation of sensitive information protection, potentially allowing malicious users to gain unauthorized access to the web service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46927 | GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev605-gfc9e29089-master contains a heap-buffer-overflow in gf_isom_use_compact_size gpac/src/isomedia/isom_write.c:3403:3 in g...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46927</link><description>GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev605-gfc9e29089-master contains a heap-buffer-overflow in gf_isom_use_compact_size gpac/src/isomedia/isom_write.c:3403:3 in gpac/MP4Box.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 14:48:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46928 | GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev605-gfc9e29089-master contains a SEGV in gpac/MP4Box in gf_media_change_pl /afltest/gpac/src/media_tools/isom_tools.c:3293:4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46928</link><description>GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev605-gfc9e29089-master contains a SEGV in gpac/MP4Box in gf_media_change_pl /afltest/gpac/src/media_tools/isom_tools.c:3293:42.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 14:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4452 | Web Server Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4452</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the EDR-810, EDR-G902, and EDR-G903 Series, making them  vulnerable to the denial-of-service vulnerability. This vulnerability stems from insufficient input validation in the URI, potentially enabling malicious users to trigger the device reboot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 14:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46930 | GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev605-gfc9e29089-master contains a SEGV in gpac/MP4Box in gf_isom_find_od_id_for_track /afltest/gpac/src/isomedia/media_odf.c:...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46930</link><description>GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev605-gfc9e29089-master contains a SEGV in gpac/MP4Box in gf_isom_find_od_id_for_track /afltest/gpac/src/isomedia/media_odf.c:522:14.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 14:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46931 | GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev605-gfc9e29089-master contains a heap-buffer-overflow in ffdmx_parse_side_data /afltest/gpac/src/filters/ff_dmx.c:202:14 in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46931</link><description>GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev605-gfc9e29089-master contains a heap-buffer-overflow in ffdmx_parse_side_data /afltest/gpac/src/filters/ff_dmx.c:202:14 in gpac/MP4Box.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 14:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5625 | Patch regression for cve-2021-21419 in some red hat builds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5625</link><description>A regression was introduced in the Red Hat build of python-eventlet due to a change in the patch application strategy, resulting in a patch for CVE-2021-21419 not being applied for all builds of all products.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 13:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48454 | In wifi service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48454</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48455 | In wifi service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48455</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48456 | In camera driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48456</link><description>In camera driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48457 | In TeleService, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local denial of service with no additi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48457</link><description>In TeleService, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48458 | In TeleService, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local denial of service with no additi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48458</link><description>In TeleService, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48459 | In TeleService, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local denial of service with no additi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48459</link><description>In TeleService, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48460 | In setting service, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to local denial of service with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48460</link><description>In setting service, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48461 | In sensor driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48461</link><description>In sensor driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1714 | Bitrix24 Remote Command Execution (RCE) via Unsafe Variable Extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1714</link><description>Unsafe variable extraction in bitrix/modules/main/classes/general/user_options.php in Bitrix24 22.0.300 allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via (1) appending arbitrary content to existing PHP files or (2) PHAR deserialization.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1715 | Bitrix24 Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via Improper Input Neutralization on Invoice Edit Page (1 of 2)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1715</link><description>A logic error when using mb_strpos() to check for potential XSS payload in Bitrix24 22.0.300 allows attackers to bypass XSS sanitisation via placing HTML tags at the begining of the payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1716 | Bitrix24 Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via Improper Input Neutralization on Invoice Edit Page (2 of 2)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1716</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Invoice Edit Page in Bitrix24 22.0.300 allows attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim's browser, and possibly execute arbitrary PHP code on the server if the victim has administrator privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1717 | Bitrix24 Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via Client-side Prototype Pollution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1717</link><description>Prototype pollution in bitrix/templates/bitrix24/components/bitrix/menu/left_vertical/script.js in Bitrix24 22.0.300 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victims browser, and possibly execute arbitrary PHP code on the server if the victim has administrator privilege, via polluting `__proto__[tag]` and `__proto__[text]`.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1718 | Bitrix24 Denial-of-Service (DoS) via Improper File Stream Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1718</link><description>Improper file stream access in /desktop_app/file.ajax.php?action=uploadfile in Bitrix24 22.0.300 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to cause denial-of-service via a crafted "tmp_url".</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1719 | Bitrix24 Insecure Global Variable Extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1719</link><description>Global variable extraction in bitrix/modules/main/tools.php in Bitrix24 22.0.300 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to (1) enumerate attachments on the server and (2) execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim's browser, and possibly execute arbitrary PHP code on the server if the victim has administrator privilege, via overwriting uninitialised variables.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1720 | Bitrix24 Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1720</link><description>Lack of mime type response header in Bitrix24 22.0.300 allows authenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim's browser, and possibly execute arbitrary PHP code on the server if the victim has administrator privilege, via uploading a crafted HTML file through /desktop_app/file.ajax.php?action=uploadfile.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42631 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42631</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42632 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42632</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42633 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42633</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42634 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42634</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42635 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42635</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42636 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42636</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42637 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42637</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42638 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42638</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42639 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42639</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42640 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42640</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42641 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42641</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42642 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42642</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42643 | In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42643</link><description>In validationtools, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42644 | In dm service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42644</link><description>In dm service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42645 | In sim service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42645</link><description>In sim service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42646 | In Ifaa service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42646</link><description>In Ifaa service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42647 | In Ifaa service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42647</link><description>In Ifaa service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42648 | In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42648</link><description>In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42649 | In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42649</link><description>In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42650 | In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42650</link><description>In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42651 | In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42651</link><description>In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42652 | In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42652</link><description>In engineermode, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42653 | In faceid service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42653</link><description>In faceid service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42654 | In dm service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42654</link><description>In dm service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42655 | In sim service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42655</link><description>In sim service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42750 | In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42750</link><description>In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1713 | Bitrix24 Remote Command Execution (RCE) via Insecure Temporary File Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1713</link><description>Insecure temporary file creation in bitrix/modules/crm/lib/order/import/instagram.php in Bitrix24 22.0.300 hosted on Apache HTTP Server allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted ".htaccess" file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:23:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4198 | Dolibarr ERP CRM (&amp;lt;= 17.0.3) Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4198</link><description>Improper Access Control in Dolibarr ERP CRM &lt;= v17.0.3 allows an unauthorized authenticated user to read a database table containing customer data</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 08:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4197 | Dolibarr ERP CRM (&amp;lt;= 18.0.1) Improper Input Sanitization Authenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4197</link><description>Improper input validation in Dolibarr ERP CRM &lt;= v18.0.1 fails to strip certain PHP code from user-supplied input when creating a Website, allowing an attacker to inject and evaluate arbitrary PHP code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 08:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5516 | Poorly constructed webap requests and URI components with special characters trigger unhandled errors and exceptions, disclosing
information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5516</link><description>Poorly constructed webap requests and URI components with special characters trigger unhandled errors and exceptions, disclosing
information about the underlying technology and other sensitive information details. The website unintentionally reveals sensitive information including technical details like version Info, endpoints,
backend server, Internal IP. etc., which can potentially expose additional attack surface containing other interesting vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:58:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5515 | The responses for web queries with certain parameters disclose internal path of resources. This information can be used to learn internal st...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5515</link><description>The responses for web queries with certain parameters disclose internal path of resources. This information can be used to learn internal structure of the application and to further plot attacks against
web servers and deployed web applications.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:58:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5514 | The response messages received from the eSOMS report generation using certain parameter queries with full file path can be
abused for enumer...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5514</link><description>The response messages received from the eSOMS report generation using certain parameter queries with full file path can be
abused for enumerating the local file system structure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2622 | Authenticated clients can read arbitrary files on the MAIN Computer
system using the remote procedure call (RPC) of the InspectSetup
service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2622</link><description>Authenticated clients can read arbitrary files on the MAIN Computer
system using the remote procedure call (RPC) of the InspectSetup
service endpoint. The low privilege client is then allowed to read arbitrary files that they do not have authorization to read.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2621 | The McFeeder server (distributed as part of SSW package), is susceptible to an arbitrary file write vulnerability on the MAIN computer
syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2621</link><description>The McFeeder server (distributed as part of SSW package), is susceptible to an arbitrary file write vulnerability on the MAIN computer
system. This vulnerability stems from the use of an outdated version of a third-party library, which is used to extract archives uploaded to McFeeder server. An authenticated malicious client can
exploit this vulnerability by uploading a crafted ZIP archive via the
network to McFeeders service endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5889 | Insufficient Session Expiration in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5889</link><description>Insufficient Session Expiration in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5890 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5890</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5891 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5891</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5892 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5892</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5893 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5893</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5894 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in pkp/ojs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5894</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository pkp/ojs prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5895 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - DOM in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5895</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - DOM in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5896 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5896</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.4.0-4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5897 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in pkp/customLocale</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5897</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in GitHub repository pkp/customLocale prior to 1.2.0-1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5898 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5898</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5899 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5899</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5900 | Missing Authorization in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5900</link><description>Missing Authorization in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5901 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5901</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5902 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5902</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5903 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5903</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5904 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in pkp/pkp-lib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5904</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository pkp/pkp-lib prior to 3.3.0-16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47094 | An issue was discovered in Virtualmin 7.7. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the Account Plans tab of Syst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47094</link><description>An issue was discovered in Virtualmin 7.7. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the Account Plans tab of System Settings via the Plan Name field. Whenever the module is accessed, the XSS payload is executed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 23:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47095 | An issue was discovered in Virtualmin 7.7. The Custom Fields feature of Edit Virtual Server under System Customization allows XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47095</link><description>An issue was discovered in Virtualmin 7.7. The Custom Fields feature of Edit Virtual Server under System Customization allows XSS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 23:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47096 | An issue was discovered in Virtualmin 7.7. The Cloudmin Services Client under System Settings allows XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47096</link><description>An issue was discovered in Virtualmin 7.7. The Cloudmin Services Client under System Settings allows XSS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 23:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47097 | An issue was discovered in Virtualmin 7.7. The Server Templates feature under System Settings allows XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47097</link><description>An issue was discovered in Virtualmin 7.7. The Server Templates feature under System Settings allows XSS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 23:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47098 | An issue was discovered in Virtualmin 7.7. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Create Extra Administrator tab vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47098</link><description>An issue was discovered in Virtualmin 7.7. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Create Extra Administrator tab via the "Real name or description" field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 23:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47099 | An issue was discovered in Virtualmin 7.7. The Create Virtual Server functionality allows XSS attacks against anyone who accesses the Virtua...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47099</link><description>An issue was discovered in Virtualmin 7.7. The Create Virtual Server functionality allows XSS attacks against anyone who accesses the Virtual Server Summary tab.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 23:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46278 | Uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in Cybozu Remote Service 4.1.0 to 4.1.1 allows a remote authenticated attacker to consume hu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46278</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in Cybozu Remote Service 4.1.0 to 4.1.1 allows a remote authenticated attacker to consume huge storage space or cause significantly delayed communication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 23:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39695 | Insufficient session expiration in Elenos ETG150 FM Transmitter v3.12 allows attackers to arbitrarily change transmitter configuration and d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39695</link><description>Insufficient session expiration in Elenos ETG150 FM Transmitter v3.12 allows attackers to arbitrarily change transmitter configuration and data after logging out.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 22:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37833 | Improper access control in Elenos ETG150 FM transmitter v3.12 allows attackers to make arbitrary configuration edits that are only accessed ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37833</link><description>Improper access control in Elenos ETG150 FM transmitter v3.12 allows attackers to make arbitrary configuration edits that are only accessed by privileged users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 22:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46378 | Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MiniCMS 1.1.1 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted string appended to /mc-a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46378</link><description>Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MiniCMS 1.1.1 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted string appended to /mc-admin/conf.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 22:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44486 | Online Blood Donation Management System v1.0 - Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44486</link><description>Online Blood Donation Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Store Cross-Site Scripting vulnerabilities.The 'address' parameter of the users/register.php resource is copied into the users/member.php document as plain text between tags. Any input is echoed unmodified in the users/member.php response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 21:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5306 | Online Blood Donation Management System v1.0 - Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5306</link><description>Online Blood Donation Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Store Cross-Site Scripting vulnerabilities.The 'city' parameter of the users/register.php resource is copied into the users/member.php document as plain text between tags. Any input is echoed unmodified in the users/member.php response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 21:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44484 | Online Blood Donation Management System v1.0 - Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44484</link><description>Online Blood Donation Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Store Cross-Site Scripting vulnerabilities.The 'firstName' parameter of the users/register.php resource is copied into the users/member.php document as plain text between tags. Any input is echoed unmodified in the users/member.php response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 21:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44485 | Online Blood Donation Management System v1.0 - Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44485</link><description>Online Blood Donation Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Store Cross-Site Scripting vulnerabilities.The 'lastName' parameter of the users/register.php resource is copied into the users/member.php document as plain text between tags. Any input is echoed unmodified in the users/member.php response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 21:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20886 | VMware Workspace ONE UEM console contains an open redirect vulnerability.


A malicious actor may be able to redirect a victim to an attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20886</link><description>VMware Workspace ONE UEM console contains an open redirect vulnerability.


A malicious actor may be able to redirect a victim to an attacker and retrieve their SAML response to login as the victim user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 20:56:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39610 | An issue in TP-Link Tapo C100 v1.1.15 Build 211130 Rel.15378n(4555) and before allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via suppl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39610</link><description>An issue in TP-Link Tapo C100 v1.1.15 Build 211130 Rel.15378n(4555) and before allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted web request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 20:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3955 | Kubernetes - Windows nodes - Insufficient input sanitization leads to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3955</link><description>A security issue was discovered in Kubernetes where a user
 that can create pods on Windows nodes may be able to escalate to admin 
privileges on those nodes. Kubernetes clusters are only affected if they
 include Windows nodes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 20:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43295 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Click Studios (SA) Pty Ltd Passwordstate v.Build 9785 and before allows a local attacker to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43295</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Click Studios (SA) Pty Ltd Passwordstate v.Build 9785 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 20:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3676 | Kubernetes - Windows nodes - Insufficient input sanitization leads to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3676</link><description>A security issue was discovered in Kubernetes where a user
 that can create pods on Windows nodes may be able to escalate to admin 
privileges on those nodes. Kubernetes clusters are only affected if they
 include Windows nodes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 20:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46485 | An issue in TOTOlink X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the setTracerouteCfg function of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46485</link><description>An issue in TOTOlink X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the setTracerouteCfg function of the stecgi.cgi component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 20:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46484 | An issue in TOTOlink X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the setLedCfg function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46484</link><description>An issue in TOTOlink X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the setLedCfg function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 20:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37832 | A lack of rate limiting in Elenos ETG150 FM transmitter v3.12 allows attackers to obtain user credentials via brute force and cause other un...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37832</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in Elenos ETG150 FM transmitter v3.12 allows attackers to obtain user credentials via brute force and cause other unspecified impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 17:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37831 | An issue discovered in Elenos ETG150 FM transmitter v3.12 allows attackers to enumerate user accounts based on server responses when credent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37831</link><description>An issue discovered in Elenos ETG150 FM transmitter v3.12 allows attackers to enumerate user accounts based on server responses when credentials are submitted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 17:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45955 | An issue discovered in Nanoleaf Light strip v3.5.10 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted write binding attribute comman...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45955</link><description>An issue discovered in Nanoleaf Light strip v3.5.10 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted write binding attribute commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 17:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43796 | Synapse vulnerable to leak of remote user device information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43796</link><description>Synapse is an open-source Matrix homeserver Prior to versions 1.95.1 and 1.96.0rc1, cached device information of remote users can be queried from Synapse. This can be used to enumerate the remote users known to a homeserver. System administrators are encouraged to upgrade to Synapse 1.95.1 or 1.96.0rc1 to receive a patch. As a workaround, the `federation_domain_whitelist` can be used to limit federation traffic with a homeserver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 17:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5739 | Certain versions of HP PC Hardware Diagnostics Windows are potentially vulnerable to elevation of privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5739</link><description>Certain versions of HP PC Hardware Diagnostics Windows are potentially vulnerable to elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46722 | Pimcore Admin Classic Bundle Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in PDF previews</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46722</link><description>The Pimcore Admin Classic Bundle provides a backend UI for Pimcore. Prior to version 1.2.0, a cross-site scripting vulnerability has the potential to steal a user's cookie and gain unauthorized access to that user's account through the stolen cookie or redirect users to other malicious sites. Users should upgrade to version 1.2.0 to receive a patch or, as a workaround, apply the patch manually.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46723 | lte-pic32-writer&amp;#x27;s sendto.txt may disclose URL and the API key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46723</link><description>lte-pic32-writer is a writer for PIC32 devices. In versions 0.0.1 and prior, those who use `sendto.txt` are vulnerable to attackers who known the IMEI reading the sendto.txt. The sendto.txt file can contain the SNS(such as slack and zulip) URL and API key. As of time of publication, a patch is not yet available. As workarounds, avoid using `sendto.txt` or use `.htaccess` to block access to `sendto.txt`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46256 | PX4-Autopilot Heap Buffer Overflow Bug</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46256</link><description>PX4-Autopilot provides PX4 flight control solution for drones. In versions 1.14.0-rc1 and prior, PX4-Autopilot has a heap buffer overflow vulnerability in the parser function due to the absence of `parserbuf_index` value checking. A malfunction of the sensor device can cause a heap buffer overflow with leading unexpected drone behavior. Malicious applications can exploit the vulnerability even if device sensor malfunction does not occur. Up to the maximum value of an `unsigned int`, bytes sized data can be written to the heap memory area. As of time of publication, no fixed version is available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46250 | pypdf possible Infinite Loop when PdfWriter(clone_from) is used with a PDF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46250</link><description>pypdf is a free and open-source pure-python PDF library. An attacker who uses a vulnerability present in versions 3.7.0 through 3.16.4 can craft a PDF which leads to an infinite loop. This infinite loop blocks the current process and can utilize a single core of the CPU by 100%. It does not affect memory usage. That is, for example, the case when the pypdf-user manipulates an incoming malicious PDF e.g. by merging it with another PDF or by adding annotations. The issue was fixed in version 3.17.0. As a workaround, apply the patch manually by modifying `pypdf/generic/_data_structures.py`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46255 | `SPICEDB_DATASTORE_CONN_URI` is leaked when URI cannot be parsed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46255</link><description>SpiceDB is an open source, Google Zanzibar-inspired database for creating and managing security-critical application permissions. Prior to version 1.27.0, when the provided datastore URI is malformed (e.g. by having a password which contains `:`) the full URI (including the provided password) is printed, so that the password is shown in the logs. Version 1.27.0 patches this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46249 | authentik potential installation takeover when default admin user is deleted</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46249</link><description>authentik is an open-source Identity Provider. Prior to versions 2023.8.4 and 2023.10.2, when the default admin user has been deleted, it is potentially possible for an attacker to set the password of the default admin user without any authentication. authentik uses a blueprint to create the default admin user, which can also optionally set the default admin users' password from an environment variable. When the user is deleted, the `initial-setup` flow used to configure authentik after the first installation becomes available again. authentik 2023.8.4 and 2023.10.2 fix this issue. As a workaround, ensure the default admin user (Username `akadmin`) exists and has a password set. It is recommended to use a very strong password for this user, and store it in a secure location like a password manager. It is also possible to deactivate the user to prevent any logins as akadmin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:25:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46245 | Kimai (Authenticated) SSTI to RCE by Uploading a Malicious Twig File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46245</link><description>Kimai is a web-based multi-user time-tracking application. Versions 2.1.0 and prior are vulnerable to a Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) which can be escalated to Remote Code Execution (RCE). The vulnerability arises when a malicious user uploads a specially crafted Twig file, exploiting the software's PDF and HTML rendering functionalities. As of time of publication, no patches or known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:25:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46248 | Overwrite of builtin Cody commands facilitates RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46248</link><description>Cody is an artificial intelligence (AI) coding assistant. The Cody AI VSCode extension versions 0.10.0 through 0.14.0 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution under certain conditions. An attacker in control of a malicious repository could modify the Cody configuration file `.vscode/cody.json` and overwrite Cody commands. If a user with the extension installed opens this malicious repository and runs a Cody command such as /explain or /doc, this could allow arbitrary code execution on the user's machine. The vulnerability is rated as critical severity, but with low exploitability. It requires the user to have a malicious repository loaded and execute the overwritten command in VS Code. The issue is exploitable regardless of the user blocking code execution on a repository through VS Code Workspace Trust. The issue was found during a regular 3rd party penetration test. The maintainers of Cody do not have evidence of open source repositories having malicious `.vscode/cody.json` files to exploit this vulnerability. The issue is fixed in version 0.14.1 of the Cody VSCode extension. In case users can't promptly upgrade, they should not open any untrusted repositories with the Cody extension loaded.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:25:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46237 | FOG path traversal via unauthenticated endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46237</link><description>FOG is a free open-source cloning/imaging/rescue suite/inventory management system. Prior to version 1.5.10, an endpoint intended to offer limited enumeration abilities to authenticated users was accessible to unauthenticated users. This enabled unauthenticated users to discover files and their respective paths that were visible to the Apache user group. Version 1.5.10 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:25:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46239 | quic-go vulnerable to pointer dereference that can lead to panic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46239</link><description>quic-go is an implementation of the QUIC protocol in Go. Starting in version 0.37.0 and prior to version 0.37.3, by serializing an ACK frame after the CRYTPO that allows a node to complete the handshake, a remote node could trigger a nil pointer dereference (leading to a panic) when the node attempted to drop the Handshake packet number space. An attacker can bring down a quic-go node with very minimal effort. Completing the QUIC handshake only requires sending and receiving a few packets. Version 0.37.3 contains a patch. Versions before 0.37.0 are not affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:25:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46240 | CodeIgniter4 vulnerable to information disclosure when detailed error report is displayed in production environment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46240</link><description>CodeIgniter is a PHP full-stack web framework. Prior to CodeIgniter4 version 4.4.3, if an error or exception occurs, a detailed error report is displayed even if in the production environment. As a result, confidential information may be leaked. Version 4.4.3 contains a patch. As a workaround, replace `ini_set('display_errors', '0')` with `ini_set('display_errors', 'Off')` in `app/Config/Boot/production.php`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:25:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37966 | WordPress User Activity Log Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37966</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Solwin Infotech User Activity Log user-activity-log allows SQL Injection.This issue affects User Activity Log: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42425 | An issue in Turing Video Turing Edge+ EVC5FD v.1.38.6 allows remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42425</link><description>An issue in Turing Video Turing Edge+ EVC5FD v.1.38.6 allows remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the cloud connection components.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22518 | All versions of Confluence Data Center and Server are affected by this unexploited vulnerability. There is no impact to confidentiality as a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22518</link><description>All versions of Confluence Data Center and Server are affected by this unexploited vulnerability. There is no impact to confidentiality as an attacker cannot exfiltrate any instance data.

Atlassian Cloud sites are not affected by this vulnerability. If your Confluence site is accessed via an atlassian.net domain, it is hosted by Atlassian and is not vulnerable to this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37243 | The C:\Windows\Temp\Agent.Package.Availability\Agent.Package.Availability.exe file is automatically launched as SYSTEM when the system reboo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37243</link><description>The C:\Windows\Temp\Agent.Package.Availability\Agent.Package.Availability.exe file is automatically launched as SYSTEM when the system reboots. Since the C:\Windows\Temp\Agent.Package.Availability folder inherits permissions from C:\Windows\Temp and Agent.Package.Availability.exe is susceptible to DLL hijacking, standard users can write a malicious DLL to it and elevate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46236 | FOG SSRF via unauthenticated endpoint(s)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46236</link><description>FOG is a free open-source cloning/imaging/rescue suite/inventory management system. Prior to version 1.5.10, a server-side-request-forgery (SSRF) vulnerability allowed an unauthenticated user to trigger a GET request as the server to an arbitrary endpoint and URL scheme. This also allows remote access to files visible to the Apache user group. Other impacts vary based on server configuration. Version 1.5.10 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24410 | WordPress FluentForm Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.25 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24410</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Contact Form - WPManageNinja LLC Contact Form Plugin  Fastest Contact Form Builder Plugin for WordPress by Fluent Forms fluentform allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Contact Form Plugin  Fastest Contact Form Builder Plugin for WordPress by Fluent Forms: from n/a through 4.3.25.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36508 | WordPress Contact Form to DB by BestWebSoft Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36508</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in BestWebSoft Contact Form to DB by BestWebSoft  Messages Database Plugin For WordPress contact-form-to-db allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Contact Form to DB by BestWebSoft  Messages Database Plugin For WordPress: from n/a through 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46235 | FOG stored XSS on log screen via unsanitized request logging</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46235</link><description>FOG is a free open-source cloning/imaging/rescue suite/inventory management system. Prior to version 1.5.10.15, due to a lack of request sanitization in the logs, a malicious request containing XSS would be stored in a log file. When an administrator of the FOG server logged in and viewed the logs, they would be parsed as HTML and displayed accordingly. Version 1.5.10.15 contains a patch. As a workaround, view logs from an external text editor rather than the dashboard.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35879 | WordPress WooCommerce Product Vendors Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.78 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35879</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WooCommerce Product Vendors allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Product Vendors: from n/a through 2.1.78.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31212 | WordPress Contact Form Entries Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31212</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in CRM Perks Database for Contact Form 7, WPforms, Elementor forms contact-form-entries allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Database for Contact Form 7, WPforms, Elementor forms: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33927 | WordPress Multiple Page Generator Plugin  MPG Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.19 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33927</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Themeisle Multiple Page Generator Plugin  MPG multiple-pages-generator-by-porthas allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Multiple Page Generator Plugin  MPG: from n/a through 3.3.19.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40050 | Automate Vulnerable to Malicious Content Uploaded Through Embedded Compliance Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40050</link><description>Upload profile either
through API or user interface in Chef Automate prior to and including version 4.10.29 using InSpec
check command with maliciously crafted profile allows remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42658 | InSpec Archive Command Vulnerable to Maliciously Crafted Profile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42658</link><description>Archive command in Chef InSpec prior to 4.56.58 and 5.22.29 allow local command execution via maliciously crafted profile.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46993 | In TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 when dealing with setLedCfg request, there is no verification for the enable parameter, which can...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46993</link><description>In TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 when dealing with setLedCfg request, there is no verification for the enable parameter, which can lead to command injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28777 | WordPress LearnDash LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28777</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LearnDash LearnDash LMS allows SQL Injection.This issue affects LearnDash LMS: from n/a through 4.5.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46992 | TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. Attackers are able to reset serveral critical passwords w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46992</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. Attackers are able to reset serveral critical passwords without authentication by visiting specific pages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24000 | WordPress GamiPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.7 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24000</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in GamiPress gamipress allows SQL Injection.This issue affects GamiPress: from n/a through 2.5.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46978 | TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control.Attackers can reset login password &amp; WIFI passwords without...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46978</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control.Attackers can reset login password &amp; WIFI passwords without authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46979 | TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the enable parameter in the setLedCfg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46979</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the enable parameter in the setLedCfg function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4250 | EventPrime &amp;lt; 3.2.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4250</link><description>The EventPrime WordPress plugin before 3.2.0 does not sanitise and escape some parameters before outputting them back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4251 | EventPrime &amp;lt; 3.2.0 - Booking Creation via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4251</link><description>The EventPrime WordPress plugin before 3.2.0 does not have CSRF checks when creating bookings, which could allow attackers to make logged in users create unwanted bookings via CSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4390 | Popup box &amp;lt; 3.7.2 - Admin+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4390</link><description>The Popup box WordPress plugin before 3.7.2 does not sanitize and escape some Popup fields, which could allow high-privilege users such as an administrator to inject arbitrary web scripts even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in a multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4823 | WP Meta and Date Remover &amp;lt; 2.2.0 - Subscriber+ Stored XSS </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4823</link><description>The WP Meta and Date Remover WordPress plugin before 2.2.0 provides an AJAX endpoint for configuring the plugin settings. This endpoint has no capability checks and does not sanitize the user input, which is then later output unescaped. Allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber change them and perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4836 | WordPress File Sharing Plugin &amp;lt; 2.0.5 - Subscriber+ Sensitive Data and Files Exposure via IDOR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4836</link><description>The WordPress File Sharing Plugin WordPress plugin before 2.0.5 does not check authorization before displaying files and folders, allowing users to gain access to those filed by manipulating IDs which can easily be brute forced</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5098 | Campaign Monitor Forms &amp;lt; 2.5.6 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5098</link><description>The Campaign Monitor Forms by Optin Cat WordPress plugin before 2.5.6 does not prevent users with low privileges (like subscribers) from overwriting any options on a site with the string "true", which could lead to a variety of outcomes, including DoS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5211 | Fattura24 &amp;lt; 6.2.8 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5211</link><description>The Fattura24 WordPress plugin before 6.2.8 does not sanitize or escape the 'id' parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5229 | E2Pdf &amp;lt; 1.20.20 - Admin+ Stored Cross-Site Scriping</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5229</link><description>The E2Pdf WordPress plugin before 1.20.20 does not sanitize and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5237 | Memberlite Shortcodes &amp;lt; 1.3.9 - Contributor+ Stored XSS via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5237</link><description>The Memberlite Shortcodes WordPress plugin before 1.3.9 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in the page, which could allow users with a role as low as contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5238 | EventPrime &amp;lt; 3.2.0 - Reflected HTML Injection on keyword parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5238</link><description>The EventPrime WordPress plugin before 3.2.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to an HTML Injection on the plugin in the search area of the website.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5243 | Login screen manager &amp;lt;= 3.5.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5243</link><description>The Login Screen Manager WordPress plugin through 3.5.2 does not sanitize and escape some of its settings, which could allow high-privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5307 | Photos and Files Contest Gallery  Contact Form &amp;lt; 21.2.8.1 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS via HTTP Headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5307</link><description>The Photos and Files Contest Gallery WordPress plugin before 21.2.8.1 does not sanitise and escape some parameters, which could allow unauthenticated users to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks via certain headers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5360 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt; 1.3.79 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5360</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates WordPress plugin before 1.3.79 does not properly validate uploaded files, which could allow unauthenticated users to upload arbitrary files, such as PHP and achieve RCE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5458 | CITS Support svg, webp Media and TTF,OTF File Upload &amp;lt; 3.0 - Author+ Stored XSS via SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5458</link><description>The CITS Support svg, webp Media and TTF,OTF File Upload WordPress plugin before 3.0 does not sanitise uploaded SVG files, which could allow users with a role as low as Author to upload a malicious SVG containing XSS payloads.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5519 | EventPrime &amp;lt; 3.2.0 - Booking Creation via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5519</link><description>The EventPrime WordPress plugin before 3.2.0 does not have CSRF checks when creating bookings, which could allow attackers to make logged in users create unwanted bookings via CSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25047 | WordPress RSVPMarker Plugin &amp;lt;= 9.9.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25047</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in David F. Carr RSVPMaker rsvpmaker allows SQL Injection.This issue affects RSVPMaker: from n/a through 9.9.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 13:56:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46976 | TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 contains a command injection via the file_name parameter in the UploadFirmwareFile function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46976</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 contains a command injection via the file_name parameter in the UploadFirmwareFile function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 13:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46977 | TOTOLINK LR1200GB V9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the password parameter in the function loginAuth.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46977</link><description>TOTOLINK LR1200GB V9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the password parameter in the function loginAuth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 13:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25045 | WordPress RSVPMarker Plugin &amp;lt;= 9.9.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25045</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in David F. Carr RSVPMaker allows SQL Injection.This issue affects RSVPMaker: from n/a through 9.9.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 13:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5116 | The Live updates from Excel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ipushpull_page' shortcode in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5116</link><description>The Live updates from Excel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ipushpull_page' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 2.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 12:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-1203 | Improper file verification vulnerability in SaAT Netizen installer ver.1.2.0.424 and earlier, and SaAT Netizen ver.1.2.0.8 (Build427) and ea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-1203</link><description>Improper file verification vulnerability in SaAT Netizen installer ver.1.2.0.424 and earlier, and SaAT Netizen ver.1.2.0.8 (Build427) and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to conduct a man-in-the-middle attack. A successful exploitation may result in a malicious file being downloaded and executed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 12:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38994 | An issue in Univention UCS v.5.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and gain privileges via the check_univention_joinstatus f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38994</link><description>An issue in Univention UCS v.5.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and gain privileges via the check_univention_joinstatus function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5073 | The iframe forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'iframe' shortcode in versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5073</link><description>The iframe forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'iframe' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5099 | The HTML filter and csv-file search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in versions up to, and including, 2.7 via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5099</link><description>The HTML filter and csv-file search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in versions up to, and including, 2.7 via the 'src' attribute of the 'csvsearch' shortcode. This allows authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other safe file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5114 | The idbbee plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'idbbee' shortcode in versions up to, and incl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5114</link><description>The idbbee plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'idbbee' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-3007 | Unauthorized Access Vulnerability in Syska SW100 Smartwatch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3007</link><description>The vulnerability exists in Syska SW100 Smartwatch due to an improper implementation and/or configuration of Nordic Device Firmware Update (DFU) which is used for performing Over-The-Air (OTA) firmware updates on the Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) devices. An unauthenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability by setting arbitrary values to handle on the vulnerable device over Bluetooth.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform firmware update, device reboot or data manipulation on the target device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40681 | WordPress Groundhogg Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.11.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40681</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Groundhogg Inc. Groundhogg plugin &lt;=2.7.11.10 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46622 | WordPress WPPizza Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.18.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46622</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ollybach WPPizza  A Restaurant Plugin plugin &lt;=3.18.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46313 | WordPress Zotpress Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.3.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46313</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Katie Seaborn Zotpress plugin &lt;=7.3.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-2968 | LINE@ for Android version 1.0.0 and LINE@ for iOS version 1.0.0 are vulnerable to MITM (man-in-the-middle) attack since the application allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-2968</link><description>LINE@ for Android version 1.0.0 and LINE@ for iOS version 1.0.0 are vulnerable to MITM (man-in-the-middle) attack since the application allows non-SSL/TLS communications. As a result, any API may be invoked from a script injected by a MITM (man-in-the-middle) attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-0897 | LINE for Android version 5.0.2 and earlier and LINE for iOS version 5.0.0 and earlier are vulnerable to MITM (man-in-the-middle) attack sinc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-0897</link><description>LINE for Android version 5.0.2 and earlier and LINE for iOS version 5.0.0 and earlier are vulnerable to MITM (man-in-the-middle) attack since the application allows non-SSL/TLS communications. As a result, any API may be invoked from a script injected by a MITM (man-in-the-middle) attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46312 | WordPress Smart Online Order for Clover Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46312</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Zaytech Smart Online Order for Clover plugin &lt;=1.5.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:23:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5412 | The Image horizontal reel scroll slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5412</link><description>The Image horizontal reel scroll slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 13.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5428 | The Image vertical reel scroll slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5428</link><description>The Image vertical reel scroll slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 9.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5429 | The Information Reel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 10.0 d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5429</link><description>The Information Reel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 10.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5430 | The Jquery news ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.0 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5430</link><description>The Jquery news ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5431 | The Left right image slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5431</link><description>The Left right image slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5433 | The Message ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 9.2 due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5433</link><description>The Message ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 9.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5434 | The Superb slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5434</link><description>The Superb slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 13.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5435 | The Up down image slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5435</link><description>The Up down image slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5436 | The Vertical marquee plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 7.1 du...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5436</link><description>The Vertical marquee plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 7.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5437 | The WP fade in text news plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5437</link><description>The WP fade in text news plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5438 | The wp image slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5438</link><description>The wp image slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5439 | The Wp photo text slider 50 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5439</link><description>The Wp photo text slider 50 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 8.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5464 | The Jquery accordion slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5464</link><description>The Jquery accordion slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 8.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5873 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in pimcore/pimcore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5873</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository pimcore/pimcore prior to 11.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46210 | WordPress WC Captcha Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46210</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WebCource WC Captcha plugin &lt;=1.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 07:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46451 | Best Courier Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the change username field.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46451</link><description>Best Courier Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the change username field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 06:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46361 | Artifex Software jbig2dec v0.20 was discovered to contain a SEGV vulnerability via jbig2_error at /jbig2dec/jbig2.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46361</link><description>Artifex Software jbig2dec v0.20 was discovered to contain a SEGV vulnerability via jbig2_error at /jbig2dec/jbig2.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 05:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45996 | SQL injection vulnerability in Senayan Library Management Systems Slims v.9 and Bulian v.9.6.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45996</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Senayan Library Management Systems Slims v.9 and Bulian v.9.6.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the reborrowLimit parameter in the member_type.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 05:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43139 | An issue in franfinance before v.2.0.27 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the validation.php, and controllers/front/val...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43139</link><description>An issue in franfinance before v.2.0.27 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the validation.php, and controllers/front/validation.php components.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 04:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36263 | Prestashop opartlimitquantity 1.4.5 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection. OpartlimitquantityAlertlimitModuleFrontController::displayAja...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36263</link><description>Prestashop opartlimitquantity 1.4.5 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection. OpartlimitquantityAlertlimitModuleFrontController::displayAjaxPushAlertMessage()` has sensitive SQL calls that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 04:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47174 | Thorn SFTP gateway 3.4.x before 3.4.4 uses Pivotal Spring Framework for Java deserialization of untrusted data, which is not supported by Pi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47174</link><description>Thorn SFTP gateway 3.4.x before 3.4.4 uses Pivotal Spring Framework for Java deserialization of untrusted data, which is not supported by Pivotal, a related issue to CVE-2016-1000027. Also, within the specific context of Thorn SFTP gateway, this leads to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 04:28:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46356 | In the module "CSV Feeds PRO" (csvfeeds) before 2.6.1 from Bl Modules for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The method `SearchA...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46356</link><description>In the module "CSV Feeds PRO" (csvfeeds) before 2.6.1 from Bl Modules for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The method `SearchApiCsv::getProducts()` has sensitive SQL call that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 03:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27846 | SQL injection vulnerability found in PrestaShop themevolty v.4.0.8 and before allow a remote attacker to gain privileges via the tvcmsblog, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27846</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability found in PrestaShop themevolty v.4.0.8 and before allow a remote attacker to gain privileges via the tvcmsblog, tvcmsvideotab, tvcmswishlist, tvcmsbrandlist, tvcmscategorychainslider, tvcmscategoryproduct, tvcmscategoryslider, tvcmspaymenticon, tvcmstestimonial components.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 03:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45378 | In the module "PrestaBlog" (prestablog) version 4.4.7 and before from HDclic for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The script a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45378</link><description>In the module "PrestaBlog" (prestablog) version 4.4.7 and before from HDclic for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The script ajax slider_positions.php has a sensitive SQL call that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 03:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-20110 | JHipster generator-jhipster before 2.23.0 allows a timing attack against validateToken due to a string comparison that stops at the first ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-20110</link><description>JHipster generator-jhipster before 2.23.0 allows a timing attack against validateToken due to a string comparison that stops at the first character that is different. Attackers can guess tokens by brute forcing one character at a time and observing the timing. This of course drastically reduces the search space to a linear amount of guesses based on the token length times the possible characters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25155 | DOMPurify before 1.0.11 allows reverse tabnabbing in demos/hooks-target-blank-demo.html because links lack a 'rel="noopener noreferrer"' att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25155</link><description>DOMPurify before 1.0.11 allows reverse tabnabbing in demos/hooks-target-blank-demo.html because links lack a 'rel="noopener noreferrer"' attribute.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45899 | An issue in the component SuperUserSetuserModuleFrontController:init() of idnovate superuser before v2.4.2 allows attackers to bypass authen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45899</link><description>An issue in the component SuperUserSetuserModuleFrontController:init() of idnovate superuser before v2.4.2 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted HTTP call.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31794 | MuPDF v1.21.1 was discovered to contain an infinite recursion in the component pdf_mark_list_push. This vulnerability allows attackers to ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31794</link><description>MuPDF v1.21.1 was discovered to contain an infinite recursion in the component pdf_mark_list_push. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted PDF file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46040 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in GetSimpleCMS v.3.4.0a allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the a crafted payload to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46040</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in GetSimpleCMS v.3.4.0a allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the a crafted payload to the components.php function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46139 | KernelSU signature validation mismatch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46139</link><description>KernelSU is a Kernel based root solution for Android. Starting in version 0.6.1 and prior to version 0.7.0, if a KernelSU installed device is infected with a malware whose app signing block specially constructed, it can take over root privileges on the device. The vulnerable verification logic actually obtains the signature of the last block with an id of `0x7109871a`, while the verification logic during Android installation is to obtain the first one. In addition to the actual signature upgrade that has been fixed (KSU thought it was V2 but was actually V3), there is also the problem of actual signature downgrading (KSU thought it was V2 but was actually V1). Find a condition in the signature verification logic that will cause the signature not to be found error, and KernelSU does not implement the same conditions, so KSU thinks there is a V2 signature, but the APK signature verification actually uses the V1 signature. This issue is fixed in version 0.7.0. As workarounds, keep the KernelSU manager installed and avoid installing unknown apps.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5861 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in microweber/microweber</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5861</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository microweber/microweber prior to 2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5862 | Missing Authorization in hamza417/inure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5862</link><description>Missing Authorization in GitHub repository hamza417/inure prior to Build95.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5863 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in thorsten/phpmyfaq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5863</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in GitHub repository thorsten/phpmyfaq prior to 3.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5864 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in thorsten/phpmyfaq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5864</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository thorsten/phpmyfaq prior to 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5865 | Insufficient Session Expiration in thorsten/phpmyfaq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5865</link><description>Insufficient Session Expiration in GitHub repository thorsten/phpmyfaq prior to 3.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5866 | Sensitive Cookie in HTTPS Session Without &amp;#x27;Secure&amp;#x27; Attribute in thorsten/phpmyfaq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5866</link><description>Sensitive Cookie in HTTPS Session Without 'Secure' Attribute in GitHub repository thorsten/phpmyfaq prior to 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5867 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in thorsten/phpmyfaq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5867</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository thorsten/phpmyfaq prior to 3.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46138 | JumpServer default admin user email leak password reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46138</link><description>JumpServer is an open source bastion host and maintenance security audit system that complies with 4A specifications. Prior to version 3.8.0, the default email for initial user admin is `admin[@]mycompany[.]com`, and users reset their passwords by sending an email. Currently, the domain `mycompany.com` has not been registered. However, if it is registered in the future, it may affect the password reset functionality. This issue has been patched in version 3.8.0 by changing the default email domain to `example.com`. Those who cannot upgrade may change the default email domain to `example.com` manually.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46129 | xkeys Seal encryption used fixed key for all encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46129</link><description>NATS.io is a high performance open source pub-sub distributed communication technology, built for the cloud, on-premise, IoT, and edge computing. The cryptographic key handling library, nkeys, recently gained support for encryption, not just for signing/authentication. This is used in nats-server 2.10 (Sep 2023) and newer for authentication callouts. In nkeys versions 0.4.0 through 0.4.5, corresponding with NATS server versions 2.10.0 through 2.10.3, the nkeys library's `xkeys` encryption handling logic mistakenly passed an array by value into an internal function, where the function mutated that buffer to populate the encryption key to use. As a result, all encryption was actually to an all-zeros key. This affects encryption only, not signing.  
FIXME: FILL IN IMPACT ON NATS-SERVER AUTH CALLOUT SECURITY. nkeys Go library 0.4.6, corresponding with NATS Server 2.10.4, has a patch for this issue. No known workarounds are available. For any application handling auth callouts in Go, if using the nkeys library, update the dependency, recompile and deploy that in lockstep.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 23:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45672 | Frigate unsafe deserialization in `load_config_with_no_duplicates` of `frigate/util/builtin.py`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45672</link><description>Frigate is an open source network video recorder. Prior to version 0.13.0 Beta 3, an unsafe deserialization vulnerability was identified in the endpoints used to save configurations for Frigate. This can lead to unauthenticated remote code execution. This can be performed through the UI at `/config` or through a direct call to `/api/config/save`. Exploiting this vulnerability requires the attacker to both know very specific information about a user's Frigate server and requires an authenticated user to be tricked into clicking a specially crafted link to their Frigate instance. This vulnerability could exploited by an attacker under the following circumstances: Frigate publicly exposed to the internet (even with authentication); attacker knows the address of a user's Frigate instance; attacker crafts a specialized page which links to the user's Frigate instance; attacker finds a way to get an authenticated user to visit their specialized page and click the button/link. Input is initially accepted through `http.py`. The user-provided input is then parsed and loaded by `load_config_with_no_duplicates`. However, `load_config_with_no_duplicates` does not sanitize this input by merit of using `yaml.loader.Loader` which can instantiate custom constructors. A provided payload will be executed directly at `frigate/util/builtin.py:110`. This issue may lead to pre-authenticated Remote Code Execution. Version 0.13.0 Beta 3 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 22:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46502 | An issue in OpenCRX v.5.2.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46502</link><description>An issue in OpenCRX v.5.2.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 22:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45670 | Frigate cross-site request forgery in `config_save` and `config_set` request handlers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45670</link><description>Frigate is an open source network video recorder. Prior to version 0.13.0 Beta 3, the `config/save` and `config/set` endpoints of Frigate do not implement any CSRF protection. This makes it possible for a request sourced from another site to update the configuration of the Frigate server (e.g. via "drive-by" attack). Exploiting this vulnerability requires the attacker to both know very specific information about a user's Frigate server and requires an authenticated user to be tricked into clicking a specially crafted link to their Frigate instance. This vulnerability could exploited by an attacker under the following circumstances: Frigate publicly exposed to the internet (even with authentication); attacker knows the address of a user's Frigate instance; attacker crafts a specialized page which links to the user's Frigate instance; attacker finds a way to get an authenticated user to visit their specialized page and click the button/link. This issue can lead to arbitrary configuration updates for the Frigate server, resulting in denial of service and possible data exfiltration. Version 0.13.0 Beta 3 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 22:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45671 | Frigate reflected XSS through `/&amp;lt;camera_name&amp;gt;` API endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45671</link><description>Frigate is an open source network video recorder. Prior to version 0.13.0 Beta 3, there is a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in any API endpoints reliant on the `/&lt;camera_name&gt;` base path as values provided for the path are not sanitized. Exploiting this vulnerability requires the attacker to both know very specific information about a user's Frigate server and requires an authenticated user to be tricked into clicking a specially crafted link to their Frigate instance. This vulnerability could exploited by an attacker under the following circumstances: Frigate publicly exposed to the internet (even with authentication); attacker knows the address of a user's Frigate instance; attacker crafts a specialized page which links to the user's Frigate instance; attacker finds a way to get an authenticated user to visit their specialized page and click the button/link. As the reflected values included in the URL are not sanitized or escaped, this permits execution arbitrary Javascript payloads. Version 0.13.0 Beta 3 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 22:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43798 | BigBlueButton Blind SSRF When Uploading Presentation (mitigation bypass)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43798</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom. BigBlueButton prior to versions 2.6.12 and 2.7.0-rc.1 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF). This issue is a bypass of CVE-2023-33176. A patch in versions 2.6.12 and 2.7.0-rc.1 disabled follow redirect at `httpclient.execute` since the software no longer has to follow it when using `finalUrl`. There are no known workarounds. We recommend upgrading to a patched version of BigBlueButton.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 22:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44397 | CloudExplorer Lite permission bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44397</link><description>CloudExplorer Lite is an open source, lightweight cloud management platform. Prior to version 1.4.1, the gateway filter of CloudExplorer Lite uses a controller with path starting with `matching/API/`, which can cause a permission bypass. Version 1.4.1 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 22:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43797 | BigBlueButton Stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability at Guest Lobby</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43797</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom. Prior to versions 2.6.11 and 2.7.0-beta.3, Guest Lobby was vulnerable to cross-site scripting when users wait to enter the meeting due to inserting unsanitized messages to the element using unsafe innerHTML. Text sanitizing was added for lobby messages starting in versions 2.6.11 and 2.7.0-beta.3. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 22:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46478 | An issue in minCal v.1.0.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the customer_data parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46478</link><description>An issue in minCal v.1.0.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the customer_data parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 22:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42323 | Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in DouHaocms v.3.3 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the adminAction.cl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42323</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in DouHaocms v.3.3 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the adminAction.class.php file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 21:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-39172 | A stored XSS in the process overview (bersicht zugewiesener Vorgaenge) in mbsupport openVIVA c2 20220101 allows a remote, authenticated, low...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39172</link><description>A stored XSS in the process overview (bersicht zugewiesener Vorgaenge) in mbsupport openVIVA c2 20220101 allows a remote, authenticated, low-privileged attacker to execute arbitrary code in the victim's browser via name field of a process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 21:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45956 | An issue discovered in Govee LED Strip v3.00.42 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted Move and MoveWithOnoff commands.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45956</link><description>An issue discovered in Govee LED Strip v3.00.42 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted Move and MoveWithOnoff commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 21:47:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5349 | Draw while calling getdrawinfo()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5349</link><description>A memory leak flaw was found in ruby-magick, an interface between Ruby and ImageMagick. This issue can lead to a denial of service (DOS) by memory exhaustion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 20:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43792 | baserCMS Code Injection Vulnerability in Mail Form Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43792</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. In versions 4.6.0 through 4.7.6, there is a Code Injection vulnerability in the mail form of baserCMS. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 20:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43648 | baserCMS Directory Traversal vulnerability in Form submission data management Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43648</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. Prior to version 4.8.0, there is a Directory Traversal Vulnerability in the form submission data management feature of baserCMS. Version 4.8.0 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43649 | baserCMS CSRF vulnerability in Content preview Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43649</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. Prior to version 4.8.0, there is a cross site request forgery vulnerability in the content preview feature of baserCMS. Version 4.8.0 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36767 | tinyfiledialogs (aka tiny file dialogs) before 3.8.0 allows shell metacharacters in titles, messages, and other input data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36767</link><description>tinyfiledialogs (aka tiny file dialogs) before 3.8.0 allows shell metacharacters in titles, messages, and other input data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42804 | BigBlueButton Path Traversal  Reading Certain File Extensions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42804</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom. BigBlueButton prior to version 2.6.0-beta.1 has a path traversal vulnerability that allows an attacker with a valid starting folder path, to traverse and read other files without authentication, assuming the files have certain extensions (txt, swf, svg, png). In version 2.6.0-beta.1, input validation was added on the parameters being passed and dangerous characters are stripped. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43647 | baserCMS Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in File upload Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43647</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. Prior to version 4.8.0, there is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the file upload feature of baserCMS. Version 4.8.0 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47104 | tinyfiledialogs (aka tiny file dialogs) before 3.15.0 allows shell metacharacters (such as a backquote or a dollar sign) in titles, messages...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47104</link><description>tinyfiledialogs (aka tiny file dialogs) before 3.15.0 allows shell metacharacters (such as a backquote or a dollar sign) in titles, messages, and other input data. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2020-36767, which only considered single and double quote characters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42803 | BigBlueButton Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42803</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom. BigBlueButton prior to version 2.6.0-beta.2 is vulnerable to unrestricted file upload, where the insertDocument API call does not validate the given file extension before saving the file, and does not remove it in case of validation failures. BigBlueButton 2.6.0-beta.2 contains a patch. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41891 | FlyteAdmin SQL Injection in List Filters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41891</link><description>FlyteAdmin is the control plane for Flyte responsible for managing entities and administering workflow executions. Prior to version 1.1.124, list endpoints on FlyteAdmin have a SQL vulnerability where a malicious user can send a REST request with custom SQL statements as list filters. The attacker needs to have access to the FlyteAdmin installation, typically either behind a VPN or authentication. Version 1.1.124 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47101 | The installer (aka openvpn-client-installer) in Securepoint SSL VPN Client before 2.0.40 allows local privilege escalation during installati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47101</link><description>The installer (aka openvpn-client-installer) in Securepoint SSL VPN Client before 2.0.40 allows local privilege escalation during installation or repair.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21301 | In ActivityManagerService, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21301</link><description>In ActivityManagerService, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21302 | In Package Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21302</link><description>In Package Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21303 | In Content, here is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21303</link><description>In Content, here is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21304 | In Content Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21304</link><description>In Content Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21305 | In Content, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21305</link><description>In Content, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21367 | In Scudo, there is a possible way to exploit certain heap OOB read/write issues due to an insecure implementation/design. This could lead to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21367</link><description>In Scudo, there is a possible way to exploit certain heap OOB read/write issues due to an insecure implementation/design. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21368 | In Audio, there is a possible out of bounds read due to missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21368</link><description>In Audio, there is a possible out of bounds read due to missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21369 | In Usage Access, there is a possible way to display a Settings usage access restriction toggle screen due to a permissions bypass. This coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21369</link><description>In Usage Access, there is a possible way to display a Settings usage access restriction toggle screen due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21370 | In the Security Element API, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21370</link><description>In the Security Element API, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21371 | In Secure Element, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21371</link><description>In Secure Element, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21372 | In libdexfile, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21372</link><description>In libdexfile, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21373 | In Telephony, there is a possible way for a guest user to change the preferred SIM due to a missing permission check. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21373</link><description>In Telephony, there is a possible way for a guest user to change the preferred SIM due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21374 | In System UI, there is a possible factory reset protection bypass due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21374</link><description>In System UI, there is a possible factory reset protection bypass due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21375 | In Sysproxy, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer underflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21375</link><description>In Sysproxy, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer underflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21376 | In Telephony, there is a possible way to retrieve the ICCID due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local information disclosur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21376</link><description>In Telephony, there is a possible way to retrieve the ICCID due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21377 | In SELinux Policy, there is a possible restriction bypass due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local information disclosure with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21377</link><description>In SELinux Policy, there is a possible restriction bypass due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21378 | In Telecomm, there is a possible way to silence the ring for calls of secondary users due to a missing permission check. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21378</link><description>In Telecomm, there is a possible way to silence the ring for calls of secondary users due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21379 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure in the B...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21379</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure in the Bluetooth server with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21380 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21380</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21381 | In Media Resource Manager, there is a possible local arbitrary code execution due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21381</link><description>In Media Resource Manager, there is a possible local arbitrary code execution due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21382 | In Content Resolver, there is a possible method to access metadata about existing content providers on the device due to a missing permissio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21382</link><description>In Content Resolver, there is a possible method to access metadata about existing content providers on the device due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21383 | In Settings, there is a possible way for the user to unintentionally send extra data due to an unclear prompt. This could lead to local info...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21383</link><description>In Settings, there is a possible way for the user to unintentionally send extra data due to an unclear prompt. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21384 | In Package Manager, there is a possible possible permissions bypass due to an unsafe PendingIntent. This could lead to local information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21384</link><description>In Package Manager, there is a possible possible permissions bypass due to an unsafe PendingIntent. This could lead to local information disclosure with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21385 | In Whitechapel, there is a possible out of bounds read due to memory corruption. This could lead to local information disclosure with no add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21385</link><description>In Whitechapel, there is a possible out of bounds read due to memory corruption. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21387 | In User Backup Manager, there is a possible way to leak a token to bypass user confirmation for backup due to log information disclosure. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21387</link><description>In User Backup Manager, there is a possible way to leak a token to bypass user confirmation for backup due to log information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21388 | In Settings, there is a possible restriction bypass due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21388</link><description>In Settings, there is a possible restriction bypass due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21389 | In Settings, there is a possible bypass of profile owner restrictions due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21389</link><description>In Settings, there is a possible bypass of profile owner restrictions due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21390 | In Sim, there is a possible way to evade mobile preference restrictions due to a permission bypass. This could lead to local escalation of p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21390</link><description>In Sim, there is a possible way to evade mobile preference restrictions due to a permission bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21391 | In Messaging, there is a possible way to disable the messaging application due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21391</link><description>In Messaging, there is a possible way to disable the messaging application due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21392 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible way to corrupt memory due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege when conne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21392</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible way to corrupt memory due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege when connecting to a Bluetooth device with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21393 | In Settings, there is a possible way for the user to change SIM due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21393</link><description>In Settings, there is a possible way for the user to change SIM due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21394 | In Telecomm, there is a possible bypass of a multi user security boundary due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21394</link><description>In Telecomm, there is a possible bypass of a multi user security boundary due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21395 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a use after free. This could lead to remote information disclosure over Bluetoot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21395</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a use after free. This could lead to remote information disclosure over Bluetooth with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21396 | In Activity Manager, there is a possible background activity launch due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21396</link><description>In Activity Manager, there is a possible background activity launch due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21397 | In Setup Wizard, there is a possible way to save a WiFi network due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21397</link><description>In Setup Wizard, there is a possible way to save a WiFi network due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21398 | In sdksandbox, there is a possible strandhogg style overlay attack due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21398</link><description>In sdksandbox, there is a possible strandhogg style overlay attack due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40101 | In collapse of canonicalize_md.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40101</link><description>In collapse of canonicalize_md.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45780 | In Print Service, there is a possible background activity launch due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45780</link><description>In Print Service, there is a possible background activity launch due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21297 | In SEPolicy, there is a possible way to access the factory MAC address due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21297</link><description>In SEPolicy, there is a possible way to access the factory MAC address due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21298 | In Slice, there is a possible disclosure of installed applications due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21298</link><description>In Slice, there is a possible disclosure of installed applications due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21299 | In Package Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21299</link><description>In Package Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21300 | In PackageManager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21300</link><description>In PackageManager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21306 | In ContentService, there is a possible way to read installed sync content providers due to side channel information disclosure. This could l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21306</link><description>In ContentService, there is a possible way to read installed sync content providers due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21307 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible way for a paired Bluetooth device to access a long term identifier for an Android device due to a permissi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21307</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible way for a paired Bluetooth device to access a long term identifier for an Android device due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21308 | In Composer, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21308</link><description>In Composer, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21309 | In libcore, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no ad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21309</link><description>In libcore, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21310 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21310</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21311 | In Settings, there is a possible way to control private DNS settings from a secondary user due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21311</link><description>In Settings, there is a possible way to control private DNS settings from a secondary user due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21312 | In IntentResolver, there is a possible cross-user media read due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21312</link><description>In IntentResolver, there is a possible cross-user media read due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21313 | In Core, there is a possible way to forward calls without user knowledge due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21313</link><description>In Core, there is a possible way to forward calls without user knowledge due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21314 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21314</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21315 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21315</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21316 | In Content, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21316</link><description>In Content, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21317 | In ContentService, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21317</link><description>In ContentService, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21318 | In Content, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21318</link><description>In Content, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21319 | In UsageStatsService, there is a possible way to read installed 3rd party apps due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21319</link><description>In UsageStatsService, there is a possible way to read installed 3rd party apps due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21320 | In Device Policy, there is a possible way to verify if a particular admin app is registered on the device due to side channel information di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21320</link><description>In Device Policy, there is a possible way to verify if a particular admin app is registered on the device due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21321 | In Package Manager, there is a possible cross-user settings disclosure due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21321</link><description>In Package Manager, there is a possible cross-user settings disclosure due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21323 | In Activity Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel inform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21323</link><description>In Activity Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21324 | In Package Installer, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel infor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21324</link><description>In Package Installer, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21325 | In Settings, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21325</link><description>In Settings, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21326 | In Package Manager Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21326</link><description>In Package Manager Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21327 | In Permission Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel info...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21327</link><description>In Permission Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21328 | In Package Installer, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to a missing permissi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21328</link><description>In Package Installer, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21329 | In Activity Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed due to a missing permission check. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21329</link><description>In Activity Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21330 | In Overlay Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21330</link><description>In Overlay Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21331 | In InputMethod, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21331</link><description>In InputMethod, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21332 | In Text Services, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21332</link><description>In Text Services, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21333 | In Text Services, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21333</link><description>In Text Services, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21334 | In App Ops Service, there is a possible disclosure of information about installed packages due to a logic error in the code. This could lead...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21334</link><description>In App Ops Service, there is a possible disclosure of information about installed packages due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21335 | In Settings, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21335</link><description>In Settings, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21336 | In Input Method, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21336</link><description>In Input Method, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21337 | In InputMethod, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21337</link><description>In InputMethod, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21338 | In Input Method, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21338</link><description>In Input Method, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21339 | In Minikin, there is a possible way to trigger ANR by showing a malicious message due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to remote deni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21339</link><description>In Minikin, there is a possible way to trigger ANR by showing a malicious message due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21340 | In Telecomm, there is a possible way to get the call state due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21340</link><description>In Telecomm, there is a possible way to get the call state due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21341 | In Permission Manager, there is a possible way to bypass required permissions due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21341</link><description>In Permission Manager, there is a possible way to bypass required permissions due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21342 | In Speech, there is a possible way to bypass background activity launch due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21342</link><description>In Speech, there is a possible way to bypass background activity launch due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21343 | In ActivityStarter, there is a possible background activity launch due to an unsafe PendingIntent. This could lead to local escalation of pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21343</link><description>In ActivityStarter, there is a possible background activity launch due to an unsafe PendingIntent. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21344 | In Job Scheduler, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21344</link><description>In Job Scheduler, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21345 | In Game Manager Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21345</link><description>In Game Manager Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21346 | In the Device Idle Controller, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side chan...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21346</link><description>In the Device Idle Controller, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21347 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21347</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21348 | In Window Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21348</link><description>In Window Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21349 | In Package Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21349</link><description>In Package Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21350 | In Media Projection, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel inform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21350</link><description>In Media Projection, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21351 | In Activity Manager, there is a possible background activity launch due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21351</link><description>In Activity Manager, there is a possible background activity launch due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21352 | In NFA, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21352</link><description>In NFA, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21353 | In NFA, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no addit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21353</link><description>In NFA, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21354 | In Package Manager Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21354</link><description>In Package Manager Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21355 | In libaudioclient, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21355</link><description>In libaudioclient, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21356 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) code exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21356</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21357 | In NFC, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21357</link><description>In NFC, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21358 | In UWB Google, there is a possible way for a malicious app to masquerade as system app com.android.uwb.resources due to improperly used cryp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21358</link><description>In UWB Google, there is a possible way for a malicious app to masquerade as system app com.android.uwb.resources due to improperly used crypto. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21359 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure in the B...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21359</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure in the Bluetooth server with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21360 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21360</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21361 | In Bluetooth, there is a possibility of code-execution due to a use after free. This could lead to paired device escalation of privilege in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21361</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possibility of code-execution due to a use after free. This could lead to paired device escalation of privilege in the privileged Bluetooth process with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21362 | In Usage, there is a possible permanent DoS due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21362</link><description>In Usage, there is a possible permanent DoS due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21364 | In ContactsProvider, there is a possible crash loop due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local persistent denial of service in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21364</link><description>In ContactsProvider, there is a possible crash loop due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local persistent denial of service in the Phone app with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21365 | In Contacts, there is a possible crash loop due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local denial of service in the Phone app with Use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21365</link><description>In Contacts, there is a possible crash loop due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local denial of service in the Phone app with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21366 | In Scudo, there is a possible way for an attacker to predict heap allocation patterns due to insecure implementation/design. This could lead...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21366</link><description>In Scudo, there is a possible way for an attacker to predict heap allocation patterns due to insecure implementation/design. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36920 | Clickjacking vulnerability in SAP Enable Now</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36920</link><description>In SAP Enable Now - versions WPB_MANAGER 1.0, WPB_MANAGER_CE 10, WPB_MANAGER_HANA 10, ENABLE_NOW_CONSUMP_DEL 1704, the X-FRAME-OPTIONS response header is not implemented, allowing an unauthenticated attacker to attempt clickjacking, which could result in disclosure or modification of information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47090 | NATS nats-server before 2.9.23 and 2.10.x before 2.10.2 has an authentication bypass. An implicit $G user in an authorization block can some...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47090</link><description>NATS nats-server before 2.9.23 and 2.10.x before 2.10.2 has an authentication bypass. An implicit $G user in an authorization block can sometimes be used for unauthenticated access, even when the intention of the configuration was for each user to have an account. The earliest affected version is 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-39810 | In NFC, there is a possible way to setup a default contactless payment app without user consent due to a missing permission check. This coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39810</link><description>In NFC, there is a possible way to setup a default contactless payment app without user consent due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-20264 | In Usage Stats Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions due to side channel info...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20264</link><description>In Usage Stats Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21293 | In PackageManagerNative, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21293</link><description>In PackageManagerNative, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21294 | In Slice, there is a possible disclosure of installed packages due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information discl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21294</link><description>In Slice, there is a possible disclosure of installed packages due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:34:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21295 | In SliceManagerService, there is a possible way to check if a content provider is installed due to a missing null check. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21295</link><description>In SliceManagerService, there is a possible way to check if a content provider is installed due to a missing null check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:34:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21296 | In Permission, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21296</link><description>In Permission, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44323 | PDF Jbig2 memory-corruption Vulnerability - MSFT T5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44323</link><description>Adobe Acrobat for Edge version 118.0.2088.46 (and earlier) is affected by a Use After Free vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker could leverage this vulnerability to achieve an application denial-of-service in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48189 | An SMM driver input validation vulnerability in the BIOS of some ThinkPad models could allow an attacker with local access and elevated priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48189</link><description>An SMM driver input validation vulnerability in the BIOS of some ThinkPad models could allow an attacker with local access and elevated privileges to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4575 | A vulnerability due to improper write protection of UEFI variables was reported in the BIOS of some ThinkPad models could allow an attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4575</link><description>A vulnerability due to improper write protection of UEFI variables was reported in the BIOS of some ThinkPad models could allow an attacker with physical or local access and elevated privileges the ability to bypass Secure Boot.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4573 | An SMI handler input validation vulnerability in the ThinkPad X1 Fold Gen 1 could allow an attacker with local access and elevated privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4573</link><description>An SMI handler input validation vulnerability in the ThinkPad X1 Fold Gen 1 could allow an attacker with local access and elevated privileges to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4574 | An SMI handler input validation vulnerability in the BIOS of some ThinkPad models could allow an attacker with local access and elevated pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4574</link><description>An SMI handler input validation vulnerability in the BIOS of some ThinkPad models could allow an attacker with local access and elevated privileges to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4964 | Potential open redirect vulnerability in opentext SMAX and AMX product. </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4964</link><description>Potential open redirect vulnerability
in opentext Service Management Automation X
(SMAX)  versions 2020.05, 2020.08,
2020.11, 2021.02, 2021.05, 2021.08, 2021.11, 2022.05, 2022.11 and opentext Asset
Management X (AMX) versions 2021.08, 2021.11, 2022.05, 2022.11. The
vulnerability could allow attackers to redirect a user to
malicious websites.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5049 | The Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'rafflepress' and 'raffl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5049</link><description>The Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'rafflepress' and 'rafflepress_gutenberg' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.12.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on 'giframe' user supplied attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5164 | The Bellows Accordion Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5164</link><description>The Bellows Accordion Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 1.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5199 | The PHP to Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable Local File Inclusion to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 0.3 via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5199</link><description>The PHP to Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable Local File Inclusion to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 0.3 via the 'php-to-page' shortcode. This allows authenticated attackers with subscriber-level permissions or above, to include local file and potentially execute code on the server. While subscribers may need to poison log files or otherwise get a file installed in order to achieve remote code execution, author and above users can upload files by default and achieve remote code execution easily.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5250 | The Grid Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in versions up to, and including, 1.3.2 via a shortcode attribute. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5250</link><description>The Grid Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in versions up to, and including, 1.3.2 via a shortcode attribute. This allows subscriber-level, and above, attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where PHP files with arbitrary content can be uploaded and included. This is limited to .php files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5251 | The Grid Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to a missing capability check on ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5251</link><description>The Grid Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'grid_plus_save_layout_callback' and 'grid_plus_delete_callback' functions in versions up to, and including, 1.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber privileges or above, to add, update or delete grid layout.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5252 | The FareHarbor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 3.6.7 due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5252</link><description>The FareHarbor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 3.6.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5315 | The Google Maps made Simple plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5315</link><description>The Google Maps made Simple plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 0.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5335 | The Buzzsprout Podcasting plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'buzzsprout' shortcode in versions up to, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5335</link><description>The Buzzsprout Podcasting plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'buzzsprout' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5362 | The Carousel, Recent Post Slider and Banner Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'spice_post_slider'...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5362</link><description>The Carousel, Recent Post Slider and Banner Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'spice_post_slider' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5565 | The Shortcode Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'shortmenu' shortcode in versions up to, and includ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5565</link><description>The Shortcode Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'shortmenu' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5566 | The Simple Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 1.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5566</link><description>The Simple Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 1.0.20 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5583 | The WP Simple Galleries plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.34 via deserializatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5583</link><description>The WP Simple Galleries plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.34 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'wpsimplegallery_gallery' post meta via 'wpsgallery' shortcode. This allows authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5666 | The Accordion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tcpaccordion' shortcode in all versions up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5666</link><description>The Accordion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tcpaccordion' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5843 | The Ads by datafeedr.com plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 1.1.3 via the 'dfads_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5843</link><description>The Ads by datafeedr.com plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 1.1.3 via the 'dfads_ajax_load_ads' function. This allows unauthenticated attackers to execute code on the server. The parameters of the callable function are limited, they cannot be specified arbitrarily.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5832 | Improper Input Validation in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5832</link><description>Improper Input Validation in GitHub repository mintplex-labs/anything-llm prior to 0.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 12:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5833 | Improper Access Control in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5833</link><description>Improper Access Control in GitHub repository mintplex-labs/anything-llm prior to 0.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 12:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42431 | Potential XSS on user preferences page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42431</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in BlueSpiceAvatars extension of BlueSpice allows logged in user to inject arbitrary HTML into the profile image dialog on Special:Preferences. This only applies to the genuine user context.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 10:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5844 | Unverified Password Change in pimcore/admin-ui-classic-bundle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5844</link><description>Unverified Password Change in GitHub repository pimcore/admin-ui-classic-bundle prior to 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 10:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45798 | Yettiesoft VestCert Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45798</link><description>In Yettiesoft VestCert versions 2.36 to 2.5.29, a vulnerability exists due to improper validation of third-party modules. This allows malicious actors to load arbitrary third-party modules, leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 06:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45799 | MLSoft TCO!stream Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45799</link><description>In MLSoft TCO!stream versions 8.0.22.1115 and below, a vulnerability exists due to insufficient permission validation. This allows an attacker to make the victim download and execute arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 06:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45797 | DreamSecurity MagicLine Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45797</link><description>A Buffer overflow vulnerability in DreamSecurity MagicLine4NX versions 1.0.0.1 to 1.0.0.26 allows an attacker to remotely execute code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 06:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45746 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability in Movable Type series allows a remote authenticated attacker to inject an arbitrary script. Affected pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45746</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability in Movable Type series allows a remote authenticated attacker to inject an arbitrary script. Affected products/versions are as follows: Movable Type 7 r.5405 and earlier (Movable Type 7 Series), Movable Type Advanced 7 r.5405 and earlier (Movable Type 7 Series), Movable Type Premium 1.58 and earlier, Movable Type Premium Advanced 1.58 and earlier, Movable Type Cloud Edition (Version 7) r.5405 and earlier, and Movable Type Premium Cloud Edition 1.58 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 05:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44141 | Inkdrop prior to v5.6.0 allows a local attacker to conduct a code injection attack by having a legitimate user open a specially crafted mark...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44141</link><description>Inkdrop prior to v5.6.0 allows a local attacker to conduct a code injection attack by having a legitimate user open a specially crafted markdown file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 03:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46866 | In International Color Consortium DemoIccMAX 79ecb74, CIccCLUT::Interp3d in IccProfLib/IccTagLut.cpp in libSampleICC.a attempts to access ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46866</link><description>In International Color Consortium DemoIccMAX 79ecb74, CIccCLUT::Interp3d in IccProfLib/IccTagLut.cpp in libSampleICC.a attempts to access array elements at out-of-bounds indexes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46867 | In International Color Consortium DemoIccMAX 79ecb74, CIccXformMatrixTRC::GetCurve in IccCmm.cpp in libSampleICC.a has a NULL pointer derefe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46867</link><description>In International Color Consortium DemoIccMAX 79ecb74, CIccXformMatrixTRC::GetCurve in IccCmm.cpp in libSampleICC.a has a NULL pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-25736 | Windows kube-proxy LoadBalancer contention</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25736</link><description>Kube-proxy
 on Windows can unintentionally forward traffic to local processes 
listening on the same port (spec.ports[*].port) as a LoadBalancer 
Service when the LoadBalancer controller
 does not set the status.loadBalancer.ingress[].ip field. Clusters 
where the LoadBalancer controller sets the 
status.loadBalancer.ingress[].ip field are unaffected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46865 | /api/v1/company/upload-logo in CompanyController.php in crater through 6.0.6 allows a superadmin to execute arbitrary PHP code by placing th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46865</link><description>/api/v1/company/upload-logo in CompanyController.php in crater through 6.0.6 allows a superadmin to execute arbitrary PHP code by placing this code into an image/png IDAT chunk of a Company Logo image.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:05:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5842 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in dolibarr/dolibarr</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5842</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository dolibarr/dolibarr prior to 16.0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:05:55 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>