<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:48:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-66412 | Angular Stored XSS Vulnerability via SVG Animation, SVG URL and MathML Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66412</link><description>Angular is a development platform for building mobile and desktop web applications using TypeScript/JavaScript and other languages. Prior to 21.0.2, 20.3.15, and 19.2.17, A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in the Angular Template Compiler. It occurs because the compiler's internal security schema is incomplete, allowing attackers to bypass Angular's built-in security sanitization. Specifically, the schema fails to classify certain URL-holding attributes (e.g., those that could contain javascript: URLs) as requiring strict URL security, enabling the injection of malicious scripts. This vulnerability is fixed in 21.0.2, 20.3.15, and 19.2.17.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66415 | fastify-reply-from bypass of reply forwarding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66415</link><description>fastify-reply-from is a Fastify plugin to forward the current HTTP request to another server. Prior to 12.5.0, by crafting a malicious URL, an attacker could access routes that are not allowed, even though the reply.from is defined for specific routes in @fastify/reply-from. This vulnerability is fixed in 12.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66405 | Portkey.ai Gateway: Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in Custom Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66405</link><description>Portkey.ai Gateway is a blazing fast AI Gateway with integrated guardrails. Prior to 1.14.0, the gateway determined the destination baseURL by prioritizing the value in the x-portkey-custom-host request header. The proxy route then appends the client-specified path to perform an external fetch. This can be maliciously used by users for SSRF attacks. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.14.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:36:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66410 | Gin-vue-admin has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66410</link><description>Gin-vue-admin is a backstage management system based on vue and gin. In 2.8.6 and earlier, attackers can delete any file on the server at will, causing damage or unavailability of server resources. Attackers can control the 'FileMd5' parameter to delete any file and folder.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:36:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66313 | ChurchCRM vulnerable to a time-based blind SQL injection via the 1FieldSec parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66313</link><description>ChurchCRM is an open-source church management system. In ChurchCRM 6.2.0 and earlier, there is a time-based blind SQL injection in the handling of the 1FieldSec parameter. Injecting SLEEP() causes deterministic server-side delays, proving the value is incorporated into a SQL query without proper parameterization. The issue allows data exfiltration and modification via blind techniques.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66400 | mdast-util-to-hast unsanitized class attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66400</link><description>mdast-util-to-hast is an mdast utility to transform to hast. From 13.0.0 to before 13.2.1, multiple (unprefixed) classnames could be added in markdown source by using character references. This could make rendered user supplied markdown code elements appear like the rest of the page. This vulnerability is fixed in 13.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66403 | FileRise Vulnerable to Stored XSS via SVG Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66403</link><description>FileRise is a self-hosted web-based file manager with multi-file upload, editing, and batch operations. Prior to 2.2.3, a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Filerise application due to improper handling of uploaded SVG files. The application accepts user-supplied SVG uploads without sanitizing or restricting embedded script content. When a malicious SVG containing inline JavaScript or event-based payloads is uploaded, it is later rendered directly in the browser whenever viewed within the application. Because SVGs are XML-based and allow scripting, they execute in the origin context of the application, enabling full stored XSS. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66309 | Grav vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Reflected endpoint /admin/pages/[page], parameter data[header][content][items], located in the &amp;quot;Blog Config&amp;quot; tab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66309</link><description>This admin plugin for Grav is an HTML user interface that provides a convenient way to configure Grav and easily create and modify pages. Prior to 1.11.0-beta.1, a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the /admin/pages/[page] endpoint of the Grav application. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into the data[header][content][items] parameter. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.11.0-beta.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66310 | Grav vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Stored endpoint `/admin/pages/[page]` parameter `data[header][template]` in Advanced Tab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66310</link><description>This admin plugin for Grav is an HTML user interface that provides a convenient way to configure Grav and easily create and modify pages. Prior to 1.11.0-beta.1, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the /admin/pages/[page] endpoint of the Grav application. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into the data[header][template] parameter. The script is saved within the page's frontmatter and executed automatically whenever the affected content is rendered in the administrative interface or frontend view. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.11.0-beta.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66311 | Grav vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Stored endpoint `/admin/pages/[page]` in Multiples parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66311</link><description>This admin plugin for Grav is an HTML user interface that provides a convenient way to configure Grav and easily create and modify pages. Prior to 1.11.0-beta.1, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the /admin/pages/[page] endpoint of the Grav application. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into the data[header][metadata], data[header][taxonomy][category], and data[header][taxonomy][tag] parameters. These scripts are stored in the page frontmatter and executed automatically whenever the affected page is accessed or rendered in the administrative interface. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.11.0-beta.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66312 | Grav Admin Plugin vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Stored endpoint `/admin/accounts/groups/[group]` parameter `data[readableName]`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66312</link><description>This admin plugin for Grav is an HTML user interface that provides a convenient way to configure Grav and easily create and modify pages. Prior to 1.11.0-beta.1, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the /admin/accounts/groups/Grupo endpoint of the Grav application. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into the data[readableName] parameter. The injected scripts are stored on the server and executed automatically whenever the affected page is accessed by users, posing a significant security risk. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.11.0-beta.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66308 | Grav Admin Plugin vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Stored endpoint `/admin/config/site` parameter `data[taxonomies]`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66308</link><description>This admin plugin for Grav is an HTML user interface that provides a convenient way to configure Grav and easily create and modify pages. Prior to 1.11.0-beta.1, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the /admin/config/site endpoint of the Grav application. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into the data[taxonomies] parameter. The injected payload is stored on the server and automatically executed in the browser of any user who accesses the affected site configuration, resulting in a persistent attack vector. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.11.0-beta.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66307 | Grav Admin Plugin vulnerable to User Enumeration &amp;amp; Email Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66307</link><description>This admin plugin for Grav is an HTML user interface that provides a convenient way to configure Grav and easily create and modify pages. Prior to 1.11.0-beta.1, a user enumeration and email disclosure vulnerability exists in Grav. The "Forgot Password" functionality at /admin/forgot leaks information about valid usernames and their associated email addresses through distinct server responses. This allows an attacker to enumerate users and disclose sensitive email addresses, which can be leveraged for targeted attacks such as password spraying, phishing, or social engineering. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.11.0-beta.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66306 | Grav vulnerable to Information Disclosure via IDOR in Grav Admin Panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66306</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, there is an IDOR (Insecure Direct Object Reference) vulnerability in the Grav CMS Admin Panel which allows low-privilege users to access sensitive information from other accounts. Although direct account takeover is not possible, admin email addresses and other metadata can be exposed, increasing the risk of phishing, credential stuffing, and social engineering. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:56:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66304 | Grav Exposes Password Hashes Leading to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66304</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, users with read access on the user account management section of the admin panel can view the password hashes of all users, including the admin user. This exposure can potentially lead to privilege escalation if an attacker can crack these password hashes. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66305 | Grav vulnerable to Denial of Service via Improper Input Handling in &amp;#x27;Supported&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66305</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability was identified in the "Languages" submenu of the Grav admin configuration panel (/admin/config/system). Specifically, the Supported parameter fails to properly validate user input. If a malformed value is inserted—such as a single forward slash (/) or an XSS test string—it causes a fatal regular expression parsing error on the server. This leads to application-wide failure due to the use of the preg_match() function with an improperly constructed regular expression, resulting in an error. Once triggered, the site becomes completely unavailable to all users. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66302 | Grav vulnerable to Path Traversal allowing server files backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66302</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, A path traversal vulnerability has been identified in Grav CMS, allowing authenticated attackers with administrative privileges to read arbitrary files on the underlying server filesystem. This vulnerability arises due to insufficient input sanitization in the backup tool, where user-supplied paths are not properly restricted, enabling access to files outside the intended webroot directory. The impact of this vulnerability depends on the privileges of the user account running the application. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66303 | Grav is vulnerable to a DOS on the admin panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66303</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, A Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability has been identified in Grav related to the handling of scheduled_at parameters. Specifically, the application fails to properly sanitize input for cron expressions. By manipulating the scheduled_at parameter with a malicious input, such as a single quote, the application admin panel becomes non-functional, causing significant disruptions to administrative operations. The only way to recover from this issue is to manually access the host server and modify the backup.yaml file to correct the corrupted cron expression. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66301 | Grav ihas Broken Access Control which allows an Editor to modify the page&amp;#x27;s YAML Frontmatter to alter form processing actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66301</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, due to improper authorization checks when modifying critical fields on a POST request to /admin/pages/{page_name}, an editor with only permissions to change basic content on the form is now able to change the functioning of the form through modifying the content of the data[_json][header][form] which is the YAML frontmatter which includes the process section which dictates what happens after a user submits the form which include some important actions that could lead to further vulnerabilities. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:38:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66299 | Security Sandbox Bypass with SSTI (Server Side Template Injection) in the Grav CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66299</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, Grav CMS is vulnerable to a Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) that allows any authenticated user with editor permissions to execute arbitrary code on the remote server, bypassing the existing security sandbox. Since the security sandbox does not fully protect the Twig object, it is possible to interact with it (e.g., call methods, read/write attributes) through maliciously crafted Twig template directives injected into a web page. This allows an authenticated editor to add arbitrary functions to the Twig attribute system.twig.safe_filters, effectively bypassing the Grav CMS sandbox. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66300 | Grav is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66300</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, A low privilege user account with page editing privilege can read any server files using "Frontmatter" form. This includes Grav user account files (/grav/user/accounts/*.yaml), which store hashed user password, 2FA secret, and the password reset token. This can allow an adversary to compromise any registered account by resetting a password for a user to get access to the password reset token from the file or by cracking the hashed password. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65622 | Snipe-IT before 8.3.4 allows stored XSS via the Locations "Country" field, enabling a low-privileged authenticated user to inject JavaScript...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65622</link><description>Snipe-IT before 8.3.4 allows stored XSS via the Locations "Country" field, enabling a low-privileged authenticated user to inject JavaScript that executes in another user's session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66298 | Grav is vulnerable to Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) via Forms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66298</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, having a simple form on site can reveal the whole Grav configuration details (including plugin configuration details) by using the correct POST payload to exploit a Server-Side Template (SST) vulnerability. Sensitive information may be contained in the configuration details. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66296 | Grav vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in Grav Admin: Missing Username Uniqueness Check Allows Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66296</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, a privilege escalation vulnerability exists in Grav’s Admin plugin due to the absence of username uniqueness validation when creating users. A user with the create user permission can create a new account using the same username as an existing administrator account, set a new password/email, and then log in as that administrator. This effectively allows privilege escalation from limited user-manager permissions to full administrator access. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66297 | Grav vulnerable to Privilege Escalation and Authenticated Remote Code Execution via Twig Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66297</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, a user with admin panel access and permissions to create or edit pages in Grav CMS can enable Twig processing in the page frontmatter. By injecting malicious Twig expressions, the user can escalate their privileges to admin or execute arbitrary system commands via the scheduler API. This results in both Privilege Escalation (PE) and Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerabilities. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65621 | Snipe-IT before 8.3.4 allows stored XSS, allowing a low-privileged authenticated user to inject JavaScript that executes in an administrator...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65621</link><description>Snipe-IT before 8.3.4 allows stored XSS, allowing a low-privileged authenticated user to inject JavaScript that executes in an administrator's session, enabling privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66294 | Grav is vulnerable to RCE via SSTI through Twig Sandbox Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66294</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, a Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability exists in Grav that allows authenticated attackers with editor permissions to execute arbitrary commands on the server and, under certain conditions, may also be exploited by unauthenticated attackers. This vulnerability stems from weak regex validation in the cleanDangerousTwig method. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66295 | Grav vulnerable to Path traversal / arbitrary YAML write via user creation leading to Account Takeover / System Corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66295</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, when a user with privilege of user creation creates a new user through the Admin UI and supplies a username containing path traversal sequences (for example ..\Nijat or ../Nijat), Grav writes the account YAML file to an unintended path outside user/accounts/. The written YAML can contain account fields such as email, fullname, twofa_secret, and hashed_password. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65840 | PublicCMS V5.202506.b is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the CkEditorAdminController.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65840</link><description>PublicCMS V5.202506.b is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the CkEditorAdminController.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66205 | Frappe has the possibility of SQL Injection due to improper validations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66205</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. Prior to 15.86.0 and 14.99.2, a certain endpoint was vulnerable to error-based SQL injection due to lack of validation of parameters. Some information like version could be retrieved. This vulnerability is fixed in 15.86.0 and 14.99.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66206 | Frappe vulnerable to a path traversal allowing reading certain files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66206</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. Prior to 15.86.0 and 14.99.2, certain requests were vulnerable to path traversal attacks, wherein some files from the server could be retrieved if the full path was known. Sites hosted on Frappe Cloud, and even other setups that are behind a reverse proxy like NGINX are unaffected. This would mainly affect someone directly using werkzeug/gunicorn. In those cases, either an upgrade or changing the setup to use a reverse proxy is recommended. This vulnerability is fixed in 15.86.0 and 14.99.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51999 | express improperly controls modification of query properties</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51999</link><description>Express.js minimalist web framework for node. Prior to 5.2.0 and 4.22.0, when using the extended query parser in express ('query parser': 'extended'), the request.query object inherits all object prototype properties, but these properties can be overwritten by query string parameter keys that match the property names. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.2.0 and 4.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55749 | The XWiki Jetty package (XJetty) allows accessing any application file through URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55749</link><description>XWiki is an open-source wiki software platform. From 16.7.0 to 16.10.11, 17.4.4, or 17.7.0, in an instance which is using the XWiki Jetty package (XJetty), a context is exposed to statically access any file located in the webapp/ folder. It allows accessing files which might contains credentials. Fixed in 16.10.11, 17.4.4, and 17.7.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58044 | JumpServer has an Open Redirect Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58044</link><description>JumpServer is an open source bastion host and an operation and maintenance security audit system. Prior to v3.10.19 and v4.10.5, The /core/i18n// endpoint uses the Referer header as the redirection target without proper validation, which could lead to an Open Redirect vulnerability. This vulnerability is fixed in v3.10.19 and v4.10.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65838 | PublicCMS V5.202506.b is vulnerable to path traversal via the doUploadSitefile method.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65838</link><description>PublicCMS V5.202506.b is vulnerable to path traversal via the doUploadSitefile method.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12756 | Insecure Direct Object Reference in Mattermost Boards Plugin Enables Unauthorised Comment Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12756</link><description>Mattermost versions 11.0.x &lt;= 11.0.2, 10.12.x &lt;= 10.12.1, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.4, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.12 fail to validate user permissions when deleting comments in Boards, which allows an authenticated user with the editor role to delete comments created by other users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:56:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63317 | Todoist v8896 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /api/v1/uploads. Uploaded SVG files have no sanitization applied, so embedded J...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63317</link><description>Todoist v8896 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /api/v1/uploads. Uploaded SVG files have no sanitization applied, so embedded JavaScript executes when a user opens the attachment from a task/comment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65836 | PublicCMS V5.202506.b is vulnerable to SSRF. in the chat interface of SimpleAiAdminController.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65836</link><description>PublicCMS V5.202506.b is vulnerable to SSRF. in the chat interface of SimpleAiAdminController.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51682 | mJobtime 15.7.2 handles authorization on the client side, which allows an attacker to modify the client-side code and gain access to adminis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51682</link><description>mJobtime 15.7.2 handles authorization on the client side, which allows an attacker to modify the client-side code and gain access to administrative features. Additionally, they can craft requests based on the client-side code to call these administrative functions directly.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51683 | A blind SQL Injection (SQLi) vulnerability in mJobtime v15.7.2 allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL statements via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51683</link><description>A blind SQL Injection (SQLi) vulnerability in mJobtime v15.7.2 allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL statements via a crafted POST request to the /Default.aspx/update_profile_Server endpoint .</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11772 | Co-Installer Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11772</link><description>A carefully crafted DLL, copied to 

C:\ProgramData\Synaptics

 folder, allows a local user to execute 
arbitrary code with elevated privileges during driver installation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:20:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34297 | KissFFT Integer Overflow Heap Buffer Overflow via kiss_fft_alloc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34297</link><description>KissFFT versions prior to the fix commit 1b083165 contain an integer overflow in kiss_fft_alloc() in kiss_fft.c on platforms where size_t is 32-bit. The nfft parameter is not validated before being used in a size calculation (sizeof(kiss_fft_cpx) * (nfft - 1)), which can wrap to a small value when nfft is large. As a result, malloc() allocates an undersized buffer and the subsequent twiddle-factor initialization loop writes nfft elements, causing a heap buffer overflow. This vulnerability only affects 32-bit architectures.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63365 | SoftSea EPUB File Reader 1.0.0.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The vulnerability resides in the EPUB file processing component, spec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63365</link><description>SoftSea EPUB File Reader 1.0.0.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The vulnerability resides in the EPUB file processing component, specifically in the functionality responsible for extracting and handling EPUB archive contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65407 | A use-after-free in the MPEG1or2Demux::newElementaryStream() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause a Den...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65407</link><description>A use-after-free in the MPEG1or2Demux::newElementaryStream() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted MPEG Program stream.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13653 | Unauthorized access to documents in data streams with specially crafted requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13653</link><description>In Search Guard FLX versions from 3.1.0 up to 4.0.0 with enterprise modules being disabled, there exists an issue which allows authenticated users to use specially crafted requests to read documents from data streams without having the respective privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:26:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13836 | Excessive read buffering DoS in http.client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13836</link><description>When reading an HTTP response from a server, if no read amount is specified, the default behavior will be to use Content-Length. This allows a malicious server to cause the client to read large amounts of data into memory, potentially causing OOM or other DoS.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13837 | Out-of-memory when loading Plist</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13837</link><description>When loading a plist file, the plistlib module reads data in size specified by the file itself, meaning a malicious file can cause OOM and DoS issues</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13835 | WordPress Arconix Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.19 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13835</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tyche Softwares Arconix Shortcodes allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Arconix Shortcodes: from n/a through 2.1.19.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65408 | A NULL pointer dereference in the ADTSAudioFileServerMediaSubsession::createNewRTPSink() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65408</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference in the ADTSAudioFileServerMediaSubsession::createNewRTPSink() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted ADTS file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7007 | Null pointer dereference in Avast Antivirus on  macOS (16.0.0) or Linux (3.0.3)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7007</link><description>NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in Avast Antivirus on MacOS, Avast Anitvirus on Linux when scanning a malformed Windows PE file causes the antivirus process to crash.This issue affects Antivirus: 16.0.0; Anitvirus: 3.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65406 | A heap overflow in the MatroskaFile::createRTPSinkForTrackNumber() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65406</link><description>A heap overflow in the MatroskaFile::createRTPSinkForTrackNumber() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted MKV file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3500 | Integer Overflow in Avast Antiviurs 25.1.981.6 on Windows may result in privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3500</link><description>Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Avast Antivirus (25.1.981.6) on Windows allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Antivirus: from 25.1.981.6 before 25.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64775 | Apache Struts: File leak in multipart request processing causes disk exhaustion (DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64775</link><description>Denial of Service vulnerability in Apache Struts, file leak in multipart request processing causes disk exhaustion.

This issue affects Apache Struts: from 2.0.0 through 6.7.0, from 7.0.0 through 7.0.3.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 6.8.0 or 7.1.1, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65403 | A buffer overflow in the g_cfg.MaxUsers component of LightFTP v2.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65403</link><description>A buffer overflow in the g_cfg.MaxUsers component of LightFTP v2.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65404 | A buffer overflow in the getSideInfo2() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65404</link><description>A buffer overflow in the getSideInfo2() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted MP3 stream.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65405 | A use-after-free in the ADTSAudioFileSource::samplingFrequency() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65405</link><description>A use-after-free in the ADTSAudioFileSource::samplingFrequency() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted ADTS/AAC file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13829 | Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Data Illusion Zumbrunn NGSurveyallows any logged-in user to obtain the private information of any o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13829</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Data Illusion Zumbrunn NGSurveyallows any logged-in user to obtain the private information of any other user.



 Critical information retrieved: 
  *  APIKEY (1 year user Session)
  *  RefreshToken (10 minutes user Session)
  *  Password hashed with bcrypt
  *  User IP
  *  Email
  *  Full Name</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61229 | An issue in Shirt Pocket's SuperDuper! 3.10 and earlier allow a local attacker to modify the default task template to execute an arbitrary p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61229</link><description>An issue in Shirt Pocket's SuperDuper! 3.10 and earlier allow a local attacker to modify the default task template to execute an arbitrary preflight script with root privileges and Full Disk Access, thus bypassing macOS privacy controls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8351 | Heap-based Buffer Overflow, Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in Avast Antivirus on MacOS when scanning a malformed file may allow Local Exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8351</link><description>Heap-based Buffer Overflow, Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in Avast Antivirus on MacOS when scanning a malformed file may allow Local Execution of Code or Denial-of-Service of the anitvirus engine process.This issue affects Antivirus: from 8.3.70.94 before 8.3.70.98.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32384 | Kerlink gateways running KerOS prior to version 5.10 expose their web interface exclusively over HTTP, without HTTPS support. This lack of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32384</link><description>Kerlink gateways running KerOS prior to version 5.10 expose their web interface exclusively over HTTP, without HTTPS support. This lack of transport layer security allows a man-in-the-middle attacker to intercept and modify traffic between the client and the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39148 | The service wmp-agent of KerOS prior 5.12 does not properly validate so-called ‘magic URLs’ allowing an unauthenticated remote attacker to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39148</link><description>The service wmp-agent of KerOS prior 5.12 does not properly validate so-called ‘magic URLs’ allowing an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands as root when the service is reachable over network. Typically, the service is protected via local firewall.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32388 | Due to a firewall misconfiguration, Kerlink devices running KerOS prior to 5.12 incorrectly accept specially crafted UDP packets. This allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32388</link><description>Due to a firewall misconfiguration, Kerlink devices running KerOS prior to 5.12 incorrectly accept specially crafted UDP packets. This allows an attacker to bypass the firewall and access UDP-based services that would otherwise be protected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45370 | An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in the User profile management functionality of Socomec Easy Config System 2.6.1.0. A speciall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45370</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in the User profile management functionality of Socomec Easy Config System 2.6.1.0. A specially crafted database record can lead to unauthorized access. An attacker can modify a local database to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48882 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted network p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48882</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to denial of service. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48894 | A cleartext transmission vulnerability exists in the WEBVIEW-M functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted HTTP ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48894</link><description>A cleartext transmission vulnerability exists in the WEBVIEW-M functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to a disclosure of sensitive information. An attacker can sniff network traffic to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49572 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted network p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49572</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to denial of service and weaken credentials resulting in default documented credentials being applied to the device. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53684 | A cross-site request forgery (csrf) vulnerability exists in the WEBVIEW-M functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53684</link><description>A cross-site request forgery (csrf) vulnerability exists in the WEBVIEW-M functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to unauthorized access. An attacker can stage a malicious webpage to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10101 | Heap-based Buffer Overflow, Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in Avast Antivirus on MacOS of a crafted Mach-O file may allow Local Execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10101</link><description>Heap-based Buffer Overflow, Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in Avast Antivirus on MacOS of a crafted Mach-O file may allow Local Execution of Code or Denial of Service of antivirus protection.
This issue affects Antivirus: from 15.7 before 3.9.2025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20085 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20085</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to denial of service and weaken credentials resulting in default documented credentials being applied to the device. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23417 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23417</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to denial of service. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26858 | A buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted set of netw...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26858</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted set of network packets can lead to denial of service. An attacker can send a sequence of unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54848 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54848</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted series of network requests can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can send a sequence of unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability.An attacker can trigger this denial-of-service condition by sending a sequence of Modbus TCP messages to port 502 using the Write Single Register function code (6). The attack sequence begins with a message to register 58112 with a value of 1000, indicating that a configuration change will follow. Next, a message is sent to register 29440 with a value corresponding to the new Modbus address to be configured. Finally, a message to register 57856 with a value of 161 commits the configuration change. After this configuration change, the device will be in a denial-of-service state.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54849 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54849</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted series of network requests can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can send a sequence of unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability.An attacker can trigger this denial-of-service condition by sending a single Modbus TCP message to port 502 using the Write Single Register function code (6) to write the value 1 to register 4352. This action changes the Modbus address to 15. After this message is sent, the device will be in a denial-of-service state.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54850 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54850</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted series of network requests can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can send a sequence of unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability.An attacker can trigger this denial-of-service condition by sending a sequence of Modbus RTU over TCP messages to port 503 using the Write Single Register function code (6). The attack sequence begins with a message to register 58112 with a value of 1000, indicating that a configuration change will follow. Next, a message is sent to register 29440 with a value corresponding to the new Modbus address to be configured. Finally, a message to register 57856 with a value of 161 commits the configuration change.
After this configuration change, the device will be in a denial-of-service state.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54851 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54851</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted series of network requests can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can send a sequence of unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability.An attacker can trigger this denial-of-service condition by sending a single Modbus TCP message to port 503 using the Write Single Register function code (6) to write the value 1 to register 4352. This action changes the Modbus address to 15. After this message is sent, the device will be in a denial-of-service state.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55221 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP USB Function functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55221</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP USB Function functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability is specific to the malicious message sent via Modbus TCP over port 502.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55222 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP USB Function functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55222</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP USB Function functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability is specific to the malicious message sent via Modbus RTU over TCP on port 503.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57489 | Incorrect access control in the SDAgent component of Shirt Pocket SuperDuper! v3.10 allows attackers to escalate privileges to root due to t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57489</link><description>Incorrect access control in the SDAgent component of Shirt Pocket SuperDuper! v3.10 allows attackers to escalate privileges to root due to the improper use of a setuid binary.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61228 | An issue in Shirt Pocket SuperDuper! V.3.10 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the software update mechanism</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61228</link><description>An issue in Shirt Pocket SuperDuper! V.3.10 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the software update mechanism</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11699 | CVE-2025-11699</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11699</link><description>nopCommerce v4.70 and prior, and version 4.80.3, does not invalidate session cookies after logout or session termination, allowing an attacker who has a 
a valid session cookie access to privileged endpoints (such as /admin) even after the legitimate user has logged out, enabling session hijacking. Any version above 4.70 that is not 4.80.3 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63095 | Improper input validation in the BitstreamWriter::write_bits() function of Tempus Ex hello-video-codec v0.1.0 allows attackers to cause a De...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63095</link><description>Improper input validation in the BitstreamWriter::write_bits() function of Tempus Ex hello-video-codec v0.1.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63532 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the cancel.php component. The application fails to prope...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63532</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the cancel.php component. The application fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input in SQL queries, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary SQL code. By manipulating the search field, an attacker can bypass authentication and gain unauthorized access to the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63533 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the updateprofile.php and rprofile.php comp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63533</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the updateprofile.php and rprofile.php components. The application fails to properly sanitize or encode user-supplied input before rendering it in response. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript payloads into the rname, remail, rpassword, rphone, rcity parameters, which are then executed in the victim's browser when the page is viewed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63534 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the login.php component. The application fa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63534</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the login.php component. The application fails to properly sanitize or encode user-supplied input before rendering it in response. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript payloads into the msg and error parameters, which are then executed in the victim's browser when the page is viewed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63535 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the abs.php component. The application fails to properly...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63535</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the abs.php component. The application fails to properly sanitize usersupplied input in SQL queries, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary SQL code. By manipulating the search field, an attacker can bypass authentication and gain unauthorized access to the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63525 | An issue was discovered in Blood Bank Management System 1.0 allowing authenticated attackers to perform actions with escalated privileges vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63525</link><description>An issue was discovered in Blood Bank Management System 1.0 allowing authenticated attackers to perform actions with escalated privileges via crafted request to delete.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63526 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System within the abs.php component. The application fails to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63526</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System within the abs.php component. The application fails to properly sanitize or encode user-supplied input before rendering it in response. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript payloads into the msg parameter, which is then executed in the victim's browser when the page is viewed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63527 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the updateprofile.php and hprofile.php comp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63527</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the updateprofile.php and hprofile.php components. The application fails to properly sanitize or encode user-supplied input before rendering it in response. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript payloads into the hname, hemail, hpassword, hphone, hcity parameters, which are then executed in the victim's browser when the page is viewed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63528 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the blooddinfo.php component. The applicati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63528</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the blooddinfo.php component. The application fails to properly sanitize or encode user-supplied input before rendering it in response. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript payloads into the error parameter, which is then executed in the victim's browser when the page is viewed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63529 | A session fixation vulnerability exists in Blood Bank Management System 1.0 in login.php that allows an attacker to set or predict a user's ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63529</link><description>A session fixation vulnerability exists in Blood Bank Management System 1.0 in login.php that allows an attacker to set or predict a user's session identifier prior to authentication. When the victim logs in, the application continues to use the attacker-supplied session ID rather than generating a new one, enabling the attacker to hijack the authenticated session and gain unauthorized access to the victim's account.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63531 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the receiverLogin.php component. The application fails t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63531</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the receiverLogin.php component. The application fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input in SQL queries, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary SQL code. By manipulating the remail and rpassword fields, an attacker can bypass authentication and gain unauthorized access to the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63520 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in FeehiCMS 2.1.1 via the id parameter of the User Update function (?r=user%2Fupdate).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63520</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in FeehiCMS 2.1.1 via the id parameter of the User Update function (?r=user%2Fupdate).</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63522 | Reverse Tabnabbing vulnerability in FeehiCMS 2.1.1 in the Comments Management function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63522</link><description>Reverse Tabnabbing vulnerability in FeehiCMS 2.1.1 in the Comments Management function</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63523 | FeehiCMS version 2.1.1 fails to enforce server-side immutability for parameters that are presented to clients as "read-only." An authenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63523</link><description>FeehiCMS version 2.1.1 fails to enforce server-side immutability for parameters that are presented to clients as "read-only." An authenticated attacker can intercept and modify the parameter in transit and the backend accepts the changes. This can lead to unintended username changes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64030 | Eximbills Enterprise 4.1.5 (Built on 2020-10-30) is vulnerable to authenticated stored cross-site scripting (CWE-79) via the /EximBillWeb/se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64030</link><description>Eximbills Enterprise 4.1.5 (Built on 2020-10-30) is vulnerable to authenticated stored cross-site scripting (CWE-79) via the /EximBillWeb/servlets/WSTrxManager endpoint. Unsanitized user input in the TMPL_INFO parameter is stored server-side and rendered to other users, enabling arbitrary JavaScript execution in their browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 14:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56089 | An issue in Technitium through v13.2.2 enables attackers to conduct a DNS cache poisoning attack and inject fake responses by reviving the b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56089</link><description>An issue in Technitium through v13.2.2 enables attackers to conduct a DNS cache poisoning attack and inject fake responses by reviving the birthday attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 14:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13129 | Business Logic Error in Seneka Software&amp;#x27;s Onaylarım</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13129</link><description>Improper Enforcement of Behavioral Workflow vulnerability in Seneka Software Hardware Information Technology Trade Contracting and Industry Ltd. Co. Onaylarım allows Functionality Misuse.This issue affects Onaylarım: from 25.09.26.01 through 18112025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 14:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49642 | Agent builds for AIX vulnerable to library loading hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49642</link><description>Library loading on AIX Zabbix Agent builds can be hijacked by local users with write access to the /home/cecuser directory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49643 | Frontend DoS vulnerability due to asymmetric resource consumption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49643</link><description>An authenticated Zabbix user (including Guest) is able to cause disproportionate CPU load on the webserver by sending specially crafted parameters to /imgstore.php, leading to potential denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12106 | Insufficient argument validation in OpenVPN 2.7_alpha1 through 2.7_rc1 allows an attacker to trigger a heap buffer over-read when parsing IP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12106</link><description>Insufficient argument validation in OpenVPN 2.7_alpha1 through 2.7_rc1 allows an attacker to trigger a heap buffer over-read when parsing IP addresses</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:10:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27232 | Frontend arbitrary file read in oauth.authorize action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27232</link><description>An authenticated Zabbix Super Admin can exploit the oauth.authorize action to read arbitrary files from the webserver leading to potential confidentiality loss.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:10:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13296 | CSRF in Tekrom Technology&amp;#x27;s T-Soft E-Commerce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13296</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Tekrom Technology Inc. T-Soft E-Commerce allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects T-Soft E-Commerce: through 28112025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 11:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58408 | GPU DDK - KASAN Read UAF in the PVRSRVBridgeRGXSubmitTransfer2 due to improper error handling code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58408</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to trigger reads of stale data that can lead to kernel exceptions and write use-after-free.

The Use After Free common weakness enumeration was chosen as the stale data can include handles to resources in which the reference counts can become unbalanced. This can lead to the premature destruction of a resource while in use.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 11:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41070 | Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in Sanoma&amp;#x27;s Clickedu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41070</link><description>Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sanoma's Clickedu. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending them a malicious URL in '/students/carpetes_varies.php'. This vulnerability can be exploited to steal sensitive user data, such as session cookies, or to perform actions on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2879 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2879</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user process to perform improper GPU processing operations to expose sensitive data.This issue affects Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r29p0 through r49p4, from r50p0 through r54p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r49p4, from r50p0 through r54p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59789 | Apache bRPC: Stack Exhaustion via Unbounded Recursion in JSON Parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59789</link><description>Uncontrolled recursion in the json2pb component in Apache bRPC (version &lt; 1.15.0) on all platforms allows remote attackers to make the server crash via sending deep recursive json data.

Root Cause:
The bRPC json2pb component uses rapidjson to parse json data from the network. The rapidjson parser uses a recursive parsing method by default. If the input json has a large depth of recursive structure, the parser function may run into stack overflow.

Affected Scenarios:
Use bRPC server with protobuf message to serve http+json requests from untrusted network. Or directly use JsonToProtoMessage to convert json from untrusted input.



How to Fix: 
(Choose one of the following options) 
1. Upgrade bRPC to version 1.15.0, which fixes this issue.
2. Apply this patch:  https://github.com/apache/brpc/pull/3099 



Note:
No matter which option 

you choose, you should know that the fix introduces a recursion depth limit with default value 100. It affects these functions: 

ProtoMessageToJson, ProtoMessageToProtoJson, JsonToProtoMessage, and ProtoJsonToProtoMessage.

 If your requests contain json or protobuf messages that have a depth exceeding the limit, the request will be failed after applying the fix. You can modify the gflag json2pb_max_recursion_depth to change the limit.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6349 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU memory processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6349</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user process to perform improper GPU memory processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r53p0 through r54p1; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r53p0 through r54p1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8045 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8045</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user process to perform improper GPU processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r53p0 through r54p1; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r53p0 through r54p1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41700 | CODESYS Development System - Deserialization of Untrusted Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41700</link><description>An unauthenticated attacker can trick a local user into executing arbitrary code by opening a deliberately manipulated CODESYS project file with a CODESYS development system. This arbitrary code is executed in the user context.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41738 | CODESYS Control - Invalid type usage in visualization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41738</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker may cause the visualisation server of the CODESYS Control runtime system to access a resource with a pointer of wrong type, potentially leading to a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41739 | CODESYS Control - Linux/QNX SysSocket flaw</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41739</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker, who beats a race condition, can exploit a flaw in the communication servers of the CODESYS Control runtime system on Linux and QNX to trigger an out-of-bounds read via crafted socket communication, potentially causing a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13819 | Open redirect in web server of MiR robots and MiR fleet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13819</link><description>Open redirect in the web server component of MiR Robot and Fleet software allows a remote attacker to redirect users to arbitrary external websites via a crafted parameter, facilitating phishing or social engineering attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 09:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13816 | moxi159753 Mogu Blog v2 ZIP File unzipFile FileOperation.unzip path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13816</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in moxi159753 Mogu Blog v2 up to 5.2. The impacted element is the function FileOperation.unzip of the file /networkDisk/unzipFile of the component ZIP File Handler. Such manipulation of the argument fileUrl leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 08:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13815 | moxi159753 Mogu Blog v2 pictures unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13815</link><description>A weakness has been identified in moxi159753 Mogu Blog v2 up to 5.2. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /file/pictures. This manipulation of the argument filedatas causes unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 08:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11131 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11131</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11132 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11132</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11133 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11133</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3012 | In dpc modem, there is a possible system crash due to null pointer dereference. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3012</link><description>In dpc modem, there is a possible system crash due to null pointer dereference. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61607 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61607</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61608 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61608</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61609 | In modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61609</link><description>In modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61610 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61610</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61617 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61617</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61618 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61618</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61619 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61619</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13814 | moxi159753 Mogu Blog v2 uploadPicsByUrl LocalFileServiceImpl.uploadPictureByUrl server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13814</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in moxi159753 Mogu Blog v2 up to 5.2. Impacted is the function LocalFileServiceImpl.uploadPictureByUrl of the file /file/uploadPicsByUrl. The manipulation results in server-side request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13813 | moxi159753 Mogu Blog v2 Storage Management Endpoint storage authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13813</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in moxi159753 Mogu Blog v2 up to 5.2. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /storage/ of the component Storage Management Endpoint. The manipulation leads to missing authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13811 | jsnjfz WebStack-Guns PageFactory.java sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13811</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in jsnjfz WebStack-Guns 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file src/main/java/com/jsnjfz/manage/core/common/constant/factory/PageFactory.java. Executing manipulation of the argument sort can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:02:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13810 | jsnjfz WebStack-Guns KaptchaController.java renderPicture path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13810</link><description>A vulnerability was found in jsnjfz WebStack-Guns 1.0. This affects the function renderPicture of the file src/main/java/com/jsnjfz/manage/modular/system/controller/KaptchaController.java. Performing manipulation results in path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 06:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13809 | orionsec orion-ops SSH Connection MachineInfoController.java server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13809</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in orionsec orion-ops up to 5925824997a3109651bbde07460958a7be249ed1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file orion-ops-api/orion-ops-web/src/main/java/cn/orionsec/ops/controller/MachineInfoController.java of the component SSH Connection Handler. Such manipulation of the argument host/sshPort/username/password/authType leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 05:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13808 | orionsec orion-ops User Profile UserController.java update improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13808</link><description>A flaw has been found in orionsec orion-ops up to 5925824997a3109651bbde07460958a7be249ed1. Affected by this vulnerability is the function update of the file orion-ops-api/orion-ops-web/src/main/java/cn/orionsec/ops/controller/UserController.java of the component User Profile Handler. This manipulation of the argument ID causes improper authorization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 05:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13807 | orionsec orion-ops API MachineKeyController.java MachineKeyController improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13807</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in orionsec orion-ops up to 5925824997a3109651bbde07460958a7be249ed1. Affected is the function MachineKeyController of the file orion-ops-api/orion-ops-web/src/main/java/cn/orionsec/ops/controller/MachineKeyController.java of the component API. The manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 05:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13806 | nutzam NutzBoot Transaction API EthModule.java improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13806</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in nutzam NutzBoot up to 2.6.0-SNAPSHOT. This impacts an unknown function of the file nutzboot-demo/nutzboot-demo-simple/nutzboot-demo-simple-web3j/src/main/java/io/nutz/demo/simple/module/EthModule.java of the component Transaction API. The manipulation of the argument from/to/wei leads to improper authorization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 05:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13805 | nutzam NutzBoot LiteRpc-Serializer HttpServletRpcEndpoint.java getInputStream deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13805</link><description>A weakness has been identified in nutzam NutzBoot up to 2.6.0-SNAPSHOT. This affects the function getInputStream of the file nutzcloud/nutzcloud-literpc/src/main/java/org/nutz/boot/starter/literpc/impl/endpoint/http/HttpServletRpcEndpoint.java of the component LiteRpc-Serializer. Executing manipulation can lead to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is reported as difficult. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 04:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13804 | nutzam NutzBoot Ethereum Wallet EthModule.java information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13804</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in nutzam NutzBoot up to 2.6.0-SNAPSHOT. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file nutzboot-demo/nutzboot-demo-simple/nutzboot-demo-simple-web3j/src/main/java/io/nutz/demo/simple/module/EthModule.java of the component Ethereum Wallet Handler. Performing manipulation results in information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 04:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13802 | jairiidriss RestaurantWebsite Make a Reservation cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13802</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in jairiidriss RestaurantWebsite up to e7911f12d035e8e2f9a75e7a28b59e4ef5c1d654. Impacted is an unknown function of the component Make a Reservation. This manipulation of the argument selected_date causes cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 03:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13803 | MediaCrush Header paths.py http headers for scripting syntax</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13803</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in MediaCrush 1.0.0/1.0.1. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /mediacrush/paths.py of the component Header Handler. Such manipulation of the argument Host leads to improper neutralization of http headers for scripting syntax. The attack can be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 03:04:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13800 | ADSLR NBR1005GPEV2 send_order.cgi set_mesh_disconnect command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13800</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ADSLR NBR1005GPEV2 250814-r037c. This issue affects the function set_mesh_disconnect of the file /send_order.cgi. The manipulation of the argument mac results in command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 03:04:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13799 | ADSLR NBR1005GPEV2 send_order.cgi ap_macfilter_del command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13799</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in ADSLR NBR1005GPEV2 250814-r037c. This vulnerability affects the function ap_macfilter_del of the file /send_order.cgi. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 03:04:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13797 | ADSLR B-QE2W401 send_order.cgi parameterdel_swifimac command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13797</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in ADSLR B-QE2W401 250814-r037c. Affected by this issue is the function parameterdel_swifimac of the file /send_order.cgi. Performing manipulation of the argument del_swifimac results in command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13798 | ADSLR NBR1005GPEV2 send_order.cgi ap_macfilter_add command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13798</link><description>A flaw has been found in ADSLR NBR1005GPEV2 250814-r037c. This affects the function ap_macfilter_add of the file /send_order.cgi. Executing manipulation of the argument mac can lead to command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64772 | The installer of INZONE Hub 1.0.10.3 to 1.0.17.0 contains an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to insecurely loading Dynamic Li...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64772</link><description>The installer of INZONE Hub 1.0.10.3 to 1.0.17.0 contains an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to insecurely loading Dynamic Link Libraries. As a result, arbitrary code may be executed with the privilege of the user invoking the installer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13796 | deco-cx apps Parameter analyticsScript.ts AnalyticsScript server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13796</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in deco-cx apps up to 0.120.1. Affected by this vulnerability is the function AnalyticsScript of the file website/loaders/analyticsScript.ts of the component Parameter Handler. Such manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. Upgrading to version 0.120.2 addresses this issue. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 23:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13795 | codingWithElias School Management System Edit Student Info student-view.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13795</link><description>A weakness has been identified in codingWithElias School Management System up to f1ac334bfd89ae9067cc14dea12ec6ff3f078c01. Affected is an unknown function of the file /student-view.php of the component Edit Student Info Page. This manipulation of the argument First Name causes cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 23:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35028 | HexStrike AI MCP Server Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35028</link><description>By providing a command-line argument starting with a semi-colon ; to an API endpoint created by the EnhancedCommandExecutor class of the HexStrike AI MCP server, the resultant composed command is executed directly in the context of the MCP server’s normal privilege; typically, this is root. There is no attempt to sanitize these arguments in the default configuration of this MCP server at the affected version (as of commit 2f3a5512 in September of 2025.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 21:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13793 | winston-dsouza Ecommerce-Website GET Parameter header_menu.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13793</link><description>A weakness has been identified in winston-dsouza Ecommerce-Website up to 87734c043269baac0b4cfe9664784462138b1b2e. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /includes/header_menu.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument Error can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This product implements a rolling release for ongoing delivery, which means version information for affected or updated releases is unavailable. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13792 | Qualitor getResumo.php eval code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13792</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Qualitor 8.20/8.24. Affected by this vulnerability is the function eval of the file /html/st/stdeslocamento/request/getResumo.php. Performing manipulation of the argument passageiros results in code injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13791 | Scada-LTS Project Import ZIPProjectManager.java Common.getHomeDir path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13791</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Scada-LTS up to 2.7.8.1. Affected is the function Common.getHomeDir of the file br/org/scadabr/vo/exporter/ZIPProjectManager.java of the component Project Import. Such manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 15:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13790 | Scada-LTS cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13790</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Scada-LTS up to 2.7.8.1. This impacts an unknown function. This manipulation causes cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 14:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13789 | ZenTao model.php makeRequest server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13789</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZenTao up to 21.7.6-8564. This affects the function makeRequest of the file module/ai/model.php. The manipulation of the argument Base results in server-side request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. Upgrading to version 21.7.6 mitigates this issue. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 13:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13788 | Chanjet CRM upgradeattribute.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13788</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Chanjet CRM up to 20251106. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /tools/upgradeattribute.php. The manipulation of the argument gblOrgID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 13:05:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13787 | ZenTao File control.php delete privileges management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13787</link><description>A flaw has been found in ZenTao up to 21.7.6-8564. The affected element is the function file::delete of the file module/file/control.php of the component File Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument fileID can lead to improper privilege management. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 21.7.7 is sufficient to fix this issue. You should upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 10:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13786 | taosir WTCMS index.php fetch code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13786</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in taosir WTCMS up to 01a5f68a3dfc2fdddb44eed967bb2d4f60487665. Impacted is the function fetch of the file /index.php. Performing manipulation of the argument content results in code injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 09:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13785 | yungifez Skuul School Management System Image profile information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13785</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in yungifez Skuul School Management System up to 2.6.5. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /user/profile of the component Image Handler. Such manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 07:41:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13784 | yungifez Skuul School Management System SVG File edit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13784</link><description>A weakness has been identified in yungifez Skuul School Management System up to 2.6.5. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /dashboard/schools/1/edit of the component SVG File Handler. This manipulation causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 07:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13783 | taosir WTCMS CommentadminController CommentadminController.class.php delete sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13783</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in taosir WTCMS up to 01a5f68a3dfc2fdddb44eed967bb2d4f60487665. This affects the function check/uncheck/delete of the file application/Comment/Controller/CommentadminController.class.php of the component CommentadminController. The manipulation of the argument ids results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. This product implements a rolling release for ongoing delivery, which means version information for affected or updated releases is unavailable. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 06:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66432 | In Oxide control plane 15 through 17 before 17.1, API tokens can be renewed past their expiration date.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66432</link><description>In Oxide control plane 15 through 17 before 17.1, API tokens can be renewed past their expiration date.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 04:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66433 | HTCondor Access Point before 25.3.1 allows an authenticated user to impersonate other users on the local machine by submitting a batch job. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66433</link><description>HTCondor Access Point before 25.3.1 allows an authenticated user to impersonate other users on the local machine by submitting a batch job. This is fixed in 24.12.14, 25.0.3, and 25.3.1. The earliest affected version is 24.7.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 04:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13782 | taosir WTCMS SlideController SlideController.class.php delete sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13782</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in taosir WTCMS up to 01a5f68a3dfc2fdddb44eed967bb2d4f60487665. Affected by this issue is the function delete of the file application/Admin/Controller/SlideController.class.php of the component SlideController. The manipulation of the argument ids leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 03:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66420 | Tryton sao (aka tryton-sao) before 7.6.9 allows XSS via an HTML attachment. This is fixed in 7.6.9, 7.4.19, 7.0.38, and 6.0.67.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66420</link><description>Tryton sao (aka tryton-sao) before 7.6.9 allows XSS via an HTML attachment. This is fixed in 7.6.9, 7.4.19, 7.0.38, and 6.0.67.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 03:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66421 | Tryton sao (aka tryton-sao) before 7.6.11 allows XSS because it does not escape completion values. This is fixed in 7.6.11, 7.4.21, 7.0.40, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66421</link><description>Tryton sao (aka tryton-sao) before 7.6.11 allows XSS because it does not escape completion values. This is fixed in 7.6.11, 7.4.21, 7.0.40, and 6.0.69.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 03:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66422 | Tryton trytond before 7.6.11 allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive trace-back (server setup) information. This is fixed in 7.6.11, 7.4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66422</link><description>Tryton trytond before 7.6.11 allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive trace-back (server setup) information. This is fixed in 7.6.11, 7.4.21, 7.0.40, and 6.0.70.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 03:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66423 | Tryton trytond 6.0 before 7.6.11 does not enforce access rights for the route of the HTML editor. This is fixed in 7.6.11, 7.4.21, 7.0.40, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66423</link><description>Tryton trytond 6.0 before 7.6.11 does not enforce access rights for the route of the HTML editor. This is fixed in 7.6.11, 7.4.21, 7.0.40, and 6.0.70.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 03:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66424 | Tryton trytond 6.0 before 7.6.11 does not enforce access rights for data export. This is fixed in 7.6.11, 7.4.21, 7.0.40, and 6.0.70.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66424</link><description>Tryton trytond 6.0 before 7.6.11 does not enforce access rights for data export. This is fixed in 7.6.11, 7.4.21, 7.0.40, and 6.0.70.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 03:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13615 | StreamTube Core &amp;lt;= 4.78 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13615</link><description>The StreamTube Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary User Password Change in versions up to, and including, 4.78. This is due to the plugin providing user-controlled access to objects, letting a user bypass authorization and access system resources. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change user passwords and potentially take over administrator accounts. Note: This can only be exploited if the 'registration password fields' enabled in theme options.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 02:22:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6666 | motogadget mo.lock Ignition Lock NFC hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6666</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in motogadget mo.lock Ignition Lock up to 20251125. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component NFC Handler. Executing manipulation can lead to use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The physical device can be targeted for the attack. A high complexity level is associated with this attack. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 09:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65540 | Multiple Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities exist in xmall v1.1 due to improper handling of user-supplied data. User input fields su...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65540</link><description>Multiple Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities exist in xmall v1.1 due to improper handling of user-supplied data. User input fields such as username and description are directly rendered into HTML without proper sanitization or encoding, allowing attackers to inject and execute malicious scripts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65892 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (rXSS) in krpano before version 1.23.2 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65892</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (rXSS) in krpano before version 1.23.2 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the victim's browser via a crafted URL to the passQueryParameters function with the xml parameter enabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66224 | OrangeHRM is Vulnerable to Code Execution Through Arbitrary File Write from Sendmail Parameter Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66224</link><description>OrangeHRM is a comprehensive human resource management (HRM) system. From version 5.0 to 5.7, the application contains an input-neutralization flaw in its mail configuration and delivery workflow that allows user-controlled values to flow directly into the system’s sendmail command. Because these values are not sanitized or constrained before being incorporated into the command execution path, certain sendmail behaviors can be unintentionally invoked during email processing. This makes it possible for the application to write files on the server as part of the mail-handling routine, and in deployments where those files end up in web-accessible locations, the behavior can be leveraged to achieve execution of attacker-controlled content. The issue stems entirely from constructing OS-level command strings using unsanitized input within the mail-sending logic. This issue has been patched in version 5.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66225 | OrangeHRM is Vulnerable to Account Takeover Through Unvalidated Username in Password Reset Workflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66225</link><description>OrangeHRM is a comprehensive human resource management (HRM) system. From version 5.0 to 5.7, the password reset workflow does not enforce that the username submitted in the final reset request matches the account for which the reset process was originally initiated. After obtaining a valid reset link for any account they can receive email for, an attacker can alter the username parameter in the final reset request to target a different user. Because the system accepts the supplied username without verification, the attacker can set a new password for any chosen account, including privileged accounts, resulting in full account takeover. This issue has been patched in version 5.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66289 | OrangeHRM is Vulnerable to Persistent Session Access Due to Missing Invalidation After User Disable and Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66289</link><description>OrangeHRM is a comprehensive human resource management (HRM) system. From version 5.0 to 5.7, the application does not invalidate existing sessions when a user is disabled or when a password change occurs, allowing active session cookies to remain valid indefinitely. As a result, a disabled user, or an attacker using a compromised account, can continue to access protected pages and perform operations as long as a prior session remains active. Because the server performs no session revocation or session-store cleanup during these critical state changes, disabling an account or updating credentials has no effect on already-established sessions. This makes administrative disable actions ineffective and allows unauthorized users to retain full access even after an account is closed or a password is reset, exposing the system to prolonged unauthorized use and significantly increasing the impact of account takeover scenarios. This issue has been patched in version 5.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66290 | OrangeHRM is Vulnerable to Improper Authorization Allowing Unauthorized Access to Candidate Attachments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66290</link><description>OrangeHRM is a comprehensive human resource management (HRM) system. From version 5.0 to 5.7, the application’s recruitment attachment retrieval endpoint does not enforce the required authorization checks before serving candidate files. Even users restricted to ESS-level access, who have no permission to view the Recruitment module, can directly access candidate attachment URLs. When an authenticated request is made to the attachment endpoint, the system validates the session but does not confirm that the requesting user has the necessary recruitment permissions. As a result, any authenticated user can download CVs and other uploaded documents for arbitrary candidates by issuing direct requests to the attachment endpoint, leading to unauthorized exposure of sensitive applicant data. This issue has been patched in version 5.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66291 | OrangeHRM is Vulnerable to Improper Authorization Allowing Unauthorized Access to Interview Attachments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66291</link><description>OrangeHRM is a comprehensive human resource management (HRM) system. From version 5.0 to 5.7, the interview attachment retrieval endpoint in the Recruitment module serves files based solely on an authenticated session and user-supplied identifiers, without verifying whether the requester has permission to access the associated interview record. Because the server does not perform any recruitment-level authorization checks, an ESS-level user with no access to recruitment workflows can directly request interview attachment URLs and receive the corresponding files. This exposes confidential interview documents—including candidate CVs, evaluations, and supporting files—to unauthorized users. The issue arises from relying on predictable object identifiers and session presence rather than validating the user’s association with the relevant recruitment process. This issue has been patched in version 5.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53899 | Kiteworks MFT is vulnerable to an Incorrectly Specified Destination in a Communication Channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53899</link><description>Kiteworks MFT orchestrates end-to-end file transfer workflows. Prior to version 9.1.0, the back-end of Kiteworks MFT is vulnerable to an incorrectly specified destination in a communication channel which allows an attacker with administrative privileges on the system under certain circumstances to intercept upstream communication which could lead to an escalation of privileges. This issue has been patched in version 9.1.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:03:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53900 | Kiteworks MFT has a Privilege Defined With Unsafe Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53900</link><description>Kiteworks MFT orchestrates end-to-end file transfer workflows. Prior to version 9.1.0, an unfavourable definition of roles and permissions in Kiteworks MFT on managing Connections could lead to unexpected escalation of privileges for authorized users. This issue has been patched in version 9.1.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:03:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53939 | Kiteworks Core is vulnerable to Improper Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53939</link><description>Kiteworks is a private data network (PDN). Prior to version 9.1.0, improper input validation when managing roles of a shared folder could lead to unexpectedly elevate another user's permissions on the share. This issue has been patched in version 9.1.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:03:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66221 | Werkzeug safe_join() allows Windows special device names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66221</link><description>Werkzeug is a comprehensive WSGI web application library. Prior to version 3.1.4, Werkzeug's safe_join function allows path segments with Windows device names. On Windows, there are special device names such as CON, AUX, etc that are implicitly present and readable in every directory. send_from_directory uses safe_join to safely serve files at user-specified paths under a directory. If the application is running on Windows, and the requested path ends with a special device name, the file will be opened successfully, but reading will hang indefinitely. This issue has been patched in version 3.1.4.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:03:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66223 | OpenObserve&amp;#x27;s Invite Token Lifecycle Misconfiguration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66223</link><description>OpenObserve is a cloud-native observability platform. Prior to version 0.16.0, organization invitation tokens do not expire once issued, remain valid even after the invited user is removed from the organization, and allow multiple invitations to the same email with different roles where all issued links remain valid simultaneously. This results in broken access control where a removed or demoted user can regain access or escalate privileges. This issue has been patched in version 0.16.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:03:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53896 | Kiteworks MFT is vulnerable to Insufficient Session Expiration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53896</link><description>Kiteworks MFT orchestrates end-to-end file transfer workflows. Prior to version 9.1.0, a bug in Kiteworks MFT could cause under certain circumstances that a user's active session would not properly time out due to inactivity. This issue has been patched in version 9.1.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:03:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53897 | Kiteworks MFT has a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53897</link><description>Kiteworks MFT orchestrates end-to-end file transfer workflows. Prior to version 9.1.0, this vulnerability could allow an external attacker to gain access to log information from the system by tricking an administrator into browsing a specifically crafted fake page of Kiteworks MFT. This issue has been patched in version 9.1.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:03:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58436 | OpenPrinting CUPS slow client can halt cupsd, leading to a possible DoS attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58436</link><description>OpenPrinting CUPS is an open source printing system for Linux and other Unix-like operating systems. Prior to version 2.4.15, a client that connects to cupsd but sends slow messages, e.g. only one byte per second, delays cupsd as a whole, such that it becomes unusable by other clients. This issue has been patched in version 2.4.15.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:03:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61915 | OpenPrinting CUPS vulnerable to stack based out-of-bound write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61915</link><description>OpenPrinting CUPS is an open source printing system for Linux and other Unix-like operating systems. Prior to version 2.4.15, a user in the lpadmin group can use the cups web ui to change the config and insert a malicious line. Then the cupsd process which runs as root will parse the new config and cause an out-of-bound write. This issue has been patched in version 2.4.15.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:03:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66216 | AIS-catcher has a Buffer Overflow vulnerability in `AIS::Message` leading to DoS/RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66216</link><description>AIS-catcher is a multi-platform AIS receiver. Prior to version 0.64, a heap buffer overflow vulnerability has been identified in the AIS::Message class of AIS-catcher. This vulnerability allows an attacker to write approximately 1KB of arbitrary data into a 128-byte buffer. This issue has been patched in version 0.64.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:03:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66217 | AIS-catcher Integer Underflow in MQTT Packet Parsing leading to Heap Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66217</link><description>AIS-catcher is a multi-platform AIS receiver. Prior to version 0.64, an integer underflow vulnerability exists in the MQTT parsing logic of AIS-catcher. This vulnerability allows an attacker to trigger a massive Heap Buffer Overflow by sending a malformed MQTT packet with a manipulated Topic Length field. This leads to an immediate Denial of Service (DoS) and, when used as a library, severe Memory Corruption that can be leveraged for Remote Code Execution (RCE). This issue has been patched in version 0.64.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:03:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66036 | Retro is vulnerable to XSS vulnerability in input handling component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66036</link><description>Retro is an online platform providing items of vintage collections. Prior to version 2.4.7, Retro is vulnerable to a cross-site scripting (XSS) in the input handling component. This issue has been patched in version 2.4.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 01:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66201 | LibreChat is Vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in Actions Capability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66201</link><description>LibreChat is a ChatGPT clone with additional features. Prior to version 0.8.1-rc2, LibreChat is vulnerable to Server-side Request Forgery (SSRF), by passing specially crafted OpenAPI specs to its "Actions" feature and making the LLM use those actions. It could be used by an authenticated user with access to this feature to access URLs only accessible to the LibreChat server (such as cloud metadata services, through which impersonation of the server might be possible). This issue has been patched in version 0.8.1-rc2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 01:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66219 | willitmerge has a command Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66219</link><description>willitmerge is a command line tool to check if pull requests are mergeable. In versions 0.2.1 and prior, there is a command Injection vulnerability in willitmerge. The vulnerability manifests in this package due to the use of insecure child process execution API (exec) to which it concatenates user input, whether provided to the command-line flag, or is in user control in the target repository. At time of publication, no known fix is public.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 01:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66027 | Rallly Information Disclosure Vulnerability in Participant API Leaks Names and Emails Despite Pro Privacy Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66027</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.6, an information disclosure vulnerability exposes participant details, including names and email addresses through the /api/trpc/polls.get,polls.participants.list endpoint, even when Pro privacy features are enabled. This bypasses intended privacy controls that should prevent participants from viewing other users’ personal information. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 01:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66034 | fontTools is Vulnerable to Arbitrary File Write and XML injection in fontTools.varLib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66034</link><description>fontTools is a library for manipulating fonts, written in Python. In versions from 4.33.0 to before 4.60.2, the fonttools varLib (or python3 -m fontTools.varLib) script has an arbitrary file write vulnerability that leads to remote code execution when a malicious .designspace file is processed. The vulnerability affects the main() code path of fontTools.varLib, used by the fonttools varLib CLI and any code that invokes fontTools.varLib.main(). This issue has been patched in version 4.60.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 01:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65112 | PubNet Critical Authentication Bypass Allows Unauthenticated Package Upload and Identity Spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65112</link><description>PubNet is a self-hosted Dart &amp; Flutter package service. Prior to version 1.1.3, the /api/storage/upload endpoint in PubNet allows unauthenticated users to upload packages as any user by providing arbitrary author-id values. This enables identity spoofing, privilege escalation, and supply chain attacks. This issue has been patched in version 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 01:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65113 | ClipBucket v5 Unauthenticated Object Flagging Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65113</link><description>ClipBucket v5 is an open source video sharing platform. Prior to version 5.5.2 - #164, an authorization bypass vulnerability in the AJAX flagging system allows any unauthenticated user to flag any content (users, videos, photos, collections) on the platform. This can lead to mass flagging attacks, content disruption, and moderation system abuse. This issue has been patched in version 5.5.2 - #164.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 01:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64715 | Cilium with misconfigured toGroups in policies can lead to unrestricted egress traffic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64715</link><description>Cilium is a networking, observability, and security solution with an eBPF-based dataplane. Prior to versions 1.16.17, 1.17.10, and 1.18.4, CiliumNetworkPolicys which use egress.toGroups.aws.securityGroupsIds to reference AWS security group IDs that do not exist or are not attached to any network interface may unintentionally allow broader outbound access than intended by the policy authors. In such cases, the toCIDRset section of the derived policy is not generated, which means outbound traffic may be permitted to more destinations than originally intended. This issue has been patched in versions 1.16.17, 1.17.10, and 1.18.4. There are no workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 01:52:51 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>