<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 13:46:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-29152 | Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in lemeconsultoria HCM galera.app v.4.58.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via multiple comp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29152</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in lemeconsultoria HCM galera.app v.4.58.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via multiple components, including Strategic Planning Perspective Registration, Training Request, Perspective Editing, Education Registration, Hierarchical Level Registration, Decision Level Registration, Perspective Registration, Company Group Registration, Company Registration, News Registration, Employee Editing, Goal Team Registration, Learning Resource Type Registration, Learning Resource Family Registration, Learning Resource Supplier Registration, and Cycle Maintenance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 13:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29153 | SQL Injection vulnerability in lemeconsultoria HCM galera.app v.4.58.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Data export, fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29153</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in lemeconsultoria HCM galera.app v.4.58.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Data export, filters functions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 13:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29154 | HTML injection vulnerability in lemeconsultoria HCM galera.app v.4.58.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the .galera.app/ted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29154</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability in lemeconsultoria HCM galera.app v.4.58.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the .galera.app/ted/solicitacao_treinamento/, .galera.app/rh/metas/perspectiva_estrategica/edicao/, .galera.app/rh/cadastros/perspectivas/listagem/adc/, .galera.app/escolaridade/listagem/, .galera.app/estados_civis/cadastro/, .galera.app/nivel_hierarquico/listagem/, .galera.app/nivel_decisorio/cadastro/, .galera.app/escolaridade/cadastro/, .galera.app/nivel_decisorio/listagem/, .galera.app/rh/cadastros/perspectivas/listagem/, .galera.app/empresas_grupo/cadastro/, .galera.app/empresas/edicao/, .galera.app/liais/listagem/, .galera.app/noticias/listagem/, .galera.app/gerenciamento-de-ciclo/abertura/cadastrar, .galera.app/colaborador/cadastro/cursos/adc/edicao/, .galera.app/colaborador/cadastro/adc/, .galera.app/cads_aux/escalact/, .galera.app/ncf/tec/cadastro/ct/ .galera.app/rh/metas/painel/, .galera.app/rh/metas/equipe/edicao/, .galera.app/rh/pdi/tipo_recursos/edicao/, .galera.app/rh/pdi/familia_recursos/cadastro/, .galera.app/rh/pdi/fornecedores/edicao/, and .galera.app/rh/pdi/recursos/cadastro/ components.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 13:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29602 | flatpress 1.3.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in Administration area via Manage categories.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29602</link><description>flatpress 1.3.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in Administration area via Manage categories.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 13:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36791 | net_sched: keep alloc_hash updated after hash allocation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36791</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net_sched: keep alloc_hash updated after hash allocation

In commit 599be01ee567 ("net_sched: fix an OOB access in cls_tcindex")
I moved cp-&gt;hash calculation before the first
tcindex_alloc_perfect_hash(), but cp-&gt;alloc_hash is left untouched.
This difference could lead to another out of bound access.

cp-&gt;alloc_hash should always be the size allocated, we should
update it after this tcindex_alloc_perfect_hash().</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 13:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33093 | IBM Sterling Partner Engagement Manager information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33093</link><description>IBM Sterling Partner Engagement Manager 6.1.0, 6.2.0, 6.2.2 JWT secret is stored in public Helm Charts and is not stored as a Kubernetes secret.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 11:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4104 | Frontend Dashboard 1.0 - 2.2.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via fed_wp_ajax_fed_login_form_post Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4104</link><description>The Frontend Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check on the fed_wp_ajax_fed_login_form_post() function in versions 1.0 to 2.2.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the administrator’s email and password, and elevate their privileges to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 09:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27533 | Apache ActiveMQ: Unchecked buffer length can cause excessive memory allocation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27533</link><description>Memory Allocation with Excessive Size Value vulnerability in Apache ActiveMQ.

During unmarshalling of OpenWire commands the size value of buffers was not properly validated which could lead to excessive memory allocation and be exploited to cause a denial of service (DoS) by depleting process memory, thereby affecting applications and services that rely on the availability of the ActiveMQ broker when not using mutual TLS connections.
This issue affects Apache ActiveMQ: from 6.0.0 before 6.1.6, from 5.18.0 before 5.18.7, from 5.17.0 before 5.17.7, before 5.16.8. ActiveMQ 5.19.0 is not affected.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 6.1.6+, 5.19.0+,  5.18.7+, 5.17.7, or 5.16.8 or which fixes the issue.

Existing users may implement mutual TLS to mitigate the risk on affected brokers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 09:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39361 | WordPress Royal Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1017 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39361</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WProyal Royal Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Royal Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.7.1017.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 09:14:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20980 | Out-of-bounds write in libsavscmn prior to Android 15 allows local attackers to cause memory corruption.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20980</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in libsavscmn prior to Android 15 allows local attackers to cause memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20937 | Out-of-bounds write in Keymaster trustlet prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20937</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in Keymaster trustlet prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20949 | Path traversal vulnerability in Samsung Members prior to version 5.0.00.11 allows attackers to read and write arbitrary file with the privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20949</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability in Samsung Members prior to version 5.0.00.11 allows attackers to read and write arbitrary file with the privilege of Samsung Members.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20953 | Improper access control in SmartManagerCN prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch activities within SmartManagerCN.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20953</link><description>Improper access control in SmartManagerCN prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch activities within SmartManagerCN.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20954 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in EnrichedCall prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitiv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20954</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in EnrichedCall prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive information. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20955 | Improper Export of Android Application Components in NotificationHistoryImageProvider prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20955</link><description>Improper Export of Android Application Components in NotificationHistoryImageProvider prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access notification images.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20956 | Improper export of android application components in Settings in Galaxy Watch prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20956</link><description>Improper export of android application components in Settings in Galaxy Watch prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access developer settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20957 | Improper access control in SmartManagerCN prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch arbitrary activities with SmartMa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20957</link><description>Improper access control in SmartManagerCN prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch arbitrary activities with SmartManagerCN privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20958 | Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver in UnifiedWFC prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to manipulate VoW...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20958</link><description>Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver in UnifiedWFC prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to manipulate VoWiFi related behaviors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20959 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in Wi-Fi P2P service prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20959</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in Wi-Fi P2P service prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20960 | Improper handling of insufficient permission in CocktailBarService prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to use the privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20960</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permission in CocktailBarService prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to use the privileged api.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20961 | Improper handling of insufficient permission or privileges in sepunion service prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20961</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permission or privileges in sepunion service prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to access files with system privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20962 | Improper handling of insufficient permission in SpenGesture service prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to track the S Pe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20962</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permission in SpenGesture service prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to track the S Pen position.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20963 | Out-of-bounds write in memory initialization in libsavsvc.so prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out-of-bounds m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20963</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in memory initialization in libsavsvc.so prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20964 | Out-of-bounds write in parsing media files in libsavsvc.so prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out-of-bounds mem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20964</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in parsing media files in libsavsvc.so prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20965 | Improper handling of insufficient permission in Bixby wakeup prior to version 2.3.74.8 allows local attackers to access sensitive data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20965</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permission in Bixby wakeup prior to version 2.3.74.8 allows local attackers to access sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20966 | Improper access control in Samsung Gallery prior to version 14.5.10.3 in Global Android 13, 14.5.09.3 in China Android 13, and 15.5.04.5 in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20966</link><description>Improper access control in Samsung Gallery prior to version 14.5.10.3 in Global Android 13, 14.5.09.3 in China Android 13, and 15.5.04.5 in Android 14 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profiles.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20967 | Improper access control in Samsung Gallery prior to version 14.5.10.3 in Global Android 13, 14.5.09.3 in China Android 13, and 15.5.04.5 in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20967</link><description>Improper access control in Samsung Gallery prior to version 14.5.10.3 in Global Android 13, 14.5.09.3 in China Android 13, and 15.5.04.5 in Android 14 allows attackers to read and write arbitrary file with the privilege of Samsung Gallery.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20968 | Improper access control in Samsung Gallery prior to version 14.5.10.3 in Global Android 13, 14.5.09.3 in China Android 13, and 15.5.04.5 in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20968</link><description>Improper access control in Samsung Gallery prior to version 14.5.10.3 in Global Android 13, 14.5.09.3 in China Android 13, and 15.5.04.5 in Android 14 allows remote attackers to access data and perform internal operations within Samsung Gallery.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20969 | Improper input validation in Samsung Gallery prior to version 14.5.10.3 in Global Android 13, 14.5.09.3 in China Android 13, and 15.5.04.5 i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20969</link><description>Improper input validation in Samsung Gallery prior to version 14.5.10.3 in Global Android 13, 14.5.09.3 in China Android 13, and 15.5.04.5 in Android 14 allows local attackers to access data within Samsung Gallery.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20970 | Improper access control in Bixby Vision prior to version 3.8.1 in Android 13, 3.8.3 in Android 14, 3.8.21 in Android 15 allows local attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20970</link><description>Improper access control in Bixby Vision prior to version 3.8.1 in Android 13, 3.8.3 in Android 14, 3.8.21 in Android 15 allows local attackers to access image files with Bixby Vision privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20971 | Improper input validation in Samsung Flow prior to version 4.9.17.6 allows local attackers to access data within Samsung Flow.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20971</link><description>Improper input validation in Samsung Flow prior to version 4.9.17.6 allows local attackers to access data within Samsung Flow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20972 | Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver in Samsung Flow prior to version 4.9.17.6 allows local attackers to modify Samsung Flo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20972</link><description>Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver in Samsung Flow prior to version 4.9.17.6 allows local attackers to modify Samsung Flow configuration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20973 | Improper authentication in Secure Folder prior to version 1.8.12.0 in Android 13, and 1.9.21.00 in Android 14 allows physical attackers to r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20973</link><description>Improper authentication in Secure Folder prior to version 1.8.12.0 in Android 13, and 1.9.21.00 in Android 14 allows physical attackers to reset the lock type of Secure Folder.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20974 | Improper handling of insufficient permission in PackageInstallerCN prior to version 15.0.11.0 allows local attacker to bypass user interacti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20974</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permission in PackageInstallerCN prior to version 15.0.11.0 allows local attacker to bypass user interaction for requested installation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20975 | Improper Export of Android Application Components in AODService prior to version 8.8.28.12 allows local attackers to launch arbitrary activi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20975</link><description>Improper Export of Android Application Components in AODService prior to version 8.8.28.12 allows local attackers to launch arbitrary activity with systemui privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20976 | Out-of-bounds read in applying binary of text content in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.29.23 allows attackers to read out-of-bounds mem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20976</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in applying binary of text content in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.29.23 allows attackers to read out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20977 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in translation in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.29.23 allows local attackers to get ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20977</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in translation in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.29.23 allows local attackers to get sensitive information. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20978 | Improper access control in PENUP prior to version 3.9.19.32 allows local attackers to access files with PENUP privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20978</link><description>Improper access control in PENUP prior to version 3.9.19.32 allows local attackers to access files with PENUP privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20979 | Out-of-bounds write in libsavscmn prior to Android 15 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20979</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in libsavscmn prior to Android 15 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0666 | BOINC Server Stored XSS Injection in host_venue_action.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0666</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BOINC Server allows Stored XSS.This issue affects BOINC Server: through 1.4.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0667 | BOINC Server Stored XSS Injection in pm.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0667</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BOINC Server allows Stored XSS.This issue affects BOINC Server: through 1.4.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0668 | BOINC Server Multiple SQL Injections</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0668</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BOINC Server allows Stored XSS.This issue affects BOINC Server: before 1.4.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:49:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0669 | BOINC Server Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0669</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in BOINC Server allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects BOINC Server: before 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:49:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12120 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.7.1017 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12120</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown widget display_message_text parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1017 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4171 | WZ Followed Posts – Display what visitors are reading &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4171</link><description>The WZ Followed Posts – Display what visitors are reading plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wfp' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:31:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1399 | Out-of-bounds Read in libplctag library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1399</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in unpack_response (session.c) in libplctag from 2.0 through 2.6.3 allows Overread Buffers via network.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1400 | Out-of-bounds Read in libplctag library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1400</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in unpack_response (conn.c) in libplctag from 2.0 through 2.6.3 allows Overread Buffers via network.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32396 | An Heap-based Buffer Overflow in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to induce a crash in IO devices that use the libr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32396</link><description>An Heap-based Buffer Overflow in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to induce a crash in IO devices that use the library by sending a malicious RPC packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32397 | An Heap-based Buffer Overflow in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to induce a crash in IO devices that use the libr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32397</link><description>An Heap-based Buffer Overflow in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to induce a crash in IO devices that use the library by sending a malicious RPC packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32398 | A NULL Pointer Dereference in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to induce a crash in IO devices that use the library...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32398</link><description>A NULL Pointer Dereference in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to induce a crash in IO devices that use the library by sending a malicious RPC packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32399 | An Unchecked Input for Loop Condition in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to cause IO devices that use the library ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32399</link><description>An Unchecked Input for Loop Condition in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to cause IO devices that use the library to enter an infinite loop by sending a malicious RPC packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:16:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32400 | An Heap-based Buffer Overflow in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to induce a crash in IO devices that use the libr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32400</link><description>An Heap-based Buffer Overflow in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to induce a crash in IO devices that use the library by sending a malicious RPC packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:16:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32401 | An Heap-based Buffer Overflow in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to corrupt the memory of IO devices that use the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32401</link><description>An Heap-based Buffer Overflow in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to corrupt the memory of IO devices that use the library by sending a malicious RPC packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32402 | An Out-of-bounds Write in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to induce a crash in IO devices that use the library by ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32402</link><description>An Out-of-bounds Write in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to induce a crash in IO devices that use the library by sending a malicious RPC packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32403 | An Out-of-bounds Write in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to corrupt the memory of IO devices that use the library...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32403</link><description>An Out-of-bounds Write in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to corrupt the memory of IO devices that use the library by sending a malicious RPC packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32404 | An Out-of-bounds Write in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to corrupt the memory of IO devices that use the library...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32404</link><description>An Out-of-bounds Write in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to corrupt the memory of IO devices that use the library by sending a malicious RPC packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32405 | An Out-of-bounds Write in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to induce a crash in IO devices that use the library by ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32405</link><description>An Out-of-bounds Write in RT-Labs P-Net version 1.0.1 or earlier allows an attacker to induce a crash in IO devices that use the library by sending a malicious RPC packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3766 | Login Lockdown &amp;amp; Protection &amp;lt;= 2.11 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary IP Whitelisting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3766</link><description>The Login Lockdown &amp; Protection plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized nonce access due to a missing capability check on the ajax_run_tool function in all versions up to, and including, 2.11. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to obtain a valid nonce that can be used to generate a global unlock key, which can in turn be used to add arbitrary IP address to the plugin allowlist. This can only by exploited on new installations where the site administrator hasn't visited the loginlockdown page yet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 04:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4054 | Relevanssi &amp;lt;= 4.24.3 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Search Highlights</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4054</link><description>The Relevanssi – A Better Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the highlights functionality in all versions up to, and including, 4.24.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page via the search results.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 03:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2821 | Search Exclude &amp;lt;= 2.4.9 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Plugin Settings Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2821</link><description>The Search Exclude plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the get_rest_permission function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings, excluding content from search results.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:26:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3844 | PeproDev Ultimate Profile Solutions 1.9.1 - 7.5.2 - Authentication Bypass to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3844</link><description>The PeproDev Ultimate Profile Solutions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in versions 1.9.1 to 7.5.2. This is due to handel_ajax_req() function not having proper restrictions on the change_user_meta functionality that makes it possible to set a OTP code and subsequently log in with that OTP code. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to login as other users on the site, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:26:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3851 | Download Manager and Payment Form WordPress Plugin – WP SmartPay 1.1.0 - 2.7.13 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3851</link><description>The Download Manager and Payment Form WordPress Plugin – WP SmartPay plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in versions 1.1.0 to 2.7.13 via the show() function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view other user's data like email address, name, and notes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3852 | WPshop 2 – E-Commerce 2.0.0 - 2.6.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3852</link><description>The WPshop 2 – E-Commerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in versions 2.0.0 to 2.6.0. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their details like email &amp; password through the update() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to change arbitrary user's passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3853 | WPshop 2 – E-Commerce 2.0.0 - 2.6.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary User Key Generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3853</link><description>The WPshop 2 – E-Commerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in versions 2.0.0 to 2.6.0 via the callback_generate_api_key() due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create valid API keys on behalf of other users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3860 | CarDealerPress &amp;lt;= 6.7.2504.00 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via saleclass Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3860</link><description>The CarDealerPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘saleclass' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.7.2504.00 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3921 | PeproDev Ultimate Profile Solutions 1.9.1 - 7.5.2 - Missing Authorization to Limited Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Meta Update via handel_ajax_req Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3921</link><description>The PeproDev Ultimate Profile Solutions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the handel_ajax_req() function in versions 1.9.1 to 7.5.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary user's metadata which can be leveraged to block an administrator from accessing their site when wp_capabilities is set to 0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3924 | PeproDev Ultimate Profile Solutions 1.9.1 - 7.5.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Email Enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3924</link><description>The PeproDev Ultimate Profile Solutions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data via its publicly exposed reset-password endpoint. The plugin looks up the 'valid_email' value based solely on a supplied username parameter, without verifying that the requester is associated with that user account. This allows unauthenticated attackers to enumerate email addresses for any user, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4055 | Multiple Post Type Order &amp;lt;= 1.10.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via mpto Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4055</link><description>The Multiple Post Type Order plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'mpto' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.10.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4220 | Xavin&amp;#x27;s List Subpages &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4220</link><description>The Xavin&amp;#039;s List Subpages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'xls' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4335 | Woocommerce Multiple Addresses &amp;lt;= 1.0.7.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4335</link><description>The Woocommerce Multiple Addresses plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7.1. This is due to insufficient restrictions on user meta that can be updated through the save_multiple_shipping_addresses() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to elevate their privileges to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3218 | IBM i improper certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3218</link><description>IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, 7.5, and 7.6 is vulnerable to authentication and authorization attacks due to incorrect validation processing in IBM i Netserver.  A malicious actor could use the weaknesses, in conjunction with brute force authentication attacks or to bypass authority restrictions, to access the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:27:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0855 | PGS Core &amp;lt;= 5.8.0 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0855</link><description>The PGS Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 5.8.0 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'import_header' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 22:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0856 | PGS Core &amp;lt;= 5.8.0 - Missing Authorization via Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0856</link><description>The PGS Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access, modification, and loss of data due to a missing capability check on multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 5.8.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add, modify, or plugin options.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 22:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4372 | Use after free in WebAudio in Google Chrome prior to 136.0.7103.92 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4372</link><description>Use after free in WebAudio in Google Chrome prior to 136.0.7103.92 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47420 | User Permissions on Network API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47420</link><description>266 vulnerability in Crestron Automate VX allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Automate VX: from 5.6.8161.21536 through 6.4.0.49.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0853 | PGS Core &amp;lt;= 5.8.0 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0853</link><description>The PGS Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'event' parameter in the 'save_header_builder' function in all versions up to, and including, 5.8.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:31:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44073 | SeaCMS v13.3 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component admin_comment_news.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44073</link><description>SeaCMS v13.3 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component admin_comment_news.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:17:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47419 | Non-Secure Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47419</link><description>Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information vulnerability in Crestron Automate VX allows Sniffing Network Traffic.

The device allows Web UI and API access over non-secure network ports which exposes sensitive information such as user passwords.


This issue affects Automate VX: from 5.6.8161.21536 through 6.4.0.49.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44899 | There is a stack overflow vulnerability in Tenda RX3 V1.0br_V16.03.13.11 In the fromSetWifiGusetBasic function of the web url /goform/ WifiG...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44899</link><description>There is a stack overflow vulnerability in Tenda RX3 V1.0br_V16.03.13.11 In the fromSetWifiGusetBasic function of the web url /goform/ WifiGuestSet, the manipulation of the parameter shareSpeed leads to stack overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46573 | passport-wsfed-saml2 Has SAML Authentication Bypass via Attribute Smuggling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46573</link><description>passport-wsfed-saml2 provides passport strategy for both WS-fed and SAML2 protocol. A vulnerability present starting in version 3.0.5 up to and including version 4.6.3 allows an attacker to impersonate any user during SAML authentication by tampering with a valid SAML response. This can be done by adding attributes to the response. Users are affected specifically when the service provider is using `passport-wsfed-saml2` and a valid SAML Response signed by the Identity Provider can be obtained. Version 4.6.4 contains a fix for the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:33:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0649 | Stack Exhaustion In Tensorflow Serving</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0649</link><description>Incorrect JSON input stringification in Google's Tensorflow serving versions up to 2.18.0 allows for potentially unbounded recursion leading to server crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46572 | passport-wsfed-saml2 Has SAML Authentication Bypass via Signature Wrapping</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46572</link><description>passport-wsfed-saml2 provides passport strategy for both WS-fed and SAML2 protocol. A vulnerability present starting in version 3.0.5 up to and including version 4.6.3 allows an attacker to impersonate any user in the Auth0 tenant during SAML authentication by crafting a SAMLResponse. This can be done by using a valid SAML object that was signed by the configured IdP. Users are affected specifically when the service provider is using passport-wsfed-saml2 and a valid SAML document signed by the Identity Provider can be obtained. Version 4.6.4 contains a fix for the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47418 | Recording</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47418</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Crestron Automate VX allows Functionality Misuse.

There is no visible indication when the system is recording and recording can be enabled remotely via a network API. 
This issue affects Automate VX: from 5.6.8161.21536 through 6.4.0.49.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47256 | Libxmp through 4.6.2 has a stack-based buffer overflow in depack_pha in loaders/prowizard/pha.c via a malformed Pha format tracker module in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47256</link><description>Libxmp through 4.6.2 has a stack-based buffer overflow in depack_pha in loaders/prowizard/pha.c via a malformed Pha format tracker module in a .mod file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12225 | Io.quarkus:quarkus-security-webauthn: quarkus webauthn unexpected authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12225</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Quarkus in the quarkus-security-webauthn module. The Quarkus WebAuthn module publishes default REST endpoints for registering and logging users in while allowing developers to provide custom REST endpoints. When developers provide custom REST endpoints, the default endpoints remain accessible, potentially allowing attackers to obtain a login cookie that has no corresponding user in the Quarkus application or, depending on how the application is written, could correspond to an existing user that has no relation with the current attacker, allowing anyone to log in as an existing user by just knowing that user's user name.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 19:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47417 | Enable Debug Images</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47417</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Crestron Automate VX allows Functionality Misuse.



When Enable Debug Images in Crestron Automate VX is active, snapshots of the captured video or portions thereof are stored locally on the system, and there is no visible indication that this is being done.


This issue affects Automate VX: from 5.6.8161.21536 through 6.4.0.49.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 19:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46820 | phpgt/Dom exposes the GITHUB_TOKEN in Dom workflow run artifact</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46820</link><description>phpgt/Dom provides access to modern DOM APIs. Versions of phpgt/Dom prior to 4.1.8 expose the GITHUB_TOKEN in the Dom workflow run artifact. The ci.yml workflow file uses actions/upload-artifact@v4 to upload the build artifact. This artifact is a zip of the current directory, which includes the automatically generated .git/config file containing the run's GITHUB_TOKEN. Seeing as the artifact can be downloaded prior to the end of the workflow, there is a few seconds where an attacker can extract the token from the artifact and use it with the GitHub API to push malicious code or rewrite release commits in your repository. Any downstream user of the repository may be affected, but the token should only be valid for the duration of the workflow run, limiting the time during which exploitation could occur. Version 4.1.8 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 18:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46816 | goshs route not protected, allows command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46816</link><description>goshs is a SimpleHTTPServer written in Go. Starting in version 0.3.4 and prior to version 1.0.5, running goshs without arguments makes it possible for anyone to execute commands on the server. The function `dispatchReadPump` does not checks the option cli `-c`, thus allowing anyone to execute arbitrary command through the use of websockets. Version 1.0.5 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 18:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4388 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4388</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.5, 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12, 7.4 GA through update 92 allows an remote non-authenticated attacker to inject JavaScript into the modules/apps/marketplace/marketplace-app-manager-web.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 18:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25014 | Kibana arbitrary code execution via prototype pollution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25014</link><description>A Prototype pollution vulnerability in Kibana leads to arbitrary code execution via crafted HTTP requests to machine learning and reporting endpoints.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 17:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37730 | Logstash Improper Certificate Validation in TCP output</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37730</link><description>Improper certificate validation in Logstash's TCP output could lead to a man-in-the-middle (MitM) attack in “client” mode, as hostname verification in TCP output was not being performed when the ssl_verification_mode =&gt; full was set.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 17:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44900 | In Tenda RX3 V1.0br_V16.03.13.11 in the GetParentControlInfo function of the web url /goform/GetParentControlInfo, the manipulation of the p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44900</link><description>In Tenda RX3 V1.0br_V16.03.13.11 in the GetParentControlInfo function of the web url /goform/GetParentControlInfo, the manipulation of the parameter mac leads to stack overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 17:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46815 | ZITADEL Allows IdP Intent Token Reuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46815</link><description>The identity infrastructure software ZITADEL offers developers the ability to manage user sessions using the Session API. This API enables the use of IdPs for authentication, known as idp intents. Following a successful idp intent, the client receives an id and token on a predefined URI. These id and token can then be used to authenticate the user or their session. However, prior to versions 3.0.0, 2.71.9, and 2.70.10, it was possible to exploit this feature by repeatedly using intents. This allowed an attacker with access to the application’s URI to retrieve the id and token, enabling them to authenticate on behalf of the user. It's important to note that the use of additional factors (MFA) prevents a complete authentication process and, consequently, access to the ZITADEL API. Versions 3.0.0, 2.71.9, and 2.70.10 contain a fix for the issue. No known workarounds other than upgrading are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 17:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46736 | Umbraco Makes User Enumeration Feasible Based on Timing of Login Response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46736</link><description>Umbraco is a free and open source .NET content management system. Prior to versions 10.8.10 and 13.8.1, based on an analysis of the timing of post login API responses, it's possible to determine whether an account exists. The issue is patched in versions 10.8.10 and 13.8.1. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 17:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32022 | Finit has heap based buffer overwrite in urandom.so plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32022</link><description>Finit provides fast init for Linux systems. Finit's urandom plugin has a heap buffer overwrite vulnerability at boot which leads to it overwriting other parts of the heap, possibly causing random instabilities and undefined behavior. The urandom plugin is enabled by default, so this bug affects everyone using Finit 4.2 or later that do not explicitly disable the plugin at build time. This bug is fixed in Finit 4.12. Those who cannot upgrade or backport the fix to urandom.c are strongly recommended to disable the plugin in the call to the `configure` script.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 17:09:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46735 | Terraform WinDNS Provider improperly sanitizes input variables in `windns_record`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46735</link><description>Terraform WinDNS Provider allows users to manage their Windows DNS server resources through Terraform. A security issue has been found in Terraform WinDNS Provider before version `1.0.5`. The `windns_record` resource did not sanitize the input variables. This could lead to authenticated command injection in the underlyding powershell command prompt. Version 1.0.5 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 17:09:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30165 | Remote Code Execution Vulnerability in vLLM Multi-Node Cluster Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30165</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models. In a multi-node vLLM deployment using the V0 engine, vLLM uses ZeroMQ for some multi-node communication purposes. The secondary vLLM hosts open a `SUB` ZeroMQ socket and connect to an `XPUB` socket on the primary vLLM host. When data is received on this `SUB` socket, it is deserialized with `pickle`. This is unsafe, as it can be abused to execute code on a remote machine. Since the vulnerability exists in a client that connects to the primary vLLM host, this vulnerability serves as an escalation point. If the primary vLLM host is compromised, this vulnerability could be used to compromise the rest of the hosts in the vLLM deployment. Attackers could also use other means to exploit the vulnerability without requiring access to the primary vLLM host. One example would be the use of ARP cache poisoning to redirect traffic to a malicious endpoint used to deliver a payload with arbitrary code to execute on the target machine. Note that this issue only affects the V0 engine, which has been off by default since v0.8.0. Further, the issue only applies to a deployment using tensor parallelism across multiple hosts, which we do not expect to be a common deployment pattern. Since V0 is has been off by default since v0.8.0 and the fix is fairly invasive, the maintainers of vLLM have decided not to fix this issue. Instead, the maintainers recommend that users ensure their environment is on a secure network in case this pattern is in use. The V1 engine is not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 17:09:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26262 | An issue in the component /internals/functions of R-fx Networks Linux Malware Detect v1.6.5 allows attackers to escalate privileges and exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26262</link><description>An issue in the component /internals/functions of R-fx Networks Linux Malware Detect v1.6.5 allows attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code via supplying a file that contains a crafted filename.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:55:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45250 | MrDoc v0.95 and before is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the validate_url function of the app_doc/utils.py file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45250</link><description>MrDoc v0.95 and before is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the validate_url function of the app_doc/utils.py file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:55:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4041 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials Optigo Networks ONS NC600</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4041</link><description>In Optigo Networks ONS NC600 versions 4.2.1-084 through 4.7.2-330, an attacker could connect with the device's ssh server and utilize the system's components to perform OS command executions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33770 | Real Estate Management System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the message parameter at /contact.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33770</link><description>Real Estate Management System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the message parameter at /contact.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22476 | Dell Storage Center - Dell Storage Manager, version(s) 20.1.20, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22476</link><description>Dell Storage Center - Dell Storage Manager, version(s) 20.1.20, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with adjacent network access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Remote execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:25:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22477 | Dell Storage Center - Dell Storage Manager, version(s) 20.1.20, contain(s) an Improper Authentication vulnerability. An unauthenticated atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22477</link><description>Dell Storage Center - Dell Storage Manager, version(s) 20.1.20, contain(s) an Improper Authentication vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with adjacent network access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:25:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4384 | Certificate validity not properly verified</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4384</link><description>The MQTT add-on of PcVue fails to verify that a remote device’s certificate has not already expired or has not yet become valid. This allows malicious devices to present certificates that are not rejected properly.

The use of a client certificate reduces the risk for random devices to take advantage of this flaw.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:25:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22478 | Dell Storage Center - Dell Storage Manager, version(s) 20.1.20, contain(s) an Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22478</link><description>Dell Storage Center - Dell Storage Manager, version(s) 20.1.20, contain(s) an Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with adjacent network access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure and Information tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:59:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22479 | Dell Storage Center - Dell Storage Manager, version(s) 20.0.21, contain(s) an Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22479</link><description>Dell Storage Center - Dell Storage Manager, version(s) 20.0.21, contain(s) an Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with adjacent network access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Script injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45492 | Netgear EX8000 V1.0.0.126 is vulnerable to Command Injection via the Iface parameter in the action_wireless function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45492</link><description>Netgear EX8000 V1.0.0.126 is vulnerable to Command Injection via the Iface parameter in the action_wireless function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45487 | Linksys E5600 v1.1.0.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the runtime.InternetConnection function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45487</link><description>Linksys E5600 v1.1.0.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the runtime.InternetConnection function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45488 | Linksys E5600 v1.1.0.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the runtime.ddnsStatus DynDNS function via the mailex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45488</link><description>Linksys E5600 v1.1.0.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the runtime.ddnsStatus DynDNS function via the mailex parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45489 | Linksys E5600 v1.1.0.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the runtime.ddnsStatus DynDNS function via the hostna...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45489</link><description>Linksys E5600 v1.1.0.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the runtime.ddnsStatus DynDNS function via the hostname parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45490 | Linksys E5600 v1.1.0.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the runtime.ddnsStatus DynDNS function via the passwo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45490</link><description>Linksys E5600 v1.1.0.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the runtime.ddnsStatus DynDNS function via the password parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23379 | Dell Storage Center - Dell Storage Manager, version(s) 21.0.20, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23379</link><description>Dell Storage Center - Dell Storage Manager, version(s) 21.0.20, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with adjacent network access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Script injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45491 | Linksys E5600 v1.1.0.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the runtime.ddnsStatus DynDNS function via the userna...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45491</link><description>Linksys E5600 v1.1.0.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the runtime.ddnsStatus DynDNS function via the username parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4363 | itsourcecode Gym Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4363</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in itsourcecode Gym Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ajax.php?action=end_membership. The manipulation of the argument rid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4368 | Tenda AC8 MtuSetMacWan formGetRouterStatus buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4368</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.06. Affected is the function formGetRouterStatus of the file /goform/MtuSetMacWan. The manipulation of the argument shareSpeed leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4362 | itsourcecode Gym Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4362</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Gym Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /ajax.php?action=save_membership. The manipulation of the argument member_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:23:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46814 | FastAPI Guard Remote Header Injection via X-Forwarded-For Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46814</link><description>FastAPI Guard is a security library for FastAPI that provides middleware to control IPs, log requests, and detect penetration attempts. An HTTP header injection vulnerability has been identified in versions prior to 2.0.0. By manipulating the X-Forwarded-For header, an attacker can potentially inject arbitrary IP addresses into the request. This vulnerability can allow attackers to bypass IP-based access controls, mislead logging systems, and impersonate trusted clients. It is especially impactful when the application relies on the X-Forwarded-For header for IP-based authorization or authentication. Users should upgrade to FastAPI Guard version 2.0.0 to receive a fix.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4373 | Glib: buffer underflow on glib through glib/gstring.c via function g_string_insert_unichar</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4373</link><description>A flaw was found in GLib, which is vulnerable to an integer overflow in the g_string_insert_unichar() function. When the position at which to insert the character is large, the position will overflow, leading to a buffer underwrite.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4374 | Quay: incorrect privilege assignment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4374</link><description>A flaw was found in Quay. When an organization acts as a proxy cache, and a user or robot pulls an image that hasn't been mirrored yet, they are granted "Admin" permissions on the newly created repository.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2898 | IBM Maximo Application Suite privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2898</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite 9.0 could allow an attacker with some level of access to elevate their privileges due to a security configuration vulnerability in Role-Based Access Control (RBAC) configurations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4360 | itsourcecode Gym Management System view_member.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4360</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in itsourcecode Gym Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /view_member.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4361 | PHPGurukul Company Visitor Management System department.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4361</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Company Visitor Management System 2.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /department.php. The manipulation of the argument departmentname leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4359 | itsourcecode Gym Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4359</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Gym Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_member. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4357 | Tenda RX3 telnet command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4357</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11_multi. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/telnet. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4358 | PHPGurukul Company Visitor Management System admin-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4358</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Company Visitor Management System 2.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument adminname leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4356 | Tenda DAP-1520 Authentication storage mod_graph_auth_uri_handler stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4356</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda DAP-1520 1.10B04_BETA02. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function mod_graph_auth_uri_handler of the file /storage of the component Authentication Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4354 | Tenda DAP-1520 storage check_dws_cookie stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4354</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda DAP-1520 1.10B04_BETA02 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function check_dws_cookie of the file /storage. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:09:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4355 | Tenda DAP-1520 api set_ws_action heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4355</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda DAP-1520 1.10B04_BETA02. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function set_ws_action of the file /dws/api/. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:09:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4352 | Golden Link Secondary System tcEntrFlowSelect.htm sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4352</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Golden Link Secondary System up to 20250424. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /reprotframework/tcEntrFlowSelect.htm. The manipulation of the argument custTradeId leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4353 | Golden Link Secondary System queryTsDictionaryType.htm sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4353</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Golden Link Secondary System up to 20250424. Affected is an unknown function of the file /paraframework/queryTsDictionaryType.htm. The manipulation of the argument dictCn1 leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 12:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4349 | D-Link DIR-600L formSysCmd command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4349</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in D-Link DIR-600L up to 2.07B01. This affects the function formSysCmd. The manipulation of the argument host leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 11:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4350 | D-Link DIR-600L wake_on_lan command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4350</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DIR-600L up to 2.07B01. This vulnerability affects the function wake_on_lan. The manipulation of the argument host leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 11:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0984 | Arbitrary File Upload in Netoloji Software&amp;#x27;s E-Flow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0984</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type, Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Netoloji Software E-Flow allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs, Stored XSS, File Content Injection.This issue affects E-Flow: before 3.23.00.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 11:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4348 | D-Link DIR-600L formSetWanL2TP buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4348</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-600L up to 2.07B01. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formSetWanL2TP. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 11:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40620 | Multiple vulnerabilities in TCMAN&amp;#x27;s GIM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40620</link><description>SQL injection in TCMAN's GIM v11. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject an SQL statement to obtain, update and delete all information in the database. This vulnerability was found in each of the following parameters according to the vulnerability identifier ‘User’ parameter of the ‘ValidateUserAndWS’ endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40621 | Multiple vulnerabilities in TCMAN&amp;#x27;s GIM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40621</link><description>SQL injection in TCMAN's GIM v11. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject an SQL statement to obtain, update and delete all information in the database. This vulnerability was found in each of the following parameters according to the vulnerability identifier ‘User’ parameter of the ‘ValidateUserAndGetData’ endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40622 | Multiple vulnerabilities in TCMAN&amp;#x27;s GIM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40622</link><description>SQL injection in TCMAN's GIM v11. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject an SQL statement to obtain, update and delete all information in the database. This vulnerability was found in each of the following parameters according to the vulnerability identifier ‘username’ parameter of the ‘GetLastDatePasswordChange’ endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40623 | Multiple vulnerabilities in TCMAN&amp;#x27;s GIM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40623</link><description>SQL injection in TCMAN's GIM v11. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject an SQL statement to obtain, update and delete all information in the database. This vulnerability was found in each of the following parameters according to the vulnerability identifier ‘Sender’ and “email” parameters of the ‘createNotificationAndroid’ endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40624 | Multiple vulnerabilities in TCMAN&amp;#x27;s GIM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40624</link><description>SQL injection in TCMAN's GIM v11. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject an SQL statement to obtain, update and delete all information in the database. This vulnerability was found in each of the following parameters according to the vulnerability identifier ‘User’ and “email” parameters of the ‘updatePassword’ endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40625 | Multiple vulnerabilities in TCMAN&amp;#x27;s GIM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40625</link><description>Unrestricted file upload in TCMAN's GIM v11. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to upload any file within the server, even a malicious file to obtain a Remote Code Execution (RCE).</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4347 | D-Link DIR-600L formWlSiteSurvey buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4347</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-600L up to 2.07B01. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formWlSiteSurvey. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4345 | D-Link DIR-600L formSetLog buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4345</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-600L up to 2.07B01 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function formSetLog. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4346 | D-Link DIR-600L formSetWAN_Wizard534 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4346</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-600L up to 2.07B01. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function formSetWAN_Wizard534. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 10:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4344 | D-Link DIR-600L formLogin buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4344</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DIR-600L up to 2.07B01. This affects the function formLogin. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2011 | Slider &amp;amp; Popup Builder by Depicter &amp;lt;= 3.6.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;s&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2011</link><description>The Slider &amp; Popup Builder by Depicter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to generic SQL Injection via the ‘s' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:31:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3782 | Cision Block &amp;lt;= 4.3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3782</link><description>The Cision Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:31:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46762 | Apache Parquet Java: Potential malicious code execution from trusted packages in the parquet-avro module when reading an Avro schema from a Parquet file metadata</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46762</link><description>Schema parsing in the parquet-avro module of Apache Parquet 1.15.0 and previous versions allows bad actors to execute arbitrary code.

While 1.15.1 introduced a fix to restrict untrusted packages, the default setting of trusted packages still allows malicious classes from these packages to be executed.

The exploit is only applicable if the client code of parquet-avro uses the "specific" or the "reflect" models deliberately for reading Parquet files. ("generic" model is not impacted)

Users are recommended to upgrade to 1.15.2 or set the system property "org.apache.parquet.avro.SERIALIZABLE_PACKAGES" to an empty string on 1.15.1. Both are sufficient to fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:31:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22886 | distributeddatamgr_udmf has a memory leak vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22886</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker case DOS through missing release of memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:10:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25052 | arkcompiler_ets_runtime has a buffer overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25052</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause DOS through buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:10:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27132 | arkcompiler_ets_runtime has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27132</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through out-of-bounds write. This vulnerability can be exploited only in restricted scenarios.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27241 | multimedia_av_codec has a NULL pointer dereference vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27241</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker case DOS through NULL pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27248 | ai_neural_network_runtime has a NULL pointer dereference vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27248</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker case DOS through NULL pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:10:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4343 | D-Link DIR-600L formEasySetupWizard buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4343</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-600L up to 2.07B01 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formEasySetupWizard. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:10:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25218 | third_party_mksh has a NULL pointer dereference vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25218</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker case DOS through NULL pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45554 | Use After Free in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45554</link><description>Memory corruption during concurrent SSR execution due to race condition on the global maps list.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45562 | Use After Free in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45562</link><description>Memory corruption during concurrent access to server info object due to unprotected critical field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45563 | Out-of-bounds Write in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45563</link><description>Memory corruption while handling schedule request in Camera Request Manager(CRM) due to invalid link count in the corresponding session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45564 | Use After Free in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45564</link><description>Memory corruption during concurrent access to server info object due to incorrect reference count update.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45565 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45565</link><description>Memory corruption when blob structure is modified by user-space after kernel verification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45566 | Use After Free in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45566</link><description>Memory corruption during concurrent buffer access due to modification of the reference count.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45567 | Use After Free in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45567</link><description>Memory corruption while encoding JPEG format.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45568 | Buffer Over-read in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45568</link><description>Memory corruption due to improper bounds check while command handling in camera-kernel driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45570 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45570</link><description>Memory corruption may occur during IO configuration processing when the IO port count is invalid.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45574 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45574</link><description>Memory corruption during array access in Camera kernel due to invalid index from invalid command data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45575 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45575</link><description>Memory corruption Camera kernel when large number of devices are attached through userspace.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45576 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45576</link><description>Memory corruption while prociesing command buffer buffer in OPE module.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45577 | Improper Input Validation in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45577</link><description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTL calls from userspace to camera kernel driver to dump request information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45578 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45578</link><description>Memory corruption while acquire and update IOCTLs during IFE output resource ID validation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45579 | Improper Input Validation in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45579</link><description>Memory corruption may occur when invoking IOCTL calls from userspace to the camera kernel driver to dump request information, due to a missing memory requirement check.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45581 | Out-of-bounds Write in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45581</link><description>Memory corruption while sound model registration for voice activation with audio kernel driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45583 | Use After Free in Secure Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45583</link><description>Memory corruption while handling multiple IOCTL calls from userspace to operate DMA operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49829 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49829</link><description>Memory corruption can occur during context user dumps due to inadequate checks on buffer length.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49830 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49830</link><description>Memory corruption while processing an IOCTL call to set mixer controls.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49835 | Out-of-bounds Write in SPS Applications</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49835</link><description>Memory corruption while reading secure file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49841 | Detection of Error Condition Without Action in Hypervisor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49841</link><description>Memory corruption during memory assignment to headless peripheral VM due to incorrect error code handling.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49842 | Improper Access Control in Hypervisor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49842</link><description>Memory corruption during memory mapping into protected VM address space due to incorrect API restrictions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49844 | Improper Input Validation in Automotive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49844</link><description>Memory corruption while triggering commands in the PlayReady Trusted application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49845 | Improper Input Validation in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49845</link><description>Memory corruption during the FRS UDS generation process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49846 | Buffer Over-read in Multi-Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49846</link><description>Memory corruption while decoding of OTA messages from T3448 IE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49847 | Buffer Over-read in Multi-Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49847</link><description>Transient DOS while processing of a registration acceptance OTA due to incorrect ciphering key data IE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21453 | Use After Free in GPS HLOS Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21453</link><description>Memory corruption while processing a data structure, when an iterator is accessed after it has been removed, potential failures occur.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21459 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21459</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing per STA profile in ML IE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21460 | Improper Input Validation in Automotive Software platform based on QNX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21460</link><description>Memory corruption while processing a message, when the buffer is controlled by a Guest VM, the value can be changed continuously.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21462 | Out-of-bounds Write in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21462</link><description>Memory corruption while processing an IOCTL request, when buffer significantly exceeds the command argument limit.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21467 | Out-of-bounds Write in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21467</link><description>Memory corruption while reading the FW response from the shared queue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21468 | Out-of-bounds Write in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21468</link><description>Memory corruption while reading response from FW, when buffer size is changed by FW while driver is using this size to write null character at the end of buffer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21469 | Improper Access Control in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21469</link><description>Memory corruption while processing image encoding, when input buffer length is 0 in IOCTL call.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21470 | Improper Access Control in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21470</link><description>Memory corruption while processing image encoding, when configuration is NULL in IOCTL parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21475 | Buffer Over-read in Display</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21475</link><description>Memory corruption while processing escape code, when DisplayId is passed with large unsigned value.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4341 | D-Link DIR-880L Request Header ssdpcgi sub_16570 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4341</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DIR-880L up to 104WWb01. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_16570 of the file /htdocs/ssdpcgi of the component Request Header Handler. The manipulation of the argument HTTP_ST/REMOTE_ADDR/REMOTE_PORT/SERVER_ID leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4342 | D-Link DIR-600L formEasySetupWizard3 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4342</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DIR-600L up to 2.07B01. Affected by this issue is the function formEasySetupWizard3. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3020 | Wiesemann &amp;amp; Theis: Multiple W&amp;amp;T Products are vulnerable to cross-site-scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3020</link><description>An low privileged remote Attacker can execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into several fields of the configuration webpage with limited impact.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4333 | feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp/production_ssm FileServiceImpl.java uploadFile unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4333</link><description>A vulnerability was found in feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp and production_ssm up to 0.0.1. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function uploadFile of the file src/main/java/com/megagao/production/ssm/service/impl/FileServiceImpl.java. The manipulation of the argument uploadFile leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is distributed under two entirely different names.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4340 | D-Link DIR-890L/DIR-806A1 soap.cgi sub_175C8 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4340</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in D-Link DIR-890L and DIR-806A1 up to 100CNb11/108B03. Affected is the function sub_175C8 of the file /htdocs/soap.cgi. The manipulation leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4332 | PHPGurukul Company Visitor Management System visitor-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4332</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Company Visitor Management System 2.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /visitor-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3281 | User Registration &amp;amp; Membership – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile &amp;lt;= 4.2.1 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Limited User Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3281</link><description>The User Registration &amp; Membership – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.1 via the create_stripe_subscription() function, due to missing validation on the 'member_id' user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary user accounts that have registered through the plugin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4331 | SourceCodester Online Student Clearance System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4331</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Online Student Clearance System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3281 | User Registration &amp;amp; Membership – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile &amp;lt;= 4.2.1 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Limited User Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3281</link><description>The User Registration &amp; Membership – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.1 via the create_stripe_subscription() function, due to missing validation on the 'member_id' user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary user accounts that have registered through the plugin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4331 | SourceCodester Online Student Clearance System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4331</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Online Student Clearance System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58252 | Vulnerability of insufficient information protection in the media library module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58252</link><description>Vulnerability of insufficient information protection in the media library module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46587 | Permission control vulnerability in the media library module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confid...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46587</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the media library module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46588 | Vulnerability of unauthorized access in the app lock module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect integrity and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46588</link><description>Vulnerability of unauthorized access in the app lock module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect integrity and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46589 | Vulnerability of unauthorized access in the app lock module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect integrity and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46589</link><description>Vulnerability of unauthorized access in the app lock module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect integrity and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46590 | Bypass vulnerability in the network search instruction authentication module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can bypas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46590</link><description>Bypass vulnerability in the network search instruction authentication module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can bypass authentication and enable access to some network search functions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46591 | Out-of-bounds data read vulnerability in the authorization module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46591</link><description>Out-of-bounds data read vulnerability in the authorization module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46592 | Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the USB HDI driver module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46592</link><description>Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the USB HDI driver module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46593 | Process residence vulnerability in abnormal scenarios in the print module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46593</link><description>Process residence vulnerability in abnormal scenarios in the print module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46585 | Out-of-bounds array read/write vulnerability in the kernel module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46585</link><description>Out-of-bounds array read/write vulnerability in the kernel module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46586 | Permission control vulnerability in the contacts module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46586</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the contacts module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46584 | Vulnerability of improper authentication logic implementation in the file system module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46584</link><description>Vulnerability of improper authentication logic implementation in the file system module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4328 | fp2952 spring-cloud-base HTTP Header MvcController.java sendBack redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4328</link><description>A vulnerability was found in fp2952 spring-cloud-base up to 7f050dc6db9afab82c5ce1d41cd74ed255ec9bfa. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sendBack of the file /spring-cloud-base-master/auth-center/auth-center-provider/src/main/java/com/peng/auth/provider/config/web/MvcController.java of the component HTTP Header Handler. The manipulation of the argument Referer leads to open redirect. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4329 | 74CMS index path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4329</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 74CMS up to 3.33.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function index of the file /index.php/index/download/index. The manipulation of the argument url leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4327 | MRCMS cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4327</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MRCMS 3.1.2. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Multiple endpoints might be affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 06:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4325 | MRCMS Category Management Page add.do cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4325</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in MRCMS 3.1.2 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/category/add.do of the component Category Management Page. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 06:25:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4326 | MRCMS Add Fragment Page add.do cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4326</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MRCMS 3.1.2 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/chip/add.do of the component Add Fragment Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 06:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4324 | MRCMS External Link Management Page edit.do cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4324</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in MRCMS 3.1.2. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/link/edit.do of the component External Link Management Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 05:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4323 | MRCMS Edit Article Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4323</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in MRCMS 3.1.2. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Edit Article Page. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 05:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4313 | SourceCodester Advanced Web Store admin_addnew_product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4313</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Advanced Web Store 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/admin_addnew_product.php. The manipulation of the argument txtProdId leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 04:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4314 | SourceCodester Advanced Web Store index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4314</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Advanced Web Store 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument txtLogin leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 04:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2802 | LayoutBoxx &amp;lt;= 0.3.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2802</link><description>The LayoutBoxx plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 0.3.1. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 04:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4337 | AHAthat Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to AHA Page Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4337</link><description>The AHAthat Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the aha_plugin_page() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete AHA pages via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 04:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4311 | itsourcecode Content Management System update_main_topic_img.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4311</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Content Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/update_main_topic_img.php?topic_id=529. The manipulation of the argument stopic_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 04:27:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4312 | SourceCodester Advanced Web Store productdetail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4312</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Advanced Web Store 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /productdetail.php. The manipulation of the argument prodid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 04:27:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4310 | itsourcecode Content Management System add_topic.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4310</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Content Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/add_topic.php?category=BBS. The manipulation of the argument Cover Image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 03:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4309 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System add-art-type.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4309</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.1. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/add-art-type.php. The manipulation of the argument arttype leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 03:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4308 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System add-art-type.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4308</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.1. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/add-art-type.php. The manipulation of the argument arttype leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 03:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3609 | Reales WP STPT &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Unauthorized User Registration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3609</link><description>The Reales WP STPT plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized user registration in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.2. This is due to the 'reales_user_signup_form' AJAX action not verifying if user registration is enabled, prior to registering a user. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create new user accounts, which can be leveraged with CVE-XX to achieve privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 02:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3610 | Reales WP STPT &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via Password Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3610</link><description>The Reales WP STPT plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.2. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their details like password. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to change arbitrary user's passwords and email addresses, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account. This can be combined with CVE-2025-3609 to achieve remote code execution as an originally unauthenticated user with no account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 02:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4306 | PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System edit-phlebotomist.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4306</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /edit-phlebotomist.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 02:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4307 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System add-art-medium.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4307</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.1. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/add-art-medium.php. The manipulation of the argument artmed leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 02:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39442 | In sprd ssense service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39442</link><description>In sprd ssense service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 02:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4304 | PHPGurukul Cyber Cafe Management System adminprofile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4304</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Cyber Cafe Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /adminprofile.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 02:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4305 | kefaming mayi File.php upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4305</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in kefaming mayi up to 1.3.9 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function Upload of the file app/tools/controller/File.php. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 02:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2509 | Out-of-Bounds Read in Virglrenderer in ChromeOS  16093.57.0 allows a malicious guest VM to achieve arbitrary address access within the crosv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2509</link><description>Out-of-Bounds Read in Virglrenderer in ChromeOS  16093.57.0 allows a malicious guest VM to achieve arbitrary address access within the crosvm sandboxed process, potentially leading to 
VM escape via crafted vertex elements data triggering an out-of-bounds read in util_format_description.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 01:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46728 | cpp-httplib has Unbounded Memory Allocation in Chunked/No-Length Requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46728</link><description>cpp-httplib is a C++ header-only HTTP/HTTPS server and client library. Prior to version 0.20.1, the library fails to enforce configured size limits on incoming request bodies when `Transfer-Encoding: chunked` is used or when no `Content-Length` header is provided. A remote attacker can send a chunked request without the terminating zero-length chunk, causing uncontrolled memory allocation on the server. This leads to potential exhaustion of system memory and results in a server crash or unresponsiveness. Version 0.20.1 fixes the issue by enforcing limits during parsing. If the limit is exceeded at any point during reading, the connection is terminated immediately. A short-term workaround through a Reverse Proxy is available. If updating the library immediately is not feasible, deploy a reverse proxy (e.g., Nginx, HAProxy) in front of the `cpp-httplib` application. Configure the proxy to enforce maximum request body size limits, thereby stopping excessively large requests before they reach the vulnerable library code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 01:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4303 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System add-phlebotomist.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4303</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /add-phlebotomist.php. The manipulation of the argument empid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 01:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4301 | itsourcecode Content Management System search-notice.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4301</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Content Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /search-notice.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 01:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4299 | Tenda AC1206 openSchedWifi setSchedWifi buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4299</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC1206 up to 15.03.06.23. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setSchedWifi of the file /goform/openSchedWifi. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 01:15:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4300 | itsourcecode Content Management System search_list.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4300</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Content Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /search_list.php. The manipulation of the argument Search leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 01:15:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4298 | Tenda AC1206 setcfm formSetCfm buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4298</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC1206 up to 15.03.06.23. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formSetCfm of the file /goform/setcfm. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 23:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4297 | PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System change-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4297</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System 2.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/change-password.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Multiple parameters might be affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 23:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4292 | MRCMS Edit User Page edit.do cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4292</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in MRCMS 3.1.3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/user/edit.do of the component Edit User Page. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 22:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4293 | MRCMS Group Edit Page edit.do cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4293</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MRCMS 3.1.3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/group/edit.do of the component Group Edit Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 22:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44071 | SeaCMS v13.3 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the component phomebak.php. This vulnerability allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44071</link><description>SeaCMS v13.3 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the component phomebak.php. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 22:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44072 | SeaCMS v13.3 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component admin_manager.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44072</link><description>SeaCMS v13.3 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component admin_manager.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 22:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44074 | SeaCMS v13.3 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component admin_topic.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44074</link><description>SeaCMS v13.3 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component admin_topic.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 22:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4291 | IdeaCMS saveUpload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4291</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in IdeaCMS up to 1.6. Affected is the function saveUpload. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 22:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4290 | PCMan FTP Server SMNT Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4290</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PCMan FTP Server 2.0.7. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component SMNT Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 21:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0915 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0915</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes DB2 Connect Server) 11.5.0 through 11.5.9 and 12.1.0 through 12.1.1 



under specific configurations could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service due to insufficient release of allocated memory resources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 21:09:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1000 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1000</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes DB2 Connect Server) 11.5.0 through 11.5.9 and 12.1.0 through 12.1.1 

could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service when connecting to a z/OS database due to improper handling of automatic client rerouting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 21:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1493 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1493</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes DB2 Connect Server) 12.1.0 through 12.1.1 





could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service due to concurrent execution of shared resources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 21:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4289 | PCMan FTP Server RNTO Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4289</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PCMan FTP Server 2.0.7. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component RNTO Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 21:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4288 | PCMan FTP Server RNFR Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4288</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PCMan FTP Server 2.0.7. This affects an unknown part of the component RNFR Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 20:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46813 | Private data leak on login-required Discourse sites</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46813</link><description>Discourse is an open-source community platform. A data leak vulnerability affects sites deployed between commits 10df7fdee060d44accdee7679d66d778d1136510 and 82d84af6b0efbd9fa2aeec3e91ce7be1a768511b. On login-required sites, the leak meant that some content on the site's homepage could be visible to unauthenticated users. Only login-required sites that got deployed during this timeframe are affected, roughly between April 30 2025 noon EDT and May 2 2025, noon EDT. Sites on the stable branch are unaffected. Private content on an instance's homepage could be visible to unauthenticated users on login-required sites. Versions of 3.5.0.beta4 after commit 82d84af6b0efbd9fa2aeec3e91ce7be1a768511b are not vulnerable to the issue. No workarounds are available. Sites must upgrade to a non-vulnerable version of Discourse.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 20:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4287 | PyTorch nccl.py torch.cuda.nccl.reduce denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4287</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PyTorch 2.6.0+cu124. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function torch.cuda.nccl.reduce of the file torch/cuda/nccl.py. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is identified as 5827d2061dcb4acd05ac5f8e65d8693a481ba0f5. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 20:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46734 | league/commonmark Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Attributes extension</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46734</link><description>league/commonmark is a PHP Markdown parser. A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Attributes extension of the league/commonmark library (versions 1.5.0 through 2.6.x) allows remote attackers to insert malicious JavaScript calls into HTML. The league/commonmark library provides configuration options such as `html_input: 'strip'` and `allow_unsafe_links: false` to mitigate cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks by stripping raw HTML and disallowing unsafe links. However, when the Attributes Extension is enabled, it introduces a way for users to inject arbitrary HTML attributes into elements via Markdown syntax using curly braces. Version 2.7.0 contains three changes to prevent this XSS attack vector: All attributes starting with `on` are considered unsafe and blocked by default; support for an explicit allowlist of allowed HTML attributes; and manually-added `href` and `src` attributes now respect the existing `allow_unsafe_links` configuration option. If upgrading is not feasible, please consider disabling the `AttributesExtension` for untrusted users and/or filtering the rendered HTML through a library like HTMLPurifier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 20:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1909 | BuddyBoss Platform Pro &amp;lt;= 2.7.01 - Authentication Bypass via Apple OAuth provider</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1909</link><description>The BuddyBoss Platform Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 2.7.01. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being supplied during the Apple OAuth authenticate request through the plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the email.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46730 | Mobile Security Framework (MobSF) Allows Web Server Resource Exhaustion via ZIP of Death Attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46730</link><description>MobSF is a mobile application security testing tool used. Typically, MobSF is deployed on centralized internal or cloud-based servers that also host other security tools and web applications. Access to the MobSF web interface is often granted to internal security teams, audit teams, and external vendors.  MobSF provides a feature that allows users to upload ZIP files for static analysis. Upon upload, these ZIP files are automatically extracted and stored within the MobSF directory. However, in versions up to and including 4.3.2, this functionality lacks a check on the total uncompressed size of the ZIP file, making it vulnerable to a ZIP of Death (zip bomb) attack. Due to the absence of safeguards against oversized extractions, an attacker can craft a specially prepared ZIP file that is small in compressed form but expands to a massive size upon extraction. Exploiting this, an attacker can exhaust the server's disk space, leading to a complete denial of service (DoS) not just for MobSF, but also for any other applications or websites hosted on the same server. This vulnerability can lead to complete server disruption in an organization which can affect other internal portals and tools too (which are hosted on the same server). If some organization has created their customized cloud based mobile security tool using MobSF core then an attacker can exploit this vulnerability to crash their servers. Commit 6987a946485a795f4fd38cebdb4860b368a1995d fixes this issue. As an additional mitigation, it is recommended to implement a safeguard that checks the total uncompressed size of any uploaded ZIP file before extraction. If the estimated uncompressed size exceeds a safe threshold (e.g., 100 MB), MobSF should reject the file and notify the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46731 | Craft CMS Contains a Potential Remote Code Execution Vulnerability via Twig SSTI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46731</link><description>Craft is a content management system. Versions of Craft CMS on the 4.x branch prior to 4.14.13 and on the 5.x branch prior to 5.6.16 contains a potential remote code execution vulnerability via Twig SSTI. One must have administrator access and `ALLOW_ADMIN_CHANGES` must be enabled for this to work. Users should update to the patched versions 4.14.13 or 5.6.15 to mitigate the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4286 | Intelbras InControl Dispositivos Edição Page credentials storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4286</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Intelbras InControl up to 2.21.59. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the component Dispositivos Edição Page. The manipulation of the argument Senha de Comunicação leads to unprotected storage of credentials. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. According to the vendor this issue should be fixed in a later release.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46726 | Langroid Vulnerable to XXE Injection via XMLToolMessage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46726</link><description>Langroid is a framework for building large-language-model-powered applications. Prior to version 0.53.4, a LLM application leveraging `XMLToolMessage` class may be exposed to untrusted XML input that could result in DoS and/or exposing local files with sensitive information. Version 0.53.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45607 | An issue in the component /manage/ of itranswarp v2.19 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45607</link><description>An issue in the component /manage/ of itranswarp v2.19 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45608 | Incorrect access control in the /system/user/findUserList API of Xinguan v0.0.1-SNAPSHOT allows attackers to access sensitive information vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45608</link><description>Incorrect access control in the /system/user/findUserList API of Xinguan v0.0.1-SNAPSHOT allows attackers to access sensitive information via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45609 | Incorrect access control in the doFilter function of kob latest v1.0.0-SNAPSHOT allows attackers to access sensitive information via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45609</link><description>Incorrect access control in the doFilter function of kob latest v1.0.0-SNAPSHOT allows attackers to access sensitive information via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45610 | Incorrect access control in the component /scheduleLog/info/1 of PassJava-Platform v3.0.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45610</link><description>Incorrect access control in the component /scheduleLog/info/1 of PassJava-Platform v3.0.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45611 | Incorrect access control in the /user/edit/ component of hope-boot v1.0.0 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted GET reques...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45611</link><description>Incorrect access control in the /user/edit/ component of hope-boot v1.0.0 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45612 | Incorrect access control in xmall v1.1 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted GET request to /index.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45612</link><description>Incorrect access control in xmall v1.1 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted GET request to /index.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45613 | Incorrect access control in the component /user/list of Shiro-Action v0.6 allows attackers to access sensitive information via a crafted pay...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45613</link><description>Incorrect access control in the component /user/list of Shiro-Action v0.6 allows attackers to access sensitive information via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45614 | Incorrect access control in the component /api/user/manager of One v1.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information via a crafted paylo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45614</link><description>Incorrect access control in the component /api/user/manager of One v1.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45615 | Incorrect access control in the /admin/ API of yaoqishan v0.0.1-SNAPSHOT allows attackers to gain access to Admin rights via a crafted reque...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45615</link><description>Incorrect access control in the /admin/ API of yaoqishan v0.0.1-SNAPSHOT allows attackers to gain access to Admin rights via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45616 | Incorrect access control in the /admin/** API of brcc v1.2.0 allows attackers to gain access to Admin rights via a crafted request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45616</link><description>Incorrect access control in the /admin/** API of brcc v1.2.0 allows attackers to gain access to Admin rights via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45617 | Incorrect access control in the component /user/list of production_ssm v0.0.1-SNAPSHOT allows attackers to access sensitive information via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45617</link><description>Incorrect access control in the component /user/list of production_ssm v0.0.1-SNAPSHOT allows attackers to access sensitive information via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45618 | Incorrect access control in the component /admin/sys/datasource/ajaxList of jeeweb-mybatis-springboot v0.0.1.RELEASE allows attackers to acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45618</link><description>Incorrect access control in the component /admin/sys/datasource/ajaxList of jeeweb-mybatis-springboot v0.0.1.RELEASE allows attackers to access sensitive information via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42213 | HCL BigFix Compliance is affected by inclusion of temporary files left in the production environment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42213</link><description>HCL BigFix Compliance is affected by inclusion of temporary files left in the production environment.  An attacker might gain access to these files by indexing or retrieved via predictable URLs or misconfigured permissions, leading to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29573 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Mezzanine CMS 6.0.0 in the "View Entries" feature within the Forms module.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29573</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Mezzanine CMS 6.0.0 in the "View Entries" feature within the Forms module.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46719 | Open WebUI vulnerable to stored XSS via unescaped markdown token in MarkdownTokens.svelte leading to full account takeover and RCE via functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46719</link><description>Open WebUI is a self-hosted artificial intelligence platform designed to operate entirely offline. Prior to version 0.6.6, a vulnerability in the way certain html tags in chat messages are rendered allows attackers to inject JavaScript code into a chat transcript. The JavaScript code will be executed in the user's browser every time that chat transcript is opened, allowing attackers to retrieve the user's access token and gain full control over their account. Chat transcripts can be shared with other users in the same server, or with the whole open-webui community if "Enable Community Sharing" is enabled in the admin panel. If this exploit is used against an admin user, it is possible to achieve Remote Code Execution on the server where the open-webui backend is hosted. This can be done by creating a new function which contains malicious python code. This vulnerability also affects chat transcripts uploaded to `https://openwebui.com/c//`, allowing for wormable stored XSS in https[:]//openwebui[.]com. Version 0.6.6 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46720 | Keystone has an unintended `isFilterable` bypass that can be used as an oracle to match hidden fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46720</link><description>Keystone is a content management system for Node.js. Prior to version 6.5.0, `{field}.isFilterable` access control can be bypassed in `update` and `delete` mutations by adding additional unique filters. These filters can be used as an oracle to probe the existence or value of otherwise unreadable fields. Specifically, when a mutation includes a `where` clause with multiple unique filters (e.g. `id` and `email`), Keystone will attempt to match records even if filtering by the latter fields would normally be rejected by `field.isFilterable` or `list.defaultIsFilterable`. This can allow malicious actors to infer the presence of a particular field value when a filter is successful in returning a result. This affects any project relying on the default or dynamic `isFilterable` behavior (at the list or field level) to prevent external users from using the filtering of fields as a discovery mechanism. While this access control is respected during `findMany` operations, it was not completely enforced during `update` and `delete` mutations when accepting more than one unique `where` values in filters. This has no impact on projects using `isFilterable: false` or `defaultIsFilterable: false` for sensitive fields, or for those who have otherwise omitted filtering by these fields from their GraphQL schema. This issue has been patched in `@keystone-6/core` version 6.5.0. To mitigate this issue in older versions where patching is not a viable pathway, set `isFilterable: false` statically for relevant fields to prevent filtering by them earlier in the access control pipeline (that is, don't use functions); set `{field}.graphql.omit.read: true` for relevant fields, which implicitly removes filtering by these fields from the GraphQL schema; and/or deny `update` and `delete` operations for the relevant lists completely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42212 | HCL BigFix Compliance is affected by an improper or missing SameSite attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42212</link><description>HCL BigFix Compliance is affected by an improper or missing SameSite attribute.  This can lead to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attacks, where a malicious site could trick a user's browser into making unintended requests using authenticated sessions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46571 | Open WebUI vulnerable to limited stored XSS vila uploaded html file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46571</link><description>Open WebUI is a self-hosted artificial intelligence platform designed to operate entirely offline. Prior to version 0.6.6, low privileged users can upload HTML files which contain JavaScript code via the `/api/v1/files/` backend endpoint. This endpoint returns a file id, which can be used to open the file in the browser and trigger the JavaScript code in the user's browser. Under the default settings, files uploaded by low-privileged users can only be viewed by admins or themselves, limiting the impact of this vulnerability. A link to such a file can be sent to an admin, and if clicked, will give the low-privileged user complete control over the admin's account, ultimately enabling RCE via functions. Version 0.6.6 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46340 | Misskey CSS Style Injection Vulnerability In `MkUrlPreview`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46340</link><description>Misskey is an open source, federated social media platform. Starting in version 12.0.0 and prior to version 2025.4.1, due to an oversight in the validation performed in `UrlPreviewService` and `MkUrlPreview`, it is possible for an attacker to inject arbitrary CSS into the `MkUrlPreview` component. `UrlPreviewService.wrap` falls back to returning the original URL if it's using a protocol that is likely to not be understood by Misskey, IE something other than `http` or `https`. This both can de-anonymize users and_allow further attacks in the client. Additionally, `MkUrlPreview` doesn't escape CSS when applying a `background-image` property, allowing an attacker to craft a URL that applies arbitrary styles to the preview element. Theoretically, an attacker can craft a CSS injection payload to create a fake error message that can deceive the user into giving away their credentials or similar sensitive information. Version 2025.4.1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46553 | @misskey-dev/summaly Redirect Filter Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46553</link><description>@misskey-dev/summaly is a tool for getting a summary of a web page. Starting in version 3.0.1 and prior to version 5.2.1, a logic error in the main `summaly` function causes the `allowRedirects` option to never be passed to any plugins, and as a result, isn't enforced. Misskey will follow redirects, despite explicitly requesting not to. Version 5.2.1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46559 | Misskey Directory Traversal Vulnerability in AiScript via `Mk:api`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46559</link><description>Misskey is an open source, federated social media platform. Starting in version 12.31.0 and prior to version 2025.4.1, missing validation in `Mk:api` allows malicious AiScript code to access additional endpoints that it isn't designed to have access to. The missing validation allows malicious AiScript code to prefix a URL with `../` to step out of the `/api` directory, thereby being able to make requests to other endpoints, such as `/files`, `/url`, and `/proxy`. Version 2025.4.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4283 | SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System Login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4283</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /classes/Login.php?f=login. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43849 | GHSL-2025-019_Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43849</link><description>Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI is a voice changing framework based on VITS. Versions 2.2.231006 and prior are vulnerable to unsafe deserialization. The ckpt_a and cpkt_b variables take user input (e.g. a path to a model) and pass it to the merge function in process_ckpt.py, which uses them to load the models on those paths with torch.load, which can lead to unsafe deserialization and remote code execution. As of time of publication, no known patches exist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43850 | GHSL-2025-020_Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43850</link><description>Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI is a voice changing framework based on VITS. Versions 2.2.231006 and prior are vulnerable to unsafe deserialization. The ckpt_dir variable takes user input (e.g. a path to a model) and passes it to the change_info function in export.py, which uses it to load the model on that path with torch.load, which can lead to unsafe deserialization and remote code execution. As of time of publication, no known patches exist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43851 | GHSL-2025-021_Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43851</link><description>Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI is a voice changing framework based on VITS. Versions 2.2.231006 and prior are vulnerable to unsafe deserialization. The model_choose variable takes user input (e.g. a path to a model) and passes it to the uvr function in vr.py. In uvr , a new instance of AudioPre class is created with the model_path attribute containing the aformentioned user input. In the AudioPre class, the user input, is used to load the model on that path with torch.load, which can lead to unsafe deserialization and remote code execution. As of time of publication, no known patches exist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43852 | GHSL-2025-022_Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43852</link><description>Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI is a voice changing framework based on VITS. Versions 2.2.231006 and prior are vulnerable to unsafe deserialization. The model_choose variable takes user input (e.g. a path to a model) and passes it to the uvr function in vr.py. In uvr , if model_name contains the string "DeEcho", a new instance of AudioPreDeEcho class is created with the model_path attribute containing the aforementioned user input. In the AudioPreDeEcho class, the user input is used to load the model on that path with torch.load, which can lead to unsafe deserialization and remote code execution. As of time of publication, no known patches exist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46335 | Mobile Security Framework (MobSF) Allows Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via malicious SVG Icon Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46335</link><description>Mobile Security Framework (MobSF) is a security research platform for mobile applications in Android, iOS and Windows Mobile. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in MobSF versions up to and including 4.3.2. The vulnerability arises from improper sanitization of user-supplied SVG files during the Android APK analysis workflow. Version 4.3.3 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4279 | External image replace &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4279</link><description>The External image replace plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'external_image_replace_get_posts::replace_post' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level and above permissions, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4318 | Input validation issue in AWS Amplify Studio UI component properties</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4318</link><description>The AWS Amplify Studio UI component property expressions in the aws-amplify/amplify-codegen-ui package lack input validation. This could potentially allow an authenticated user who has access to create or modify components to run arbitrary JavaScript code during the component rendering and build process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4050 | Out of bounds memory access in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 136.0.7103.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4050</link><description>Out of bounds memory access in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 136.0.7103.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4051 | Insufficient data validation in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 136.0.7103.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4051</link><description>Insufficient data validation in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 136.0.7103.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to bypass discretionary access control via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4052 | Inappropriate implementation in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 136.0.7103.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4052</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 136.0.7103.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to bypass discretionary access control via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4096 | Heap buffer overflow in HTML in Google Chrome prior to 136.0.7103.59 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4096</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in HTML in Google Chrome prior to 136.0.7103.59 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4282 | SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System Users.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4282</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /classes/Users.php?f=save. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43848 | GHSL-2025-018_Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43848</link><description>Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI is a voice changing framework based on VITS. Versions 2.2.231006 and prior are vulnerable to unsafe deserialization. The ckpt_path0 variable takes user input (e.g. a path to a model) and passes it to the change_info function in process_ckpt.py, which uses it to load the model on that path with torch.load, which can lead to unsafe deserialization and remote code execution. As of time of publication, no known patches exist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45237 | Incorrect access control in the component /config/download of DBSyncer v2.0.6 allows attackers to access the JSON file containing sensitive ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45237</link><description>Incorrect access control in the component /config/download of DBSyncer v2.0.6 allows attackers to access the JSON file containing sensitive account information, including the encrypted password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45238 | foxcms v1.2.5 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability via the delRestoreSerie method.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45238</link><description>foxcms v1.2.5 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability via the delRestoreSerie method.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45239 | An issue in the restores method (DataBackup.php) of foxcms v2.0.6 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45239</link><description>An issue in the restores method (DataBackup.php) of foxcms v2.0.6 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43847 | GHSL-2025-017_Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43847</link><description>Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI is a voice changing framework based on VITS. Versions 2.2.231006 and prior are vulnerable to unsafe deserialization. The ckpt_path2 variable takes user input (e.g. a path to a model) and passes it to the extract_small_model function in process_ckpt.py, which uses it to load the model on that path with torch.load, which can lead to unsafe deserialization and remote code execution. As of time of publication, no known patches exist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45236 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Edit Profile feature of DBSyncer v2.0.6 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45236</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Edit Profile feature of DBSyncer v2.0.6 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the Nickname parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43844 | GHSL-2025-014_Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43844</link><description>Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI is a voice changing framework based on VITS. Versions 2.2.231006 and prior are vulnerable to command injection. The variables exp_dir1, among others, take user input and pass it to the click_train function, which concatenates them into a command that is run on the server. This can lead to arbitrary command execution. As of time of publication, no known patches exist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43845 | GHSL-2025-015_Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43845</link><description>Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI is a voice changing framework based on VITS. Versions 2.2.231006 and prior are vulnerable to code injection. The ckpt_path2 variable takes user input (e.g. a path to a model) and passes it to change_info_ function, which opens and reads the file on the given path (except it changes the final on the path to train.log), and passes the contents of the file to eval, which can lead to remote code execution. As of time of publication, no known patches exist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43846 | GHSL-2025-016_Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43846</link><description>Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI is a voice changing framework based on VITS. Versions 2.2.231006 and prior are vulnerable to unsafe deserialization. The ckpt_path1 variable takes user input (e.g. a path to a model) and passes it to the show_info function in process_ckpt.py, which uses it to load the model on that path with torch.load, which can lead to unsafe deserialization and remote code execution. As of time of publication, no known patches exist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51991 | October CMS Allows Unprotected SVG Rename in Media Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51991</link><description>October is a Content Management System (CMS) and web platform. A vulnerability in versions prior to 3.7.5 affects authenticated administrators with sites that have the `media.clean_vectors` configuration enabled. This configuration will sanitize SVG files uploaded using the media manager. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to bypass this protection by uploading it with a permitted extension (for example, .jpg or .png) and later modifying it to the .svg extension. This vulnerability assumes a trusted user will attack another trusted user and cannot be actively exploited without access to the administration panel and interaction from the other user. This issue has been patched in v3.7.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:29:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24977 | OpenCTI has remote code execution and sensitive secrets exposed through web hook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24977</link><description>OpenCTI is an open cyber threat intelligence (CTI) platform. Prior to version 6.4.11 any user with the capability `manage customizations` can execute commands on the underlying infrastructure where OpenCTI is hosted and can access internal server side secrets by misusing the web-hooks. Since the malicious user gets a root shell inside a container this opens up the the infrastructure environment for further attacks and exposures. Version 6.4.11 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43842 | GHSL-2025-012_Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43842</link><description>Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI is a voice changing framework based on VITS. Versions 2.2.231006 and prior are vulnerable to command injection. The variables exp_dir1, np7, trainset_dir4 and sr2 take user input and pass it to the preprocess_dataset function, which concatenates them into a command that is run on the server. This can lead to arbitrary command execution. As of time of publication, no known patches exist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43843 | GHSL-2025-013_Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43843</link><description>Retrieval-based-Voice-Conversion-WebUI is a voice changing framework based on VITS. Versions 2.2.231006 and prior are vulnerable to command injection. The variables exp_dir1, np7 and f0method8 take user input and pass it into the extract_f0_feature function, which concatenates them into a command that is run on the server. This can lead to arbitrary command execution. As of time of publication, no known patches exist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0217 | Privileged Remote Access Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0217</link><description>BeyondTrust Privileged Remote Access (PRA) versions prior to 25.1 are vulnerable to a local authentication bypass. A local authenticated attacker can view the connection details of a ShellJump session that was initiated with external tools, allowing unauthorized access to connected sessions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1992 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1992</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes DB2 Connect Server) 11.5.0 through 11.5.9 and 12.1.0 through 12.1.1 could allow an authenticated user, under non default configurations, to cause a denial of service due to insufficient release of allocated memory after usage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57229 | NETGEAR RAX5 (AX1600 WiFi Router) V1.0.2.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the devname parameter in the res...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57229</link><description>NETGEAR RAX5 (AX1600 WiFi Router) V1.0.2.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the devname parameter in the reset_wifi function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57231 | NETGEAR RAX5 (AX1600 WiFi Router) V1.0.2.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the apcl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57231</link><description>NETGEAR RAX5 (AX1600 WiFi Router) V1.0.2.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the apcli_do_enr_pbc_wps function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57232 | NETGEAR RAX5 (AX1600 WiFi Router) V1.0.2.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the apcl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57232</link><description>NETGEAR RAX5 (AX1600 WiFi Router) V1.0.2.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the apcli_wps_gen_pincode function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11615 | Envolve Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Unauthenticated Language File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11615</link><description>The Envolve Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 via the 'zetra_deleteLanguageFile' and 'zetra_deleteFontsFile' functions. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a file or its path prior to deleting it. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete language files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57230 | NETGEAR RAX5 (AX1600 WiFi Router) V1.0.2.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the apcl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57230</link><description>NETGEAR RAX5 (AX1600 WiFi Router) V1.0.2.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the apcli_do_enr_pin_wps function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57233 | NETGEAR RAX5 (AX1600 WiFi Router) v1.0.2.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the iface parameter in the vif_d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57233</link><description>NETGEAR RAX5 (AX1600 WiFi Router) v1.0.2.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the iface parameter in the vif_disable function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57234 | NETGEAR RAX5 (AX1600 WiFi Router) V1.0.2.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the apcl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57234</link><description>NETGEAR RAX5 (AX1600 WiFi Router) V1.0.2.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the apcli_cancel_wps function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57235 | NETGEAR RAX5 (AX1600 WiFi Router) V1.0.2.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the iface parameter in the vif_e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57235</link><description>NETGEAR RAX5 (AX1600 WiFi Router) V1.0.2.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the iface parameter in the vif_enable function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43915 | In Buoyant Edge releases before edge-25.2.1 and Enterprise for Linkerd releases 2.16.* before 2.16.5, 2.17.* before 2.17.2, and 2.18.* befor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43915</link><description>In Buoyant Edge releases before edge-25.2.1 and Enterprise for Linkerd releases 2.16.* before 2.16.5, 2.17.* before 2.17.2, and 2.18.* before 2.18.0, resource exhaustion can occur for Linkerd proxy metrics.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45240 | foxcms v1.2.5 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the executeCommand method in DataBackup.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45240</link><description>foxcms v1.2.5 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the executeCommand method in DataBackup.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45242 | Rhymix v2.1.22 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability via the procFileAdminEditImage method in /file/file.admin....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45242</link><description>Rhymix v2.1.22 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability via the procFileAdminEditImage method in /file/file.admin.controller.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26241 | A SQL injection vulnerability in the "Search" functionality of "tickets.php" page in osTicket &lt;=1.17.5 allows authenticated attackers to exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26241</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in the "Search" functionality of "tickets.php" page in osTicket &lt;=1.17.5 allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the "keywords" and "topic_id" URL parameters combination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28062 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability was discovered in ERPNEXT 14.82.1 and 14.74.3. The vulnerability allows an attacker to per...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28062</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability was discovered in ERPNEXT 14.82.1 and 14.74.3. The vulnerability allows an attacker to perform unauthorized actions such as user deletion, password resets, and privilege escalation due to missing CSRF protections.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4281 | Shenzhen Sixun Software Sixun Shanghui Group Business Management System LoadData information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4281</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Shenzhen Sixun Software Sixun Shanghui Group Business Management System 7. This affects an unknown part of the file /api/GylOperator/LoadData. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27920 | Output Messenger before 2.0.63 was vulnerable to a directory traversal attack through improper file path handling. By using ../ sequences in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27920</link><description>Output Messenger before 2.0.63 was vulnerable to a directory traversal attack through improper file path handling. By using ../ sequences in parameters, attackers could access sensitive files outside the intended directory, potentially leading to configuration leakage or arbitrary file access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27921 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in Output Messenger before 2.0.63, where unsanitized input could be inje...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27921</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in Output Messenger before 2.0.63, where unsanitized input could be injected into the web application’s response. This vulnerability occurs when user-controlled input is reflected back into the browser without proper sanitization or encoding.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:51:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45322 | kashipara Online Service Management Portal V1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in osms/Requester/CheckStatus.php via the checkid parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45322</link><description>kashipara Online Service Management Portal V1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in osms/Requester/CheckStatus.php via the checkid parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:51:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45042 | Tenda AC9 v15.03.05.14 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the Telnet function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45042</link><description>Tenda AC9 v15.03.05.14 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the Telnet function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45320 | A Directory Listing Vulnerability was found in the /osms/Requester/ directory of the Kashipara Online Service Management Portal V1.0.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45320</link><description>A Directory Listing Vulnerability was found in the /osms/Requester/ directory of the Kashipara Online Service Management Portal V1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45321 | kashipara Online Service Management Portal V1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /osms/Requester/Requesterchangepass.php via the parameter:...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45321</link><description>kashipara Online Service Management Portal V1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /osms/Requester/Requesterchangepass.php via the parameter: rPassword.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25504 | An issue in the /usr/local/bin/jncs.sh script of Gefen WebFWC (In AV over IP products) v1.85h, v1.86v, and v1.70 allows attackers with netwo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25504</link><description>An issue in the /usr/local/bin/jncs.sh script of Gefen WebFWC (In AV over IP products) v1.85h, v1.86v, and v1.70 allows attackers with network access to connect to the device over TCP port 4444 without authentication and execute arbitrary commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58098 | bpf: track changes_pkt_data property for global functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58098</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: track changes_pkt_data property for global functions

When processing calls to certain helpers, verifier invalidates all
packet pointers in a current state. For example, consider the
following program:

    __attribute__((__noinline__))
    long skb_pull_data(struct __sk_buff *sk, __u32 len)
    {
        return bpf_skb_pull_data(sk, len);
    }

    SEC("tc")
    int test_invalidate_checks(struct __sk_buff *sk)
    {
        int *p = (void *)(long)sk-&gt;data;
        if ((void *)(p + 1) &gt; (void *)(long)sk-&gt;data_end) return TCX_DROP;
        skb_pull_data(sk, 0);
        *p = 42;
        return TCX_PASS;
    }

After a call to bpf_skb_pull_data() the pointer 'p' can't be used
safely. See function filter.c:bpf_helper_changes_pkt_data() for a list
of such helpers.

At the moment verifier invalidates packet pointers when processing
helper function calls, and does not traverse global sub-programs when
processing calls to global sub-programs. This means that calls to
helpers done from global sub-programs do not invalidate pointers in
the caller state. E.g. the program above is unsafe, but is not
rejected by verifier.

This commit fixes the omission by computing field
bpf_subprog_info-&gt;changes_pkt_data for each sub-program before main
verification pass.
changes_pkt_data should be set if:
- subprogram calls helper for which bpf_helper_changes_pkt_data
  returns true;
- subprogram calls a global function,
  for which bpf_subprog_info-&gt;changes_pkt_data should be set.

The verifier.c:check_cfg() pass is modified to compute this
information. The commit relies on depth first instruction traversal
done by check_cfg() and absence of recursive function calls:
- check_cfg() would eventually visit every call to subprogram S in a
  state when S is fully explored;
- when S is fully explored:
  - every direct helper call within S is explored
    (and thus changes_pkt_data is set if needed);
  - every call to subprogram S1 called by S was visited with S1 fully
    explored (and thus S inherits changes_pkt_data from S1).

The downside of such approach is that dead code elimination is not
taken into account: if a helper call inside global function is dead
because of current configuration, verifier would conservatively assume
that the call occurs for the purpose of the changes_pkt_data
computation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58100 | bpf: check changes_pkt_data property for extension programs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58100</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: check changes_pkt_data property for extension programs

When processing calls to global sub-programs, verifier decides whether
to invalidate all packet pointers in current state depending on the
changes_pkt_data property of the global sub-program.

Because of this, an extension program replacing a global sub-program
must be compatible with changes_pkt_data property of the sub-program
being replaced.

This commit:
- adds changes_pkt_data flag to struct bpf_prog_aux:
  - this flag is set in check_cfg() for main sub-program;
  - in jit_subprogs() for other sub-programs;
- modifies bpf_check_attach_btf_id() to check changes_pkt_data flag;
- moves call to check_attach_btf_id() after the call to check_cfg(),
  because it needs changes_pkt_data flag to be set:

    bpf_check:
      ...                             ...
    - check_attach_btf_id             resolve_pseudo_ldimm64
      resolve_pseudo_ldimm64   --&gt;    bpf_prog_is_offloaded
      bpf_prog_is_offloaded           check_cfg
      check_cfg                     + check_attach_btf_id
      ...                             ...

The following fields are set by check_attach_btf_id():
- env-&gt;ops
- prog-&gt;aux-&gt;attach_btf_trace
- prog-&gt;aux-&gt;attach_func_name
- prog-&gt;aux-&gt;attach_func_proto
- prog-&gt;aux-&gt;dst_trampoline
- prog-&gt;aux-&gt;mod
- prog-&gt;aux-&gt;saved_dst_attach_type
- prog-&gt;aux-&gt;saved_dst_prog_type
- prog-&gt;expected_attach_type

Neither of these fields are used by resolve_pseudo_ldimm64() or
bpf_prog_offload_verifier_prep() (for netronome and netdevsim
drivers), so the reordering is safe.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58237 | bpf: consider that tail calls invalidate packet pointers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58237</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: consider that tail calls invalidate packet pointers

Tail-called programs could execute any of the helpers that invalidate
packet pointers. Hence, conservatively assume that each tail call
invalidates packet pointers.

Making the change in bpf_helper_changes_pkt_data() automatically makes
use of check_cfg() logic that computes 'changes_pkt_data' effect for
global sub-programs, such that the following program could be
rejected:

    int tail_call(struct __sk_buff *sk)
    {
    	bpf_tail_call_static(sk, &amp;amp;jmp_table, 0);
    	return 0;
    }

    SEC("tc")
    int not_safe(struct __sk_buff *sk)
    {
    	int *p = (void *)(long)sk-&gt;data;
    	... make p valid ...
    	tail_call(sk);
    	*p = 42; /* this is unsafe */
    	...
    }

The tc_bpf2bpf.c:subprog_tc() needs change: mark it as a function that
can invalidate packet pointers. Otherwise, it can't be freplaced with
tailcall_freplace.c:entry_freplace() that does a tail call.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4316 | Improper access control in PAM feature in Devolutions Server 2025.1.6.0 and earlier allows a PAM user to self approve their PAM requests eve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4316</link><description>Improper access control in PAM feature in Devolutions Server 2025.1.6.0 and earlier allows a PAM user to self approve their PAM requests even if disallowed by the configured policy via specific user interface actions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45751 | SourceCodester Web Based Pharmacy Product Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in add-admin.php via the Fullnam...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45751</link><description>SourceCodester Web Based Pharmacy Product Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in add-admin.php via the Fullname text field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28168 | Outsystems Multiple File Upload &lt; 3.1.0 is vulnerable to Unrestricted File Upload. The vulnerability is because file extension and size vali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28168</link><description>Outsystems Multiple File Upload &lt; 3.1.0 is vulnerable to Unrestricted File Upload. The vulnerability is because file extension and size validations are enforced solely on the client side. An attacker can intercept the upload request and modify the parameter to bypass extension restrictions and upload arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47268 | ping in iputils through 20240905 allows a denial of service (application error or incorrect data collection) via a crafted ICMP Echo Reply p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47268</link><description>ping in iputils through 20240905 allows a denial of service (application error or incorrect data collection) via a crafted ICMP Echo Reply packet, because of a signed 64-bit integer overflow in timestamp multiplication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2545 | Cryptographic algorithm not recommended in Request Tracker by Best Practical Solutions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2545</link><description>Vulnerability in Best Practical Solutions, LLC's Request Tracker v5.0.7, where the Triple DES (3DES) cryptographic algorithm is used within SMIME code to encrypt S/MIME emails. Triple DES is considered obsolete and insecure due to its susceptibility to birthday attacks, which could compromise the confidentiality of encrypted messages.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 11:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4272 | Mechrevo Control Console GCUService csCAPI.dll uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4272</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Mechrevo Control Console 1.0.2.70. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality in the library C:\Program Files\OEM\MECHREVO Control Center\UniwillService\MyControlCenter\csCAPI.dll of the component GCUService. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. An attack has to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 11:16:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2905 | Unauthenticated XML External Entity (XXE) Vulnerability in WSO2 API Manager Gateway Component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2905</link><description>An XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability exists in the gateway component of WSO2 API Manager due to insufficient validation of XML input in crafted URL paths. User-supplied XML is parsed without appropriate restrictions, enabling external entity resolution.


This vulnerability can be exploited by an unauthenticated remote attacker to read files from the server’s filesystem or perform denial-of-service (DoS) attacks.



  *  
On systems running JDK 7 or early JDK 8, full file contents may be exposed.




  *  
On later versions of JDK 8 and newer, only the first line of a file may be read, due to improvements in XML parser behavior.




  *  
DoS attacks such as "Billion Laughs" payloads can cause service disruption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 09:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4271 | TOTOLINK A720R cstecgi.cgi information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4271</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A720R 4.1.5cu.374. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument topicurl with the input showSyslog leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 08:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4270 | TOTOLINK A720R Config cstecgi.cgi information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4270</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A720R 4.1.5cu.374. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component Config Handler. The manipulation of the argument topicurl with the input getInitCfg/getSysStatusCfg leads to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 07:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4269 | TOTOLINK A720R Log cstecgi.cgi access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4269</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A720R 4.1.5cu.374 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component Log Handler. The manipulation of the argument topicurl with the input clearDiagnosisLog/clearSyslog/clearTracerouteLog leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 07:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4268 | TOTOLINK A720R cstecgi.cgi missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4268</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A720R 4.1.5cu.374 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument topicurl with the input RebootSystem leads to missing authentication. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 06:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39363 | WordPress Custom Login and Registration &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39363</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AlphaEfficiencyTeam Custom Login and Registration allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Custom Login and Registration: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 06:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3583 | Newsletter &amp;lt; 8.7.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3583</link><description>The Newsletter  WordPress plugin before 8.7.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 06:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4267 | SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System Purchase Order Details Page view_po sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4267</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/?page=purchase_order/view_po of the component Purchase Order Details Page. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 06:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4266 | PHPGurukul Notice Board System bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4266</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Notice Board System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /bwdates-reports-details.php?vid=2. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/tomdate leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 05:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4265 | PHPGurukul Emergency Ambulance Hiring Portal contact-us.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4265</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Emergency Ambulance Hiring Portal 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/contact-us.php. The manipulation of the argument mobnum leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 05:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4264 | PHPGurukul Emergency Ambulance Hiring Portal edit-ambulance.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4264</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Emergency Ambulance Hiring Portal 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit-ambulance.php. The manipulation of the argument dconnum leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 04:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4263 | PHPGurukul Online DJ Booking Management System booking-search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4263</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online DJ Booking Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/booking-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 04:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4262 | PHPGurukul Online DJ Booking Management System user-search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4262</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online DJ Booking Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/user-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 03:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4261 | GAIR-NLP factool tool.py run_single code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4261</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GAIR-NLP factool up to 3f3914bc090b644be044b7e0005113c135d8b20f. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function run_single of the file factool/factool/math/tool.py. The manipulation leads to code injection. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 03:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20665 | In devinfo, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing SELinux policy. This could lead to local information disclosure of d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20665</link><description>In devinfo, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing SELinux policy. This could lead to local information disclosure of device identifier with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09555228; Issue ID: MSV-2760.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 03:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20666 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20666</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY00650610; Issue ID: MSV-2933.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 03:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20667 | In Modem, there is a possible information disclosure due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote information disclosure, if a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20667</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible information disclosure due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote information disclosure, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01513293; Issue ID: MSV-2741.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 03:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20668 | In scp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20668</link><description>In scp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09625562; Issue ID: MSV-3027.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 03:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20670 | In Modem, there is a possible permission bypass due to improper certificate validation. This could lead to remote information disclosure, if...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20670</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible permission bypass due to improper certificate validation. This could lead to remote information disclosure, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01334347; Issue ID: MSV-2772.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 03:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20671 | In thermal, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20671</link><description>In thermal, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09698599; Issue ID: MSV-3228.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 03:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4260 | zhangyanbo2007 youkefu TemplateController.java impsave deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4260</link><description>A vulnerability was found in zhangyanbo2007 youkefu up to 4.2.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function impsave of the file m\web\handler\admin\system\TemplateController.java. The manipulation of the argument dataFile leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 03:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4259 | newbee-mall UploadController.java upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4259</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in newbee-mall 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Upload of the file ltd/newbee/mall/controller/common/UploadController.java. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 02:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4258 | zhangyanbo2007 youkefu MediaController.java upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4258</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in zhangyanbo2007 youkefu up to 4.2.0. Affected is the function Upload of the file \youkefu-master\src\main\java\com\ukefu\webim\web\handler\resource\MediaController.java. The manipulation of the argument imgFile leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 02:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4257 | SeaCMS admin_pay.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4257</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SeaCMS 13.2. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin_pay.php. The manipulation of the argument cstatus leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 01:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4256 | SeaCMS admin_paylog.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4256</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SeaCMS 13.2. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin_paylog.php. The manipulation of the argument cstatus leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 01:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4255 | PCMan FTP Server RMD Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4255</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PCMan FTP Server 2.0.7. This affects an unknown part of the component RMD Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 01:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>