<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 03:46:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2015-20111 | miniupnp before 4c90b87, as used in Bitcoin Core before 0.12 and other products, lacks checks for snprintf return values, leading to a buffe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-20111</link><description>miniupnp before 4c90b87, as used in Bitcoin Core before 0.12 and other products, lacks checks for snprintf return values, leading to a buffer overflow and significant data leak, a different vulnerability than CVE-2019-12107. In Bitcoin Core before 0.12, remote code execution was possible in conjunction with CVE-2015-6031 exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 03:46:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25220 | Bitcoin Core before 24.0.1 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (daemon crash) via a flood of low-difficulty header chains (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25220</link><description>Bitcoin Core before 24.0.1 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (daemon crash) via a flood of low-difficulty header chains (aka a "Chain Width Expansion" attack) because a node does not first verify that a presented chain has enough work before committing to store it.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 03:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52912 | Bitcoin Core before 0.21.0 allows a network split that is resultant from an integer overflow (calculating the time offset for newly connecti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52912</link><description>Bitcoin Core before 0.21.0 allows a network split that is resultant from an integer overflow (calculating the time offset for newly connecting peers) and an abs64 logic bug.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 03:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52913 | In Bitcoin Core before 0.21.0, an attacker could prevent a node from seeing a specific unconfirmed transaction, because transaction re-reque...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52913</link><description>In Bitcoin Core before 0.21.0, an attacker could prevent a node from seeing a specific unconfirmed transaction, because transaction re-requests are mishandled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 03:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52914 | In Bitcoin Core before 0.18.0, a node could be stalled for hours when processing the orphans of a crafted unconfirmed transaction.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52914</link><description>In Bitcoin Core before 0.18.0, a node could be stalled for hours when processing the orphans of a crafted unconfirmed transaction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 03:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52915 | Bitcoin Core before 0.20.0 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (memory consumption) via a crafted INV message.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52915</link><description>Bitcoin Core before 0.20.0 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (memory consumption) via a crafted INV message.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 03:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52916 | Bitcoin Core before 0.15.0 allows a denial of service (OOM kill of a daemon process) via a flood of minimum difficulty headers.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52916</link><description>Bitcoin Core before 0.15.0 allows a denial of service (OOM kill of a daemon process) via a flood of minimum difficulty headers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 03:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52917 | Bitcoin Core before 22.0 has a miniupnp infinite loop in which it allocates memory on the basis of random data received over the network, e....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52917</link><description>Bitcoin Core before 22.0 has a miniupnp infinite loop in which it allocates memory on the basis of random data received over the network, e.g., large M-SEARCH replies from a fake UPnP device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 03:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52918 | Bitcoin-Qt in Bitcoin Core before 0.20.0 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (memory consumption and application crash) via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52918</link><description>Bitcoin-Qt in Bitcoin Core before 0.20.0 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (memory consumption and application crash) via a BIP21 r parameter for a URL that has a large file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 03:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52919 | Bitcoin Core before 22.0 has a CAddrMan nIdCount integer overflow and resultant assertion failure (and daemon exit) via a flood of addr mess...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52919</link><description>Bitcoin Core before 22.0 has a CAddrMan nIdCount integer overflow and resultant assertion failure (and daemon exit) via a flood of addr messages.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 03:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52920 | Bitcoin Core before 0.20.0 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (infinite loop) via a malformed GETDATA message.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52920</link><description>Bitcoin Core before 0.20.0 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (infinite loop) via a malformed GETDATA message.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 03:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52921 | In Bitcoin Core before 25.0, a peer can affect the download state of other peers by sending a mutated block.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52921</link><description>In Bitcoin Core before 25.0, a peer can affect the download state of other peers by sending a mutated block.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 03:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52922 | In Bitcoin Core before 25.1, an attacker can cause a node to not download the latest block, because there can be minutes of delay when an an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52922</link><description>In Bitcoin Core before 25.1, an attacker can cause a node to not download the latest block, because there can be minutes of delay when an announcing peer stalls instead of complying with the peer-to-peer protocol specification.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 03:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11306 | Altenergy Power Control Software database improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11306</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Altenergy Power Control Software up to 20241108. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /index.php/display/database/. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other endpoints might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 02:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11305 | Altenergy Power Control Software status_zigbee get_status_zigbee sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11305</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Altenergy Power Control Software up to 20241108. This vulnerability affects the function get_status_zigbee of the file /index.php/display/status_zigbee. The manipulation of the argument date leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 01:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43091 | Gnome-maps: gnome maps is vulnerable to a code injection attack (similar to xss)  via its service.json</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43091</link><description>A flaw was found in GNOME Maps, which is vulnerable to a code injection attack via its service.json configuration file. If the configuration file is malicious, it may execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 12:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0793 | Kube-controller-manager: malformed hpa v1 manifest causes crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0793</link><description>A flaw was found in kube-controller-manager. This issue occurs when the initial application of a HPA config YAML lacking a .spec.behavior.scaleUp block causes a denial of service due to KCM pods going into restart churn.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 10:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-25720 | Samba: check attribute access rights for ldap adds of computers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25720</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Samba where a delegated administrator with permission to create objects in Active Directory can write to all attributes of the newly created object, including security-sensitive attributes, even after the object's creation. This issue occurs because the administrator owns the object due to the lack of an Access Control List (ACL) at the time of creation and later being recognized as the 'creator owner.' The retained significant rights of the delegated administrator may not be well understood, potentially leading to unintended privilege escalation or security risks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 10:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-0657 | Keycloak: impersonation via logout token exchange</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0657</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. This issue occurs due to improperly enforcing token types when validating signatures locally. This could allow an authenticated attacker to exchange a logout token for an access token and possibly gain access to data outside of enforced permissions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 10:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1419 | Debezium: script injection via connector parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1419</link><description>A script injection vulnerability was found in the Debezium database connector, where it does not properly sanitize some parameters. This flaw allows an attacker to send a malicious request to inject a parameter that may allow the viewing of unauthorized data.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 10:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4639 | Undertow: cookie smuggling/spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4639</link><description>A flaw was found in Undertow, which incorrectly parses cookies with certain value-delimiting characters in incoming requests. This issue could allow an attacker to construct a cookie value to exfiltrate HttpOnly cookie values or spoof arbitrary additional cookie values, leading to unauthorized data access or modification. The main threat from this flaw impacts data confidentiality and integrity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 10:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6110 | Openstack: deleting a non existing access rule deletes another existing access rule in it&amp;#x27;s scope</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6110</link><description>A flaw was found in OpenStack. When a user tries to delete a non-existing access rule in it's scope, it deletes other existing access rules which are not associated with any application credentials.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 10:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52876 | Holy Stone Remote ID Module HSRID01, firmware distributed with the Drone Go2 mobile application before 1.1.8, allows unauthenticated "remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52876</link><description>Holy Stone Remote ID Module HSRID01, firmware distributed with the Drone Go2 mobile application before 1.1.8, allows unauthenticated "remote power off" actions (in broadcast mode) via multiple read operations on the ASTM Remote ID (0xFFFA) GATT.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 04:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52871 | In Flagsmith before 2.134.1, it is possible to bypass the ALLOW_REGISTRATION_WITHOUT_INVITE setting.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52871</link><description>In Flagsmith before 2.134.1, it is possible to bypass the ALLOW_REGISTRATION_WITHOUT_INVITE setting.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 03:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52872 | In Flagsmith before 2.134.1, the get_document endpoint is not correctly protected by permissions.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52872</link><description>In Flagsmith before 2.134.1, the get_document endpoint is not correctly protected by permissions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 03:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52867 | guix-daemon in GNU Guix before 5ab3c4c allows privilege escalation because build outputs are accessible by local users before file metadata ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52867</link><description>guix-daemon in GNU Guix before 5ab3c4c allows privilege escalation because build outputs are accessible by local users before file metadata concerns (e.g., for setuid and setgid programs) are properly addressed. The vulnerability can be remediated within the product via certain pull, reconfigure, and restart actions. Both 5ab3c4c and 5582241 are needed to resolve the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 02:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52397 | WordPress Convert Docx2post plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52397</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Davor Zeljkovic Convert Docx2post allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Convert Docx2post: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 22:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52398 | WordPress CDI plugin &amp;lt;= 5.5.3 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52398</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Halyra CDI.This issue affects CDI: from n/a through 5.5.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 22:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52399 | WordPress Writer Helper plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52399</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Clarisse K. Writer Helper allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Writer Helper: from n/a through 3.1.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 22:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52400 | WordPress Gallerio plugin &amp;lt;= 1.01 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52400</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Subhasis Laha Gallerio allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Gallerio: from n/a through 1.01.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 22:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52403 | WordPress User Management plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52403</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in WPExperts User Management allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects User Management: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 21:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52404 | WordPress CF7 Reply Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52404</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Bigfive CF7 Reply Manager.This issue affects CF7 Reply Manager: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 21:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52405 | WordPress B-Banner Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52405</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Bikram Joshi B-Banner Slider allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects B-Banner Slider: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 21:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52406 | WordPress CSV to html plugin &amp;lt;= 3.04 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52406</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Wibergs Web CSV to html allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects CSV to html: from n/a through 3.04.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 21:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52407 | WordPress BasePress Migration Tools plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52407</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in codeSavory BasePress Migration Tools allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects BasePress Migration Tools: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 21:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52408 | WordPress Push Notifications for WordPress by PushAssist plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52408</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Team PushAssist Push Notifications for WordPress by PushAssist allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Push Notifications for WordPress by PushAssist: from n/a through 3.0.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 21:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52409 | WordPress AJAX Random Posts plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3.3 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52409</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Phan An AJAX Random Posts allows Object Injection.This issue affects AJAX Random Posts: from n/a through 0.3.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 21:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52410 | WordPress Referrer Detector plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.1.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52410</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Phoenixheart Referrer Detector allows Object Injection.This issue affects Referrer Detector: from n/a through 4.2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 21:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52411 | WordPress Advanced Personalization plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52411</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Flowcraft UX Design Studio Advanced Personalization allows Object Injection.This issue affects Advanced Personalization: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 21:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52412 | WordPress Xin theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.8.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52412</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Stephen Cui Xin allows Object Injection.This issue affects Xin: from n/a through 1.0.8.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 21:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52413 | WordPress Airin Blog theme &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52413</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in DMC Airin Blog allows Object Injection.This issue affects Airin Blog: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 21:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52414 | WordPress WDES Responsive Mobile Menu plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.18 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52414</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Anthony Carbon WDES Responsive Mobile Menu allows Object Injection.This issue affects WDES Responsive Mobile Menu: from n/a through 5.3.18.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 21:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52386 | WordPress Classified Listing plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.15.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52386</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Business Directory Team by RadiusTheme Classified Listing classified-listing allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Classified Listing: from n/a through 3.1.15.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 21:23:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52415 | WordPress SK WP Settings Backup plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - CSRF to PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52415</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Skpstorm SK WP Settings Backup allows Object Injection.This issue affects SK WP Settings Backup: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 21:23:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52416 | WordPress Debug Tool plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Remote Code Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52416</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Eugen Bobrowski Debug Tool allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Debug Tool: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 21:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10592 | Mapster WP Maps &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10592</link><description>The Mapster WP Maps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the popup class parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 09:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11094 | 404 Solution &amp;lt;= 2.35.17 - Missing Authentication to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11094</link><description>The 404 Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.35.17 via the export feature. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data such as redirects including GET parameters which may reveal sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 09:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9887 | Login using WordPress Users ( WP as SAML IDP ) &amp;lt;= 1.15.6 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9887</link><description>The Login using WordPress Users ( WP as SAML IDP ) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.15.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 09:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10645 | Blogger 301 Redirect &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via br</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10645</link><description>The Blogger 301 Redirect plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to blind time-based SQL Injection via the ‘br’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10614 | Customer Reviews for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.61.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Import Cancellation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10614</link><description>The Customer Reviews for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the cancel_import() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.61.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to cancel and import or check on the status.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 05:47:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10728 | PostX &amp;lt;= 4.1.16 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary Plugin Installation/Activation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10728</link><description>The Post Grid Gutenberg Blocks and WordPress Blog Plugin – PostX plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin installation/activation due to a missing capability check on the 'install_required_plugin_callback' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.16. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to install and activate arbitrary plugins which can be leveraged to achieve remote code execution if another vulnerable plugin is installed and activated.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 04:35:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8856 | Backup and Staging by WP Time Capsule &amp;lt;= 1.22.21 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8856</link><description>The Backup and Staging by WP Time Capsule plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the the UploadHandler.php file and no direct file access prevention in all versions up to, and including, 1.22.21. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 04:35:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10533 | WP Chat App &amp;lt;= 3.6.8 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Filebird Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10533</link><description>The WP Chat App plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin installation due to a missing capability check on the ajax_install_plugin() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to install the filebird plugin.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10015 | ConvertCalculator for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via id and type Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10015</link><description>The ConvertCalculator for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' and 'type' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10017 | PJW Mime Config &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10017</link><description>The PJW Mime Config plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10147 | Steel &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via btn Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10147</link><description>The Steel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's btn shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10262 | Drop Shadow Boxes &amp;lt;= 1.7.14 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10262</link><description>The The Drop Shadow Boxes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.14. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10875 | Gallery Manager &amp;lt;= 1.6.58 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10875</link><description>The Gallery Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of remove_Query_Arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.58. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10883 | SimpleForm – Contact form made simple &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10883</link><description>The SimpleForm – Contact form made simple plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10884 | SimpleForm Contact Form Submissions &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10884</link><description>The SimpleForm Contact Form Submissions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11085 | WP Log Viewer &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11085</link><description>The WP Log Viewer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized use of functionality due to a missing capability check on several AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to access logs, update plugin-related user settings and general plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11092 | SVGPlus &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11092</link><description>The SVGPlus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via REST API SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11118 | 404 Error Monitor &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update via updatePluginSettings Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11118</link><description>The 404 Error Monitor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the updatePluginSettings() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make changes to plugin settings and clear up all the error logs via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6628 | EleForms – All In One Form Integration including DB for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.9.9.9 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6628</link><description>The EleForms – All In One Form Integration including DB for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.9.9. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation when deleting form submissions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete form submissions via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8873 | PeproDev WooCommerce Receipt Uploader &amp;lt;= 2.6.9 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8873</link><description>The PeproDev WooCommerce Receipt Uploader plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9192 | WP Video Robot &amp;lt;= 1.20.0 -  Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via User Meta Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9192</link><description>The WordPress Video Robot - The Ultimate Video Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation due to insufficient validation on user meta that can be updated in the wpvr_rate_request_result() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.20.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update their user meta on a WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update their capabilities to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9386 | Exclusive Divi – Divi Preloader, Modules for Divi &amp;amp; Extra Theme &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9386</link><description>The Exclusive Divi – Divi Preloader, Modules for Divi &amp; Extra Theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9615 | BulkPress &amp;lt;= 0.3.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9615</link><description>The BulkPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 0.3.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9839 | Uix Slideshow &amp;lt;= 1.6.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9839</link><description>The The Uix Slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.5. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9849 | 3D FlipBook, PDF Viewer, PDF Embedder – Real 3D FlipBook WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9849</link><description>The 3D FlipBook, PDF Viewer, PDF Embedder – Real 3D FlipBook WordPress Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'r3dfb_save_thumbnail_callback' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9850 | SVG Case Study &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9850</link><description>The SVG Case Study plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9935 | PDF Generator Addon for Elementor Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9935</link><description>The PDF Generator Addon for Elementor Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.5 via the rtw_pgaepb_dwnld_pdf() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9938 | Bounce Handler MailPoet 3 &amp;lt;= 1.3.21 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9938</link><description>The Bounce Handler MailPoet 3 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10786 | Simple Local Avatars &amp;lt;= 2.7.11 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) User Cache Clearing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10786</link><description>The Simple Local Avatars plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of datadue to a missing capability check on the sla_clear_user_cache function in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.11. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to clear user caches.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 02:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10795 | Popularis Extra &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10795</link><description>The Popularis Extra plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.7 via the 'elementor-template' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private or draft posts created via Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 02:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10861 | Popup Box – Create Countdown, Coupon, Video, Contact Form Popups &amp;lt;= 4.9.7 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Limited Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10861</link><description>The Popup Box – Create Countdown, Coupon, Video, Contact Form Popups plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the deactivate_plugin_option() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the 'ays_pb_upgrade_plugin' option with arbitrary data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 02:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>