<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 17:40:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-3979 | dazhouda lecms Password Change index.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3979</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in dazhouda lecms 3.0.3. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php?my-password-ajax-1 of the component Password Change Handler. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 17:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3978 | dazhouda lecms user_set.htm information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3978</link><description>A vulnerability was found in dazhouda lecms 3.0.3. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/view/default/user_set.htm. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3977 | iteachyou Dreamer CMS Attachment download improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3977</link><description>A vulnerability was found in iteachyou Dreamer CMS up to 4.1.3. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/attachment/download of the component Attachment Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 16:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46657 | Karaz Karazal through 2025-04-14 allows reflected XSS via the lang parameter to the default URI.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46657</link><description>Karaz Karazal through 2025-04-14 allows reflected XSS via the lang parameter to the default URI.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3976 | PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System new-user-testing.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3976</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /new-user-testing.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 16:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3975 | ScriptAndTools eCommerce-website-in-PHP subscriber-csv.php information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3975</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ScriptAndTools eCommerce-website-in-PHP 3.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/subscriber-csv.php. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 15:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3974 | PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System edit-phlebotomist.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3974</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /edit-phlebotomist.php?pid=11. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 15:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3973 | PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System check_availability.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3973</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /check_availability.php. The manipulation of the argument mobnumber leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 14:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3972 | PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System bwdates-report-result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3972</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /bwdates-report-result.php. The manipulation of the argument todate leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 14:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3971 | PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System add-phlebotomist.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3971</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /add-phlebotomist.php. The manipulation of the argument empid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 13:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3970 | baseweb JSite save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3970</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in baseweb JSite up to 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /sys/office/save. The manipulation of the argument Remarks leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 13:02:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3969 | codeprojects News Publishing Site Dashboard Edit Category Page edit-category.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3969</link><description>A vulnerability was found in codeprojects News Publishing Site Dashboard 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /edit-category.php of the component Edit Category Page. The manipulation of the argument category_image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 12:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3968 | codeprojects News Publishing Site Dashboard api.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3968</link><description>A vulnerability was found in codeprojects News Publishing Site Dashboard 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api.php. The manipulation of the argument cat_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 11:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3886 | CatoNetworks CatoClient up to 5.8 PrivilegedHelperTool Race Condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3886</link><description>An issue in CatoNetworks CatoClient before v.5.8.0 allows attackers to escalate privileges and achieve a race condition (TOCTOU) via the PrivilegedHelperTool component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 10:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3967 | itwanger paicoding Article post improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3967</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itwanger paicoding 1.0.3. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /article/api/post of the component Article Handler. The manipulation of the argument articleId leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 10:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3966 | itwanger paicoding Browsing History home information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3966</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itwanger paicoding 1.0.3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/home?userId=1&amp;amp;homeSelectType=read of the component Browsing History Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 10:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3965 | itwanger paicoding post cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3965</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itwanger paicoding 1.0.3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /article/app/post. The manipulation of the argument content leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 09:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3964 | withstars Books-Management-System Article del cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3964</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in withstars Books-Management-System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/article/del of the component Article Handler. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 09:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52887 | Self-XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52887</link><description>Authenticated end-user may set a specially crafted SNX bookmark that can make their browser run a script while accessing their own bookmark list.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52888 | Stored-XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52888</link><description>For an authenticated end-user the portal may run a script while attempting to display a directory or some file's properties.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3963 | withstars Books-Management-System Background Interface list authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3963</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in withstars Books-Management-System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/article/list of the component Background Interface. The manipulation leads to missing authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3962 | withstars Books-Management-System Comment add cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3962</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in withstars Books-Management-System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/comment/add of the component Comment Handler. The manipulation of the argument content leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:13:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3961 | withstars Books-Management-System do cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3961</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in withstars Books-Management-System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/article/add/do. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 06:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3960 | withstars Books-Management-System Background Interface allreaders.html authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3960</link><description>A vulnerability was found in withstars Books-Management-System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /allreaders.html of the component Background Interface. The manipulation leads to missing authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 06:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3959 | withstars Books-Management-System reader_delete.html cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3959</link><description>A vulnerability was found in withstars Books-Management-System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /reader_delete.html. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 04:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3958 | withstars Books-Management-System Book Edit Page book_edit_do.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3958</link><description>A vulnerability was found in withstars Books-Management-System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /book_edit_do.html of the component Book Edit Page. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 04:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3957 | opplus springboot-admin SysLogDao.xml sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3957</link><description>A vulnerability was found in opplus springboot-admin 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file \src\main\resources\mapper\sys\SysLogDao.xml. The manipulation of the argument order leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 03:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3956 | 201206030 novel-cloud BookInfoMapper.xml RestResp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3956</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 201206030 novel-cloud 1.4.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function RestResp of the file novel-cloud-master/novel-book/novel-book-service/src/main/resources/mapper/BookInfoMapper.xml. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 03:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46580 | ZTE GoldenDB Database product has a code-related vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46580</link><description>There is a code-related vulnerability in the GoldenDB database product. Attackers can access system tables to disrupt the normal operation of business SQL.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:49:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46574 | ZTE GoldenDB Database product has an input validation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46574</link><description>There is an information disclosure vulnerability in the GoldenDB database product. Attackers can exploit error messages to obtain the system's sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46575 | ZTE GoldenDB Database product has an information disclosure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46575</link><description>There is an information disclosure vulnerability in the GoldenDB database product. Attackers can exploit error messages to obtain the system's sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46576 | ZTE GoldenDB Database product has a privilege escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46576</link><description>There is a Permission Management and Access Control vulnerability in the GoldenDB database product. Attackers can manipulate requests to bypass privilege restrictions and delete content.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46577 | ZTE GoldenDB Database product has an SQL injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46577</link><description>There is a SQL injection vulnerability in the GoldenDB database product. Attackers can inject commands to extract database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46578 | ZTE GoldenDB Database product has SQL injection vulnerabilities in multiple interfaces</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46578</link><description>There are SQL injection vulnerabilities in multiple interfaces of the GoldenDB database product. Attackers can exploit these interfaces to inject commands and extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46579 | ZTE GoldenDB Database product has a DDE injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46579</link><description>There is a DDE injection vulnerability in the GoldenDB database product. Attackers can inject DDE expressions through the interface, and when users download and open the affected file, the DDE commands can be executed.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3955 | codeprojects Patient Record Management System edit_rpatient.php.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3955</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in codeprojects Patient Record Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /edit_rpatient.php.php. The manipulation of the argument id/lastname leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:18:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46672 | NASA CryptoLib before 1.3.2 does not check the OTAR crypto function returned status, potentially leading to spacecraft hijacking.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46672</link><description>NASA CryptoLib before 1.3.2 does not check the OTAR crypto function returned status, potentially leading to spacecraft hijacking.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:18:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46673 | NASA CryptoLib before 1.3.2 does not check whether the SA is in an operational state before use, possibly leading to a bypass of the Space D...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46673</link><description>NASA CryptoLib before 1.3.2 does not check whether the SA is in an operational state before use, possibly leading to a bypass of the Space Data Link Security protocol (SDLS).</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46674 | NASA CryptoLib before 1.3.2 uses Extended Procedures that are a Work in Progress (not intended for use during flight), potentially leading t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46674</link><description>NASA CryptoLib before 1.3.2 uses Extended Procedures that are a Work in Progress (not intended for use during flight), potentially leading to a keystream oracle.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46675 | In NASA CryptoLib before 1.3.2, the key state is not checked before use, potentially leading to spacecraft hijacking.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46675</link><description>In NASA CryptoLib before 1.3.2, the key state is not checked before use, potentially leading to spacecraft hijacking.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3954 | ChurchCRM Referer server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3954</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in ChurchCRM 5.16.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Referer Handler. The manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 21:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46656 | python-markdownify (aka markdownify) before 0.14.1 allows large headline prefixes such as &lt;h9999999&gt; in addition to &lt;h1&gt; through &lt;h6&gt;. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46656</link><description>python-markdownify (aka markdownify) before 0.14.1 allows large headline prefixes such as  in addition to &lt;h1&gt; through &lt;h6&gt;. This causes memory consumption.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 21:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46653 | Formidable (aka node-formidable) 2.1.0 through 3.x before 3.5.3 relies on hexoid to prevent guessing of filenames for untrusted executable c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46653</link><description>Formidable (aka node-formidable) 2.1.0 through 3.x before 3.5.3 relies on hexoid to prevent guessing of filenames for untrusted executable content; however, hexoid is documented as not "cryptographically secure." (Also, there is a scenario in which only the last two characters of a hexoid string need to be guessed, but this is not often relevant.) NOTE: this does not imply that, in a typical use case, attackers will be able to exploit any hexoid behavior to upload and execute their own content.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 20:46:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46654 | CodiMD through 2.2.0 has a CSP-based protection mechanism against XSS through uploaded JavaScript content, but it can be bypassed by uploadi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46654</link><description>CodiMD through 2.2.0 has a CSP-based protection mechanism against XSS through uploaded JavaScript content, but it can be bypassed by uploading a .html file that references an uploaded .js file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 20:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46655 | CodiMD through 2.5.4 has a CSP-based protection mechanism against XSS through uploaded SVG documents containing JavaScript, but it can be by...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46655</link><description>CodiMD through 2.5.4 has a CSP-based protection mechanism against XSS through uploaded SVG documents containing JavaScript, but it can be bypassed in certain cases of different-origin file storage, such as AWS S3. NOTE: it can be considered a user error if AWS is employed for hosting untrusted JavaScript content, but the selected architecture within AWS does not have components that are able to insert Content-Security-Policy headers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 20:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46652 | In IZArc through 4.5, there is a Mark-of-the-Web Bypass Vulnerability. When a user performs an extraction from an archive file that bears Ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46652</link><description>In IZArc through 4.5, there is a Mark-of-the-Web Bypass Vulnerability. When a user performs an extraction from an archive file that bears Mark-of-the-Web, Mark-of-the-Web is not propagated to the extracted files.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 17:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53636 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability via writefile.php of Serosoft Academia Student Information System (SIS) EagleR-1.0.118 allows attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53636</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability via writefile.php of Serosoft Academia Student Information System (SIS) EagleR-1.0.118 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via ../ in the filePath parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 14:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46646 | In Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0, decode_utf8 in base/gp_utf8.c mishandles overlong UTF-8 encoding. NOTE: this issue exists because of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46646</link><description>In Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0, decode_utf8 in base/gp_utf8.c mishandles overlong UTF-8 encoding. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2024-46954.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 14:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13812 | Anps Theme plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13812</link><description>The The Anps Theme plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2101 | Edumall &amp;lt;= 4.2.4 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2101</link><description>The Edumall theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.4 via the 'template' parameter of the 'edumall_lazy_load_template' AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary PHP files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where PHP files can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2851 | GL.iNet GL-A1300 Slate Plus RPC plugins.so buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2851</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in GL.iNet GL-A1300 Slate Plus, GL-AR300M16 Shadow, GL-AR300M Shadow, GL-AR750 Creta, GL-AR750S-EXT Slate, GL-AX1800 Flint, GL-AXT1800 Slate AX, GL-B1300 Convexa-B, GL-B3000 Marble, GL-BE3600 Slate 7, GL-E750, GL-E750V2 Mudi, GL-MT300N-V2 Mango, GL-MT1300 Beryl, GL-MT2500 Brume 2, GL-MT3000 Beryl AX, GL-MT6000 Flint 2, GL-SFT1200 Opal, GL-X300B Collie, GL-X750 Spitz, GL-X3000 Spitz AX, GL-XE300 Puli and GL-XE3000 Puli AX 4.x. Affected is an unknown function of the file plugins.so of the component RPC Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2850 | GL.iNet GL-A1300 Slate Plus Download Interface improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2850</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GL.iNet GL-A1300 Slate Plus, GL-AR300M16 Shadow, GL-AR300M Shadow, GL-AR750 Creta, GL-AR750S-EXT Slate, GL-AX1800 Flint, GL-AXT1800 Slate AX, GL-B1300 Convexa-B, GL-B3000 Marble, GL-BE3600 Slate 7, GL-E750, GL-E750V2 Mudi, GL-MT300N-V2 Mango, GL-MT1300 Beryl, GL-MT2500 Brume 2, GL-MT3000 Beryl AX, GL-MT6000 Flint 2, GL-SFT1200 Opal, GL-X300B Collie, GL-X750 Spitz, GL-X3000 Spitz AX, GL-XE300 Puli and GL-XE3000 Puli AX 4.x. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Download Interface. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 07:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2811 | GL.iNet GL-A1300 Slate Plus API redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2811</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GL.iNet GL-A1300 Slate Plus, GL-AR300M16 Shadow, GL-AR300M Shadow, GL-AR750 Creta, GL-AR750S-EXT Slate, GL-AX1800 Flint, GL-AXT1800 Slate AX, GL-B1300 Convexa-B, GL-B3000 Marble, GL-BE3600 Slate 7, GL-E750, GL-E750V2 Mudi, GL-MT300N-V2 Mango, GL-MT1300 Beryl, GL-MT2500 Brume 2, GL-MT3000 Beryl AX, GL-MT6000 Flint 2, GL-SFT1200 Opal, GL-X300B Collie, GL-X750 Spitz, GL-X3000 Spitz AX, GL-XE300 Puli and GL-XE3000 Puli AX 4.x. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component API. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 07:13:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2907 | Order Delivery Date Pro for WooCommerce &amp;lt; 12.3.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Option Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2907</link><description>The Order Delivery Date WordPress plugin before 12.3.1 does not have authorization and CSRF checks when importing settings. Furthermore it also lacks proper checks to only update options relevant to the Order Delivery Date WordPress plugin before 12.3.1. This leads to attackers being able to modify the default_user_role to administrator and users_can_register, allowing them to register as an administrator of the site for complete site takeover.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 06:18:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1458 | Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid, Carousel and Remote Arrows) &amp;lt;= 5.10.29 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1458</link><description>The Element Pack Addons for Elementor – Free Templates and Widgets for Your WordPress Websites plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several widgets like Dual Button, Creative Button, Image Stack and more in all versions up to, and including, 5.10.29 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 05:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2105 | Jupiter X Core &amp;lt;= 4.8.11 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection via PHAR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2105</link><description>The Jupiter X Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.11 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'file' parameter of the 'raven_download_file' function. This makes it possible for attackers to inject a PHP Object through a PHAR file. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present. This vulnerability may be exploited by unauthenticated attackers when a form is present on the site with the file download action, and the ability to upload files is also present. Otherwise, this would be considered exploitable by Contributor-level users and above, because they could create the form needed to successfully exploit this.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 05:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3491 | Add custom page template &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) PHP Code Injection to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3491</link><description>The Add custom page template plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Code Injection leading to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1 via the 'acpt_validate_setting' function. This is due to insufficient sanitization of the 'template_name' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 05:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3906 | Integração entre Eduzz e Woocommerce 1.5.0 - 1.7.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3906</link><description>The Integração entre Eduzz e Woocommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wep_opcoes' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to edit the default registration role within the plugin's registration flow to Administrator, which allows any user to create an Administrator account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 05:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3914 | Aeropage Sync for Airtable &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3914</link><description>The Aeropage Sync for Airtable plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'aeropage_media_downloader' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 05:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3915 | Aeropage Sync for Airtable &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3915</link><description>The Aeropage Sync for Airtable plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'aeropageDeletePost' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 05:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13808 | Xpro Elementor Addons - Pro &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13808</link><description>The Xpro Elementor Addons - Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.9 via the custom PHP widget. This is due to their only being client side controls when determining who can access the widget. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 04:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2801 | Create custom forms for WordPress with a smart form plugin for smart businesses &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2801</link><description>The The Create custom forms for WordPress with a smart form plugin for smart businesses plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.4. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 03:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32979 | NETSCOUT nGeniusONE before 6.4.0 b2350 allows Arbitrary File Creation by authenticated users.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32979</link><description>NETSCOUT nGeniusONE before 6.4.0 b2350 allows Arbitrary File Creation by authenticated users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32980 | NETSCOUT nGeniusONE before 6.4.0 b2350 has a Weak Sudo Configuration.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32980</link><description>NETSCOUT nGeniusONE before 6.4.0 b2350 has a Weak Sudo Configuration.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32981 | NETSCOUT nGeniusONE before 6.4.0 b2350 allows local users to leverage Insecure Permissions for the nGeniusCLI File.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32981</link><description>NETSCOUT nGeniusONE before 6.4.0 b2350 allows local users to leverage Insecure Permissions for the nGeniusCLI File.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32982 | NETSCOUT nGeniusONE before 6.4.0 b2350 has a Broken Authorization Schema for the report module.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32982</link><description>NETSCOUT nGeniusONE before 6.4.0 b2350 has a Broken Authorization Schema for the report module.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32983 | NETSCOUT nGeniusONE before 6.4.0 b2350 allows Technical Information Disclosure via a Stack Trace.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32983</link><description>NETSCOUT nGeniusONE before 6.4.0 b2350 allows Technical Information Disclosure via a Stack Trace.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32984 | NETSCOUT nGeniusONE before 6.4.0 b2350 allows Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via a certain POST parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32984</link><description>NETSCOUT nGeniusONE before 6.4.0 b2350 allows Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via a certain POST parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32985 | NETSCOUT nGeniusONE before 6.4.0 b2350 has Hardcoded Credentials that can be obtained from JAR files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32985</link><description>NETSCOUT nGeniusONE before 6.4.0 b2350 has Hardcoded Credentials that can be obtained from JAR files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32986 | NETSCOUT nGeniusONE before 6.4.0 b2350 has a Sensitive File Accessible Without Proper Authentication to an endpoint.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32986</link><description>NETSCOUT nGeniusONE before 6.4.0 b2350 has a Sensitive File Accessible Without Proper Authentication to an endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46333 | z2d OOB composition could lead to invalid memory access and corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46333</link><description>z2d is a pure Zig 2D graphics library. In version 0.6.0, when writing from one surface to another using `z2d.compositor.StrideCompositor.run`, the source surface can be completely out-of-bounds on the x-axis (but not on the y-axis) by way of a negative offset. This results in an overflow of the value controlling the length of the stride. In non-safe optimization modes (consumers compiling with `ReleaseFast` or `ReleaseSmall`), this could potentially lead to invalid memory accesses or corruption. This issue is patched in version 0.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28128 | An issue in Mytel Telecom Online Account System v1.0 allows attackers to bypass the OTP verification process via a crafted request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28128</link><description>An issue in Mytel Telecom Online Account System v1.0 allows attackers to bypass the OTP verification process via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 19:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3935 | ScreenConnect Exposure to ASP.NET ViewState Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3935</link><description>ScreenConnect versions 25.2.3 and earlier versions may be susceptible to a ViewState code injection attack. ASP.NET Web Forms use ViewState to preserve page and control state, with data encoded using Base64 protected by machine keys. 
It is important to note that to obtain these machine keys, privileged system level access must be obtained. 



If these machine keys are compromised, attackers could create and send a malicious ViewState to the website, potentially leading to remote code execution on the server. 



The risk does not originate from a vulnerability introduced by ScreenConnect, but from platform level behavior.  This had no direct impact to ScreenConnect Client. ScreenConnect 2025.4 patch disables ViewState and removes any dependency on it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 18:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30152 | HCL SX is affected by usage of a weak cryptographic algorithm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30152</link><description>HCL SX v21 is affected by usage of a weak cryptographic algorithm.  An attacker could exploit this weakness to gain access to sensitive information, modify data, or other impacts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 18:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25775 | Codeastro Bus Ticket Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL injection via the kodetiket parameter in /BusTicket-CI/tiket/cekorder.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25775</link><description>Codeastro Bus Ticket Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL injection via the kodetiket parameter in /BusTicket-CI/tiket/cekorder.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 17:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3928 | Commvault Web Server unspecified vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3928</link><description>Commvault Web Server has an unspecified vulnerability that can be exploited by a remote, authenticated attacker. According to the Commvault advisory: "Webservers can be compromised through bad actors creating and executing webshells." Fixed in version 11.36.46, 11.32.89, 11.28.141, and 11.20.217 for Windows and Linux platforms.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 16:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2068 | An open redirect vulnerability was reported in the FileZ client that could allow information disclosure if a crafted url is visited by a loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2068</link><description>An open redirect vulnerability was reported in the FileZ client that could allow information disclosure if a crafted url is visited by a local user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2069 | A cross-site scripting vulnerability was reported in the FileZ client that could allow execution of code if a crafted url is visited by a lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2069</link><description>A cross-site scripting vulnerability was reported in the FileZ client that could allow execution of code if a crafted url is visited by a local user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2070 | An improper XML parsing vulnerability was reported in the FileZ client that could allow arbitrary file reads on the system if a crafted url ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2070</link><description>An improper XML parsing vulnerability was reported in the FileZ client that could allow arbitrary file reads on the system if a crafted url is visited by a local user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56156 | Halo Vulnerable to Stored XSS and RCE via File Upload Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56156</link><description>Halo is an open source website building tool. Prior to version 2.20.13, a vulnerability in Halo allows attackers to bypass file type validation controls. This bypass enables the upload of malicious files including executables and HTML files, which can lead to stored cross-site scripting attacks and potential remote code execution under certain circumstances. This issue has been patched in version 2.20.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32432 | Craft CMS Allows Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32432</link><description>Craft is a flexible, user-friendly CMS for creating custom digital experiences on the web and beyond. Starting from version 3.0.0-RC1 to before 3.9.15, 4.0.0-RC1 to before 4.14.15, and 5.0.0-RC1 to before 5.6.17, Craft is vulnerable to remote code execution. This is a high-impact, low-complexity attack vector. This issue has been patched in versions 3.9.15, 4.14.15, and 5.6.17, and is an additional fix for CVE-2023-41892.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43862 | Dify Allows Unauthorized Access and Modification of APP Orchestration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43862</link><description>Dify is an open-source LLM app development platform. Prior to version 0.6.12, a normal user is able to access and modify APP orchestration, even though the web UI of APP orchestration is not presented for a normal user. This access control flaw allows non-admin users to make unauthorized access and changes on the APPSs. This issue has been patched in version 0.6.12. A workaround for this vulnerability involves updating the the access control mechanisms to enforce stricter user role permissions and implementing role-based access controls (RBAC) to ensure that only users with admin privileges can access Orchestration of the APPs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28076 | Multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in EasyVirt DCScope &lt;= 8.6.4 and CO2Scope &lt;= 1.3.4 allows remote authenticated attackers to execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28076</link><description>Multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in EasyVirt DCScope &lt;= 8.6.4 and CO2Scope &lt;= 1.3.4 allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the (1) timeago, (2) user, (3) filter, (4) target, (5) p1, (6) p2, (7) p3, (8) p4, (9) p5, (10) p6, (11) p7, (12) p8, (13) p9, (14) p10, (15) p11, (16) p12, (17) p13, (18) p14, (19) p15, (20) p16, (21) p17, (22) p18, (23) p19, or (24) p20 parameter to /api/management/updateihmsettings; the (25) ID, (26) NAME, (27) CPUTHREADNB, (28) RAMCAP, or (29) DISKCAP parameter to /api/capaplan/savetemplates.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32044 | Moodle: unauthenticated rest api user data exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32044</link><description>A flaw has been identified in Moodle where, on certain sites, unauthenticated users could retrieve sensitive user data—including names, contact information, and hashed passwords—via stack traces returned by specific API calls. Sites with PHP configured with zend.exception_ignore_args = 1 in the php.ini file are not affected by this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32045 | Moodle: hidden grades shown to users without permission on some grade reports</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32045</link><description>A flaw has been identified in Moodle where insufficient capability checks in certain grade reports allowed users without the necessary permissions to access hidden grades.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3625 | Moodle: user dos and name disclosure via idor in moodle mfa email factor revoke action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3625</link><description>A security vulnerability was discovered in Moodle that can allow hackers to gain access to sensitive information about students and prevent them from logging into their accounts, even after they had completed two-factor authentication (2FA).</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3627 | Moodle: partial data exposure in moodle before completing multi-factor authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3627</link><description>A security vulnerability was discovered in Moodle that allows some users to access sensitive information about other students before they finish verifying their identities using two-factor authentication (2FA).</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3628 | Moodle: moodle assignment submission search leaks anonymous student identities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3628</link><description>A flaw has was found in Moodle where anonymous assignment submissions can be de-anonymized via search, revealing student identities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3635 | Moodle: csrf risk in moodle user tours manager allows tour duplication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3635</link><description>A security vulnerability was discovered in Moodle that allows anyone to duplicate existing tours without needing to log in due to a lack of protection against cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3636 | Moodle: idor in moodle rss block allows unauthorized access to rss feeds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3636</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. This vulnerability allows unauthorized users to access and view RSS feeds due to insufficient capability checks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3637 | Moodle: csrf token exposure via url in moodle mod_data module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3637</link><description>A security vulnerability was found in Moodle where confidential information that prevents cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks was shared publicly through the site's URL. This vulnerability occurred specifically on two types of pages within the mod_data module: edit and delete pages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3638 | Moodle: csrf risk in brickfield tool&amp;#x27;s analysis request action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3638</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. The analysis request action in the Brickfield tool did not include the necessary token to prevent a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) risk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3640 | Moodle: idor in web service allows users enrolled in a course to access some details of other users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3640</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. Insufficient capability checks made it possible for a user enrolled in a course to access some details, such as the full name and profile image URL, of other users they did not have permission to access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3641 | Moodle: authenticated remote code execution risk in the moodle lms dropbox repository</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3641</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. A remote code execution risk was identified in the Moodle LMS Dropbox repository. By default, this was only available to teachers and managers on sites with the Dropbox repository enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3642 | Moodle: authenticated remote code execution risk in the moodle lms equella repository</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3642</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. A remote code execution risk was identified in the Moodle LMS EQUELLA repository. By default, this was only available to teachers and managers on sites with the EQUELLA repository enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3643 | Moodle: reflected xss risk in policy tool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3643</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. The return URL in the policy tool required additional sanitizing to prevent a reflected Cross-site scripting (XSS) risk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3644 | Moodle: ajax section delete does not respect course_can_delete_section()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3644</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. Additional checks were required to prevent users from deleting course sections they did not have permission to modify.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3645 | Moodle: idor in messaging web service allows access to some user details</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3645</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. Insufficient capability checks in a messaging web service allowed users to view other users' names and online statuses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3647 | Moodle: idor when accessing the cohorts report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3647</link><description>A flaw was discovered in Moodle. Additional checks were required to ensure that users can only access cohort data they are authorized to retrieve.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43016 | In JetBrains Rider before 2025.1.2 custom archive unpacker allowed arbitrary file overwrite during remote debug session</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43016</link><description>In JetBrains Rider before 2025.1.2 custom archive unpacker allowed arbitrary file overwrite during remote debug session</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46432 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.03.1 base64-encoded credentials could be exposed in build logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46432</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.03.1 base64-encoded credentials could be exposed in build logs</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46433 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.03.1 improper path validation in loggingPreset parameter was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46433</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.03.1 improper path validation in loggingPreset parameter was possible</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46618 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.03.1 stored XSS was possible on Data Directory tab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46618</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.03.1 stored XSS was possible on Data Directory tab</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57375 | Andamiro Pump It Up 20th Anniversary (aka Double X or XX/2019) 1.00.0-2.08.3 allows a physically proximate attacker to cause a denial of ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57375</link><description>Andamiro Pump It Up 20th Anniversary (aka Double X or XX/2019) 1.00.0-2.08.3 allows a physically proximate attacker to cause a denial of service (application crash) via certain deselect actions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3634 | Moodle: moodle allows course self-enrolment before completing mfa</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3634</link><description>A security vulnerability was discovered in Moodle that allows students to enroll themselves in courses without completing all the necessary safety checks. Specifically, users can sign up for courses prematurely, even if they haven't finished two-step verification processes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28354 | An issue in the Printer Manager Systm of Entrust Corp Printer Manager D3.18.4-3 and below allows attackers to execute a directory traversal ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28354</link><description>An issue in the Printer Manager Systm of Entrust Corp Printer Manager D3.18.4-3 and below allows attackers to execute a directory traversal via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6198 | SNORE Interface Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6198</link><description>The device exposes a web interface on ports TCP/3030 and TCP/9882. This web service runs lighttpd, which implements the “SNORE” interface. This interface is affected by a stack buffer overflow vulnerability due to insecure path parsing. An attacker
with access to the LAN network interface could use a specially crafted HTTP request to exploit a buffer overflow on the modem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 13:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6199 | Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6199</link><description>An unauthenticated attacker on the WAN interface, with the ability to intercept Dynamic DNS (DDNS) traffic between DDNS services and the modem, could manipulate specific responses to include code that forces a buffer overflow on the modem.

Customers that have not enabled Dynamic DNS on their modem are not vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 13:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11917 | JobSearch WP Job Board &amp;lt;= 2.8.8 - Authentication Bypass via Social Logins</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11917</link><description>The JobSearch WP Job Board plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.8. This is due to improper configurations in the 'jobsearch_xing_response_data_callback', 'set_access_tokes', and 'google_callback' functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as the first connected Xing user, or any connected Xing user if the Xing id is known. It is also possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as the first connected Google user if the user has logged in, without subsequently logging out, in thirty days. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 2.8.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2470 | Service Finder Bookings &amp;lt;= 5.1 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via &amp;#x27;nsl_registration_store_extra_input&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2470</link><description>The Service Finder Bookings plugin for WordPress, used by the Service Finder - Directory and Job Board WordPress Theme, is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 5.1. This is due to a lack of restriction on user role in the 'nsl_registration_store_extra_input' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register an account on the site with an arbitrary role, including Administrator, when registering via a social login. The Nextend Social Login plugin must be installed and configured to exploit the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2986 | IBM Maximo Asset Management cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2986</link><description>IBM Maximo Asset Management 7.6.1.3 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows a privileged user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3912 | WS Form LITE – Drag &amp;amp; Drop Contact Form Builder for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.10.35 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3912</link><description>The WS Form LITE – Drag &amp; Drop Contact Form Builder for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'get_config' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.10.35. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the value of the plugin's settings, including API keys for integrated services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1565 | Mayosis Core &amp;lt;= 5.4.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1565</link><description>The Mayosis Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.1 via the library/wave-audio/peaks/remote_dl.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 09:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1279 | BM Content Builder &amp;lt;= 3.16.2.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1279</link><description>The BM Content Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the ux_cb_tools_import_item_ajax AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.16.2.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 08:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3870 | 1 Decembrie 1918 &amp;lt;= 1.dec.2012 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3870</link><description>The 1 Decembrie 1918 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.dec.2012. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 1-decembrie-1918/1-decembrie-1918.php page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 08:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46535 | WordPress Custom Login and Registration plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46535</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AlphaEfficiencyTeam Custom Login and Registration allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Custom Login and Registration: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 08:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46482 | WordPress WP Quiz plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46482</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MyThemeShop WP Quiz allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Quiz: from n/a through 2.0.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 07:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2238 | Vikinger &amp;lt;= 1.9.30 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via &amp;#x27;vikinger_user_meta_update_ajax&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2238</link><description>The Vikinger theme for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.30. This is due to insufficient user_meta restrictions in the 'vikinger_user_meta_update_ajax' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to escalate their privileges to Administrator-level.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3743 | Upsell Funnel Builder for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Unauthenticated Order Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3743</link><description>The Upsell Funnel Builder for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to order manipulation in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This is due to the plugin allowing the additional product ID and discount field to be manipulated prior to processing via the 'add_offer_in_cart' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to arbitrarily update the product associated with any order bump, and arbitrarily update the discount applied to any order bump item, when adding it to the cart.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3866 | Add Google +1 (Plus one) social share Button &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3866</link><description>The Add Google +1 (Plus one) social share Button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the google-plus-one-share-button page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3867 | Ajax Comment Form CST &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3867</link><description>The Ajax Comment Form CST plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation via the 'acform_cst_settings' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3868 | Custom Admin-Bar Favorites &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3868</link><description>The Custom Admin-Bar Favorites plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'menuObject' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46616 | Quantum StorNext Web GUI API before 7.2.4 allows potential Arbitrary Remote Code Execution (RCE) via upload of a file. This affects StorNext...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46616</link><description>Quantum StorNext Web GUI API before 7.2.4 allows potential Arbitrary Remote Code Execution (RCE) via upload of a file. This affects StorNext RYO before 7.2.4, StorNext Xcellis Workflow Director before 7.2.4, and ActiveScale Cold Storage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46617 | Quantum StorNext Web GUI API before 7.2.4 grants access to internal StorNext configuration and unauthorized modification of some software co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46617</link><description>Quantum StorNext Web GUI API before 7.2.4 grants access to internal StorNext configuration and unauthorized modification of some software configuration parameters via undocumented user credentials. This affects StorNext RYO before 7.2.4, StorNext Xcellis Workflow Director before 7.2.4, and ActiveScale Cold Storage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0671 | Email Subscribers &amp;lt; 5.7.50 - Admin+ Stored XSS in Template</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0671</link><description>The Icegram Express  WordPress plugin before 5.7.50 does not sanitise and escape some of its Template settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46613 | OpenPLC 3 through 64f9c11 has server.cpp Memory Corruption because a thread may access handleConnections arguments after the parent stack fr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46613</link><description>OpenPLC 3 through 64f9c11 has server.cpp Memory Corruption because a thread may access handleConnections arguments after the parent stack frame becomes unavailable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 05:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2580 | Contact Form by Bit Form &amp;lt;= 2.18.3 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2580</link><description>The Contact Form by Bit Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 2.18.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 05:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3511 | Improper Validation of Specified Quantity in Input vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation CC-Link IE TSN Remote I/O module, CC-Lin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3511</link><description>Improper Validation of Specified Quantity in Input vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation CC-Link IE TSN Remote I/O module, CC-Link IE TSN Analog-Digital Converter module, CC-Link IE TSN Digital-Analog Converter module, CC-Link IE TSN FPGA module and CC-Link IE TSN Remote Station Communication LSI CP620 with GbE-PHY allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause a Denial of Service condition in the products by sending specially crafted UDP packets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 05:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3861 | Prevent Direct Access 2.8.6 - 2.8.8.2 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Multiple Media Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3861</link><description>The Prevent Direct Access – Protect WordPress Files plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data| due to a misconfigured capability check on the 'pda_lite_custom_permission_check' function in versions 2.8.6 to 2.8.8.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to access and change the protection status of media.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 05:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3923 | Prevent Direct Access – Protect WordPress Files &amp;lt;= 2.8.8 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3923</link><description>The Prevent Direct Access – Protect WordPress Files plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.8 via the 'generate_unique_string' due to insufficient randomness of the generated file name. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including files protected by the plugin if the attacker can determine the file name.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 05:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3752 | Able Player, accessible HTML5 media player &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via preload Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3752</link><description>The Able Player, accessible HTML5 media player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘preload’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 04:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3775 | ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp;amp; Gutenberg +20 Modules – All in One Solution (formerly WooLentor) &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery via URL Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3775</link><description>The ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg +20 Modules – All in One Solution (formerly WooLentor) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.2 via the woolentor_template_proxy function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application, and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 04:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46599 | CNCF K3s 1.32 before 1.32.4-rc1+k3s1 has a Kubernetes kubelet configuration change with the unintended consequence that, in some situations,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46599</link><description>CNCF K3s 1.32 before 1.32.4-rc1+k3s1 has a Kubernetes kubelet configuration change with the unintended consequence that, in some situations, ReadOnlyPort is set to 10255. For example, the default behavior of a K3s online installation might allow unauthenticated access to this port, exposing credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 04:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46595 | An XSS issue was discovered in the Flag module before 1.x-3.6.2 for Backdrop CMS. Flag is a module that allows flags to be added to nodes, c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46595</link><description>An XSS issue was discovered in the Flag module before 1.x-3.6.2 for Backdrop CMS. Flag is a module that allows flags to be added to nodes, comments, users, and any other type of entity. It doesn't verify flag links before performing the flag action, or verify that the response returned was provided by the flag module. This can allow crafted HTML to result in Cross Site Scripting. This is mitigated by the fact that an attacker must have a role with permission to create links on the website, for example: create or edit comments or content with a filtered text format.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46544 | In Sherpa Orchestrator 141851, a low-privileged user can elevate their privileges by creating new users and roles.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46544</link><description>In Sherpa Orchestrator 141851, a low-privileged user can elevate their privileges by creating new users and roles.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46545 | In Sherpa Orchestrator 141851, the functionality for adding or updating licenses allows for stored XSS attacks by an administrator through t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46545</link><description>In Sherpa Orchestrator 141851, the functionality for adding or updating licenses allows for stored XSS attacks by an administrator through the name parameter. The XSS payload can execute when the license expires.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46546 | In Sherpa Orchestrator 141851, multiple time-based blind SQL injections can be performed by an authenticated user. This affects api/gui/asse...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46546</link><description>In Sherpa Orchestrator 141851, multiple time-based blind SQL injections can be performed by an authenticated user. This affects api/gui/asset/list, /api/gui/files/export/csv/, /api/gui/files/list, /api/gui/process/export/csv, /api/gui/process/export/xlsx, /api/gui/process/listAll, /api/gui/processVersion/export/csv/, /api/gui/processVersion/export/xlsx/, /api/gui/processVersion/list/, /api/gui/robot/list/, /api/gui/task/export/csv/, /api/gui/task/export/xlsx/, and /api/gui/task/list/.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46547 | In Sherpa Orchestrator 141851, the web application lacks protection against CSRF attacks, with resultant effects of an attacker conducting X...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46547</link><description>In Sherpa Orchestrator 141851, the web application lacks protection against CSRF attacks, with resultant effects of an attacker conducting XSS attacks, adding a new user or role, or exploiting a SQL injection issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 02:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43864 | React Router allows a DoS via cache poisoning by forcing SPA mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43864</link><description>React Router is a router for React. Starting in version 7.2.0 and prior to version 7.5.2, it is possible to force an application to switch to SPA mode by adding a header to the request. If the application uses SSR and is forced to switch to SPA, this causes an error that completely corrupts the page. If a cache system is in place, this allows the response containing the error to be cached, resulting in a cache poisoning that strongly impacts the availability of the application. This issue has been patched in version 7.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43865 | React Router allows pre-render data spoofing on React-Router framework mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43865</link><description>React Router is a router for React. In versions on the 7.0 branch prior to version 7.5.2, it's possible to modify pre-rendered data by adding a header to the request. This allows to completely spoof its contents and modify all the values ​​of the data object passed to the HTML. This issue has been patched in version 7.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>