<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 09:31:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-13735 | HurryTimer &amp;lt;= 2.11.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Campaign Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13735</link><description>The HurryTimer – An Scarcity and Urgency Countdown Timer for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 2.11.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping of a campaign name. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 09:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26791 | DOMPurify before 3.2.4 has an incorrect template literal regular expression, sometimes leading to mutation cross-site scripting (mXSS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26791</link><description>DOMPurify before 3.2.4 has an incorrect template literal regular expression, sometimes leading to mutation cross-site scripting (mXSS).</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 08:34:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26789 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint AgentX before 1.5.0. A vulnerability caused by limited access controls allowed li-admin users to access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26789</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint AgentX before 1.5.0. A vulnerability caused by limited access controls allowed li-admin users to access sensitive information about AgentX Manager in a Logpoint deployment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 07:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1298 | Logic vulnerability in the mobile application (com.transsion.carlcare) may lead to the risk of account takeover.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1298</link><description>Logic vulnerability in the mobile application (com.transsion.carlcare) may lead to the risk of account takeover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 07:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26788 | StrongKey FIDO Server before 4.15.1 treats a non-discoverable (namedcredential) flow as a discoverable transaction.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26788</link><description>StrongKey FIDO Server before 4.15.1 treats a non-discoverable (namedcredential) flow as a discoverable transaction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 07:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22630 | WordPress Widget Options Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Arbitrary Code Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22630</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability in MarketingFire Widget Options allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects Widget Options: from n/a through 4.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 07:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9601 | Qubely – Advanced Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.8.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;align&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;UniqueID&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9601</link><description>The Qubely – Advanced Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘align’  and 'UniqueID' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 06:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57969 | app/Model/Attribute.php in MISP before 2.4.198 ignores an ACL during a GUI attribute search.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57969</link><description>app/Model/Attribute.php in MISP before 2.4.198 ignores an ACL during a GUI attribute search.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 06:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13493 | Sensly Online Presence &amp;lt;= 0.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13493</link><description>The Sensly Online Presence WordPress plugin through 0.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 06:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7052 | Forminator &amp;lt; 1.38.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7052</link><description>The Forminator Forms  WordPress plugin before 1.38.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 06:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13641 | Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.4.5 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13641</link><description>The Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce – Return Management System, RMA Exchange, Wallet And Cancel Order Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.5 via the 'attachment' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/attachment directory which can contain file attachments for order refunds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 05:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13692 | Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.4.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13692</link><description>The Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce – Return Management System, RMA Exchange, Wallet And Cancel Order Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.5 via several functions due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to overwrite linked refund image attachments, overwrite refund request message, overwrite order messages, and read order messages of other users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 05:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2240 | Docker implementation in Brocade SANnav is missing Audit Rules.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2240</link><description>Docker daemon in Brocade SANnav before SANnav 2.3.1b runs without auditing. The vulnerability could allow a remote authenticated attacker to execute various attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 04:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23406 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability caused by improper checking of TCP MSS option values exists in Cente middleware TCP/IP Network Series, whic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23406</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability caused by improper checking of TCP MSS option values exists in Cente middleware TCP/IP Network Series, which may lead to processing a specially crafted packet to cause the affected product crashed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 04:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1053 | Brocade SANnav encryption key is logged in the debug logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1053</link><description>Under certain error conditions at time of SANnav installation or upgrade, the encryption key can be written into and obtained from a Brocade SANnav supportsave.  An attacker with privileged access to the Brocade SANnav database could use the encryption key to obtain passwords used by Brocade SANnav.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 03:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26519 | musl libc 0.9.13 through 1.2.5 before 1.2.6 has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability when an attacker can trigger iconv conversion of untrus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26519</link><description>musl libc 0.9.13 through 1.2.5 before 1.2.6 has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability when an attacker can trigger iconv conversion of untrusted EUC-KR text to UTF-8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 03:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10404 | Clear text password seen in switch-asset-collectors-mw in Brocade SANnav supportsave</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10404</link><description>CalInvocationHandler in Brocade 
SANnav before 2.3.1b logs sensitive information in clear text. The 
vulnerability could allow an authenticated, local attacker to view 
Brocade Fabric OS switch sensitive information in clear text. An 
attacker with administrative privileges could retrieve sensitive 
information including passwords; SNMP responses that contain AuthSecret 
and PrivSecret after collecting a “supportsave” or getting access to an 
already collected “supportsave”. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2024-29952</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 03:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55904 | IBM DevOps Deploy / IBM UrbanCode Deploy command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55904</link><description>IBM DevOps Deploy 8.0 through 8.0.1.4, 8.1 through 8.1.0.0 / IBM UrbanCode Deploy 7.0 through 7.0.5.25, 7.1 through 7.1.2.21, 7.2 through 7.2.3.14, and 7.3 through 7.3.2.9 could allow a remote privileged authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the system by sending specially crafted input containing special elements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 03:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54951 | Monica 4.1.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). A malicious user can create a malformed contact and use that contact in the "HOW Y...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54951</link><description>Monica 4.1.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). A malicious user can create a malformed contact and use that contact in the "HOW YOU MET" customization options to trigger the XSS.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22962 | A critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the web-based management interface of GatesAir Maxiva UAXT, VAXT transmitters...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22962</link><description>A critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the web-based management interface of GatesAir Maxiva UAXT, VAXT transmitters when debugging mode is enabled. An attacker with a valid session ID (sess_id) can send specially crafted POST requests to the /json endpoint, enabling arbitrary command execution on the underlying system. This vulnerability can lead to full system compromise, including unauthorized access, privilege escalation, and potentially full device takeover.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53311 | A Stack buffer overflow in the arguments parameter in Immunity Inc. Immunity Debugger v1.85 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53311</link><description>A Stack buffer overflow in the arguments parameter in Immunity Inc. Immunity Debugger v1.85 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted input that exceeds the buffer size.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22960 | A session hijacking vulnerability exists in the web-based management interface of GatesAir Maxiva UAXT, VAXT transmitters. Unauthenticated a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22960</link><description>A session hijacking vulnerability exists in the web-based management interface of GatesAir Maxiva UAXT, VAXT transmitters. Unauthenticated attackers can access exposed log files (/logs/debug/xteLog*), potentially revealing sensitive session-related information such as session IDs (sess_id) and authentication success tokens (user_check_password OK). Exploiting this flaw could allow attackers to hijack active sessions, gain unauthorized access, and escalate privileges on affected devices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22961 | A critical information disclosure vulnerability exists in the web-based management interface of GatesAir Maxiva UAXT, VAXT transmitters due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22961</link><description>A critical information disclosure vulnerability exists in the web-based management interface of GatesAir Maxiva UAXT, VAXT transmitters due to Incorrect Access Control (CWE-284). Unauthenticated attackers can directly access sensitive database backup files (snapshot_users.db) via publicly exposed URLs (/logs/devcfg/snapshot/ and /logs/devcfg/user/). Exploiting this vulnerability allows retrieval of sensitive user data, including login credentials, potentially leading to full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53309 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Effectmatrix Total Video Converter Command Line (TVCC) 2.50 when an overly long string...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53309</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Effectmatrix Total Video Converter Command Line (TVCC) 2.50 when an overly long string is passed to the "-f" parameter. This can lead to memory corruption, potentially allowing arbitrary code execution or causing a denial of service via specially crafted input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53310 | A Structured Exception Handler based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Effectmatrix Total Video Converter Command Line (TVCC) 2.50 whe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53310</link><description>A Structured Exception Handler based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Effectmatrix Total Video Converter Command Line (TVCC) 2.50 when a specially crafted file is passed to the -ff parameter. The vulnerability occurs due to improper handling of file input with overly long characters, leading to memory corruption. This can result in arbitrary code execution or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56908 | In Perfex Crm &lt; 3.2.1, an authenticated attacker can send a crafted HTTP POST request to the affected upload_sales_file endpoint. By providi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56908</link><description>In Perfex Crm &lt; 3.2.1, an authenticated attacker can send a crafted HTTP POST request to the affected upload_sales_file endpoint. By providing malicious input in the rel_id parameter, combined with improper input validation, the attacker can bypass restrictions and upload arbitrary files to directories of their choice, potentially leading to remote code execution or server compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57782 | An issue in Docker-proxy v18.09.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57782</link><description>An issue in Docker-proxy v18.09.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34401 | Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. Inside profile folder there is a file, which ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34401</link><description>Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. Inside profile folder there is a file, which is encoded with proprietary UD2 codec. Due to missed size checks in the enapsulate file, attacker can achieve Out-of-Bound Read in heap memory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34402 | Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. Inside file is encapsulate another file, whic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34402</link><description>Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. Inside file is encapsulate another file, which service will drop during processing. Due to missed checks, attacker can achieve Arbitrary File Write with service speech rights.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34403 | Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 has Ethernet pins on Base Board to connect module CSB. Attacker can connect to this pins and get access to inte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34403</link><description>Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 has Ethernet pins on Base Board to connect module CSB. Attacker can connect to this pins and get access to internal network. A race condition can be acquired and attacker can spoof “UserData” with desirable file path and access it though backup on USB.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34404 | Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 has Ethernet pins on Base Board to connect module CSB. Attacker can connect to these pins and get access to int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34404</link><description>Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 has Ethernet pins on Base Board to connect module CSB. Attacker can connect to these pins and get access to internal network. As a result, by accessing a specific port an attacker can send call request to all registered services in router and achieve command injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34406 | An issue was discovered on Mercedes Benz NTG 6. A possible integer overflow exists in the user data import/export function of NTG (New Telem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34406</link><description>An issue was discovered on Mercedes Benz NTG 6. A possible integer overflow exists in the user data import/export function of NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6 head units. To perform this attack, local access to USB interface of the car is needed. With prepared data, an attacker can cause the User-Data service to fail. The failed service instance will restart automatically.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12054 | ZF Roll Stability Support Plus (RSSPlus) Authentication Bypass By Primary Weakness</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12054</link><description>ZF Roll Stability Support Plus (RSSPlus) 
is vulnerable to an authentication bypass vulnerability targeting 
deterministic RSSPlus SecurityAccess service seeds, which may allow an 
attacker to remotely (proximal/adjacent with RF equipment or via pivot 
from J2497 telematics devices) call diagnostic functions intended for 
workshop or repair scenarios. This can impact system availability, 
potentially degrading performance or erasing software, however the 
vehicle remains in a safe vehicle state.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37600 | An issue was discovered in Mercedes Benz NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6 through 2021. A possible stack buffer overflow in the Service Bro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37600</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mercedes Benz NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6 through 2021. A possible stack buffer overflow in the Service Broker service affects NTG 6 head units. To perform this attack, physical access to Ethernet pins of the head unit base board is needed. With a static IP address, an attacker can connect via the internal network to the Service Broker service. With prepared HTTP requests, an attacker can cause the Service-Broker service to fail.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37601 | An issue was discovered in Mercedes Benz NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6. A possible heap buffer overflow exists in the user data import/e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37601</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mercedes Benz NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6. A possible heap buffer overflow exists in the user data import/export function of NTG 6 head units. To perform this attack, local access to the USB interface of the car is needed. With prepared data, an attacker can cause the User-Data service to fail. The failed service instance will restart automatically.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37602 | An issue was discovered in Mercedes Benz NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6 through 2021. A possible NULL pointer dereference in the Apple Ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37602</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mercedes Benz NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6 through 2021. A possible NULL pointer dereference in the Apple Car Play function affects NTG 6 head units. To perform this attack, physical access to Ethernet pins of the head unit base board is needed. With a static IP address, an attacker can connect via the internal network to the AirTunes / AirPlay service. With prepared HTTP requests, an attacker can cause the Car Play service to fail.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37603 | An issue was discovered in Mercedes Benz NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6. A possible type confusion exists in the user data import/export ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37603</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mercedes Benz NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6. A possible type confusion exists in the user data import/export function of NTG 6 head units. To perform this attack, local access to the USB interface of the car is needed. With prepared data, an attacker can cause the User-Data service to fail. The failed service instance will restart automatically.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34397 | Mercedes Benz head-unit NTG 6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. During parsing you can trigger that the serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34397</link><description>Mercedes Benz head-unit NTG 6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. During parsing you can trigger that the service will be crashed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34398 | Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. Some values of this table are serialized arch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34398</link><description>Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. Some values of this table are serialized archive according boost library. The boost library contains a vulnerability/null pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34399 | Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. Some values of this table are serialized arch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34399</link><description>Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. Some values of this table are serialized archive according boost library. The version of boost library contains vulnerability integer overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34400 | Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. In case of parsing file, service try to defin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34400</link><description>Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. In case of parsing file, service try to define header inside the file and convert it to null-terminated string. If character is missed, will return null pointer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57378 | Wazuh SIEM version 4.8.2 is affected by a broken access control vulnerability. This issue allows the unauthorized creation of internal users...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57378</link><description>Wazuh SIEM version 4.8.2 is affected by a broken access control vulnerability. This issue allows the unauthorized creation of internal users without assigning any existing user role, potentially leading to privilege escalation or unauthorized access to sensitive resources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24836 | Qardio Heart Health IOS and Android Application and QardioARM A100 Uncaught Exception</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24836</link><description>With a specially crafted Python script, an attacker could send 
continuous startMeasurement commands over an unencrypted Bluetooth 
connection to the affected device. This would prevent the device from 
connecting to a clinician's app to take patient readings and ostensibly 
flood it with requests, resulting in a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20615 | Qardio Heart Health IOS Mobile Application Exposure of Private Personal Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20615</link><description>The Qardio Arm iOS application exposes sensitive data such as usernames 
and passwords in a plist file. This allows an attacker to log in to 
production-level development accounts and access an engineering backdoor
 in the application. The engineering backdoor allows the attacker to 
send hex-based commands over a UI-based terminal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23421 | Qardio iOS and Android applications Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23421</link><description>An attacker could obtain firmware files and reverse engineer their 
intended use leading to loss of confidentiality and integrity of the 
hardware devices enabled by the Qardio iOS and Android applications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25195 | Zulip events can leak private channel names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25195</link><description>Zulip is an open source team chat application. A weekly cron job (added in 50256f48314250978f521ef439cafa704e056539) demotes channels to being "inactive" after they have not received traffic for 180 days.  However, upon doing so, an event was sent to all users in the organization, not just users in the channel.  This event contained the name of the private channel. Similarly, the same commit (50256f48314250978f521ef439cafa704e056539) added functionality to notify clients when channels stopped being "inactive."  The first message sent to a private channel which had not previously had any messages for over 180 days (and were thus already marked "inactive") would leak an event to all users in the organization; this event also contained the name of the private channel. Commits 75be449d456d29fef27e9d1828bafa30174284b4 and a2a1a7f8d152296c8966f1380872c0ac69e5c87e fixed the issue. This vulnerability only existed in `main`, and was not part of any published versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25067 | mySCADA myPRO Manager OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25067</link><description>mySCADA myPRO Manager
 
is vulnerable to an OS command injection which could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22896 | mySCADA myPRO Manager Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22896</link><description>mySCADA myPRO Manager


stores credentials in cleartext, which could allow an attacker to obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23411 | mySCADA myPRO Manager Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23411</link><description>mySCADA myPRO Manager
 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery (CSRF), which could allow 
an attacker to obtain sensitive information. An attacker would need to 
trick the victim in to visiting an attacker-controlled website.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24865 | mySCADA myPRO Manager Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24865</link><description>The administrative web interface of 
mySCADA myPRO Manager

can be accessed without authentication 
which could allow an unauthorized attacker to retrieve sensitive 
information and upload files without the associated password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1283 | Dingtian DT-R0 Series Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1283</link><description>The Dingtian DT-R0 Series is vulnerable to an exploit that allows 
attackers to bypass login requirements by directly navigating to the 
main page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24861 | Outback Power Mojave Inverter Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24861</link><description>An attacker may inject commands via specially-crafted post requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25281 | Outback Power Mojave Inverter Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25281</link><description>An attacker may modify the URL to discover sensitive information about the target network.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26473 | Outback Power Mojave Inverter Use of GET Request Method With Sensitive Query Strings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26473</link><description>The Mojave Inverter uses the GET method for sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11344 | Type confusion vulnerability in the Postscript interpreter in various Lexmark devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11344</link><description>A type confusion vulnerability has been identified in the Postscript interpreter in various Lexmark devices. The vulnerability can be leveraged by an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11346 | Access of Resource Using Incompatible Type in Postscript interpreter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11346</link><description>: Access of Resource Using Incompatible Type ('Type Confusion') vulnerability in Lexmark International CX, XC, CS, et. Al. (Postscript interpreter modules) allows Resource Injection.This issue affects CX, XC, CS, et. Al.: from 001.001:0 through 081.231, from *.*.P001 through *.*.P233, from *.*.P001 through *.*.P759, from *.*.P001 through *.*.P836.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11347 | Access of Resource Using Incompatible Type in Postscript interpreter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11347</link><description>Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Lexmark International CX, XC, CS, et. Al. (Postscript interpreter modules) allows Forced Integer Overflow.The vulnerability can be leveraged by an attacker to execute arbitrary code as an unprivileged user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11345 | Heap-based memory vulnerability in the Postscript interpreter in various Lexmark devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11345</link><description>A heap-based memory vulnerability has been identified in the Postscript interpreter in various Lexmark devices. The vulnerability can be leveraged by an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1127 | Combination Path Traversal and Concurrent Execution vulnerability exists within the embedded web server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1127</link><description>The vulnerability can be leveraged by an attacker to execute arbitrary code as an unprivileged user and/or modify the contents of any data on the filesystem.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24888 | Path traversal in SecureDrop Client API.download_reply()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24888</link><description>The SecureDrop Client is a desktop application for journalists to communicate with sources and work with submissions on the SecureDrop Workstation. Prior to version 0.14.1, a malicious SecureDrop Server could obtain code execution on the SecureDrop Client virtual machine (`sd-app`). SecureDrop Server itself has multiple layers of built-in hardening, and is a dedicated physical machine exposed on the internet only via Tor hidden services for the Source and Journalist interfaces, and optionally via remote SSH access over another Tor hidden service. A newsroom's SecureDrop Workstation communicates only with its own dedicated SecureDrop Server.

The SecureDrop Client runs in a dedicated Qubes virtual machine, named `sd-app`, as part of the SecureDrop Workstation. The private OpenPGP key used to decrypt submissions and replies is stored in a separate virtual machine and never accessed directly. The vulnerability lies in the code responsible for downloading replies. The filename of the reply is obtained from the `Content-Disposition` HTTP header and used to write the encrypted reply on disk. Note that filenames are generated and sanitized server-side, and files are downloaded in an encrypted format, so a remote attacker who has not achieved server compromise, such as one posing as a source, could not craft the HTTP response necessary for this attack.

While the filename is later checked to guard against path traversal before being moved into the Client’s data storage directory, the file has already been written to a potentially arbitrary location. In this case, `safe_move()` would detect the path traversal and fail, leaving the original downloaded file in the attacker-chosen directory. Code execution can be gained by writing an autostart file in `/home/user/.config/autostart/`.

Version 0.14.1 fixes the issue. As of time of publication, there is no known evidence of exploitation in the wild. This attack requires a previously compromised SecureDrop Server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 17:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24889 | Path traversal in sd-log Qubes virtual machine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24889</link><description>The SecureDrop Client is a desktop application for journalists to communicate with sources and work with submissions on the SecureDrop Workstation. Prior to versions 0.14.1 and 1.0.1, an attacker who has already gained code execution in a virtual machine on the SecureDrop Workstation could gain code execution in the `sd-log` virtual machine by sending a specially crafted log entry. The vulnerability is not exploitable remotely and requires an attacker to already have code execution on one of the other virtual machines (VMs) of the system. Due to the Workstation's underlying usage of Qubes for strong isolation, the vulnerability would have allowed lateral movement between any log-enabled VM and the `sd-log` VM, but no further. The SecureDrop workstation collects logs centrally in an isolated virtual machine named `sd-log` for easy export for support and debugging purposes. The `sd-log`  VM is completely isolated from the internet and ingests logs via a narrow Qubes RPC policy that allows for specific inter-VM communication via the Xen vchan protocol used by Qubes's qrexec mechanism. A path traversal bug was found in the logic used to choose where to write the log file for a specific VM: the VM name, used unsanitized in the destination path in `sd-log`, is supplied by the logging VM itself instead of being read from a trusted source, such as the Qubes environment variable `QREXEC_REMOTE_DOMAIN` that is used in the fixed implementation. An attacker could provide an arbitrary source VM name, possibly overwriting logs of other VMs, or writing a file named `syslog.log`, with attacker-controlled content, in arbitrary directories as a low-privileged user. A successful attack could potentially overwrite or add configuration to software that loads configuration files from a directory. This is exploitable to achieve code execution by setting the target directory to `/home/user/.config/autostart/` and letting it write `syslog.log`, because XFCE treats any file in that directory as a `.desktop` file regardless of its extension. Versions 0.14.1 and 1.0.1 contain a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 17:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25387 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/manage-propertytype.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25387</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/manage-propertytype.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the propertytype POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 17:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25388 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/edit-propertytype.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25388</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/edit-propertytype.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the editid GET request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 17:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25389 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/forgot-password.php in Phpgurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25389</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/forgot-password.php in Phpgurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the contactno POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 17:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22480 | Dell SupportAssist OS Recovery versions prior to 5.5.13.1 contain a symbolic link attack vulnerability. A low-privileged attacker with local...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22480</link><description>Dell SupportAssist OS Recovery versions prior to 5.5.13.1 contain a symbolic link attack vulnerability. A low-privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to arbitrary file deletion and Elevation of Privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 16:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12012 | A CWE-598 “Use of GET Request Method with Sensitive Query Strings” was discovered affecting the 130.8005 TCP/IP Gateway running firmware ver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12012</link><description>A CWE-598 “Use of GET Request Method with Sensitive Query Strings” was discovered affecting the 130.8005 TCP/IP Gateway running firmware version 12h. Both the SHA-1 hash of the password as well as the session tokens are included as part of the URL and therefore exposed to information leakage scenarios. An attacker capable of accessing such values (e.g., victim browser, network traffic inspection) can exploit this vulnerability to leak both the password hash as well as session tokens and bypass the authentication mechanism using a pass-the-hash attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 16:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12013 | A CWE-1392 “Use of Default Credentials” was discovered affecting the 130.8005 TCP/IP Gateway running firmware version 12h. The device expose...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12013</link><description>A CWE-1392 “Use of Default Credentials” was discovered affecting the 130.8005 TCP/IP Gateway running firmware version 12h. The device exposes an FTP server with default and easy-to-guess admin credentials. A remote attacker capable of interacting with the FTP server could gain access and perform changes over resources exposed by the service such as configuration files where password hashes are saved or where network settings are stored.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 16:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12011 | A CWE-126 “Buffer Over-read” was discovered affecting the 130.8005 TCP/IP Gateway running firmware version 12h. The information disclosure c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12011</link><description>A CWE-126 “Buffer Over-read” was discovered affecting the 130.8005 TCP/IP Gateway running firmware version 12h. The information disclosure can be triggered by leveraging a memory leak affecting the web server. A remote unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability in order to leak valid authentication tokens from the process memory associated to users currently logged to the system and bypass the authentication mechanism.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 16:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25352 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/aboutus.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25352</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/aboutus.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the pagetitle POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 16:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25357 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/contactus.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25357</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/contactus.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the email POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 16:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25354 | A SQL Injection was found in /admin/admin-profile.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25354</link><description>A SQL Injection was found in /admin/admin-profile.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the contactnumber POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25355 | A SQL Injection in was found in /admin/bwdates-reports-details.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25355</link><description>A SQL Injection in was found in /admin/bwdates-reports-details.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the fromdate POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25356 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/bwdates-reports-details.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25356</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/bwdates-reports-details.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the " todate" POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26511 | Cassandra-Lucene-Index allows bypass of Cassandra RBAC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26511</link><description>Systems running the Instaclustr 
fork of Stratio's Cassandra-Lucene-Index plugin versions 4.0-rc1-1.0.0 
through 4.0.16-1.0.0 and 4.1.2-1.0.0 through 4.1.8-1.0.0, installed into
 Apache Cassandra version 4.x, are susceptible to a vulnerability which 
when successfully exploited could allow authenticated Cassandra users to
 remotely bypass RBAC and escalate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24904 | libsignal-service-rs doesn&amp;#x27;t sanity check plaintext envelopes are not sanity-checked</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24904</link><description>libsignal-service-rs is a Rust version of the libsignal-service-java library which implements the core functionality to communicate with Signal servers. Prior to commit 82d70f6720e762898f34ae76b0894b0297d9b2f8, plaintext content envelopes could be injected by a server or a malicious client, and may have been able to bypass the end-to-end encryption and authentication. The vulnerability is fixed per 82d70f6720e762898f34ae76b0894b0297d9b2f8. The `Metadata` struct contains an additional `was_encrypted` field, which breaks the API, but should be easily resolvable. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25287 | Lakeus vulnerable to stored XSS via system messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25287</link><description>Lakeus is a simple skin made for MediaWiki. Starting in version 1.8.0 and prior to versions 1.3.1+REL1.39, 1.3.1+REL1.42, and 1.4.0, Lakeus is vulnerable to store cross-site scripting via malicious system messages, though editing the messages requires high privileges. Those with `(editinterface)` rights can edit system messages that are improperly handled in order to send raw HTML. In the case of `lakeus-footermessage`, this will affect all users if the server is configured to link back to this repository. Otherwise, the system messages in themeDesigner.js are only used when the user enables it in their preferences. Versions 1.3.1+REL1.39, 1.3.1+REL1.42, and 1.4.0 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25897 | A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11 via the 'ip' parameter at /userRpm/WanStaticIpV6CfgRpm.htm. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25897</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11 via the 'ip' parameter at /userRpm/WanStaticIpV6CfgRpm.htm. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25898 | A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11 via the pskSecret parameter at /userRpm/WlanSecurityRpm.htm. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25898</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11 via the pskSecret parameter at /userRpm/WlanSecurityRpm.htm. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25899 | A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11 via the 'gw' parameter at /userRpm/WanDynamicIpV6CfgRpm.htm. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25899</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11 via the 'gw' parameter at /userRpm/WanDynamicIpV6CfgRpm.htm. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25900 | A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11 via the username and password parameters at /userRpm/PPPoEv6CfgRpm....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25900</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11 via the username and password parameters at /userRpm/PPPoEv6CfgRpm.htm. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0426 | A security issue was discovered in Kubernetes where a large number of container checkpoint requests made to the unauthenticated kubelet read...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0426</link><description>A security issue was discovered in Kubernetes where a large number of container checkpoint requests made to the unauthenticated kubelet read-only HTTP endpoint may cause a Node Denial of Service by filling the Node's disk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24903 | libsignal-service-rs Doesn&amp;#x27;t Check Origin of Sync Messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24903</link><description>libsignal-service-rs is a Rust version of the libsignal-service-java library which implements the core functionality to communicate with Signal servers. Prior to commit 82d70f6720e762898f34ae76b0894b0297d9b2f8, any contact may forge a sync message, impersonating another device of the local user. The origin of sync messages is not checked. Patched libsignal-service can be found after commit 82d70f6720e762898f34ae76b0894b0297d9b2f8. The `Metadata` struct contains an additional `was_encrypted` field, which breaks the API, but should be easily resolvable. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25901 | A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11, triggered by the dnsserver1 and dnsserver2 parameters at /userRpm/...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25901</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11, triggered by the dnsserver1 and dnsserver2 parameters at /userRpm/WanSlaacCfgRpm.htm. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21701 | net: avoid race between device unregistration and ethnl ops</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21701</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: avoid race between device unregistration and ethnl ops

The following trace can be seen if a device is being unregistered while
its number of channels are being modified.

  DEBUG_LOCKS_WARN_ON(lock-&gt;magic != lock)
  WARNING: CPU: 3 PID: 3754 at kernel/locking/mutex.c:564 __mutex_lock+0xc8a/0x1120
  CPU: 3 UID: 0 PID: 3754 Comm: ethtool Not tainted 6.13.0-rc6+ #771
  RIP: 0010:__mutex_lock+0xc8a/0x1120
  Call Trace:
   
   ethtool_check_max_channel+0x1ea/0x880
   ethnl_set_channels+0x3c3/0xb10
   ethnl_default_set_doit+0x306/0x650
   genl_family_rcv_msg_doit+0x1e3/0x2c0
   genl_rcv_msg+0x432/0x6f0
   netlink_rcv_skb+0x13d/0x3b0
   genl_rcv+0x28/0x40
   netlink_unicast+0x42e/0x720
   netlink_sendmsg+0x765/0xc20
   __sys_sendto+0x3ac/0x420
   __x64_sys_sendto+0xe0/0x1c0
   do_syscall_64+0x95/0x180
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x76/0x7e

This is because unregister_netdevice_many_notify might run before the
rtnl lock section of ethnl operations, eg. set_channels in the above
example. In this example the rss lock would be destroyed by the device
unregistration path before being used again, but in general running
ethnl operations while dismantle has started is not a good idea.

Fix this by denying any operation on devices being unregistered. A check
was already there in ethnl_ops_begin, but not wide enough.

Note that the same issue cannot be seen on the ioctl version
(__dev_ethtool) because the device reference is retrieved from within
the rtnl lock section there. Once dismantle started, the net device is
unlisted and no reference will be found.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:14:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26538 | WordPress Prezi Embedder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26538</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dan Rossiter Prezi Embedder allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Prezi Embedder: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26539 | WordPress Embed Google Map plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26539</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in petkivim Embed Google Map allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Embed Google Map: from n/a through 3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26543 | WordPress Simple Responsive Menu plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26543</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Pukhraj Suthar Simple Responsive Menu allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Simple Responsive Menu: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26545 | WordPress Related Posts Line-up-Exactly by Milliard plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.22 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26545</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in shisuh Related Posts Line-up-Exactly by Milliard allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Related Posts Line-up-Exactly by Milliard: from n/a through 0.0.22.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26547 | WordPress My Login Logout Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4 - CSRF to  Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26547</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in nagarjunsonti My Login Logout Plugin allows Stored XSS. This issue affects My Login Logout Plugin: from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26549 | WordPress WP Html Page Sitemap plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26549</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in pa1 WP Html Page Sitemap allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Html Page Sitemap: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26550 | WordPress Global Meta Keyword &amp;amp; Description plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - CSRF to Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26550</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Kunal Shivale Global Meta Keyword &amp; Description allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Global Meta Keyword &amp; Description: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26551 | WordPress Bootstrap collapse plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26551</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sureshdsk Bootstrap collapse allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Bootstrap collapse: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26552 | WordPress Naver Syndication V2 plugin &amp;lt;= 0.8.3 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26552</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in badrHan Naver Syndication V2 allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Naver Syndication V2: from n/a through 0.8.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26558 | WordPress Aparat Responsive plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26558</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in mkkmail Aparat Responsive allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Aparat Responsive: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26561 | WordPress Elfsight Yottie Lite Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26561</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in elfsight Elfsight Yottie Lite allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Elfsight Yottie Lite: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26562 | WordPress RSS FIlter Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - CSRF to Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26562</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Shambhu Patnaik RSS Filter allows Stored XSS. This issue affects RSS Filter: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26567 | WordPress Font Awesome WP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26567</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in farjana55 Font Awesome WP allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Font Awesome WP: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26568 | WordPress Easy Amazon Product Information plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26568</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in jensmueller Easy Amazon Product Information allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Easy Amazon Product Information: from n/a through 4.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26569 | WordPress Post Thumbs Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26569</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in callmeforsox Post Thumbs allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Post Thumbs: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26570 | WordPress Glance That plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26570</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in uamv Glance That allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Glance That: from n/a through 4.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26571 | WordPress Wibiya Toolbar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26571</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wibiya Wibiya Toolbar allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Wibiya Toolbar: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26572 | WordPress WP PHPList Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26572</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in jesseheap WP PHPList allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP PHPList: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26574 | WordPress Google Drive WP Media plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26574</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Moch Amir Google Drive WP Media allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Google Drive WP Media: from n/a through 2.4.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26577 | WordPress DX-auto-publish plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - CSRF to Stored  XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26577</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in daxiawp DX-auto-publish allows Stored XSS. This issue affects DX-auto-publish: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26578 | WordPress Simple Documentation plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26578</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in mathieuhays Simple Documentation allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Simple Documentation: from n/a through 1.2.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26580 | WordPress Page/Post Specific Social Share Buttons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26580</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CompleteWebResources Page/Post Specific Social Share Buttons allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Page/Post Specific Social Share Buttons: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26582 | WordPress TinyMCE Advanced qTranslate fix editor problems plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26582</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Blackbam TinyMCE Advanced qTranslate fix editor problems allows Stored XSS. This issue affects TinyMCE Advanced qTranslate fix editor problems: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1247 | Io.quarkus:quarkus-rest: quarkus rest endpoint request parameter leakage due to shared instance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1247</link><description>A flaw was found in Quarkus REST that allows request parameters to leak between concurrent requests if endpoints use field injection without a CDI scope. This vulnerability allows attackers to manipulate request data, impersonate users, or access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1094 | PostgreSQL quoting APIs miss neutralizing quoting syntax in text that fails encoding validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1094</link><description>Improper neutralization of quoting syntax in PostgreSQL libpq functions PQescapeLiteral(), PQescapeIdentifier(), PQescapeString(), and PQescapeStringConn() allows a database input provider to achieve SQL injection in certain usage patterns.  Specifically, SQL injection requires the application to use the function result to construct input to psql, the PostgreSQL interactive terminal.  Similarly, improper neutralization of quoting syntax in PostgreSQL command line utility programs allows a source of command line arguments to achieve SQL injection when client_encoding is BIG5 and server_encoding is one of EUC_TW or MULE_INTERNAL.  Versions before PostgreSQL 17.3, 16.7, 15.11, 14.16, and 13.19 are affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13182 | WP Directorybox Manager &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13182</link><description>The WP Directorybox Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.5. This is due to incorrect authentication in the 'wp_dp_parse_request' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1270 | Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in H6Web</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1270</link><description>Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Anapi Group's h6web, allows an authenticated attacker to access other users' information by making a POST request and modifying the “pkrelated” parameter in the “/h6web/ha_datos_hermano.php” endpoint to refer to another user. In addition, the first request could also allow the attacker to impersonate other users. As a result, all requests made after exploitation of the IDOR vulnerability will be executed with the privileges of the impersonated user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1271 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in H6Web</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1271</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Anapi Group's h6web. This security flaw could allow an attacker to inject malicious JavaScript code into a URL. When a user accesses that URL, the injected code is executed in their browser, which can result in the theft of sensitive information, identity theft or the execution of unauthorised actions on behalf of the affected user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:01:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21700 | net: sched: Disallow replacing of child qdisc from one parent to another</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21700</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: sched: Disallow replacing of child qdisc from one parent to another

Lion Ackermann was able to create a UAF which can be abused for privilege
escalation with the following script

Step 1. create root qdisc
tc qdisc add dev lo root handle 1:0 drr

step2. a class for packet aggregation do demonstrate uaf
tc class add dev lo classid 1:1 drr

step3. a class for nesting
tc class add dev lo classid 1:2 drr

step4. a class to graft qdisc to
tc class add dev lo classid 1:3 drr

step5.
tc qdisc add dev lo parent 1:1 handle 2:0 plug limit 1024

step6.
tc qdisc add dev lo parent 1:2 handle 3:0 drr

step7.
tc class add dev lo classid 3:1 drr

step 8.
tc qdisc add dev lo parent 3:1 handle 4:0 pfifo

step 9. Display the class/qdisc layout

tc class ls dev lo
 class drr 1:1 root leaf 2: quantum 64Kb
 class drr 1:2 root leaf 3: quantum 64Kb
 class drr 3:1 root leaf 4: quantum 64Kb

tc qdisc ls
 qdisc drr 1: dev lo root refcnt 2
 qdisc plug 2: dev lo parent 1:1
 qdisc pfifo 4: dev lo parent 3:1 limit 1000p
 qdisc drr 3: dev lo parent 1:2

step10. trigger the bug &lt;=== prevented by this patch
tc qdisc replace dev lo parent 1:3 handle 4:0

step 11. Redisplay again the qdiscs/classes

tc class ls dev lo
 class drr 1:1 root leaf 2: quantum 64Kb
 class drr 1:2 root leaf 3: quantum 64Kb
 class drr 1:3 root leaf 4: quantum 64Kb
 class drr 3:1 root leaf 4: quantum 64Kb

tc qdisc ls
 qdisc drr 1: dev lo root refcnt 2
 qdisc plug 2: dev lo parent 1:1
 qdisc pfifo 4: dev lo parent 3:1 refcnt 2 limit 1000p
 qdisc drr 3: dev lo parent 1:2

Observe that a) parent for 4:0 does not change despite the replace request.
There can only be one parent.  b) refcount has gone up by two for 4:0 and
c) both class 1:3 and 3:1 are pointing to it.

Step 12.  send one packet to plug
echo "" | socat -u STDIN UDP4-DATAGRAM:127.0.0.1:8888,priority=$((0x10001))
step13.  send one packet to the grafted fifo
echo "" | socat -u STDIN UDP4-DATAGRAM:127.0.0.1:8888,priority=$((0x10003))

step14. lets trigger the uaf
tc class delete dev lo classid 1:3
tc class delete dev lo classid 1:1

The semantics of "replace" is for a del/add _on the same node_ and not
a delete from one node(3:1) and add to another node (1:3) as in step10.
While we could "fix" with a more complex approach there could be
consequences to expectations so the patch takes the preventive approach of
"disallow such config".

Joint work with Lion Ackermann</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 11:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13606 | JS Help Desk – The Ultimate Help Desk &amp;amp; Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.8 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13606</link><description>The JS Help Desk – The Ultimate Help Desk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.8 via the 'jssupportticketdata' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/uploads/jssupportticketdata directory which can contain file attachments included in support tickets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 09:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13867 | Listivo - Classified Ads WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.3.67 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13867</link><description>The Listivo - Classified Ads WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 's' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.67 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 09:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46910 | Apache Atlas: An authenticated user can perform XSS and potentially impersonate another user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46910</link><description>An authenticated user can perform XSS and potentially impersonate another user.

This issue affects Apache Atlas versions 2.3.0 and earlier.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 09:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3303 | Improper Neutralization of Input Used for LLM Prompting in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3303</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.0 prior to 17.6.5, starting from 17.7 prior to 17.7.4, and starting from 17.8 prior to 17.8.2, which allows an attacker to exfiltrate contents of a private issue using prompt injection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 08:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13639 | Read More &amp;amp; Accordion &amp;lt;= 3.4.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary &amp;#x27;Read More&amp;#x27; Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13639</link><description>The Read More &amp; Accordion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the expmDeleteData() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary 'read more' posts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 08:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13345 | Avada Builder &amp;lt;= 3.11.13 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13345</link><description>The Avada Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 3.11.13. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 07:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13346 | Avada Theme &amp;lt;= 7.11.13 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13346</link><description>The Avada | Website Builder For WordPress &amp; WooCommerce theme for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 7.11.13. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 07:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0661 | DethemeKit For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Protected Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0661</link><description>The DethemeKit For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.36 via the duplicate_post() function due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be duplicated. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from password protected, private, draft, or scheduled posts that they should not have access to by duplicating the post.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 07:19:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0814 | CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause Denial-of-Service of the network
services running on the product whe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0814</link><description>CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause Denial-of-Service of the network
services running on the product when malicious IEC61850-MMS packets are sent to the device. The core
functionality of the breaker remains intact during the attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0815 | CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause Denial-of-Service of the
product when malicious ICMPV6 packets are s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0815</link><description>CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause Denial-of-Service of the
product when malicious ICMPV6 packets are sent to the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0816 | CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause Denial-of-Service of the
product when malicious IPV6 packets are sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0816</link><description>CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause Denial-of-Service of the
product when malicious IPV6 packets are sent to the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47264 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in agent-related functionality in Synology Acti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47264</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in agent-related functionality in Synology Active Backup for Business before 2.7.1-13234, 2.7.1-23234 and 2.7.1-3234 allows remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to delete arbitrary files via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47265 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in encrypted share umount functionality in Syno...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47265</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in encrypted share umount functionality in Synology Active Backup for Business before 2.7.1-13234, 2.7.1-23234 and 2.7.1-3234 allows remote authenticated users to write specific files via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47266 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in share file list functionality in Synology Ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47266</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in share file list functionality in Synology Active Backup for Business before 2.7.1-13234, 2.7.1-23234 and 2.7.1-3234 allows remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to read specific files containing non-sensitive information via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0327 | CWE-269: Improper Privilege Management vulnerability exists for two services (of which one managing audit
trail data and the other acting as...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0327</link><description>CWE-269: Improper Privilege Management vulnerability exists for two services (of which one managing audit
trail data and the other acting as server managing client request) that could cause a loss of Confidentiality,
Integrity and Availability of engineering workstation when an attacker with standard privilege modifies the
executable path of the windows services. To be exploited, services need to be restarted.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12586 | Chalet Montagne Com Tools &amp;lt;= 2.7.8 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12586</link><description>The Chalet-Montagne.com Tools WordPress plugin through 2.7.8 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13119 | ProfilePress &amp;lt; 4.15.20 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13119</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content  WordPress plugin before 4.15.20 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13120 | ProfilePress &amp;lt; 4.15.20 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13120</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content  WordPress plugin before 4.15.20 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13121 | Paid Membership Plugin &amp;lt; 4.15.20 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13121</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content  WordPress plugin before 4.15.20 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13125 | Everest Forms &amp;lt; 3.0.8.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13125</link><description>The Everest Forms  WordPress plugin before 3.0.8.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0692 | Simple Video Management System &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0692</link><description>The Simple Video Management System WordPress plugin through 1.0.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1060 | CWE-319: Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information vulnerability exists that could result in the exposure
of data when network traffic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1060</link><description>CWE-319: Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information vulnerability exists that could result in the exposure
of data when network traffic is being sniffed by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1070 | CWE-434: Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability exists that could render the device
inoperable when a malicious file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1070</link><description>CWE-434: Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability exists that could render the device
inoperable when a malicious file is downloaded.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1059 | CWE-770: Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability exists that could
cause communications to stop when malicious pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1059</link><description>CWE-770: Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability exists that could
cause communications to stop when malicious packets are sent to the webserver of the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 05:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1058 | CWE-494: Download of Code Without Integrity Check vulnerability exists that could render the device
inoperable when malicious firmware is do...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1058</link><description>CWE-494: Download of Code Without Integrity Check vulnerability exists that could render the device
inoperable when malicious firmware is downloaded.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 05:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10083 | CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause denial of service of engineering
workstation when specific driver in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10083</link><description>CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause denial of service of engineering
workstation when specific driver interface is invoked locally by an authenticated user with crafted input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 05:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10763 | Campress &amp;lt;= 1.35 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10763</link><description>The Campress theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.35 via the 'campress_woocommerce_get_ajax_products' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where php file type can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 04:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13227 | Rank Math SEO – AI SEO Tools to Dominate SEO Rankings &amp;lt;= 1.0.235 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Rank Math API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13227</link><description>The Rank Math SEO – AI SEO Tools to Dominate SEO Rankings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Rank Math API in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.235 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 04:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13229 | Rank Math SEO &amp;lt;= 1.0.235 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Schema Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13229</link><description>The Rank Math SEO – AI SEO Tools to Dominate SEO Rankings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the update_metadata() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.235. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete any schema metadata assigned to any post.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 04:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13770 | Puzzles | WP Magazine / Review with Store WordPress Theme + RTL &amp;lt;= 4.2.4 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13770</link><description>The Puzzles | WP Magazine / Review with Store WordPress Theme + RTL theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.4 via deserialization of untrusted input 'view_more_posts' AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present. The developer opted to remove the software from the repository, so an update is not available and it is recommended to find a replacement software.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 04:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0837 | Puzzles &amp;lt;= 4.2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0837</link><description>The Puzzles theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 4.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 04:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13644 | DethemeKit For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via De Gallery Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13644</link><description>The DethemeKit For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's De Gallery widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 02:19:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0896 | Orthanc Server Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0896</link><description>Orthanc server prior to version 1.5.8 does not enable basic authentication by default when remote access is enabled. This could result in unauthorized access by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 02:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1198 | Insufficient Session Expiration in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1198</link><description>An issue discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.11 prior to 17.6.5, 17.7 prior to 17.7.4, and 17.8 prior to 17.8.2 meant that long-lived connections in ActionCable potentially allowed revoked Personal Access Tokens access to streaming results.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 02:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7102 | Execution with Unnecessary Privileges in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7102</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.4 prior to 17.5.0 which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 01:03:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8266 | Execution with Unnecessary Privileges in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8266</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.1 prior to 17.6.0, which allows an attacker with maintainer role to trigger a pipeline as project owner under certain circumstances.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 01:03:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25286 | Crayfish allows Remote Code Execution via Homarus Authorization header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25286</link><description>Crayfish is a collection of Islandora 8 microservices, one of which, Homarus, provides FFmpeg as a microservice. Prior to Crayfish version 4.1.0, remote code execution may be possible in web-accessible installations of Homarus in certain configurations. The issue has been patched in `islandora/crayfish:4.1.0`. Some workarounds are available. The exploit requires making a request against the Homarus's `/convert` endpoint; therefore, the ability to exploit is much reduced if the microservice is not directly accessible from the Internet, so: Prevent general access from the Internet from hitting Homarus. Alternatively or additionally, configure auth in Crayfish to be more strongly required, such that requests with `Authorization` headers that do not validate are rejected before the problematic CLI interpolation occurs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 01:03:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34520 | An authorization bypass vulnerability exists in the Mavenir SCE Application Provisioning Portal, version PORTAL-LBS-R_1_0_24_0, which allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34520</link><description>An authorization bypass vulnerability exists in the Mavenir SCE Application Provisioning Portal, version PORTAL-LBS-R_1_0_24_0, which allows an authenticated 'guest' user to perform unauthorized administrative actions, such as accessing the 'add user' feature, by bypassing client-side access controls.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34521 | A directory traversal vulnerability exists in the Mavenir SCE Application Provisioning Portal, version PORTAL-LBS-R_1_0_24_0, which allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34521</link><description>A directory traversal vulnerability exists in the Mavenir SCE Application Provisioning Portal, version PORTAL-LBS-R_1_0_24_0, which allows an administrative user to access system files with the file permissions of the privileged system user running the application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51376 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in yeqifu carRental v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the file/downloadFi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51376</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in yeqifu carRental v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the file/downloadFile.action?path= component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 22:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-31631 | PDO::quote() may return unquoted string</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31631</link><description>In PHP versions 8.0.* before 8.0.27, 8.1.* before 8.1.15, 8.2.* before 8.2.2 when using PDO::quote() function to quote user-supplied data for SQLite, supplying an overly long string may cause the driver to incorrectly quote the data, which may further lead to SQL injection vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 22:30:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57602 | An issue in Alex Tselegidis EasyAppointments v.1.5.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the index.php file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57602</link><description>An issue in Alex Tselegidis EasyAppointments v.1.5.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the index.php file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 22:30:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57603 | An issue in MaysWind ezBookkeeping 0.7.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the lack of rate limiting.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57603</link><description>An issue in MaysWind ezBookkeeping 0.7.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the lack of rate limiting.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 22:30:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41168 | Use after free in some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi and Killerâ„¢ WiFi software for Windows before version 23.80 may allow an unauthenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41168</link><description>Use after free in some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi and Killerâ„¢ WiFi software for Windows before version 23.80 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 22:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57601 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Alex Tselegidis EasyAppointments v.1.5.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57601</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Alex Tselegidis EasyAppointments v.1.5.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the legal_settings parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 22:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57604 | An issue in MaysWind ezBookkeeping 0.7.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the token component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57604</link><description>An issue in MaysWind ezBookkeeping 0.7.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the token component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 22:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57605 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Daylight Studio Fuel CMS v.1.5.2 allows an attacker to escalate privileges via the /fuel/blocks/ and /...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57605</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Daylight Studio Fuel CMS v.1.5.2 allows an attacker to escalate privileges via the /fuel/blocks/ and /fuel/pages components.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 22:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1229 | olajowon Loggrove page os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1229</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in olajowon Loggrove up to e428fac38cc480f011afcb1d8ce6c2bad378ddd6. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /read/?page=1&amp;amp;logfile=eee&amp;amp;match=. The manipulation of the argument path leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 22:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51440 | An issue in Nothing Tech Nothing OS v.2.6 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the NtBpfService component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51440</link><description>An issue in Nothing Tech Nothing OS v.2.6 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the NtBpfService component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 22:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51122 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Zertificon Z1 SecureMail Z1 CertServer v.3.16.4-2516-debian12 alllows a remote attacker to execute arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51122</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Zertificon Z1 SecureMail Z1 CertServer v.3.16.4-2516-debian12 alllows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ST, L, O, OU, CN parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51123 | An issue in Zertificon Z1 SecureMail Z1 SecureMail Gateway 4.44.2-7240-debian12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51123</link><description>An issue in Zertificon Z1 SecureMail Z1 SecureMail Gateway 4.44.2-7240-debian12 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /compose-pdf.xhtml?convid=[id] component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56938 | LearnDash v6.7.1 was discovered to contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the materials-content class.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56938</link><description>LearnDash v6.7.1 was discovered to contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the materials-content class.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56939 | LearnDash v6.7.1 was discovered to contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the ld-comment-body class.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56939</link><description>LearnDash v6.7.1 was discovered to contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the ld-comment-body class.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56940 | An issue in the profile image upload function of LearnDash v6.7.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via excessive file upl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56940</link><description>An issue in the profile image upload function of LearnDash v6.7.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via excessive file uploads.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46922 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1480 and 2400. The absence of a null check leads to a Denial of Service at amdgpu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46922</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1480 and 2400. The absence of a null check leads to a Denial of Service at amdgpu_cs_parser_bos in the Xclipse Driver.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46923 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 2200, 1480, and 2400. The absence of a null check leads to a Denial of Service at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46923</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 2200, 1480, and 2400. The absence of a null check leads to a Denial of Service at amdgpu_cs_ib_fill in the Xclipse Driver.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1228 | olajowon Loggrove Logfile Update page path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1228</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in olajowon Loggrove up to e428fac38cc480f011afcb1d8ce6c2bad378ddd6. Affected is an unknown function of the file /read/?page=1&amp;amp;logfile=LOG_Monitor of the component Logfile Update Handler. The manipulation of the argument path leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29164 | Improper access control in BMC Firmware for the Intel(R) Server Board S2600WF, Intel(R) Server Board S2600ST, Intel(R) Server Board S2600BP,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29164</link><description>Improper access control in BMC Firmware for the Intel(R) Server Board S2600WF, Intel(R) Server Board S2600ST, Intel(R) Server Board S2600BP, before version 02.01.0017 and Intel(R) Server Board M50CYP and Intel(R) Server Board D50TNP before version R01.01.0009 may allow an authenticated user to enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31276 | Heap-based buffer overflow in BMC Firmware for the Intel(R) Server Board S2600WF, Intel(R) Server Board S2600ST, Intel(R) Server Board S2600...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31276</link><description>Heap-based buffer overflow in BMC Firmware for the Intel(R) Server Board S2600WF, Intel(R) Server Board S2600ST, Intel(R) Server Board S2600BP, before version 02.01.0017 and Intel(R) Server Board M50CYP and Intel(R) Server Board D50TNP before version R01.01.0009 may allow a privileged user to enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32277 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in I/O subsystem for some Intel(R) QAT software before version 2.0.5 may allow authenticated user to potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32277</link><description>Untrusted Pointer Dereference in I/O subsystem for some Intel(R) QAT software before version 2.0.5 may allow authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local operating system access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34440 | Improper input validation in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34440</link><description>Improper input validation in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43758 | Improper input validation in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43758</link><description>Improper input validation in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48267 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) System Security Report and System Resources Defense firmware may allow a privileged user to po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48267</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) System Security Report and System Resources Defense firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48366 | Race condition in some Intel(R) System Security Report and System Resources Defense firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48366</link><description>Race condition in some Intel(R) System Security Report and System Resources Defense firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49603 | Race condition in some Intel(R) System Security Report and System Resources Defense firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49603</link><description>Race condition in some Intel(R) System Security Report and System Resources Defense firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49615 | Improper input validation in some Intel(R) System Security Report and System Resources Defense firmware may allow a privileged user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49615</link><description>Improper input validation in some Intel(R) System Security Report and System Resources Defense firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49618 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) System Security Report and System Resources Defense firmware may allow a privileged user to po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49618</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) System Security Report and System Resources Defense firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21830 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) VPL software before version 2023.4.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21830</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) VPL software before version 2023.4.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21859 | Improper buffer restrictions in the UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21859</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in the UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24582 | Improper input validation in XmlCli feature for UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) processors may allow privileged user to potentially enable e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24582</link><description>Improper input validation in XmlCli feature for UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) processors may allow privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24852 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack install before versions 29.1 may allow an authenticated user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24852</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack install before versions 29.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25571 | Improper input validation in some Intel(R) SPS firmware before SPS_E5_06.01.04.059.0 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25571</link><description>Improper input validation in some Intel(R) SPS firmware before SPS_E5_06.01.04.059.0 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26021 | Improper initialization in the firmware for some Intel(R) AMT and Intel(R) Standard Manageability may allow a privileged user to potentially...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26021</link><description>Improper initialization in the firmware for some Intel(R) AMT and Intel(R) Standard Manageability may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28047 | Improper input validation in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28047</link><description>Improper input validation in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28127 | Improper input validation in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28127</link><description>Improper input validation in UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29214 | Improper input validation in UEFI firmware CseVariableStorageSmm for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially ena...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29214</link><description>Improper input validation in UEFI firmware CseVariableStorageSmm for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29223 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) QuickAssist Technology software before version 2.2.0 may allow an authenticated user to potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29223</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) QuickAssist Technology software before version 2.2.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30211 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) ME driver pack installer engines before version 2422.6.2.0 may allow an authenticated user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30211</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) ME driver pack installer engines before version 2422.6.2.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31068 | Improper Finite State Machines (FSMs) in Hardware Logic for some Intel(R) Processors may allow privileged user to potentially enable denial ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31068</link><description>Improper Finite State Machines (FSMs) in Hardware Logic for some Intel(R) Processors may allow privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31153 | Improper input validation for some Intel(R) QuickAssist Technology software before version 2.2.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31153</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel(R) QuickAssist Technology software before version 2.2.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31155 | Improper buffer restrictions in the UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31155</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in the UEFI firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31157 | Improper initialization in UEFI firmware OutOfBandXML module in some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31157</link><description>Improper initialization in UEFI firmware OutOfBandXML module in some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32938 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) MPI Library for Windows software before version 2021.13 may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32938</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) MPI Library for Windows software before version 2021.13 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32941 | NULL pointer dereference for some Intel(R) MLC software before version v3.11b may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32941</link><description>NULL pointer dereference for some Intel(R) MLC software before version v3.11b may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32942 | Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) DSA installer for Windows before version 24.2.19.5 may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32942</link><description>Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) DSA installer for Windows before version 24.2.19.5 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36262 | Race condition in some Intel(R) System Security Report and System Resources Defense firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36262</link><description>Race condition in some Intel(R) System Security Report and System Resources Defense firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36274 | Out-of-bounds write in the Intel(R) 800 Series Ethernet Driver for Intel(R) Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack before versions 29.1 may a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36274</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in the Intel(R) 800 Series Ethernet Driver for Intel(R) Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack before versions 29.1 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36280 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) High Level Synthesis Compiler software before version 24.2 may allow an authenticated user to pot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36280</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) High Level Synthesis Compiler software before version 24.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36283 | Uncontrolled search path for the Intel(R) Thread Director Visualizer software before version 1.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36283</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for the Intel(R) Thread Director Visualizer software before version 1.0.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36285 | Race condition in some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi and Killerâ„¢ WiFi software for Windows before version 23.80 may allow an authenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36285</link><description>Race condition in some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi and Killerâ„¢ WiFi software for Windows before version 23.80 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36291 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Chipset Software Installation Utility before version 10.1.19867.8574 may allow an authenticated u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36291</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Chipset Software Installation Utility before version 10.1.19867.8574 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36293 | Improper access control in the EDECCSSA user leaf function for some Intel(R) Processors with Intel(R) SGX may allow an authenticated user to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36293</link><description>Improper access control in the EDECCSSA user leaf function for some Intel(R) Processors with Intel(R) SGX may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37020 | Sequence of processor instructions leads to unexpected behavior in the Intel(R) DSA V1.0 for some Intel(R) Xeon(R) Processors may allow an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37020</link><description>Sequence of processor instructions leads to unexpected behavior in the Intel(R) DSA V1.0 for some Intel(R) Xeon(R) Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37355 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Graphics software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37355</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Graphics software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38307 | Improper input validation in the firmware for some Intel(R) AMT and Intel(R) Standard Manageability may allow an authenticated user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38307</link><description>Improper input validation in the firmware for some Intel(R) AMT and Intel(R) Standard Manageability may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38310 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Graphics Driver software installers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38310</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Graphics Driver software installers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39271 | Improper restriction of communication channel to intended endpoints in some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi and Killerâ„¢ WiFi software before...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39271</link><description>Improper restriction of communication channel to intended endpoints in some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi and Killerâ„¢ WiFi software before version 23.80 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39279 | Insufficient granularity of access control in UEFI firmware in some Intel(R) processors may allow a authenticated user to potentially enable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39279</link><description>Insufficient granularity of access control in UEFI firmware in some Intel(R) processors may allow a authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39284 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Advisor software before version 2024.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39284</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Advisor software before version 2024.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39286 | Incorrect execution-assigned permissions in the Linux kernel mode driver for the Intel(R) 800 Series Ethernet Driver before version 1.15.4 m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39286</link><description>Incorrect execution-assigned permissions in the Linux kernel mode driver for the Intel(R) 800 Series Ethernet Driver before version 1.15.4 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39355 | Improper handling of physical or environmental conditions in some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authenticated user to enable denial of se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39355</link><description>Improper handling of physical or environmental conditions in some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authenticated user to enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39356 | NULL pointer dereference in some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi and Killerâ„¢ WiFi software for Windows before version 23.80 may allow an una...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39356</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi and Killerâ„¢ WiFi software for Windows before version 23.80 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39365 | Uncontrolled search path for the FPGA Support Package for the Intel(R) oneAPI DPC++/C++ Compiler software for Windows before version 2024.2 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39365</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for the FPGA Support Package for the Intel(R) oneAPI DPC++/C++ Compiler software for Windows before version 2024.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39372 | Uncontrolled search path for the Intel(R) XTU software for Windows before version 7.14.2.14 may allow an authenticated user to potentially e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39372</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for the Intel(R) XTU software for Windows before version 7.14.2.14 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39606 | Improper input validation in some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi and Killerâ„¢ WiFi software for Windows before version 23.80 may allow an un...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39606</link><description>Improper input validation in some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi and Killerâ„¢ WiFi software for Windows before version 23.80 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39779 | Stack-based buffer overflow in some drivers for Intel(R) Ethernet Connection I219 Series before version 12.19.1.39 may allow an authenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39779</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow in some drivers for Intel(R) Ethernet Connection I219 Series before version 12.19.1.39 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39797 | Improper access control in some drivers for Intel(R) Ethernet Connection I219 Series before version 12.19.1.39 may allow an authenticated us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39797</link><description>Improper access control in some drivers for Intel(R) Ethernet Connection I219 Series before version 12.19.1.39 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39805 | Insufficient verification of data authenticity in some Intel(R) DSA software before version 23.4.39 may allow an authenticated user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39805</link><description>Insufficient verification of data authenticity in some Intel(R) DSA software before version 23.4.39 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39813 | Uncontrolled search path for some EPCT software before version 1.42.8.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39813</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some EPCT software before version 1.42.8.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40887 | Race condition in some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi and Killerâ„¢ WiFi software for Windows before version 23.80 may allow an unauthenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40887</link><description>Race condition in some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi and Killerâ„¢ WiFi software for Windows before version 23.80 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41166 | Stack-based buffer overflow in some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi and Killerâ„¢ WiFi software for Windows before version 23.80 may allow an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41166</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow in some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi and Killerâ„¢ WiFi software for Windows before version 23.80 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41917 | Time-of-check time-of-use race condition for some Intel(R) Battery Life Diagnostic Tool software before version 2.4.1 may allow an authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41917</link><description>Time-of-check time-of-use race condition for some Intel(R) Battery Life Diagnostic Tool software before version 2.4.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41934 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) GPA software before version 2024.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41934</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) GPA software before version 2024.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42405 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Quartus(R) Prime Software before version 23.1.1 Patch 1.01std may allow an authenticated user to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42405</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Quartus(R) Prime Software before version 23.1.1 Patch 1.01std may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42410 | Improper input validation in some Intel(R) Graphics Drivers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42410</link><description>Improper input validation in some Intel(R) Graphics Drivers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42419 | Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) GPA and Intel(R) GPA Framework software installers may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42419</link><description>Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) GPA and Intel(R) GPA Framework software installers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42492 | Uncontrolled search path element in some BIOS and System Firmware Update Package for Intel(R) Server M50FCP family before version R01.02.000...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42492</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element in some BIOS and System Firmware Update Package for Intel(R) Server M50FCP family before version R01.02.0002 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47006 | Uncontrolled search path for the Intel(R) RealSense D400 Series Universal Windows Platform (UWP) Driver for Windows(R) 10 all versions may a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47006</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for the Intel(R) RealSense D400 Series Universal Windows Platform (UWP) Driver for Windows(R) 10 all versions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20097 | Uncaught exception in OpenBMC Firmware for the Intel(R) Server M50FCP Family and Intel(R) Server D50DNP Family before version R01.02.0002 ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20097</link><description>Uncaught exception in OpenBMC Firmware for the Intel(R) Server M50FCP Family and Intel(R) Server D50DNP Family before version R01.02.0002 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31858 | Out-of-bounds write for some Intel(R) QuickAssist Technology software before version 2.2.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially en...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31858</link><description>Out-of-bounds write for some Intel(R) QuickAssist Technology software before version 2.2.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0110 | PAN-OS OpenConfig Plugin: Command Injection Vulnerability in OpenConfig Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0110</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS OpenConfig plugin enables an authenticated administrator with the ability to make gNMI requests to the PAN-OS management web interface to bypass system restrictions and run arbitrary commands. The commands are run as the “__openconfig” user (which has the Device Administrator role) on the firewall.

You can greatly reduce the risk of this issue by restricting access to the management web interface to only trusted internal IP addresses according to our recommended  best practices deployment guidelines https://live.paloaltonetworks.com/t5/community-blogs/tips-amp-tricks-how-to-secure-the-management-access-of-your-palo/ba-p/464431 .</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:16:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0113 | Cortex XDR Broker VM: Unauthorized Access to Broker VM Docker Containers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0113</link><description>A problem with the network isolation mechanism of the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR Broker VM allows attackers unauthorized access to Docker containers from the host network used by Broker VM. This may allow access to read files sent for analysis and logs transmitted by the Cortex XDR Agent to the Cortex XDR server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:16:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0108 | PAN-OS: Authentication Bypass in the Management Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0108</link><description>An authentication bypass in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an unauthenticated attacker with network access to the management web interface to bypass the authentication otherwise required by the PAN-OS management web interface and invoke certain PHP scripts. While invoking these PHP scripts does not enable remote code execution, it can negatively impact integrity and confidentiality of PAN-OS.

You can greatly reduce the risk of this issue by restricting access to the management web interface to only trusted internal IP addresses according to our recommended  best practices deployment guidelines https://live.paloaltonetworks.com/t5/community-blogs/tips-amp-tricks-how-to-secure-the-management-access-of-your-palo/ba-p/464431 .

This issue does not affect Cloud NGFW or Prisma Access software.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:16:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0109 | PAN-OS: Unauthenticated File Deletion Vulnerability on the Management Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0109</link><description>An unauthenticated file deletion vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS management web interface enables an unauthenticated attacker with network access to the management web interface to delete certain files as the “nobody” user; this includes limited logs and configuration files but does not include system files.


You can greatly reduce the risk of this issue by restricting access to the management web interface to only trusted internal IP addresses according to our recommended  best practices deployment guidelines https://live.paloaltonetworks.com/t5/community-blogs/tips-amp-tricks-how-to-secure-the-management-access-of-your-palo/ba-p/464431 .

This issue does not affect Cloud NGFW or Prisma Access software.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0111 | PAN-OS: Authenticated File Read Vulnerability in the Management Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0111</link><description>An authenticated file read vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated attacker with network access to the management web interface to read files on the PAN-OS filesystem that are readable by the “nobody” user.

You can greatly reduce the risk of this issue by restricting access to the management web interface to only trusted internal IP addresses according to our recommended  best practices deployment guidelines https://live.paloaltonetworks.com/t5/community-blogs/tips-amp-tricks-how-to-secure-the-management-access-of-your-palo/ba-p/464431 .



This issue does not affect Cloud NGFW or Prisma Access software.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1227 | ywoa AddressDao.xml selectList sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1227</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ywoa up to 2024.07.03. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function selectList of the file com/cloudweb/oa/mapper/xml/AddressDao.xml. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2024.07.04 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12673 | An improper privilege vulnerability was reported in a BIOS customization feature of Lenovo Vantage on SMB notebook devices which could allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12673</link><description>An improper privilege vulnerability was reported in a BIOS customization feature of Lenovo Vantage on SMB notebook devices which could allow a local attacker to elevate privileges on the system.

This vulnerability only affects Vantage installed on these devices:

  *  Lenovo V Series (Gen 5)
  *  ThinkBook 14 (Gen 6, 7)
  *  ThinkBook 16 (Gen 6, 7)
  *  ThinkPad E Series (Gen 1)</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 20:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1226 | ywoa setup.jsp improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1226</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ywoa up to 2024.07.03. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /oa/setup/setup.jsp. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2024.07.04 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 20:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1225 | ywoa WXCallBack Interface XMLParse.java extract xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1225</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in ywoa up to 2024.07.03. This issue affects the function extract of the file c-main/src/main/java/com/redmoon/weixin/aes/XMLParse.java of the component WXCallBack Interface. The manipulation leads to xml external entity reference. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2024.07.04 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 20:10:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1224 | ywoa UserMapper.xml listNameBySql sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1224</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in ywoa up to 2024.07.03. This vulnerability affects the function listNameBySql of the file com/cloudweb/oa/mapper/xml/UserMapper.xml. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2024.07.04 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 19:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1216 | ywoa OaNoticeMapper.xml selectNoticeList sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1216</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ywoa up to 2024.07.03. This issue affects the function selectNoticeList of the file com/cloudweb/oa/mapper/xml/OaNoticeMapper.xml. The manipulation of the argument sort leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2024.07.04 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 19:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0937 | Nomad Vulnerable To Event Stream Namespace ACL Policy Bypass Through Wildcard Namespace</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0937</link><description>Nomad Community and Nomad Enterprise ("Nomad") event stream configured with a wildcard namespace can bypass the ACL Policy allowing reads on other namespaces.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 19:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1215 | vim main.c memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1215</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in vim up to 9.1.1096. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file src/main.c. The manipulation of the argument --log leads to memory corruption. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. Upgrading to version 9.1.1097 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as c5654b84480822817bb7b69ebc97c174c91185e9. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 18:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25343 | Tenda AC6 V15.03.05.16 firmware has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the formexeCommand function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25343</link><description>Tenda AC6 V15.03.05.16 firmware has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the formexeCommand function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 18:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1146 | CrowdStrike Falcon Sensor for Linux TLS Issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1146</link><description>CrowdStrike uses industry-standard TLS (transport layer security) to secure communications from the Falcon sensor to the CrowdStrike cloud. CrowdStrike has identified a validation logic error in the Falcon sensor for Linux, Falcon Kubernetes Admission Controller, and Falcon Container Sensor where our TLS connection routine to the CrowdStrike cloud can incorrectly process server certificate validation. This could allow an attacker with the ability to control network traffic to potentially conduct a man-in-the-middle (MiTM) attack. CrowdStrike identified this issue internally and released a security fix in all Falcon sensor for Linux, Falcon Kubernetes Admission Controller, and Falcon Container Sensor versions 7.06 and above.

 
CrowdStrike identified this issue through our longstanding, rigorous security review process, which has been continually strengthened with deeper source code analysis and ongoing program enhancements as part of our commitment to security resilience. CrowdStrike has no indication of any exploitation of this issue in the wild. CrowdStrike has leveraged its world class threat hunting and intelligence capabilities to actively monitor for signs of abuse or usage of this flaw and will continue to do so. 


Windows and Mac sensors are not affected by this.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25283 | parse-duraton vulnerable to Regex Denial of Service that results in event loop delay and out of memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25283</link><description>parse-duraton is software that allows users to convert a human readable duration to milliseconds. Versions prior to 2.1.3 are vulnerable to an event loop delay due to the CPU-bound operation of resolving the provided string, from a 0.5ms and up to ~50ms per one operation, with a varying size from 0.01 MB and up to 4.3 MB respectively, and an out of memory that would crash a running Node.js application due to a string size of roughly 10 MB that utilizes unicode characters. Version 2.1.3 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 18:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25201 | Improper Validation of Admin Key in PIV Smartcard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25201</link><description>Nitrokey 3 Firmware is the the firmware of Nitrokey 3 USB keys. For release 1.8.0, and test releases with PIV enabled prior to 1.8.0, the PIV application could accept invalid keys for authentication of the admin key. This could lead to compromise of the integrity of the data stored in the application. An attacker without access to the proper administration key would be able to generate new keys and overwrite certificates. Such an attacker would not be able to read-out or extract existing private data, nor would they be able to gain access to cryptographic operations that would normally require PIN-based authentication. The issue is fixed in piv-authenticator 0.3.9, and in Nitrokey's firmware 1.8.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 18:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25205 | Remote Authentication-Bypass can lead to server crash or limited information disclosure due to faulty pattern matching</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25205</link><description>Audiobookshelf is a self-hosted audiobook and podcast server. Starting in version 2.17.0 and prior to version 2.19.1, a flaw in the authentication bypass logic allows unauthenticated requests to match certain unanchored regex patterns in the URL. Attackers can craft URLs containing substrings like "/api/items/1/cover" in a query parameter (?r=/api/items/1/cover) to partially bypass authentication or trigger server crashes under certain routes. This could lead to information disclosure of otherwise protected data and, in some cases, a complete denial of service (server crash) if downstream code expects an authenticated user object. Version 2.19.1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 18:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1214 | pihome-shc PiHome Role-Based Access Control user_accounts.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1214</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in pihome-shc PiHome 2.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /user_accounts.php?uid of the component Role-Based Access Control. The manipulation leads to missing authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 18:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25200 | Koa has Inefficient Regular Expression Complexity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25200</link><description>Koa is expressive middleware for Node.js using ES2017 async functions. Prior to versions 0.21.2, 1.7.1, 2.15.4, and 3.0.0-alpha.3, Koa uses an evil regex to parse the `X-Forwarded-Proto` and `X-Forwarded-Host` HTTP headers. This can be exploited to carry out a Denial-of-Service attack. Versions 0.21.2, 1.7.1, 2.15.4, and 3.0.0-alpha.3 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 18:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25198 | mailcow: dockerized vulnerable to password reset poisoning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25198</link><description>mailcow: dockerized is an open source groupware/email suite based on docker. Prior to version 2025-01a, a vulnerability in mailcow's password reset functionality allows an attacker to manipulate the `Host HTTP` header to generate a password reset link pointing to an attacker-controlled domain. This can lead to account takeover if a user clicks the poisoned link. Version 2025-01a contains a patch. As a workaround, deactivate the password reset functionality by clearing `Notification email sender` and `Notification email subject` under System -&gt; Configuration -&gt; Options -&gt; Password Settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 17:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25199 | BCryptGenerateSymmetricKey memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25199</link><description>go-crypto-winnative Go crypto backend for Windows using Cryptography API: Next Generation (CNG). Prior to commit f49c8e1379ea4b147d5bff1b3be5b0ff45792e41, calls to `cng.TLS1PRF` don't release the key handle, producing a small memory leak every time. Commit f49c8e1379ea4b147d5bff1b3be5b0ff45792e41 contains a fix for the issue. The fix is included in versions 1.23.6-2 and 1.22.12-2 of the Microsoft build of go, as well as in the pseudoversion 0.0.0-20250211154640-f49c8e1379ea of the `github.com/microsoft/go-crypto-winnative` Go package.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 17:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6097 | Absolute Path Traversal Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6097</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Reporting versions prior to 2025 Q1 (19.0.25.211), information disclosure is possible by a local threat actor through an absolute path vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 17:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1213 | pihome-shc PiHome index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1213</link><description>A vulnerability was found in pihome-shc PiHome 1.77. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument $_SERVER['PHP_SELF'] leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 17:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25741 | D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the IPv6_PppoePassword parameter in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25741</link><description>D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the IPv6_PppoePassword parameter in the SetIPv6PppoeSettings module.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 17:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1210 | code-projects Wazifa System control.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1210</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Wazifa System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /controllers/control.php. The manipulation of the argument to leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 17:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25743 | D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the SetVirtualServerSettings module.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25743</link><description>D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the SetVirtualServerSettings module.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 17:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25744 | D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the Password parameter in the SetDynam...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25744</link><description>D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the Password parameter in the SetDynamicDNSSettings module.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 17:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25742 | D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the AccountPassword parameter in the S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25742</link><description>D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the AccountPassword parameter in the SetSysEmailSettings module.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 16:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25746 | D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the Password parameter in the SetWanSe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25746</link><description>D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the Password parameter in the SetWanSettings module.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 16:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1209 | code-projects Wazifa System search_resualts.php searchuser cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1209</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in code-projects Wazifa System 1.0. Affected is the function searchuser of the file /search_resualts.php. The manipulation of the argument firstname/lastname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. There is a typo in the affected file name.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 16:47:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11628 | Prototype Pollution in Progress® Telerik® Kendo UI for Vue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11628</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Kendo UI for Vue versions v2.4.0 through v6.0.1, an attacker can introduce or modify properties within the global prototype chain which can result in denial of service or command injection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 16:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11629 | Telerik Document Processing RTF Export of Arbitrary File Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11629</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Document Processing Libraries, versions prior to 2025 Q1 (2025.1.205), using .NET Standard 2.0, the contents of a file at an arbitrary path can be exported to RTF.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 16:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25182 | Stroom Authentication/Authorization Bypass when using AWS ALB</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25182</link><description>Stroom is a data processing, storage and analysis platform. A vulnerability exists starting in version 7.2-beta.53 and prior to versions 7.2.24, 7.3-beta.22, 7.4.4, and 7.5-beta.2 that allows authentication bypass to a Stroom system when configured with ALB and installed in a way that the application is accessible not through the ALB itself. This vulnerability may also allow for server-side request forgery which may lead to code execution or further privileges escalations when using the AWS metadata URL. This scenario assumes that Stroom must be configured to use ALB Authentication integration and the application is network accessible. The vulnerability has been fixed in versions 7.2.24, 7.3-beta.22, 7.4.4, and 7.5-beta.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 16:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25184 | Possible Log Injection in Rack::CommonLogger</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25184</link><description>Rack provides an interface for developing web applications in Ruby. Prior to versions 2.2.11, 3.0.12, and 3.1.11, Rack::CommonLogger can be exploited by crafting input that includes newline characters to manipulate log entries. The supplied proof-of-concept demonstrates injecting malicious content into logs. When a user provides the authorization credentials via Rack::Auth::Basic, if success, the username will be put in env['REMOTE_USER'] and later be used by Rack::CommonLogger for logging purposes. The issue occurs when a server intentionally or unintentionally allows a user creation with the username contain CRLF and white space characters, or the server just want to log every login attempts. If an attacker enters a username with CRLF character, the logger will log the malicious username with CRLF characters into the logfile. Attackers can break log formats or insert fraudulent entries, potentially obscuring real activity or injecting malicious data into log files. Versions 2.2.11, 3.0.12, and 3.1.11 contain a fix.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 16:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1208 | code-projects Wazifa System Profile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1208</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Wazifa System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Profile.php. The manipulation of the argument postcontent leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 16:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11343 | Telerik Document Processing Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11343</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Document Processing Libraries, versions prior to 2025 Q1 (2025.1.205), unzipping an archive can lead to arbitrary file system access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25349 | PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker System v1.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /dets/add-expense.php via the costitem parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25349</link><description>PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker System v1.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /dets/add-expense.php via the costitem parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25351 | PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker System v1.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /dets/add-expense.php via the dateexpense parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25351</link><description>PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker System v1.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /dets/add-expense.php via the dateexpense parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12629 | Prototype Pollution in Progress® Telerik® KendoReact</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12629</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® KendoReact versions v3.5.0 through v9.4.0, an attacker can introduce or modify properties within the global prototype chain which can result in denial of service or command injection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1207 | phjounin TFTPD64 DNS denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1207</link><description>A vulnerability was found in phjounin TFTPD64 4.64. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component DNS Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack needs to be done within the local network. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9870 | Unintended Proxy or Intermediary (&amp;#x27;Confused Deputy&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9870</link><description>An external service interaction vulnerability in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 15.11 prior to 17.6.5, 17.7 prior to 17.7.4, and 17.8 prior to 17.8.2 allows an attacker to send requests from the GitLab server to unintended services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0516 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0516</link><description>Improper Authorization in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 17.7 prior to 17.7.4, 17.8 prior to 17.8.2 allow users with limited permissions to perform unauthorized actions on critical project data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0332 | Progress UI for WinForms decompression path traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0332</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® UI for WinForms, versions prior to 2025 Q1 (2025.1.211), using the improper limitation of a target path can lead to decompressing an archive's content into a restricted directory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0556 | Telerik Report Server Clear Text Transmission of Agent Commands</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0556</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Report Server, versions prior to 2025 Q1 (11.0.25.211) when using the older .NET Framework implementation, communication of non-sensitive information between the service agent process and app host process occurs over an unencrypted tunnel, which can be subjected to local network traffic sniffing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12251 | Improper neutralization special element in hyperlinks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12251</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® UI for WinUI versions prior to 2025 Q1 (3.0.0), a command injection attack is possible through improper neutralization of hyperlink elements.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12379 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12379</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 14.1 prior to 17.6.5, 17.7 prior to 17.7.4, and 17.8 prior to 17.8.2 allows an attacker to impact the availability of GitLab via unbounded symbol creation via the scopes parameter in a Personal Access Token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0376 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0376</link><description>An XSS vulnerability exists in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 13.3 prior to 17.6.5, 17.7 prior to 17.7.4 and 17.8 prior to 17.8.2 that allows an attacker to execute unauthorized actions via a change page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1212 | Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1212</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 8.3 prior to 17.6.5, 17.7 prior to 17.7.4, and 17.8 prior to 17.8.2 allows an attacker to send a crafted request to a backend server to reveal sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1042 | Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1042</link><description>An insecure direct object reference vulnerability in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 15.7 prior to 17.6.5, 17.7 prior to 17.7.4, and 17.8 prior to 17.8.2 allows an attacker to view repositories in an unauthorized way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:14:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1206 | Codezips Gym Management System viewdetailroutine.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1206</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Gym Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /dashboard/admin/viewdetailroutine.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:14:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1202 | SourceCodester Best Church Management Software edit_slider.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1202</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Best Church Management Software 1.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_slider.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 14:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54160 | dashboards-reporting (aka Dashboards Reports) before 2.19.0.0, as shipped in OpenSearch before 2.19, allows XSS because Markdown is not sani...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54160</link><description>dashboards-reporting (aka Dashboards Reports) before 2.19.0.0, as shipped in OpenSearch before 2.19, allows XSS because Markdown is not sanitized when previewing a header or footer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1244 | Emacs: shell injection vulnerability in gnu emacs via custom &amp;quot;man&amp;quot; uri scheme</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1244</link><description>A flaw was found in the Emacs text editor. Improper handling of custom "man" URI schemes allows attackers to execute arbitrary shell commands by tricking users into visiting a specially crafted website or an HTTP URL with a redirect.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 14:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1201 | SourceCodester Best Church Management Software profile_crud.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1201</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Church Management Software 1.1. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/app/profile_crud.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Multiple parameters might be affected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 14:18:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23563 | HCL Connections Docs is vulnerable to a sensitive information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23563</link><description>HCL Connections Docs is vulnerable to a sensitive information disclosure which could allow a user to obtain sensitive information they are not entitled to, caused by improper handling of request data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 14:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57952 | Revert &amp;quot;libfs: fix infinite directory reads for offset dir&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57952</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Revert "libfs: fix infinite directory reads for offset dir"

The current directory offset allocator (based on mtree_alloc_cyclic)
stores the next offset value to return in octx-&gt;next_offset. This
mechanism typically returns values that increase monotonically over
time. Eventually, though, the newly allocated offset value wraps
back to a low number (say, 2) which is smaller than other already-
allocated offset values.

Yu Kuai  reports that, after commit 64a7ce76fb90
("libfs: fix infinite directory reads for offset dir"), if a
directory's offset allocator wraps, existing entries are no longer
visible via readdir/getdents because offset_readdir() stops listing
entries once an entry's offset is larger than octx-&gt;next_offset.
These entries vanish persistently -- they can be looked up, but will
never again appear in readdir(3) output.

The reason for this is that the commit treats directory offsets as
monotonically increasing integer values rather than opaque cookies,
and introduces this comparison:

	if (dentry2offset(dentry) &gt;= last_index) {

On 64-bit platforms, the directory offset value upper bound is
2^63 - 1. Directory offsets will monotonically increase for millions
of years without wrapping.

On 32-bit platforms, however, LONG_MAX is 2^31 - 1. The allocator
can wrap after only a few weeks (at worst).

Revert commit 64a7ce76fb90 ("libfs: fix infinite directory reads for
offset dir") to prepare for a fix that can work properly on 32-bit
systems and might apply to recent LTS kernels where shmem employs
the simple_offset mechanism.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 14:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21698 | Revert &amp;quot;usb: gadget: u_serial: Disable ep before setting port to null to fix the crash caused by port being null&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21698</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Revert "usb: gadget: u_serial: Disable ep before setting port to null to fix the crash caused by port being null"

This reverts commit 13014969cbf07f18d62ceea40bd8ca8ec9d36cec.

It is reported to cause crashes on Tegra systems, so revert it for now.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 14:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21699 | gfs2: Truncate address space when flipping GFS2_DIF_JDATA flag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21699</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

gfs2: Truncate address space when flipping GFS2_DIF_JDATA flag

Truncate an inode's address space when flipping the GFS2_DIF_JDATA flag:
depending on that flag, the pages in the address space will either use
buffer heads or iomap_folio_state structs, and we cannot mix the two.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 14:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57951 | hrtimers: Handle CPU state correctly on hotplug</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57951</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

hrtimers: Handle CPU state correctly on hotplug

Consider a scenario where a CPU transitions from CPUHP_ONLINE to halfway
through a CPU hotunplug down to CPUHP_HRTIMERS_PREPARE, and then back to
CPUHP_ONLINE:

Since hrtimers_prepare_cpu() does not run, cpu_base.hres_active remains set
to 1 throughout. However, during a CPU unplug operation, the tick and the
clockevents are shut down at CPUHP_AP_TICK_DYING. On return to the online
state, for instance CFS incorrectly assumes that the hrtick is already
active, and the chance of the clockevent device to transition to oneshot
mode is also lost forever for the CPU, unless it goes back to a lower state
than CPUHP_HRTIMERS_PREPARE once.

This round-trip reveals another issue; cpu_base.online is not set to 1
after the transition, which appears as a WARN_ON_ONCE in enqueue_hrtimer().

Aside of that, the bulk of the per CPU state is not reset either, which
means there are dangling pointers in the worst case.

Address this by adding a corresponding startup() callback, which resets the
stale per CPU state and sets the online flag.

[ tglx: Make the new callback unconditionally available, remove the online
  	modification in the prepare() callback and clear the remaining
  	state in the starting callback instead of the prepare callback ]</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1200 | SourceCodester Best Church Management Software slider_crud.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1200</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Church Management Software 1.1. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/app/slider_crud.php. The manipulation of the argument del_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21694 | fs/proc: fix softlockup in __read_vmcore (part 2)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21694</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fs/proc: fix softlockup in __read_vmcore (part 2)

Since commit 5cbcb62dddf5 ("fs/proc: fix softlockup in __read_vmcore") the
number of softlockups in __read_vmcore at kdump time have gone down, but
they still happen sometimes.

In a memory constrained environment like the kdump image, a softlockup is
not just a harmless message, but it can interfere with things like RCU
freeing memory, causing the crashdump to get stuck.

The second loop in __read_vmcore has a lot more opportunities for natural
sleep points, like scheduling out while waiting for a data write to
happen, but apparently that is not always enough.

Add a cond_resched() to the second loop in __read_vmcore to (hopefully)
get rid of the softlockups.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21695 | platform/x86: dell-uart-backlight: fix serdev race</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21695</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

platform/x86: dell-uart-backlight: fix serdev race

The dell_uart_bl_serdev_probe() function calls devm_serdev_device_open()
before setting the client ops via serdev_device_set_client_ops(). This
ordering can trigger a NULL pointer dereference in the serdev controller's
receive_buf handler, as it assumes serdev-&gt;ops is valid when
SERPORT_ACTIVE is set.

This is similar to the issue fixed in commit 5e700b384ec1
("platform/chrome: cros_ec_uart: properly fix race condition") where
devm_serdev_device_open() was called before fully initializing the
device.

Fix the race by ensuring client ops are set before enabling the port via
devm_serdev_device_open().

Note, serdev_device_set_baudrate() and serdev_device_set_flow_control()
calls should be after the devm_serdev_device_open() call.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21696 | mm: clear uffd-wp PTE/PMD state on mremap()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21696</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: clear uffd-wp PTE/PMD state on mremap()

When mremap()ing a memory region previously registered with userfaultfd as
write-protected but without UFFD_FEATURE_EVENT_REMAP, an inconsistency in
flag clearing leads to a mismatch between the vma flags (which have
uffd-wp cleared) and the pte/pmd flags (which do not have uffd-wp
cleared).  This mismatch causes a subsequent mprotect(PROT_WRITE) to
trigger a warning in page_table_check_pte_flags() due to setting the pte
to writable while uffd-wp is still set.

Fix this by always explicitly clearing the uffd-wp pte/pmd flags on any
such mremap() so that the values are consistent with the existing clearing
of VM_UFFD_WP.  Be careful to clear the logical flag regardless of its
physical form; a PTE bit, a swap PTE bit, or a PTE marker.  Cover PTE,
huge PMD and hugetlb paths.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21697 | drm/v3d: Ensure job pointer is set to NULL after job completion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21697</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/v3d: Ensure job pointer is set to NULL after job completion

After a job completes, the corresponding pointer in the device must
be set to NULL. Failing to do so triggers a warning when unloading
the driver, as it appears the job is still active. To prevent this,
assign the job pointer to NULL after completing the job, indicating
the job has finished.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26339 | A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxtime/handleRoute.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26339</link><description>A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxtime/handleRoute.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to affect the device confidentiality, integrity, or availability in multiple unspecified ways via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26340 | A CWE-321 "Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key" in the JWT signing in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26340</link><description>A CWE-321 "Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key" in the JWT signing in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to bypass the authentication via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26341 | A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/accounts/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26341</link><description>A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/accounts/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to reset arbitrary user passwords via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26342 | A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/accounts/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26342</link><description>A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/accounts/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to create arbitrary users, including administrators, via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26343 | A CWE-1390 "Weak Authentication" in the PIN authentication mechanism in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26343</link><description>A CWE-1390 "Weak Authentication" in the PIN authentication mechanism in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to brute-force user PINs via multiple crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26344 | A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/guest-mode/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26344</link><description>A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/guest-mode/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to enable passwordless guest mode via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26345 | A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/menu/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26345</link><description>A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/menu/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to edit user group permissions via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26346 | A CWE-89 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection')" in maxprofile/menu/model.lua (editUserGroupM...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26346</link><description>A CWE-89 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection')" in maxprofile/menu/model.lua (editUserGroupMenu endpoint) in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26347 | A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/menu/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26347</link><description>A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/menu/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to edit user permissions via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26348 | A CWE-89 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection')" in maxprofile/menu/model.lua (editUserMenu e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26348</link><description>A CWE-89 "Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection')" in maxprofile/menu/model.lua (editUserMenu endpoint) in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26349 | A CWE-23 "Relative Path Traversal" in the file upload mechanism in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26349</link><description>A CWE-23 "Relative Path Traversal" in the file upload mechanism in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated remote attacker to overwrite arbitrary files via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26350 | A CWE-434 "Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type" in the template file uploads in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26350</link><description>A CWE-434 "Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type" in the template file uploads in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated remote attacker to upload malicious files via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26351 | A CWE-35 "Path Traversal" in the template download mechanism in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26351</link><description>A CWE-35 "Path Traversal" in the template download mechanism in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated remote attacker to read sensitive files via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26352 | A CWE-35 "Path Traversal" in the template deletion mechanism in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26352</link><description>A CWE-35 "Path Traversal" in the template deletion mechanism in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated remote attacker to delete sensitive files via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26353 | A CWE-35 "Path Traversal" in maxtime/api/sql/sql.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated remote a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26353</link><description>A CWE-35 "Path Traversal" in maxtime/api/sql/sql.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated remote attacker to read sensitive files via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26354 | A CWE-35 "Path Traversal" in maxtime/api/database/database.lua (copy endpoint) in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26354</link><description>A CWE-35 "Path Traversal" in maxtime/api/database/database.lua (copy endpoint) in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated remote attacker to overwrite sensitive files via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26355 | A CWE-35 "Path Traversal" in maxtime/api/database/database.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26355</link><description>A CWE-35 "Path Traversal" in maxtime/api/database/database.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated remote attacker to delete sensitive files via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26356 | A CWE-35 "Path Traversal" in maxtime/api/database/database.lua (setActive endpoint) in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26356</link><description>A CWE-35 "Path Traversal" in maxtime/api/database/database.lua (setActive endpoint) in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated remote attacker to overwrite sensitive files via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26357 | A CWE-35 "Path Traversal" in maxtime/api/database/database.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26357</link><description>A CWE-35 "Path Traversal" in maxtime/api/database/database.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated remote attacker to read sensitive files via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26358 | A CWE-20 "Improper Input Validation" in ldbMT.so in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated remote attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26358</link><description>A CWE-20 "Improper Input Validation" in ldbMT.so in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated remote attacker to modify system configuration via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26359 | A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/accounts/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26359</link><description>A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/accounts/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to reset user PINs via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26360 | A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/persistance/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26360</link><description>A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/persistance/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to delete dashboards via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26361 | A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/setup/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26361</link><description>A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/setup/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to factory reset the device via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26362 | A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/setup/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26362</link><description>A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/setup/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to set an arbitrary authentication profile server via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26363 | A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/setup/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26363</link><description>A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/setup/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to enable an authentication profile server via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26364 | A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/setup/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26364</link><description>A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/setup/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to disable an authentication profile server via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26365 | A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/setup/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26365</link><description>A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/setup/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to enable front panel authentication via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26366 | A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/setup/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26366</link><description>A CWE-306 "Missing Authentication for Critical Function" in maxprofile/setup/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to disable front panel authentication via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26367 | A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/user-groups/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26367</link><description>A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/user-groups/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to create arbitrary user groups via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26368 | A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/user-groups/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26368</link><description>A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/user-groups/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to remove user groups via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26369 | A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/user-groups/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26369</link><description>A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/user-groups/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to add privileges to user groups via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26370 | A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/user-groups/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26370</link><description>A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/user-groups/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to remove privileges from user groups via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26371 | A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/user-groups/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26371</link><description>A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/user-groups/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to add users to groups via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26372 | A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/user-groups/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26372</link><description>A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/user-groups/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to remove users from groups via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26373 | A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/users/routes.lua (user endpoint) in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26373</link><description>A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/users/routes.lua (user endpoint) in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to enumerate users via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26374 | A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/users/routes.lua (users endpoint) in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26374</link><description>A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/users/routes.lua (users endpoint) in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to enumerate users via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26375 | A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/users/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26375</link><description>A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/users/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to create users with arbitrary privileges via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26376 | A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/users/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26376</link><description>A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/users/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to modify user data via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26377 | A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/users/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26377</link><description>A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/users/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to remove users via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26378 | A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/users/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26378</link><description>A CWE-862 "Missing Authorization" in maxprofile/users/routes.lua in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to reset passwords, including the ones of administrator accounts, via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1100 | A CWE-259 "Use of Hard-coded Password" for the root account in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1100</link><description>A CWE-259 "Use of Hard-coded Password" for the root account in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges via SSH.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1101 | A CWE-204 "Observable Response Discrepancy" in the login page in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1101</link><description>A CWE-204 "Observable Response Discrepancy" in the login page in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to enumerate valid usernames via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1102 | A CWE-346 "Origin Validation Error" in the CORS configuration in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1102</link><description>A CWE-346 "Origin Validation Error" in the CORS configuration in Q-Free MaxTime less than or equal to version 2.11.0 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to affect the device confidentiality, integrity, or availability via crafted URLs or HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1199 | SourceCodester Best Church Management Software role_crud.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1199</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Church Management Software 1.1. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/app/role_crud.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:27:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10322 | Brizy – Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.6.8 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10322</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via REST API SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 12:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1197 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System load_user-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1197</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /_parse/load_user-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument userhash leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 12:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1196 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System search.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1196</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /search.php. The manipulation of the argument PropertyName leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 12:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1195 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System EditCategory cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1195</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Admin/EditCategory. The manipulation of the argument CategoryId leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 11:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10960 | Brizy – Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.6.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload via storeUploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10960</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'storeUploads' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 11:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12386 | WP Abstracts &amp;lt;= 2.7.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Account Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12386</link><description>The WP Abstracts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.3. This is due to missing nonce validation on multiple functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary accounts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 11:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13477 | LTL Freight Quotes – Unishippers Edition &amp;lt;= 2.5.8 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13477</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – Unishippers Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'edit_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.8 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 11:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13480 | LTL Freight Quotes – For Customers of FedEx Freight  &amp;lt;= 3.4.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13480</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – For Customers of FedEx Freight plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'edit_id' and 'dropship_edit_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 11:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13532 | Small Package Quotes – Purolator Edition &amp;lt;= 3.6.4 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13532</link><description>The Small Package Quotes – Purolator Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'edit_id' and 'dropship_edit_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 11:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0511 | Welcart e-Commerce &amp;lt;= 2.11.9 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via name Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0511</link><description>The Welcart e-Commerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘name’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.11.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 11:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1192 | SourceCodester Multi Restaurant Table Reservation System select-menu.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1192</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Multi Restaurant Table Reservation System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file select-menu.php. The manipulation of the argument table leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 11:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1230 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Prestashop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1230</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Prestashop 8.1.7, due to the lack of proper validation of user input through ‘//index.php’, affecting the ‘link’ parameter. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal their cookie session details.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 10:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1191 | SourceCodester Multi Restaurant Table Reservation System approve-reject.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1191</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Multi Restaurant Table Reservation System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /dashboard/approve-reject.php. The manipulation of the argument breject_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 10:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1190 | code-projects Job Recruitment load_user-profile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1190</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /_parse/load_user-profile.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. Multiple parameters might be affected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 10:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32838 | Apache Fineract: SQL injection vulnerabilities in offices API endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32838</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in various API endpoints - offices, dashboards, etc. Apache Fineract versions 1.9 and before have a vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker to inject malicious data into some of the REST API endpoints' query parameter. 
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.10.1, which fixes this issue.

A SQL Validator has been implemented which allows us to configure a series of tests and checks against our SQL queries that will allow us to validate and protect against nearly all potential SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1189 | 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System chart1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1189</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/chart1.php. The manipulation of the argument course_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12213 | WP Job Board Pro &amp;lt;= 1.2.76 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via process_register</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12213</link><description>The WP Job Board Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.76. This is due to the plugin allowing a user to supply the 'role' field when registering. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register as an administrator on vulnerable sites.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12296 | Apus Framework &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update in import_page_options</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12296</link><description>The Apus Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the 'import_page_options' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 09:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13365 | Security &amp;amp; Malware scan by CleanTalk &amp;lt;= 2.149 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13365</link><description>The Security &amp; Malware scan by CleanTalk plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to the plugin uploading and extracting .zip archives when scanning them for malware through the checkUploadedArchive() function  in all versions up to, and including, 2.149. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 09:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13435 | Ebook Downloader &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13435</link><description>The Ebook Downloader plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'download' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 09:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13437 | Book a Room &amp;lt;= 2.9 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13437</link><description>The Book a Room plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.9. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'bookaroom_Settings' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 09:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13456 | Easy Quiz Maker &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13456</link><description>The Easy Quiz Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wqt-question' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 09:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13459 | FuseDesk &amp;lt;= 6.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13459</link><description>The FuseDesk plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'fusedesk_newcase' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 6.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 09:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13473 | LTL Freight Quotes - Worldwide Express Edition &amp;lt;= 5.0.20 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13473</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – Worldwide Express Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'dropship_edit_id' and 'edit_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.20 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 09:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13475 | Small Package Quotes – UPS Edition &amp;lt;= 4.5.16 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13475</link><description>The Small Package Quotes – UPS Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'edit_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.16 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 09:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13490 | LTL Freight Quotes – XPO Edition &amp;lt;= 4.3.7 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13490</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – XPO Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'edit_id' and 'dropship_edit_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 09:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13528 | Customer Email Verification for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.9.5 - Authentication Bypass via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13528</link><description>The Customer Email Verification for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.5. This is due to the presence of a shortcode that will generate a confirmation link with a placeholder email. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to generate a verification link for any unverified user and log into the account. The 'Fine tune placement' option must be enabled in the plugin settings in order to exploit the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 09:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13531 | ShipEngine Shipping Quotes &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13531</link><description>The ShipEngine Shipping Quotes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'edit_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 09:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0506 | Rise Blocks – A Complete Gutenberg Page Builder &amp;lt;= 3.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via TitleTag Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0506</link><description>The Rise Blocks – A Complete Gutenberg Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the titleTag parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 09:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1188 | Codezips Gym Management System updateroutine.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1188</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Codezips Gym Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /dashboard/admin/updateroutine.php. The manipulation of the argument tid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 09:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1187 | code-projects Police FIR Record Management System Delete Record stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1187</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Police FIR Record Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Delete Record Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 08:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12315 | Export All Posts, Products, Orders, Refunds &amp;amp; Users &amp;lt;= 2.9.3 - Information Disclosure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12315</link><description>The Export All Posts, Products, Orders, Refunds &amp; Users plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.3 via the exports directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/uploads/smack_uci_uploads/exports/ directory which can contain information like exported user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 08:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13814 | Global Gallery - WordPress Responsive Gallery &amp;lt;= 9.1.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13814</link><description>The The Global Gallery - WordPress Responsive Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 9.1.5. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 08:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1186 | dayrui XunRuiCMS Api.php deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1186</link><description>A vulnerability was found in dayrui XunRuiCMS up to 4.6.4. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Control/Api/Api.php. The manipulation of the argument thumb leads to deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 08:18:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49780 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in acmailer CGI ver.4.0.5 and earlier. An arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49780</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in acmailer CGI ver.4.0.5 and earlier. An arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the management page of the affected product.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 07:50:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13794 | Hide My WP Ghost – Security &amp;amp; Firewall &amp;lt;= 5.3.02 - Unauthenticated Login Page Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13794</link><description>The WP Ghost (Hide My WP Ghost) – Security &amp; Firewall plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Login Page Dislcosure in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.02. This is due to the plugin not properly restricting the /wp-register.php path. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to discover the hidden login page location.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 07:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13821 | WP Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 10.10 - Unauthenticated Post-Confirmation Booking Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13821</link><description>The WP Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unauthenticated Post-Confirmation Booking Manipulation in all versions up to, and including, 10.10. This is due to the plugin not properly requiring re-verification after a booking has been made and a change is being attempted. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to manipulate their confirmed bookings, even after they have been approved.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 07:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1185 | pihome-shc PiHome ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1185</link><description>A vulnerability was found in pihome-shc PiHome 2.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /ajax.php?Ajax=GetModal_Sensor_Graph. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 07:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1183 | CodeZips Gym Management System more-userprofile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1183</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CodeZips Gym Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /dashboard/admin/more-userprofile.php. The manipulation of the argument login_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 07:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1184 | pihome-shc PiHome ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1184</link><description>A vulnerability was found in pihome-shc PiHome 1.77 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /ajax.php?Ajax=GetModal_MQTTEdit. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 07:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26520 | Cacti through 1.2.29 allows SQL injection in the template function in host_templates.php via the graph_template parameter. NOTE: this issue ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26520</link><description>Cacti through 1.2.29 allows SQL injection in the template function in host_templates.php via the graph_template parameter. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2024-54146.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 06:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13374 | WP Table Manager &amp;lt;= 4.1.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Directory Traversal to Folder/File Name Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13374</link><description>The WP Table Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on thewptm_getFolders AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read arbitrary file names and directories.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 05:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13600 | Majestic Support – The Leading-Edge Help Desk &amp;amp; Customer Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13600</link><description>The Majestic Support – The Leading-Edge Help Desk &amp; Customer Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.5 via the 'majesticsupportdata' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/uploads/majesticsupportdata directory which can contain file attachments included in support tickets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 05:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13601 | Majestic Support – The Leading-Edge Help Desk &amp;amp; Customer Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13601</link><description>The Majestic Support – The Leading-Edge Help Desk &amp; Customer Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.5 via the 'exportusereraserequest' function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to export ticket data for any user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 05:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13714 | All-Images.ai – IA Image Bank and Custom Image creation &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13714</link><description>The All-Images.ai – IA Image Bank and Custom Image creation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the '_get_image_by_url' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 05:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11746 | Discover the Best Woocommerce Product Brands Plugin for WordPress – Woocommerce Brands Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11746</link><description>The Discover the Best Woocommerce Product Brands Plugin for WordPress – Woocommerce Brands Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'product_brand' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 04:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12164 | WPSyncSheets Lite For WPForms – WPForms Google Spreadsheet Addon &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12164</link><description>The WPSyncSheets Lite For WPForms – WPForms Google Spreadsheet Addon plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the wpsslwp_reset_settings() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to reset the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 04:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13421 | Real Estate 7 WordPress &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation to Administrator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13421</link><description>The Real Estate 7 WordPress theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.1. This is due to the plugin not properly restricting the roles allowed to be selected during registration. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register a new administrative user account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 04:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13653 | ZoxPress - The All-In-One WordPress News Theme &amp;lt;= 2.12.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13653</link><description>The ZoxPress - The All-In-One WordPress News Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the 'backup_options' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 04:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13654 | ZoxPress - The All-In-One WordPress News Theme &amp;lt;= 2.12.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13654</link><description>The ZoxPress - The All-In-One WordPress News Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to a denial of service due to a missing capability check on the 'reset_options' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary option values on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to delete an option that would create an error on the site and deny service to legitimate users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 04:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13656 | Click Mag - Viral WordPress News Magazine/Blog Theme &amp;lt;= 3.6.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13656</link><description>The Click Mag - Viral WordPress News Magazine/Blog Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to a denial of service due to a missing capability check on the propanel_of_ajax_callback() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary option values on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to delete an option that would create an error on the site and deny service to legitimate users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 04:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13658 | NGG Smart Image Search &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13658</link><description>The NGG Smart Image Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'hr_SIS_nextgen_searchbox' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 04:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13665 | Admire Extra &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13665</link><description>The Admire Extra plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'space' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 04:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13769 | Puzzles | WP Magazine / Review with Store WordPress Theme + RTL &amp;lt;= 4.2.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13769</link><description>The Puzzles | WP Magazine / Review with Store WordPress Theme + RTL theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting due to a missing capability check on the 'theme_options_ajax_post_action' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugin's settings and inject malicious web scripts. The developer opted to remove the software from the repository, so an update is not available and it is recommended to find a replacement software.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 04:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13800 | Popup Plugin For WordPress - ConvertPlus &amp;lt;= 3.5.30 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13800</link><description>The ConvertPlus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to a denial of service due to a missing capability check on the 'cp_dismiss_notice' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.30. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update option values to '1' on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update an option that would create an error on the site and deny service to legitimate users or be used to set some values to true such as registration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 04:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13539 | AForms Eats &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13539</link><description>The AForms Eats plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1. This is due the /vendor/aura/payload-interface/phpunit.php file being publicly accessible and displaying error messages. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 03:24:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13541 | aDirectory – WordPress Directory Listing Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13541</link><description>The aDirectory – WordPress Directory Listing Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the adqs_delete_listing() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 03:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13554 | The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended &amp;lt;= 3.0.13 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Post Order Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13554</link><description>The The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the reorder_route() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.13. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reorder posts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 03:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13701 | Liveticker (by stklcode) &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13701</link><description>The Liveticker (by stklcode) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'liveticker' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 03:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13749 | StaffList &amp;lt;= 3.2.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13749</link><description>The StaffList plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'stafflist' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 03:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0808 | Houzez Property Feed &amp;lt;= 2.4.21 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Property Feed Export Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0808</link><description>The Houzez Property Feed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.21. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the "deleteexport" action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete property feed exports via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 03:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29172 | Dell BSAFE SSL-J contains a deadlock vulnerability. A remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to a Denial of S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29172</link><description>Dell BSAFE SSL-J contains a deadlock vulnerability. A remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 02:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29171 | Dell BSAFE SSL-J contains an Improper certificate verification vulnerability. A remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29171</link><description>Dell BSAFE SSL-J contains an Improper certificate verification vulnerability. A remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 02:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53880 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server contains a vulnerability in the model loading API, where a user could cause an integer overflow or wraparound...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53880</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server contains a vulnerability in the model loading API, where a user could cause an integer overflow or wraparound error by loading a model with an extra-large file size that overflows an internal variable. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 01:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23359 | NVIDIA Container Toolkit for Linux contains a Time-of-Check Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) vulnerability when used with default configuration, where a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23359</link><description>NVIDIA Container Toolkit for Linux contains a Time-of-Check Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) vulnerability when used with default configuration, where a crafted container image could gain access to the host file system. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 01:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0143 | NVIDIA nvJPEG2000 library contains a vulnerability where an attacker can cause an out-of-bounds write issue by means of a specially crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0143</link><description>NVIDIA nvJPEG2000 library contains a vulnerability where an attacker can cause an out-of-bounds write issue by means of a specially crafted JPEG2000 file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 01:26:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0144 | NVIDIA nvJPEG2000 library contains a vulnerability where an attacker can cause a buffer overflow issue by means of a specially crafted JPEG2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0144</link><description>NVIDIA nvJPEG2000 library contains a vulnerability where an attacker can cause a buffer overflow issue by means of a specially crafted JPEG2000 file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 01:26:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0145 | NVIDIA nvJPEG2000 library contains a vulnerability where an attacker can cause a heap-based buffer overflow issue by means of a specially cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0145</link><description>NVIDIA nvJPEG2000 library contains a vulnerability where an attacker can cause a heap-based buffer overflow issue by means of a specially crafted JPEG2000 file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 01:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1243 | Field in api-go proxy not transformed before version 1.44.1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1243</link><description>The Temporal api-go library prior to version 1.44.1 did not send `update response` information to Data Converter when the proxy package within the api-go module was used in a gRPC proxy prior to transmission. This resulted in information contained within the `update response` field not having Data Converter transformations (e.g. encryption) applied. This is an issue only when using the UpdateWorkflowExecution APIs (released on 13th January 2025)  with a proxy leveraging the api-go library before version 1.44.1.

Other data fields were correctly sent to Data Converter. This issue does not impact the Data Converter server. Data was encrypted in transit. Temporal Cloud services are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 01:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0142 | NVIDIA nvJPEG2000 library contains a vulnerability where an attacker can cause an out-of-bounds write issue by means of a specially crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0142</link><description>NVIDIA nvJPEG2000 library contains a vulnerability where an attacker can cause an out-of-bounds write issue by means of a specially crafted JPEG2000 file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 01:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21971 | Improper input validation in AMD Crash Defender could allow an attacker to provide the Windows® system process ID to a kernel-mode driver, r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21971</link><description>Improper input validation in AMD Crash Defender could allow an attacker to provide the Windows® system process ID to a kernel-mode driver, resulting in an operating system crash, potentially leading to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 01:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>