<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 07:40:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-9325 | Intelbras InControl incontrol-service-watchdog.exe unquoted search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9325</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Intelbras InControl up to 2.21.56. This affects an unknown part of the file C:\Program Files (x86)\Intelbras\Incontrol Cliente\incontrol_webcam\incontrol-service-watchdog.exe. The manipulation leads to unquoted search path. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The vendor was informed early on 2024-08-05 about this issue. The release of a fixed version 2.21.58 was announced for the end of August 2024 but then was postponed until 2024-09-20.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 07:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9324 | Intelbras InControl Relatório de Operadores Page operador code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9324</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Intelbras InControl up to 2.21.57. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /v1/operador/ of the component Relatório de Operadores Page. The manipulation of the argument fields leads to code injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was informed early on 2024-07-19 about this issue. The release of a fixed version 2.21.58 was announced for the end of August 2024 but then was postponed until 2024-09-20.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 07:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9323 | SourceCodester Inventory Management System add_staff.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9323</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Inventory Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /app/action/add_staff.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 06:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9322 | code-projects Supply Chain Management edit_manufacturer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9322</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Supply Chain Management 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_manufacturer.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 03:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9321 | SourceCodester Online Railway Reservation System view_details.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9321</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Railway Reservation System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/inquiries/view_details.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 00:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9320 | SourceCodester Online Timesheet App Add Timesheet Form add-timesheet.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9320</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Timesheet App 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /endpoint/add-timesheet.php of the component Add Timesheet Form. The manipulation of the argument day/task leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 00:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9319 | SourceCodester Online Timesheet App delete-timesheet.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9319</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Online Timesheet App 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /endpoint/delete-timesheet.php. The manipulation of the argument timesheet leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 23:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9318 | SourceCodester Advocate Office Management System activate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9318</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Advocate Office Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /control/activate.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 23:16:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9317 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop Master.php delete_category sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9317</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function delete_category of the file /classes/Master.php?f=delete_category. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 21:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9316 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System B+.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9316</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/blood/update/B+.php. The manipulation of the argument Bloodname leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 20:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9315 | SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System manage_department.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9315</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/maintenance/manage_department.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 19:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9300 | SourceCodester Online Railway Reservation System Message Us Form contact_us.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9300</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Online Railway Reservation System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file contact_us.php of the component Message Us Form. The manipulation of the argument fullname/email/message leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 14:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9299 | SourceCodester Online Railway Reservation System ?page=reserve cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9299</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Online Railway Reservation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /?page=reserve. The manipulation of the argument First Name/Middle Name/Last Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 14:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9298 | SourceCodester Online Railway Reservation System Ticket ?page=tickets access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9298</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Railway Reservation System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /?page=tickets of the component Ticket Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to improper access controls. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 13:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8189 | WP MultiTasking - WP Utilities &amp;lt;= 0.1.17 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8189</link><description>The WP MultiTasking – WP Utilities plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘wpmt_menu_name’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.17 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 12:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9297 | SourceCodester Online Railway Reservation System admin improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9297</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Railway Reservation System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/. The manipulation of the argument page with the input trains/schedules/system_info leads to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 12:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9296 | SourceCodester Advocate Office Management System forgot_pass.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9296</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Advocate Office Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /control/forgot_pass.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 09:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8712 | GTM Server Side &amp;lt;= 2.1.19 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8712</link><description>The GTM Server Side plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.19. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 08:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9295 | SourceCodester Advocate Office Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9295</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Advocate Office Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /control/login.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 07:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23923 | Alpine Halo9 prh_l2_sar_data_ind Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23923</link><description>Alpine Halo9 prh_l2_sar_data_ind Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Alpine Halo9 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prh_l2_sar_data_ind function. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.

Was ZDI-CAN-22945</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 06:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23924 | Alpine Halo9 UPDM_wemCmdCreatSHA256Hash Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23924</link><description>Alpine Halo9 UPDM_wemCmdCreatSHA256Hash Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Alpine Halo9 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the UPDM_wemCmdCreatSHA256Hash function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.

Was ZDI-CAN-23105</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 06:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23935 | Alpine Halo9 DecodeUTF7 Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23935</link><description>Alpine Halo9 DecodeUTF7 Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Alpine Halo9 devices. An attacker must first obtain the ability to pair a malicious Bluetooth device with the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DecodeUTF7 function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.

Was ZDI-CAN-23249</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 06:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23958 | Autel MaxiCharger AC Elite Business C50 BLE Hardcoded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23958</link><description>Autel MaxiCharger AC Elite Business C50 BLE Hardcoded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Autel MaxiCharger AC Elite Business C50 charging stations. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the BLE AppAuthenRequest command handler. The handler uses hardcoded credentials as a fallback in case of an authentication request failure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system.

Was ZDI-CAN-23196</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 06:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23959 | Autel MaxiCharger AC Elite Business C50 BLE AppChargingControl Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23959</link><description>Autel MaxiCharger AC Elite Business C50 BLE AppChargingControl Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autel MaxiCharger AC Elite Business C50 charging stations. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of the AppChargingControl BLE command. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device.

Was ZDI-CAN-23194</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 06:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23960 | Alpine Halo9 Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23960</link><description>Alpine Halo9 Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to bypass signature validation mechanism on affected installations of Alpine Halo9 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware metadata signature validation mechanism. The issue results from the lack of proper verification of a cryptographic signature. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root.

Was ZDI-CAN-23102</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 06:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23961 | Alpine Halo9 UPDM_wemCmdUpdFSpeDecomp Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23961</link><description>Alpine Halo9 UPDM_wemCmdUpdFSpeDecomp Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Alpine Halo9 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the UPDM_wemCmdUpdFSpeDecomp function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.

Was ZDI-CAN-23306</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 06:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23967 | Autel MaxiCharger AC Elite Business C50 WebSocket Base64 Decoding Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23967</link><description>Autel MaxiCharger AC Elite Business C50 WebSocket Base64 Decoding Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autel MaxiCharger AC Elite Business C50 chargers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of base64-encoded data within WebSocket messages. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device.

Was ZDI-CAN-23230</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 06:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23938 | Silicon Labs Gecko OS Debug Interface Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23938</link><description>Silicon Labs Gecko OS Debug Interface Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Silicon Labs Gecko OS. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the debug interface. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device.

Was ZDI-CAN-23184</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 06:12:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23957 | Autel MaxiCharger AC Elite Business C50 DLB_HostHeartBeat Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23957</link><description>Autel MaxiCharger AC Elite Business C50 DLB_HostHeartBeat Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autel MaxiCharger AC Elite Business C50 charging stations. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DLB_HostHeartBeat handler of the DLB protocol implementation. When parsing an AES key, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device.

Was ZDI-CAN-23241</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 06:12:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8715 | Simple LDAP Login &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8715</link><description>The Simple LDAP Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 02:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8353 | GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform &amp;lt;= 3.16.1 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8353</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.16.1 via deserialization of untrusted input via several parameters like 'give_title' and 'card_address'. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. The additional presence of a POP chain allows attackers to delete arbitrary files and achieve remote code execution. This is essentially the same vulnerability as CVE-2024-5932, however, it was discovered the the presence of stripslashes_deep on user_info allows the is_serialized check to be bypassed. This issue was mostly patched in 3.16.1, but further hardening was added in 3.16.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 02:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8547 | Simple Popup Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8547</link><description>The Simple Popup Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's [popup] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 02:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8788 | EU/UK VAT Manager for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.12.12 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8788</link><description>The EU/UK VAT Manager for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.11. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 02:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9023 | WP-WebAuthn &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wwa_login_form Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9023</link><description>The WP-WebAuthn plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wwa_login_form shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 02:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9189 | EU/UK VAT Manager for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.12.12 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9189</link><description>The EU/UK VAT Manager for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the alg_wc_eu_vat_exempt_vat_from_admin() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.12. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the VAT status for any order.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 02:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38796 | Integer overflow in PeCoffLoaderRelocateImage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38796</link><description>EDK2 contains a vulnerability in the PeCoffLoaderRelocateImage(). An Attacker may cause memory corruption due to an overflow via an adjacent network. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a loss of Confidentiality, Integrity, and/or Availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 21:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9294 | dingfanzu CMS saveNewPwd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9294</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in dingfanzu CMS up to 29d67d9044f6f93378e6eb6ff92272217ff7225c. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file saveNewPwd.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 21:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23586 | An insufficient session timeout vulnerability affects HCL Nomad server on Domino</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23586</link><description>HCL Nomad is susceptible to an insufficient session expiration vulnerability.   Under certain circumstances, an unauthenticated attacker could obtain old session information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 21:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47186 | Filament has unvalidated ColorColumn and ColorEntry values that can be used for Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47186</link><description>Filament is a collection of full-stack components for Laravel development. Versions of Filament from v3.0.0 through v3.2.114 are affected by a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. If values passed to a `ColorColumn` or `ColumnEntry` are not valid and contain a specific set of characters, applications are vulnerable to XSS attack against a user who opens a page on which a color column or entry is rendered. Filament v3.2.115 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 21:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9291 | kalvinGit kvf-admin XML File cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9291</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in kalvinGit kvf-admin up to f12a94dc1ebb7d1c51ee978a85e4c7ed75c620ff. Affected is an unknown function of the file /ueditor/upload?configPath=ueditor/config.json&amp;amp;action=uploadfile of the component XML File Handler. The manipulation of the argument upfile leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The GitHub repository of the project did not receive an update for more than two years.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 21:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9293 | skyselang yylAdmin Backend File.php list sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9293</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in skyselang yylAdmin up to 3.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function list of the file /app/admin/controller/file/File.php of the component Backend. The manipulation of the argument is_disable leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 21:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46453 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /test/ of iq3xcite v2.31 to v3.05 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46453</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /test/ of iq3xcite v2.31 to v3.05 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 20:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6436 | Rockwell Automation Input Validation Vulnerability exists in the SequenceManager™ Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6436</link><description>An input validation vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation Sequence Manager™ which could allow a malicious user to send malformed packets to the server and cause a denial-of-service condition. If exploited, the device would become unresponsive, and a manual restart will be required for recovery. Additionally, if exploited, there could be a loss of view for the downstream equipment sequences in the controller. Users would not be able to view the status or command the equipment sequences, however the equipment sequence would continue to execute uninterrupted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 19:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9160 | Security Misconfiguration in Forge module PEADM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9160</link><description>In versions of the PEADM Forge Module prior to 3.24.0 a security misconfiguration was discovered.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 19:19:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33368 | An issue in Plasmoapp RPShare Fabric mod v.1.0.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the build method in DonwloadPromptSc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33368</link><description>An issue in Plasmoapp RPShare Fabric mod v.1.0.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the build method in DonwloadPromptScreen</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 18:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33369 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in Plasmoapp RPShare Fabric mod v.1.0.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the getFile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33369</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in Plasmoapp RPShare Fabric mod v.1.0.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the getFileNameFromConnection method in DownloadTask</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 18:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25412 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Flatpress v1.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25412</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Flatpress v1.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the email field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39364 | Advantech ADAM-5630 Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39364</link><description>Advantech ADAM-5630 
has built-in commands that can be executed without authenticating the 
user. These commands allow for restarting the operating system, 
rebooting the hardware, and stopping the execution. The commands can be 
sent to a simple HTTP request and are executed by the device 
automatically, without discrimination of origin or level of privileges 
of the user sending the commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25411 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Flatpress v1.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25411</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Flatpress v1.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the username parameter in setup.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28948 | Advantech ADAM-5630 Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28948</link><description>Advantech ADAM-5630 contains a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. It allows an attacker to partly circumvent the same 
origin policy, which is designed to prevent different websites from 
interfering with each other.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34542 | Advantech ADAM-5630 Weak Encoding for Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34542</link><description>Advantech ADAM-5630 shares user credentials plain text between the device and the user source device during the login process.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9301 | A path traversal issue in E2Nest prior to commit 8a41948e553c89c56b14410c6ed395e9cfb9250a</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9301</link><description>A path traversal issue in E2Nest prior to commit 8a41948e553c89c56b14410c6ed395e9cfb9250a</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:55:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39275 | Advantech ADAM-5630 Use of Persistent Cookies Containing Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39275</link><description>Cookies of authenticated Advantech ADAM-5630 users remain as active valid cookies when a 
session is closed. Forging requests with a legitimate cookie, even if 
the session was terminated, allows an unauthorized attacker to act with 
the same level of privileges of the legitimate user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46257 | A Command injection vulnerability in requestLetsEncryptSslWithDnsChallenge in NginxProxyManager 2.11.3 allows an attacker to achieve remote ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46257</link><description>A Command injection vulnerability in requestLetsEncryptSslWithDnsChallenge in NginxProxyManager 2.11.3 allows an attacker to achieve remote code execution via Add Let's Encrypt Certificate. NOTE: this is not part of any NGINX software shipped by F5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37187 | Advantech ADAM-5550 Weak Encoding for Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37187</link><description>Advantech ADAM-5550 share user credentials with a low level of encryption, consisting of base 64 encoding.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38308 | Advantech ADAM-5550 Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38308</link><description>Advantech ADAM 5550's web application includes a "logs" page where all 
the HTTP requests received are displayed to the user. The device doesn't
 correctly neutralize malicious code when parsing HTTP requests to 
generate page output.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46256 | A Command injection vulnerability in requestLetsEncryptSsl in NginxProxyManager 2.11.3 allows an attacker to RCE via Add Let's Encrypt Certi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46256</link><description>A Command injection vulnerability in requestLetsEncryptSsl in NginxProxyManager 2.11.3 allows an attacker to RCE via Add Let's Encrypt Certificate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46097 | TestLink 1.9.20 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control in the TestPlan editing section. When a new TestPlan is created, an ID with an inc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46097</link><description>TestLink 1.9.20 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control in the TestPlan editing section. When a new TestPlan is created, an ID with an incremental value is automatically generated. Using the edit function you can change the tplan_id parameter to another ID. The application does not carry out a check on the user's permissions maing it possible to recover the IDs of all the TestPlans (even the administrative ones) and modify them even with minimal privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22170 | Unchecked buffer in Dynamic DNS client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22170</link><description>Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer vulnerability in Western Digital My Cloud ddns-start on Linux allows Overflow Buffers.This issue affects My Cloud: before 5.29.102.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46367 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Webkul Krayin CRM 1.3.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary JavaScript code by ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46367</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Webkul Krayin CRM 1.3.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary JavaScript code by submitting a malicious payload within the username field. This can lead to privilege escalation when the payload is executed, granting the attacker elevated permissions within the CRM system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38809 | Applications that parse ETags from "If-Match" or "If-None-Match" request headers are vulnerable to DoS attack.

Users of affected versions s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38809</link><description>Applications that parse ETags from "If-Match" or "If-None-Match" request headers are vulnerable to DoS attack.

Users of affected versions should upgrade to the corresponding fixed version.

Users of older, unsupported versions could enforce a size limit on "If-Match" and "If-None-Match" headers, e.g. through a Filter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 16:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8310 | OPW Fuel Management Systems SiteSentinel Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8310</link><description>OPW Fuel Management Systems SiteSentinel 
could allow an attacker to bypass authentication to the server and obtain full admin privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 16:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9284 | TP-LINK TL-WR841ND popupSiteSurveyRpm.htm stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9284</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TP-LINK TL-WR841ND up to 20240920. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /userRpm/popupSiteSurveyRpm.htm. The manipulation of the argument ssid leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 16:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46366 | A Client-side Template Injection (CSTI) vulnerability in Webkul Krayin CRM 1.3.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary client-side te...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46366</link><description>A Client-side Template Injection (CSTI) vulnerability in Webkul Krayin CRM 1.3.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary client-side template code by injecting a malicious payload during the lead creation process. This can lead to privilege escalation when the payload is executed, granting the attacker elevated permissions within the CRM system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 16:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8630 | Alisonic Sibylla SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8630</link><description>Alisonic Sibylla devices are vulnerable to SQL injection attacks, which could allow complete access to the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 16:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6981 | OMNTEC Proteus Tank Monitoring Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6981</link><description>OMNTEC Proteus Tank Monitoring OEL8000III Series


could allow an attacker to perform administrative actions without proper authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 16:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45744 | TopQuadrant TopBraid EDG stores external credentials insecurely. An authenticated attacker with file system access can read edg-setup.proper...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45744</link><description>TopQuadrant TopBraid EDG stores external credentials insecurely. An authenticated attacker with file system access can read edg-setup.properites and obtain the secret to decrypt external passwords stored in edg-vault.properties. An authenticated attacker could gain file system access using a separate vulnerability such as CVE-2024-45745. 
At least version 7.1.3 is affected. Version 7.3 adds HashiCorp Vault integration that does not store external passwords locally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 16:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45745 | TopQuadrant TopBraid EDG before version 8.0.1 allows an authenticated attacker to upload an XML DTD file and execute JavaScript to read loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45745</link><description>TopQuadrant TopBraid EDG before version 8.0.1 allows an authenticated attacker to upload an XML DTD file and execute JavaScript to read local files or access URLs (XXE). Fixed in 8.0.1 (bug fix: TBS-6721).</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 16:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6983 | Remote Code Execution in mudler/localai</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6983</link><description>mudler/localai version 2.17.1 is vulnerable to remote code execution. The vulnerability arises because the localai backend receives inputs not only from the configuration file but also from other inputs, allowing an attacker to upload a binary file and execute malicious code. This can lead to the attacker gaining full control over the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 15:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47077 | authentik cross-provider token validation problems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47077</link><description>authentik is an open-source identity provider. Prior to versions 2024.8.3 and 2024.6.5, access tokens issued to one application can be stolen by that application and used to impersonate the user against any other proxy provider. Also, a user can steal an access token they were legitimately issued for one application and use it to access another application that they aren't allowed to access. Anyone who has more than one proxy provider application with different trust domains or different access control is affected. Versions 2024.8.3 and 2024.6.5 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 15:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47070 | Password authentication bypass via X-Forwarded-For HTTP header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47070</link><description>authentik is an open-source identity provider. A vulnerability that exists in versions prior to 2024.8.3 and 2024.6.5 allows bypassing password login by adding X-Forwarded-For header with an unparsable IP address, e.g. `a`. This results in a possibility of logging into any account with a known login or email address. The vulnerability requires the authentik instance to trust X-Forwarded-For header provided by the attacker, thus it is not reproducible from external hosts on a properly configured environment.  The issue occurs due to the password stage having a policy bound to it, which skips the password stage if the Identification stage is setup to also contain a password stage. Due to the invalid X-Forwarded-For header, which does not get validated to be an IP Address early enough, the exception happens later and the policy fails. The default blueprint doesn't correctly set `failure_result` to `True` on the policy binding meaning that due to this exception the policy returns false and the password stage is skipped. Versions 2024.8.3 and 2024.6.5 fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 15:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46472 | CodeAstro Membership Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the parameter 'email' in the Login Page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46472</link><description>CodeAstro Membership Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the parameter 'email' in the Login Page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46331 | ModStartCMS v8.8.0 was discovered to contain an open redirect vulnerability in the redirect parameter at /admin/login. This vulnerability al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46331</link><description>ModStartCMS v8.8.0 was discovered to contain an open redirect vulnerability in the redirect parameter at /admin/login. This vulnerability allows attackers to redirect users to an arbitrary website via a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46333 | An authenticated cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Piwigo v14.5.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46333</link><description>An authenticated cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Piwigo v14.5.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Album Name parameter under the Add Album function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46470 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in CodeAstro Membership Management System 1.0 allows attackers to run malicious JavaScript via the member...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46470</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in CodeAstro Membership Management System 1.0 allows attackers to run malicious JavaScript via the membership_type field in the edit-type.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46471 | The Directory Listing in /uploads/ Folder in CodeAstro Membership Management System 1.0 exposes the structure and contents of directories, p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46471</link><description>The Directory Listing in /uploads/ Folder in CodeAstro Membership Management System 1.0 exposes the structure and contents of directories, potentially revealing sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3373 | SQLi in RSM Design&amp;#x27;s Website Template</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3373</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in RSM Design Website Template allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Website Template: before 1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40509 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in openPetra v.2023.02 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the serverMFinDev.asm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40509</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in openPetra v.2023.02 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the serverMFinDev.asmx function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40510 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in openPetra v.2023.02 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the serverMCommon.asm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40510</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in openPetra v.2023.02 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the serverMCommon.asmx function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44910 | NASA CryptoLib v1.3.0 was discovered to contain an Out-of-Bounds read via the AOS subsystem (crypto_aos.c).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44910</link><description>NASA CryptoLib v1.3.0 was discovered to contain an Out-of-Bounds read via the AOS subsystem (crypto_aos.c).</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44911 | NASA CryptoLib v1.3.0 was discovered to contain an Out-of-Bounds read via the TC subsystem (crypto_aos.c).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44911</link><description>NASA CryptoLib v1.3.0 was discovered to contain an Out-of-Bounds read via the TC subsystem (crypto_aos.c).</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44912 | NASA CryptoLib v1.3.0 was discovered to contain an Out-of-Bounds read via the TM subsystem (crypto_tm.c).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44912</link><description>NASA CryptoLib v1.3.0 was discovered to contain an Out-of-Bounds read via the TM subsystem (crypto_tm.c).</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47184 | Ampache vulnerable to Stored XSS via Democratic Playlist Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47184</link><description>Ampache is a web based audio/video streaming application and file manager. Prior to version 6.6.0, the Democratic Playlist Name is vulnerable to a stored cross-site scripting. Version 6.6.0 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47182 | Dozzle uses unsafe hash for passwords</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47182</link><description>Dozzle is a realtime log viewer for docker containers. Before version 8.5.3, the app uses sha-256 as the hash for passwords, which leaves users susceptible to rainbow table attacks. The app switches to bcrypt, a more appropriate hash for passwords, in version 8.5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9283 | RelaxedJS ReLaXed Pug to PDF Converter cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9283</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in RelaxedJS ReLaXed up to 0.2.2. Affected is an unknown function of the component Pug to PDF Converter. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45773 | A use-after-free vulnerability involving upgradeToRocket requests can cause the application to crash or potentially result in code execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45773</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability involving upgradeToRocket requests can cause the application to crash or potentially result in code execution or other undesirable effects. This issue affects Facebook Thrift prior to v2024.09.09.00.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45863 | A null-dereference vulnerability involving parsing requests specifying invalid protocols can cause the application to crash or potentially r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45863</link><description>A null-dereference vulnerability involving parsing requests specifying invalid protocols can cause the application to crash or potentially result in other undesirable effects. This issue affects Facebook Thrift from v2024.09.09.00 until v2024.09.23.00.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7149 | Event Manager, Events Calendar, Tickets, Registrations – Eventin &amp;lt;= 4.0.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7149</link><description>The Event Manager, Events Calendar, Tickets, Registrations – Eventin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.8 via multiple style parameters. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40511 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in openPetra v.2023.02 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the serverMServerAdmi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40511</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in openPetra v.2023.02 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the serverMServerAdmin.asmx function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40512 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in openPetra v.2023.02 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the serverMReporting....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40512</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in openPetra v.2023.02 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the serverMReporting.asmx function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9282 | bg5sbk MiniCMS page-edit.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9282</link><description>A vulnerability was found in bg5sbk MiniCMS 1.11. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file page-edit.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions confusing version and file name information. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46441 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in YPay 1.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a ZIP archive to themePutFile in app/com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46441</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in YPay 1.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a ZIP archive to themePutFile in app/common/util/Upload.php (called from app/admin/controller/ypay/Home.php). The file extension of an uncompressed file is not checked.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46802 | drm/amd/display: added NULL check at start of dc_validate_stream</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46802</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: added NULL check at start of dc_validate_stream

[Why]
prevent invalid memory access

[How]
check if dc and stream are NULL</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46803 | drm/amdkfd: Check debug trap enable before write dbg_ev_file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46803</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdkfd: Check debug trap enable before write dbg_ev_file

In interrupt context, write dbg_ev_file will be run by work queue. It
will cause write dbg_ev_file execution after debug_trap_disable, which
will cause NULL pointer access.
v2: cancel work "debug_event_workarea" before set dbg_ev_file as NULL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46804 | drm/amd/display: Add array index check for hdcp ddc access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46804</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Add array index check for hdcp ddc access

[Why]
Coverity reports OVERRUN warning. Do not check if array
index valid.

[How]
Check msg_id valid and valid array index.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46805 | drm/amdgpu: fix the waring dereferencing hive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46805</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdgpu: fix the waring dereferencing hive

Check the amdgpu_hive_info *hive that maybe is NULL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46806 | drm/amdgpu: Fix the warning division or modulo by zero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46806</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdgpu: Fix the warning division or modulo by zero

Checks the partition mode and returns an error for an invalid mode.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46807 | drm/amd/amdgpu: Check tbo resource pointer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46807</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/amdgpu: Check tbo resource pointer

Validate tbo resource pointer, skip if NULL</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46808 | drm/amd/display: Add missing NULL pointer check within dpcd_extend_address_range</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46808</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Add missing NULL pointer check within dpcd_extend_address_range

[Why &amp; How]
ASSERT if return NULL from kcalloc.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46809 | drm/amd/display: Check BIOS images before it is used</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46809</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Check BIOS images before it is used

BIOS images may fail to load and null checks are added before they are
used.

This fixes 6 NULL_RETURNS issues reported by Coverity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46810 | drm/bridge: tc358767: Check if fully initialized before signalling HPD event via IRQ</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46810</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/bridge: tc358767: Check if fully initialized before signalling HPD event via IRQ

Make sure the connector is fully initialized before signalling any
HPD events via drm_kms_helper_hotplug_event(), otherwise this may
lead to NULL pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46811 | drm/amd/display: Fix index may exceed array range within fpu_update_bw_bounding_box</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46811</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Fix index may exceed array range within fpu_update_bw_bounding_box

[Why]
Coverity reports OVERRUN warning. soc.num_states could
be 40. But array range of bw_params-&gt;clk_table.entries is 8.

[How]
Assert if soc.num_states greater than 8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46812 | drm/amd/display: Skip inactive planes within ModeSupportAndSystemConfiguration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46812</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Skip inactive planes within ModeSupportAndSystemConfiguration

[Why]
Coverity reports Memory - illegal accesses.

[How]
Skip inactive planes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46813 | drm/amd/display: Check link_index before accessing dc-&amp;gt;links[]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46813</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Check link_index before accessing dc-&gt;links[]

[WHY &amp; HOW]
dc-&gt;links[] has max size of MAX_LINKS and NULL is return when trying to
access with out-of-bound index.

This fixes 3 OVERRUN and 1 RESOURCE_LEAK issues reported by Coverity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46814 | drm/amd/display: Check msg_id before processing transcation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46814</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Check msg_id before processing transcation

[WHY &amp; HOW]
HDCP_MESSAGE_ID_INVALID (-1) is not a valid msg_id nor is it a valid
array index, and it needs checking before used.

This fixes 4 OVERRUN issues reported by Coverity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46815 | drm/amd/display: Check num_valid_sets before accessing reader_wm_sets[]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46815</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Check num_valid_sets before accessing reader_wm_sets[]

[WHY &amp; HOW]
num_valid_sets needs to be checked to avoid a negative index when
accessing reader_wm_sets[num_valid_sets - 1].

This fixes an OVERRUN issue reported by Coverity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46816 | drm/amd/display: Stop amdgpu_dm initialize when link nums greater than max_links</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46816</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Stop amdgpu_dm initialize when link nums greater than max_links

[Why]
Coverity report OVERRUN warning. There are
only max_links elements within dc-&gt;links. link
count could up to AMDGPU_DM_MAX_DISPLAY_INDEX 31.

[How]
Make sure link count less than max_links.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46817 | drm/amd/display: Stop amdgpu_dm initialize when stream nums greater than 6</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46817</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Stop amdgpu_dm initialize when stream nums greater than 6

[Why]
Coverity reports OVERRUN warning. Should abort amdgpu_dm
initialize.

[How]
Return failure to amdgpu_dm_init.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46818 | drm/amd/display: Check gpio_id before used as array index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46818</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Check gpio_id before used as array index

[WHY &amp; HOW]
GPIO_ID_UNKNOWN (-1) is not a valid value for array index and therefore
should be checked in advance.

This fixes 5 OVERRUN issues reported by Coverity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46819 | drm/amdgpu: the warning dereferencing obj for nbio_v7_4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46819</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdgpu: the warning dereferencing obj for nbio_v7_4

if ras_manager obj null, don't print NBIO err data</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46820 | drm/amdgpu/vcn: remove irq disabling in vcn 5 suspend</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46820</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdgpu/vcn: remove irq disabling in vcn 5 suspend

We do not directly enable/disable VCN IRQ in vcn 5.0.0.
And we do not handle the IRQ state as well. So the calls to
disable IRQ and set state are removed. This effectively gets
rid of the warining of
      "WARN_ON(!amdgpu_irq_enabled(adev, src, type))"
in amdgpu_irq_put().</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46821 | drm/amd/pm: Fix negative array index read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46821</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/pm: Fix negative array index read

Avoid using the negative values
for clk_idex as an index into an array pptable-&gt;DpmDescriptor.

V2: fix clk_index return check (Tim Huang)</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46822 | arm64: acpi: Harden get_cpu_for_acpi_id() against missing CPU entry</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46822</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

arm64: acpi: Harden get_cpu_for_acpi_id() against missing CPU entry

In a review discussion of the changes to support vCPU hotplug where
a check was added on the GICC being enabled if was online, it was
noted that there is need to map back to the cpu and use that to index
into a cpumask. As such, a valid ID is needed.

If an MPIDR check fails in acpi_map_gic_cpu_interface() it is possible
for the entry in cpu_madt_gicc[cpu] == NULL.  This function would
then cause a NULL pointer dereference.   Whilst a path to trigger
this has not been established, harden this caller against the
possibility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46823 | kunit/overflow: Fix UB in overflow_allocation_test</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46823</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

kunit/overflow: Fix UB in overflow_allocation_test

The 'device_name' array doesn't exist out of the
'overflow_allocation_test' function scope. However, it is being used as
a driver name when calling 'kunit_driver_create' from
'kunit_device_register'. It produces the kernel panic with KASAN
enabled.

Since this variable is used in one place only, remove it and pass the
device name into kunit_device_register directly as an ascii string.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46824 | iommufd: Require drivers to supply the cache_invalidate_user ops</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46824</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

iommufd: Require drivers to supply the cache_invalidate_user ops

If drivers don't do this then iommufd will oops invalidation ioctls with
something like:

  Unable to handle kernel NULL pointer dereference at virtual address 0000000000000000
  Mem abort info:
    ESR = 0x0000000086000004
    EC = 0x21: IABT (current EL), IL = 32 bits
    SET = 0, FnV = 0
    EA = 0, S1PTW = 0
    FSC = 0x04: level 0 translation fault
  user pgtable: 4k pages, 48-bit VAs, pgdp=0000000101059000
  [0000000000000000] pgd=0000000000000000, p4d=0000000000000000
  Internal error: Oops: 0000000086000004 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
  Modules linked in:
  CPU: 2 PID: 371 Comm: qemu-system-aar Not tainted 6.8.0-rc7-gde77230ac23a #9
  Hardware name: linux,dummy-virt (DT)
  pstate: 81400809 (Nzcv daif +PAN -UAO -TCO +DIT -SSBS BTYPE=-c)
  pc : 0x0
  lr : iommufd_hwpt_invalidate+0xa4/0x204
  sp : ffff800080f3bcc0
  x29: ffff800080f3bcf0 x28: ffff0000c369b300 x27: 0000000000000000
  x26: 0000000000000000 x25: 0000000000000000 x24: 0000000000000000
  x23: 0000000000000000 x22: 00000000c1e334a0 x21: ffff0000c1e334a0
  x20: ffff800080f3bd38 x19: ffff800080f3bd58 x18: 0000000000000000
  x17: 0000000000000000 x16: 0000000000000000 x15: 0000ffff8240d6d8
  x14: 0000000000000000 x13: 0000000000000000 x12: 0000000000000000
  x11: 0000000000000000 x10: 0000000000000000 x9 : 0000000000000000
  x8 : 0000001000000002 x7 : 0000fffeac1ec950 x6 : 0000000000000000
  x5 : ffff800080f3bd78 x4 : 0000000000000003 x3 : 0000000000000002
  x2 : 0000000000000000 x1 : ffff800080f3bcc8 x0 : ffff0000c6034d80
  Call trace:
   0x0
   iommufd_fops_ioctl+0x154/0x274
   __arm64_sys_ioctl+0xac/0xf0
   invoke_syscall+0x48/0x110
   el0_svc_common.constprop.0+0x40/0xe0
   do_el0_svc+0x1c/0x28
   el0_svc+0x34/0xb4
   el0t_64_sync_handler+0x120/0x12c
   el0t_64_sync+0x190/0x194

All existing drivers implement this op for nesting, this is mostly a
bisection aid.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46825 | wifi: iwlwifi: mvm: use IWL_FW_CHECK for link ID check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46825</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: iwlwifi: mvm: use IWL_FW_CHECK for link ID check

The lookup function iwl_mvm_rcu_fw_link_id_to_link_conf() is
normally called with input from the firmware, so it should use
IWL_FW_CHECK() instead of WARN_ON().</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46826 | ELF: fix kernel.randomize_va_space double read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46826</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ELF: fix kernel.randomize_va_space double read

ELF loader uses "randomize_va_space" twice. It is sysctl and can change
at any moment, so 2 loads could see 2 different values in theory with
unpredictable consequences.

Issue exactly one load for consistent value across one exec.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46827 | wifi: ath12k: fix firmware crash due to invalid peer nss</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46827</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: ath12k: fix firmware crash due to invalid peer nss

Currently, if the access point receives an association
request containing an Extended HE Capabilities Information
Element with an invalid MCS-NSS, it triggers a firmware
crash.

This issue arises when EHT-PHY capabilities shows support
for a bandwidth and MCS-NSS set for that particular
bandwidth is filled by zeros and due to this, driver obtains
peer_nss as 0 and sending this value to firmware causes
crash.

Address this issue by implementing a validation step for
the peer_nss value before passing it to the firmware. If
the value is greater than zero, proceed with forwarding
it to the firmware. However, if the value is invalid,
reject the association request to prevent potential
firmware crashes.

Tested-on: QCN9274 hw2.0 PCI WLAN.WBE.1.0.1-00029-QCAHKSWPL_SILICONZ-1</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46828 | sched: sch_cake: fix bulk flow accounting logic for host fairness</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46828</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

sched: sch_cake: fix bulk flow accounting logic for host fairness

In sch_cake, we keep track of the count of active bulk flows per host,
when running in dst/src host fairness mode, which is used as the
round-robin weight when iterating through flows. The count of active
bulk flows is updated whenever a flow changes state.

This has a peculiar interaction with the hash collision handling: when a
hash collision occurs (after the set-associative hashing), the state of
the hash bucket is simply updated to match the new packet that collided,
and if host fairness is enabled, that also means assigning new per-host
state to the flow. For this reason, the bulk flow counters of the
host(s) assigned to the flow are decremented, before new state is
assigned (and the counters, which may not belong to the same host
anymore, are incremented again).

Back when this code was introduced, the host fairness mode was always
enabled, so the decrement was unconditional. When the configuration
flags were introduced the *increment* was made conditional, but
the *decrement* was not. Which of course can lead to a spurious
decrement (and associated wrap-around to U16_MAX).

AFAICT, when host fairness is disabled, the decrement and wrap-around
happens as soon as a hash collision occurs (which is not that common in
itself, due to the set-associative hashing). However, in most cases this
is harmless, as the value is only used when host fairness mode is
enabled. So in order to trigger an array overflow, sch_cake has to first
be configured with host fairness disabled, and while running in this
mode, a hash collision has to occur to cause the overflow. Then, the
qdisc has to be reconfigured to enable host fairness, which leads to the
array out-of-bounds because the wrapped-around value is retained and
used as an array index. It seems that syzbot managed to trigger this,
which is quite impressive in its own right.

This patch fixes the issue by introducing the same conditional check on
decrement as is used on increment.

The original bug predates the upstreaming of cake, but the commit listed
in the Fixes tag touched that code, meaning that this patch won't apply
before that.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46829 | rtmutex: Drop rt_mutex::wait_lock before scheduling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46829</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

rtmutex: Drop rt_mutex::wait_lock before scheduling

rt_mutex_handle_deadlock() is called with rt_mutex::wait_lock held.  In the
good case it returns with the lock held and in the deadlock case it emits a
warning and goes into an endless scheduling loop with the lock held, which
triggers the 'scheduling in atomic' warning.

Unlock rt_mutex::wait_lock in the dead lock case before issuing the warning
and dropping into the schedule for ever loop.

[ tglx: Moved unlock before the WARN(), removed the pointless comment,
  	massaged changelog, added Fixes tag ]</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46830 | KVM: x86: Acquire kvm-&amp;gt;srcu when handling KVM_SET_VCPU_EVENTS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46830</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

KVM: x86: Acquire kvm-&gt;srcu when handling KVM_SET_VCPU_EVENTS

Grab kvm-&gt;srcu when processing KVM_SET_VCPU_EVENTS, as KVM will forcibly
leave nested VMX/SVM if SMM mode is being toggled, and leaving nested VMX
reads guest memory.

Note, kvm_vcpu_ioctl_x86_set_vcpu_events() can also be called from KVM_RUN
via sync_regs(), which already holds SRCU.  I.e. trying to precisely use
kvm_vcpu_srcu_read_lock() around the problematic SMM code would cause
problems.  Acquiring SRCU isn't all that expensive, so for simplicity,
grab it unconditionally for KVM_SET_VCPU_EVENTS.

 =============================
 WARNING: suspicious RCU usage
 6.10.0-rc7-332d2c1d713e-next-vm #552 Not tainted
 -----------------------------
 include/linux/kvm_host.h:1027 suspicious rcu_dereference_check() usage!

 other info that might help us debug this:

 rcu_scheduler_active = 2, debug_locks = 1
 1 lock held by repro/1071:
  #0: ffff88811e424430 (&amp;amp;vcpu-&gt;mutex){+.+.}-{3:3}, at: kvm_vcpu_ioctl+0x7d/0x970 [kvm]

 stack backtrace:
 CPU: 15 PID: 1071 Comm: repro Not tainted 6.10.0-rc7-332d2c1d713e-next-vm #552
 Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS 0.0.0 02/06/2015
 Call Trace:
  
  dump_stack_lvl+0x7f/0x90
  lockdep_rcu_suspicious+0x13f/0x1a0
  kvm_vcpu_gfn_to_memslot+0x168/0x190 [kvm]
  kvm_vcpu_read_guest+0x3e/0x90 [kvm]
  nested_vmx_load_msr+0x6b/0x1d0 [kvm_intel]
  load_vmcs12_host_state+0x432/0xb40 [kvm_intel]
  vmx_leave_nested+0x30/0x40 [kvm_intel]
  kvm_vcpu_ioctl_x86_set_vcpu_events+0x15d/0x2b0 [kvm]
  kvm_arch_vcpu_ioctl+0x1107/0x1750 [kvm]
  ? mark_held_locks+0x49/0x70
  ? kvm_vcpu_ioctl+0x7d/0x970 [kvm]
  ? kvm_vcpu_ioctl+0x497/0x970 [kvm]
  kvm_vcpu_ioctl+0x497/0x970 [kvm]
  ? lock_acquire+0xba/0x2d0
  ? find_held_lock+0x2b/0x80
  ? do_user_addr_fault+0x40c/0x6f0
  ? lock_release+0xb7/0x270
  __x64_sys_ioctl+0x82/0xb0
  do_syscall_64+0x6c/0x170
  entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x4b/0x53
 RIP: 0033:0x7ff11eb1b539</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46831 | net: microchip: vcap: Fix use-after-free error in kunit test</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46831</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: microchip: vcap: Fix use-after-free error in kunit test

This is a clear use-after-free error. We remove it, and rely on checking
the return code of vcap_del_rule.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46832 | MIPS: cevt-r4k: Don&amp;#x27;t call get_c0_compare_int if timer irq is installed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46832</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

MIPS: cevt-r4k: Don't call get_c0_compare_int if timer irq is installed

This avoids warning:

[    0.118053] BUG: sleeping function called from invalid context at kernel/locking/mutex.c:283

Caused by get_c0_compare_int on secondary CPU.

We also skipped saving IRQ number to struct clock_event_device *cd as
it's never used by clockevent core, as per comments it's only meant
for "non CPU local devices".</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46833 | net: hns3: void array out of bound when loop tnl_num</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46833</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: hns3: void array out of bound when loop tnl_num

When query reg inf of SSU, it loops tnl_num times. However, tnl_num comes
from hardware and the length of array is a fixed value. To void array out
of bound, make sure the loop time is not greater than the length of array</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46834 | ethtool: fail closed if we can&amp;#x27;t get max channel used in indirection tables</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46834</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ethtool: fail closed if we can't get max channel used in indirection tables

Commit 0d1b7d6c9274 ("bnxt: fix crashes when reducing ring count with
active RSS contexts") proves that allowing indirection table to contain
channels with out of bounds IDs may lead to crashes. Currently the
max channel check in the core gets skipped if driver can't fetch
the indirection table or when we can't allocate memory.

Both of those conditions should be extremely rare but if they do
happen we should try to be safe and fail the channel change.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46835 | drm/amdgpu: Fix smatch static checker warning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46835</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdgpu: Fix smatch static checker warning

adev-&gt;gfx.imu.funcs could be NULL</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46836 | usb: gadget: aspeed_udc: validate endpoint index for ast udc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46836</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: gadget: aspeed_udc: validate endpoint index for ast udc

We should verify the bound of the array to assure that host
may not manipulate the index to point past endpoint array.

Found by static analysis.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46837 | drm/panthor: Restrict high priorities on group_create</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46837</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/panthor: Restrict high priorities on group_create

We were allowing any users to create a high priority group without any
permission checks. As a result, this was allowing possible denial of
service.

We now only allow the DRM master or users with the CAP_SYS_NICE
capability to set higher priorities than PANTHOR_GROUP_PRIORITY_MEDIUM.

As the sole user of that uAPI lives in Mesa and hardcode a value of
MEDIUM [1], this should be safe to do.

Additionally, as those checks are performed at the ioctl level,
panthor_group_create now only check for priority level validity.

[1]https://gitlab.freedesktop.org/mesa/mesa/-/blob/f390835074bdf162a63deb0311d1a6de527f9f89/src/gallium/drivers/panfrost/pan_csf.c#L1038</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46838 | userfaultfd: don&amp;#x27;t BUG_ON() if khugepaged yanks our page table</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46838</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

userfaultfd: don't BUG_ON() if khugepaged yanks our page table

Since khugepaged was changed to allow retracting page tables in file
mappings without holding the mmap lock, these BUG_ON()s are wrong - get
rid of them.

We could also remove the preceding "if (unlikely(...))" block, but then we
could reach pte_offset_map_lock() with transhuge pages not just for file
mappings but also for anonymous mappings - which would probably be fine
but I think is not necessarily expected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46839 | workqueue: Improve scalability of workqueue watchdog touch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46839</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

workqueue: Improve scalability of workqueue watchdog touch

On a ~2000 CPU powerpc system, hard lockups have been observed in the
workqueue code when stop_machine runs (in this case due to CPU hotplug).
This is due to lots of CPUs spinning in multi_cpu_stop, calling
touch_nmi_watchdog() which ends up calling wq_watchdog_touch().
wq_watchdog_touch() writes to the global variable wq_watchdog_touched,
and that can find itself in the same cacheline as other important
workqueue data, which slows down operations to the point of lockups.

In the case of the following abridged trace, worker_pool_idr was in
the hot line, causing the lockups to always appear at idr_find.

  watchdog: CPU 1125 self-detected hard LOCKUP @ idr_find
  Call Trace:
  get_work_pool
  __queue_work
  call_timer_fn
  run_timer_softirq
  __do_softirq
  do_softirq_own_stack
  irq_exit
  timer_interrupt
  decrementer_common_virt
  * interrupt: 900 (timer) at multi_cpu_stop
  multi_cpu_stop
  cpu_stopper_thread
  smpboot_thread_fn
  kthread

Fix this by having wq_watchdog_touch() only write to the line if the
last time a touch was recorded exceeds 1/4 of the watchdog threshold.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46840 | btrfs: clean up our handling of refs == 0 in snapshot delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46840</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: clean up our handling of refs == 0 in snapshot delete

In reada we BUG_ON(refs == 0), which could be unkind since we aren't
holding a lock on the extent leaf and thus could get a transient
incorrect answer.  In walk_down_proc we also BUG_ON(refs == 0), which
could happen if we have extent tree corruption.  Change that to return
-EUCLEAN.  In do_walk_down() we catch this case and handle it correctly,
however we return -EIO, which -EUCLEAN is a more appropriate error code.
Finally in walk_up_proc we have the same BUG_ON(refs == 0), so convert
that to proper error handling.  Also adjust the error message so we can
actually do something with the information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46841 | btrfs: don&amp;#x27;t BUG_ON on ENOMEM from btrfs_lookup_extent_info() in walk_down_proc()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46841</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: don't BUG_ON on ENOMEM from btrfs_lookup_extent_info() in walk_down_proc()

We handle errors here properly, ENOMEM isn't fatal, return the error.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46842 | scsi: lpfc: Handle mailbox timeouts in lpfc_get_sfp_info</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46842</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

scsi: lpfc: Handle mailbox timeouts in lpfc_get_sfp_info

The MBX_TIMEOUT return code is not handled in lpfc_get_sfp_info and the
routine unconditionally frees submitted mailbox commands regardless of
return status.  The issue is that for MBX_TIMEOUT cases, when firmware
returns SFP information at a later time, that same mailbox memory region
references previously freed memory in its cmpl routine.

Fix by adding checks for the MBX_TIMEOUT return code.  During mailbox
resource cleanup, check the mbox flag to make sure that the wait did not
timeout.  If the MBOX_WAKE flag is not set, then do not free the resources
because it will be freed when firmware completes the mailbox at a later
time in its cmpl routine.

Also, increase the timeout from 30 to 60 seconds to accommodate boot
scripts requiring longer timeouts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46843 | scsi: ufs: core: Remove SCSI host only if added</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46843</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

scsi: ufs: core: Remove SCSI host only if added

If host tries to remove ufshcd driver from a UFS device it would cause a
kernel panic if ufshcd_async_scan fails during ufshcd_probe_hba before
adding a SCSI host with scsi_add_host and MCQ is enabled since SCSI host
has been defered after MCQ configuration introduced by commit 0cab4023ec7b
("scsi: ufs: core: Defer adding host to SCSI if MCQ is supported").

To guarantee that SCSI host is removed only if it has been added, set the
scsi_host_added flag to true after adding a SCSI host and check whether it
is set or not before removing it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46844 | um: line: always fill *error_out in setup_one_line()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46844</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

um: line: always fill *error_out in setup_one_line()

The pointer isn't initialized by callers, but I have
encountered cases where it's still printed; initialize
it in all possible cases in setup_one_line().</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46845 | tracing/timerlat: Only clear timer if a kthread exists</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46845</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tracing/timerlat: Only clear timer if a kthread exists

The timerlat tracer can use user space threads to check for osnoise and
timer latency. If the program using this is killed via a SIGTERM, the
threads are shutdown one at a time and another tracing instance can start
up resetting the threads before they are fully closed. That causes the
hrtimer assigned to the kthread to be shutdown and freed twice when the
dying thread finally closes the file descriptors, causing a use-after-free
bug.

Only cancel the hrtimer if the associated thread is still around. Also add
the interface_lock around the resetting of the tlat_var-&gt;kthread.

Note, this is just a quick fix that can be backported to stable. A real
fix is to have a better synchronization between the shutdown of old
threads and the starting of new ones.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46846 | spi: rockchip: Resolve unbalanced runtime PM / system PM handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46846</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

spi: rockchip: Resolve unbalanced runtime PM / system PM handling

Commit e882575efc77 ("spi: rockchip: Suspend and resume the bus during
NOIRQ_SYSTEM_SLEEP_PM ops") stopped respecting runtime PM status and
simply disabled clocks unconditionally when suspending the system. This
causes problems when the device is already runtime suspended when we go
to sleep -- in which case we double-disable clocks and produce a
WARNing.

Switch back to pm_runtime_force_{suspend,resume}(), because that still
seems like the right thing to do, and the aforementioned commit makes no
explanation why it stopped using it.

Also, refactor some of the resume() error handling, because it's not
actually a good idea to re-disable clocks on failure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46847 | mm: vmalloc: ensure vmap_block is initialised before adding to queue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46847</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: vmalloc: ensure vmap_block is initialised before adding to queue

Commit 8c61291fd850 ("mm: fix incorrect vbq reference in
purge_fragmented_block") extended the 'vmap_block' structure to contain a
'cpu' field which is set at allocation time to the id of the initialising
CPU.

When a new 'vmap_block' is being instantiated by new_vmap_block(), the
partially initialised structure is added to the local 'vmap_block_queue'
xarray before the 'cpu' field has been initialised.  If another CPU is
concurrently walking the xarray (e.g.  via vm_unmap_aliases()), then it
may perform an out-of-bounds access to the remote queue thanks to an
uninitialised index.

This has been observed as UBSAN errors in Android:

 | Internal error: UBSAN: array index out of bounds: 00000000f2005512 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
 |
 | Call trace:
 |  purge_fragmented_block+0x204/0x21c
 |  _vm_unmap_aliases+0x170/0x378
 |  vm_unmap_aliases+0x1c/0x28
 |  change_memory_common+0x1dc/0x26c
 |  set_memory_ro+0x18/0x24
 |  module_enable_ro+0x98/0x238
 |  do_init_module+0x1b0/0x310

Move the initialisation of 'vb-&gt;cpu' in new_vmap_block() ahead of the
addition to the xarray.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46848 | perf/x86/intel: Limit the period on Haswell</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46848</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

perf/x86/intel: Limit the period on Haswell

Running the ltp test cve-2015-3290 concurrently reports the following
warnings.

perfevents: irq loop stuck!
  WARNING: CPU: 31 PID: 32438 at arch/x86/events/intel/core.c:3174
  intel_pmu_handle_irq+0x285/0x370
  Call Trace:
   
   ? __warn+0xa4/0x220
   ? intel_pmu_handle_irq+0x285/0x370
   ? __report_bug+0x123/0x130
   ? intel_pmu_handle_irq+0x285/0x370
   ? __report_bug+0x123/0x130
   ? intel_pmu_handle_irq+0x285/0x370
   ? report_bug+0x3e/0xa0
   ? handle_bug+0x3c/0x70
   ? exc_invalid_op+0x18/0x50
   ? asm_exc_invalid_op+0x1a/0x20
   ? irq_work_claim+0x1e/0x40
   ? intel_pmu_handle_irq+0x285/0x370
   perf_event_nmi_handler+0x3d/0x60
   nmi_handle+0x104/0x330

Thanks to Thomas Gleixner's analysis, the issue is caused by the low
initial period (1) of the frequency estimation algorithm, which triggers
the defects of the HW, specifically erratum HSW11 and HSW143. (For the
details, please refer https://lore.kernel.org/lkml/87plq9l5d2.ffs@tglx/)

The HSW11 requires a period larger than 100 for the INST_RETIRED.ALL
event, but the initial period in the freq mode is 1. The erratum is the
same as the BDM11, which has been supported in the kernel. A minimum
period of 128 is enforced as well on HSW.

HSW143 is regarding that the fixed counter 1 may overcount 32 with the
Hyper-Threading is enabled. However, based on the test, the hardware
has more issues than it tells. Besides the fixed counter 1, the message
'interrupt took too long' can be observed on any counter which was armed
with a period &lt; 32 and two events expired in the same NMI. A minimum
period of 32 is enforced for the rest of the events.
The recommended workaround code of the HSW143 is not implemented.
Because it only addresses the issue for the fixed counter. It brings
extra overhead through extra MSR writing. No related overcounting issue
has been reported so far.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46849 | ASoC: meson: axg-card: fix &amp;#x27;use-after-free&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46849</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ASoC: meson: axg-card: fix 'use-after-free'

Buffer 'card-&gt;dai_link' is reallocated in 'meson_card_reallocate_links()',
so move 'pad' pointer initialization after this function when memory is
already reallocated.

Kasan bug report:

==================================================================
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in axg_card_add_link+0x76c/0x9bc
Read of size 8 at addr ffff000000e8b260 by task modprobe/356

CPU: 0 PID: 356 Comm: modprobe Tainted: G O 6.9.12-sdkernel #1
Call trace:
 dump_backtrace+0x94/0xec
 show_stack+0x18/0x24
 dump_stack_lvl+0x78/0x90
 print_report+0xfc/0x5c0
 kasan_report+0xb8/0xfc
 __asan_load8+0x9c/0xb8
 axg_card_add_link+0x76c/0x9bc [snd_soc_meson_axg_sound_card]
 meson_card_probe+0x344/0x3b8 [snd_soc_meson_card_utils]
 platform_probe+0x8c/0xf4
 really_probe+0x110/0x39c
 __driver_probe_device+0xb8/0x18c
 driver_probe_device+0x108/0x1d8
 __driver_attach+0xd0/0x25c
 bus_for_each_dev+0xe0/0x154
 driver_attach+0x34/0x44
 bus_add_driver+0x134/0x294
 driver_register+0xa8/0x1e8
 __platform_driver_register+0x44/0x54
 axg_card_pdrv_init+0x20/0x1000 [snd_soc_meson_axg_sound_card]
 do_one_initcall+0xdc/0x25c
 do_init_module+0x10c/0x334
 load_module+0x24c4/0x26cc
 init_module_from_file+0xd4/0x128
 __arm64_sys_finit_module+0x1f4/0x41c
 invoke_syscall+0x60/0x188
 el0_svc_common.constprop.0+0x78/0x13c
 do_el0_svc+0x30/0x40
 el0_svc+0x38/0x78
 el0t_64_sync_handler+0x100/0x12c
 el0t_64_sync+0x190/0x194</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46850 | drm/amd/display: Avoid race between dcn35_set_drr() and dc_state_destruct()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46850</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Avoid race between dcn35_set_drr() and dc_state_destruct()

dc_state_destruct() nulls the resource context of the DC state. The pipe
context passed to dcn35_set_drr() is a member of this resource context.

If dc_state_destruct() is called parallel to the IRQ processing (which
calls dcn35_set_drr() at some point), we can end up using already nulled
function callback fields of struct stream_resource.

The logic in dcn35_set_drr() already tries to avoid this, by checking tg
against NULL. But if the nulling happens exactly after the NULL check and
before the next access, then we get a race.

Avoid this by copying tg first to a local variable, and then use this
variable for all the operations. This should work, as long as nobody
frees the resource pool where the timing generators live.

(cherry picked from commit 0607a50c004798a96e62c089a4c34c220179dcb5)</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46851 | drm/amd/display: Avoid race between dcn10_set_drr() and dc_state_destruct()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46851</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Avoid race between dcn10_set_drr() and dc_state_destruct()

dc_state_destruct() nulls the resource context of the DC state. The pipe
context passed to dcn10_set_drr() is a member of this resource context.

If dc_state_destruct() is called parallel to the IRQ processing (which
calls dcn10_set_drr() at some point), we can end up using already nulled
function callback fields of struct stream_resource.

The logic in dcn10_set_drr() already tries to avoid this, by checking tg
against NULL. But if the nulling happens exactly after the NULL check and
before the next access, then we get a race.

Avoid this by copying tg first to a local variable, and then use this
variable for all the operations. This should work, as long as nobody
frees the resource pool where the timing generators live.

(cherry picked from commit a3cc326a43bdc48fbdf53443e1027a03e309b643)</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46852 | dma-buf: heaps: Fix off-by-one in CMA heap fault handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46852</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

dma-buf: heaps: Fix off-by-one in CMA heap fault handler

Until VM_DONTEXPAND was added in commit 1c1914d6e8c6 ("dma-buf: heaps:
Don't track CMA dma-buf pages under RssFile") it was possible to obtain
a mapping larger than the buffer size via mremap and bypass the overflow
check in dma_buf_mmap_internal. When using such a mapping to attempt to
fault past the end of the buffer, the CMA heap fault handler also checks
the fault offset against the buffer size, but gets the boundary wrong by
1. Fix the boundary check so that we don't read off the end of the pages
array and insert an arbitrary page in the mapping.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46853 | spi: nxp-fspi: fix the KASAN report out-of-bounds bug</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46853</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

spi: nxp-fspi: fix the KASAN report out-of-bounds bug

Change the memcpy length to fix the out-of-bounds issue when writing the
data that is not 4 byte aligned to TX FIFO.

To reproduce the issue, write 3 bytes data to NOR chip.

dd if=3b of=/dev/mtd0
[   36.926103] ==================================================================
[   36.933409] BUG: KASAN: slab-out-of-bounds in nxp_fspi_exec_op+0x26ec/0x2838
[   36.940514] Read of size 4 at addr ffff00081037c2a0 by task dd/455
[   36.946721]
[   36.948235] CPU: 3 UID: 0 PID: 455 Comm: dd Not tainted 6.11.0-rc5-gc7b0e37c8434 #1070
[   36.956185] Hardware name: Freescale i.MX8QM MEK (DT)
[   36.961260] Call trace:
[   36.963723]  dump_backtrace+0x90/0xe8
[   36.967414]  show_stack+0x18/0x24
[   36.970749]  dump_stack_lvl+0x78/0x90
[   36.974451]  print_report+0x114/0x5cc
[   36.978151]  kasan_report+0xa4/0xf0
[   36.981670]  __asan_report_load_n_noabort+0x1c/0x28
[   36.986587]  nxp_fspi_exec_op+0x26ec/0x2838
[   36.990800]  spi_mem_exec_op+0x8ec/0xd30
[   36.994762]  spi_mem_no_dirmap_read+0x190/0x1e0
[   36.999323]  spi_mem_dirmap_write+0x238/0x32c
[   37.003710]  spi_nor_write_data+0x220/0x374
[   37.007932]  spi_nor_write+0x110/0x2e8
[   37.011711]  mtd_write_oob_std+0x154/0x1f0
[   37.015838]  mtd_write_oob+0x104/0x1d0
[   37.019617]  mtd_write+0xb8/0x12c
[   37.022953]  mtdchar_write+0x224/0x47c
[   37.026732]  vfs_write+0x1e4/0x8c8
[   37.030163]  ksys_write+0xec/0x1d0
[   37.033586]  __arm64_sys_write+0x6c/0x9c
[   37.037539]  invoke_syscall+0x6c/0x258
[   37.041327]  el0_svc_common.constprop.0+0x160/0x22c
[   37.046244]  do_el0_svc+0x44/0x5c
[   37.049589]  el0_svc+0x38/0x78
[   37.052681]  el0t_64_sync_handler+0x13c/0x158
[   37.057077]  el0t_64_sync+0x190/0x194
[   37.060775]
[   37.062274] Allocated by task 455:
[   37.065701]  kasan_save_stack+0x2c/0x54
[   37.069570]  kasan_save_track+0x20/0x3c
[   37.073438]  kasan_save_alloc_info+0x40/0x54
[   37.077736]  __kasan_kmalloc+0xa0/0xb8
[   37.081515]  __kmalloc_noprof+0x158/0x2f8
[   37.085563]  mtd_kmalloc_up_to+0x120/0x154
[   37.089690]  mtdchar_write+0x130/0x47c
[   37.093469]  vfs_write+0x1e4/0x8c8
[   37.096901]  ksys_write+0xec/0x1d0
[   37.100332]  __arm64_sys_write+0x6c/0x9c
[   37.104287]  invoke_syscall+0x6c/0x258
[   37.108064]  el0_svc_common.constprop.0+0x160/0x22c
[   37.112972]  do_el0_svc+0x44/0x5c
[   37.116319]  el0_svc+0x38/0x78
[   37.119401]  el0t_64_sync_handler+0x13c/0x158
[   37.123788]  el0t_64_sync+0x190/0x194
[   37.127474]
[   37.128977] The buggy address belongs to the object at ffff00081037c2a0
[   37.128977]  which belongs to the cache kmalloc-8 of size 8
[   37.141177] The buggy address is located 0 bytes inside of
[   37.141177]  allocated 3-byte region [ffff00081037c2a0, ffff00081037c2a3)
[   37.153465]
[   37.154971] The buggy address belongs to the physical page:
[   37.160559] page: refcount:1 mapcount:0 mapping:0000000000000000 index:0x0 pfn:0x89037c
[   37.168596] flags: 0xbfffe0000000000(node=0|zone=2|lastcpupid=0x1ffff)
[   37.175149] page_type: 0xfdffffff(slab)
[   37.179021] raw: 0bfffe0000000000 ffff000800002500 dead000000000122 0000000000000000
[   37.186788] raw: 0000000000000000 0000000080800080 00000001fdffffff 0000000000000000
[   37.194553] page dumped because: kasan: bad access detected
[   37.200144]
[   37.201647] Memory state around the buggy address:
[   37.206460]  ffff00081037c180: fa fc fc fc fa fc fc fc fa fc fc fc fa fc fc fc
[   37.213701]  ffff00081037c200: fa fc fc fc 05 fc fc fc 03 fc fc fc 02 fc fc fc
[   37.220946] &gt;ffff00081037c280: 06 fc fc fc 03 fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc
[   37.228186]                                ^
[   37.232473]  ffff00081037c300: fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc
[   37.239718]  ffff00081037c380: fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc
[   37.246962] ==============================================================
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46854 | net: dpaa: Pad packets to ETH_ZLEN</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46854</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: dpaa: Pad packets to ETH_ZLEN

When sending packets under 60 bytes, up to three bytes of the buffer
following the data may be leaked. Avoid this by extending all packets to
ETH_ZLEN, ensuring nothing is leaked in the padding. This bug can be
reproduced by running

	$ ping -s 11 destination</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46855 | netfilter: nft_socket: fix sk refcount leaks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46855</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nft_socket: fix sk refcount leaks

We must put 'sk' reference before returning.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46856 | net: phy: dp83822: Fix NULL pointer dereference on DP83825 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46856</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: phy: dp83822: Fix NULL pointer dereference on DP83825 devices

The probe() function is only used for DP83822 and DP83826 PHY,
leaving the private data pointer uninitialized for the DP83825 models
which causes a NULL pointer dereference in the recently introduced/changed
functions dp8382x_config_init() and dp83822_set_wol().

Add the dp8382x_probe() function, so all PHY models will have a valid
private data pointer to fix this issue and also prevent similar issues
in the future.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46857 | net/mlx5: Fix bridge mode operations when there are no VFs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46857</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/mlx5: Fix bridge mode operations when there are no VFs

Currently, trying to set the bridge mode attribute when numvfs=0 leads to a
crash:

bridge link set dev eth2 hwmode vepa

[  168.967392] BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000030
[...]
[  168.969989] RIP: 0010:mlx5_add_flow_rules+0x1f/0x300 [mlx5_core]
[...]
[  168.976037] Call Trace:
[  168.976188]  
[  168.978620]  _mlx5_eswitch_set_vepa_locked+0x113/0x230 [mlx5_core]
[  168.979074]  mlx5_eswitch_set_vepa+0x7f/0xa0 [mlx5_core]
[  168.979471]  rtnl_bridge_setlink+0xe9/0x1f0
[  168.979714]  rtnetlink_rcv_msg+0x159/0x400
[  168.980451]  netlink_rcv_skb+0x54/0x100
[  168.980675]  netlink_unicast+0x241/0x360
[  168.980918]  netlink_sendmsg+0x1f6/0x430
[  168.981162]  ____sys_sendmsg+0x3bb/0x3f0
[  168.982155]  ___sys_sendmsg+0x88/0xd0
[  168.985036]  __sys_sendmsg+0x59/0xa0
[  168.985477]  do_syscall_64+0x79/0x150
[  168.987273]  entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x76/0x7e
[  168.987773] RIP: 0033:0x7f8f7950f917

(esw-&gt;fdb_table.legacy.vepa_fdb is null)

The bridge mode is only relevant when there are multiple functions per
port. Therefore, prevent setting and getting this setting when there are no
VFs.

Note that after this change, there are no settings to change on the PF
interface using `bridge link` when there are no VFs, so the interface no
longer appears in the `bridge link` output.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46858 | mptcp: pm: Fix uaf in __timer_delete_sync</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46858</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mptcp: pm: Fix uaf in __timer_delete_sync

There are two paths to access mptcp_pm_del_add_timer, result in a race
condition:

     CPU1				CPU2
     ====                               ====
     net_rx_action
     napi_poll                          netlink_sendmsg
     __napi_poll                        netlink_unicast
     process_backlog                    netlink_unicast_kernel
     __netif_receive_skb                genl_rcv
     __netif_receive_skb_one_core       netlink_rcv_skb
     NF_HOOK                            genl_rcv_msg
     ip_local_deliver_finish            genl_family_rcv_msg
     ip_protocol_deliver_rcu            genl_family_rcv_msg_doit
     tcp_v4_rcv                         mptcp_pm_nl_flush_addrs_doit
     tcp_v4_do_rcv                      mptcp_nl_remove_addrs_list
     tcp_rcv_established                mptcp_pm_remove_addrs_and_subflows
     tcp_data_queue                     remove_anno_list_by_saddr
     mptcp_incoming_options             mptcp_pm_del_add_timer
     mptcp_pm_del_add_timer             kfree(entry)

In remove_anno_list_by_saddr(running on CPU2), after leaving the critical
zone protected by "pm.lock", the entry will be released, which leads to the
occurrence of uaf in the mptcp_pm_del_add_timer(running on CPU1).

Keeping a reference to add_timer inside the lock, and calling
sk_stop_timer_sync() with this reference, instead of "entry-&gt;add_timer".

Move list_del(&amp;amp;entry-&gt;list) to mptcp_pm_del_add_timer and inside the pm lock,
do not directly access any members of the entry outside the pm lock, which
can avoid similar "entry-&gt;x" uaf.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46859 | platform/x86: panasonic-laptop: Fix SINF array out of bounds accesses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46859</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

platform/x86: panasonic-laptop: Fix SINF array out of bounds accesses

The panasonic laptop code in various places uses the SINF array with index
values of 0 - SINF_CUR_BRIGHT(0x0d) without checking that the SINF array
is big enough.

Not all panasonic laptops have this many SINF array entries, for example
the Toughbook CF-18 model only has 10 SINF array entries. So it only
supports the AC+DC brightness entries and mute.

Check that the SINF array has a minimum size which covers all AC+DC
brightness entries and refuse to load if the SINF array is smaller.

For higher SINF indexes hide the sysfs attributes when the SINF array
does not contain an entry for that attribute, avoiding show()/store()
accessing the array out of bounds and add bounds checking to the probe()
and resume() code accessing these.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46860 | wifi: mt76: mt7921: fix NULL pointer access in mt7921_ipv6_addr_change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46860</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: mt76: mt7921: fix NULL pointer access in mt7921_ipv6_addr_change

When disabling wifi mt7921_ipv6_addr_change() is called as a notifier.
At this point mvif-&gt;phy is already NULL so we cannot use it here.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46861 | usbnet: ipheth: do not stop RX on failing RX callback</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46861</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usbnet: ipheth: do not stop RX on failing RX callback

RX callbacks can fail for multiple reasons:

* Payload too short
* Payload formatted incorrecly (e.g. bad NCM framing)
* Lack of memory

None of these should cause the driver to seize up.

Make such failures non-critical and continue processing further
incoming URBs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46862 | ASoC: Intel: soc-acpi-intel-mtl-match: add missing empty item</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46862</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ASoC: Intel: soc-acpi-intel-mtl-match: add missing empty item

There is no links_num in struct snd_soc_acpi_mach {}, and we test
!link-&gt;num_adr as a condition to end the loop in hda_sdw_machine_select().
So an empty item in struct snd_soc_acpi_link_adr array is required.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46863 | ASoC: Intel: soc-acpi-intel-lnl-match: add missing empty item</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46863</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ASoC: Intel: soc-acpi-intel-lnl-match: add missing empty item

There is no links_num in struct snd_soc_acpi_mach {}, and we test
!link-&gt;num_adr as a condition to end the loop in hda_sdw_machine_select().
So an empty item in struct snd_soc_acpi_link_adr array is required.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46864 | x86/hyperv: fix kexec crash due to VP assist page corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46864</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/hyperv: fix kexec crash due to VP assist page corruption

commit 9636be85cc5b ("x86/hyperv: Fix hyperv_pcpu_input_arg handling when
CPUs go online/offline") introduces a new cpuhp state for hyperv
initialization.

cpuhp_setup_state() returns the state number if state is
CPUHP_AP_ONLINE_DYN or CPUHP_BP_PREPARE_DYN and 0 for all other states.
For the hyperv case, since a new cpuhp state was introduced it would
return 0. However, in hv_machine_shutdown(), the cpuhp_remove_state() call
is conditioned upon "hyperv_init_cpuhp &gt; 0". This will never be true and
so hv_cpu_die() won't be called on all CPUs. This means the VP assist page
won't be reset. When the kexec kernel tries to setup the VP assist page
again, the hypervisor corrupts the memory region of the old VP assist page
causing a panic in case the kexec kernel is using that memory elsewhere.
This was originally fixed in commit dfe94d4086e4 ("x86/hyperv: Fix kexec
panic/hang issues").

Get rid of hyperv_init_cpuhp entirely since we are no longer using a
dynamic cpuhp state and use CPUHP_AP_HYPERV_ONLINE directly with
cpuhp_remove_state().</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46865 | fou: fix initialization of grc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46865</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fou: fix initialization of grc

The grc must be initialize first. There can be a condition where if
fou is NULL, goto out will be executed and grc would be used
uninitialized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46866 | drm/xe/client: add missing bo locking in show_meminfo()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46866</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/xe/client: add missing bo locking in show_meminfo()

bo_meminfo() wants to inspect bo state like tt and the ttm resource,
however this state can change at any point leading to stuff like NPD and
UAF, if the bo lock is not held. Grab the bo lock when calling
bo_meminfo(), ensuring we drop any spinlocks first. In the case of
object_idr we now also need to hold a ref.

v2 (MattB)
  - Also add xe_bo_assert_held()

(cherry picked from commit 4f63d712fa104c3ebefcb289d1e733e86d8698c7)</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46867 | drm/xe/client: fix deadlock in show_meminfo()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46867</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/xe/client: fix deadlock in show_meminfo()

There is a real deadlock as well as sleeping in atomic() bug in here, if
the bo put happens to be the last ref, since bo destruction wants to
grab the same spinlock and sleeping locks.  Fix that by dropping the ref
using xe_bo_put_deferred(), and moving the final commit outside of the
lock. Dropping the lock around the put is tricky since the bo can go
out of scope and delete itself from the list, making it difficult to
navigate to the next list entry.

(cherry picked from commit 0083b8e6f11d7662283a267d4ce7c966812ffd8a)</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46868 | firmware: qcom: uefisecapp: Fix deadlock in qcuefi_acquire()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46868</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

firmware: qcom: uefisecapp: Fix deadlock in qcuefi_acquire()

If the __qcuefi pointer is not set, then in the original code, we would
hold onto the lock.  That means that if we tried to set it later, then
it would cause a deadlock.  Drop the lock on the error path.  That's
what all the callers are expecting.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9281 | bg5sbk MiniCMS post-edit.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9281</link><description>A vulnerability was found in bg5sbk MiniCMS up to 1.11 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file post-edit.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions confusing version and file name information. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:05:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8607 | SQLi in Oceanic Software&amp;#x27;s ValeApp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8607</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Oceanic Software ValeApp allows SQL Injection.This issue affects ValeApp: before v2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 12:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8608 | Stored XSS in Oceanic Software&amp;#x27;s ValeApp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8608</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Oceanic Software ValeApp allows Stored XSS.This issue affects ValeApp: before v2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 12:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9280 | kalvinGit kvf-admin FileUploadKit.java fileUpload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9280</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in kalvinGit kvf-admin up to f12a94dc1ebb7d1c51ee978a85e4c7ed75c620ff and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function fileUpload of the file FileUploadKit.java. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 12:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8609 | Improper Access Control in Oceanic Software&amp;#x27;s ValeApp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8609</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Oceanic Software ValeApp allows Query System for Information.This issue affects ValeApp: before v2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 11:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8643 | Session Hijacking in Oceanic Software&amp;#x27;s ValeApp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8643</link><description>Session Fixation vulnerability in Oceanic Software ValeApp allows Brute Force, Session Hijacking.This issue affects ValeApp: before v2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 11:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8644 | Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information in Oceanic Software&amp;#x27;s ValeApp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8644</link><description>Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information in a Cookie vulnerability in Oceanic Software ValeApp allows Protocol Manipulation, : JSON Hijacking (aka JavaScript Hijacking).This issue affects ValeApp: before v2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 11:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9279 | funnyzpc Mee-Admin User Center index cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9279</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in funnyzpc Mee-Admin up to 1.6. This affects an unknown part of the file /mee/index of the component User Center. The manipulation of the argument User Nickname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 11:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9277 | Langflow HTTP POST Request utils.py redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9277</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Langflow up to 1.0.18. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file \src\backend\base\langflow\interface\utils.py of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument remaining_text leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 11:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9278 | HuankeMao SCRM Administrator Backend WxkConfig.php upload_domain_verification_file unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9278</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in HuankeMao SCRM up to 0.0.3. Affected by this issue is the function upload_domain_verification_file of the file WxkConfig.php of the component Administrator Backend. The manipulation of the argument domain_verification_file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 11:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47292 | Path traversal vulnerability in the Bluetooth module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentialit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47292</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability in the Bluetooth module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 10:34:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47293 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the HAL-WIFI module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47293</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the HAL-WIFI module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 10:34:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47294 | Access permission verification vulnerability in the input method framework module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47294</link><description>Access permission verification vulnerability in the input method framework module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 10:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9136 | Access permission verification vulnerability in the App Multiplier module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9136</link><description>Access permission verification vulnerability in the App Multiplier module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 10:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9275 | jeanmarc77 123solar admin_invt2.php file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9275</link><description>A vulnerability was found in jeanmarc77 123solar up to 1.8.4.5. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/admin_invt2.php. The manipulation of the argument PROTOCOLx leads to file inclusion. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 10:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9276 | TMsoft MyAuth Gateway index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9276</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in TMsoft MyAuth Gateway 3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument console/nocache/cmd leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 10:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47290 | Input validation vulnerability in the USB service module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47290</link><description>Input validation vulnerability in the USB service module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 10:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47291 | Permission vulnerability in the ActivityManagerService (AMS) module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47291</link><description>Permission vulnerability in the ActivityManagerService (AMS) module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 10:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9202 | EDC DataSetResolver policy filtering missing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9202</link><description>In Eclipse Dataspace Components versions 0.1.3 to 0.9.0, the Connector component filters which datasets (= data offers) another party can see in a requested catalog, to ensure that only authorized parties are able to view restricted offers.
However, there is the possibility to request a single dataset, which should be subject to the same filtering process, but currently is missing the correct filtering.


This enables parties to potentially see datasets they should not have access to, thereby exposing sensitive information. Exploiting this vulnerability requires knowing the ID of a restricted dataset, but some IDs may be guessed by trying out many IDs in an automated way.


Affected code:
 DatasetResolverImpl, L76-79 https://github.com/eclipse-edc/Connector/blob/v0.9.0/core/control-plane/control-plane-catalog/src/main/java/org/eclipse/edc/connector/controlplane/catalog/DatasetResolverImpl.java</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 09:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41930 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in MF Teacher Performance Management System version 6. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41930</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in MF Teacher Performance Management System version 6. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the website using the product.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 09:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6654 | Denial of Service vulnerability in ESET products for macOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6654</link><description>Products for macOS enables a user logged on to the system to perform a denial-of-service attack, which could be misused to disable the protection of the ESET security product and cause general system slow-down.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 09:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6931 | The Events Calendar &amp;lt;= 6.6.3 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6931</link><description>The The Events Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via RSVP name field in all versions up to, and including, 6.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 08:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38861 | Lack of TLS validation in plugin MikroTik on Checkmk Exchange</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38861</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation in Checkmk Exchange plugin MikroTik allows attackers in MitM position to intercept traffic. This issue affects MikroTik: from 2.0.0 through 2.5.5, from 0.4a_mk through 2.0a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 08:28:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39431 | In UMTS RLC driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39431</link><description>In UMTS RLC driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with System execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 07:48:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39432 | In UMTS RLC driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39432</link><description>In UMTS RLC driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with System execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 07:48:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39433 | In drm service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39433</link><description>In drm service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 07:48:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39434 | In drm service, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39434</link><description>In drm service, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 07:48:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39435 | In Logmanager service, there is a possible missing verification incorrect input. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no ad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39435</link><description>In Logmanager service, there is a possible missing verification incorrect input. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 07:48:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7400 | Local privilege escalation in ESET products for Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7400</link><description>The vulnerability potentially allowed an attacker to misuse ESET’s file operations during the removal of a detected file on the Windows operating system to delete files without having proper permissions to do so.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 07:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8681 | Premium Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.10.52 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Media Grid Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8681</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Media Grid widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.52 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 07:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8991 | OSM &amp;lt;= 6.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via osm_map and osm_map_v3 Shortcodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8991</link><description>The OSM – OpenStreetMap plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's osm_map and osm_map_v3 shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 07:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9029 | Freeimage: heap buffer overflow in tiff_read_iptc_profile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9029</link><description>A flaw was found in freeimage library. Processing a crafted image can cause a buffer over-read of 1 byte in the read_iptc_profile function in the Source/Metadata/IPTC.cpp file because the size of the profile is not being sanitized, causing a crash in the application linked to the library, resulting in a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 07:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9049 | Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.8.3.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via Button Group Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9049</link><description>The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Button Group module in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.3.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 07:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7713 | AI Chatbot with ChatGPT by AYS &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Unauthenticated OpenAI Key Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7713</link><description>The AI ChatBot with ChatGPT and Content Generator by AYS WordPress plugin before 2.1.0 discloses the Open AI API Key, allowing unauthenticated users to obtain it</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 06:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7714 | AI Assistant with ChatGPT by AYS &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Unauthenticated AJAX Calls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7714</link><description>The AI ChatBot with ChatGPT and Content Generator by AYS WordPress plugin before 2.1.0 lacks sufficient access controls allowing an unauthenticated user to disconnect the AI ChatBot with ChatGPT and Content Generator by AYS WordPress plugin before 2.1.0 from OpenAI, thereby disabling the AI ChatBot with ChatGPT and Content Generator by AYS WordPress plugin before 2.1.0. Multiple actions are accessible: 'ays_chatgpt_disconnect', 'ays_chatgpt_connect', and  'ays_chatgpt_save_feedback'</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 06:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8922 | Product Enquiry for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.2.33.33 - Authenticated (Author+) PHP Object Injection in enquiry_detail.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8922</link><description>The Product Enquiry for WooCommerce, WooCommerce product catalog plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.33.32 via deserialization of untrusted input in enquiry_detail.php. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 05:35:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8965 | Absolute Reviews &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via Criteria Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8965</link><description>The Absolute Reviews plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Name' field of a custom post criteria in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 05:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9130 | GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform &amp;lt;= 3.16.1 - Authenticated (GiveWP Manager+) SQL Injection via order Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9130</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘order’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.16.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with GiveWP Manager-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries within the Legacy View mode, that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 05:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7011 | Sharp NEC Projectors (NP-CB4500UL, NP-CB4500WL, NP-CB4700UL, NP-P525UL, NP-P525UL+, NP-P525ULG, NP-P525ULJL, NP-P525WL, NP-P525WL+, NP-P525W...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7011</link><description>Sharp NEC Projectors (NP-CB4500UL, NP-CB4500WL, NP-CB4700UL, NP-P525UL, NP-P525UL+, NP-P525ULG, NP-P525ULJL, NP-P525WL, NP-P525WL+, NP-P525WLG, NP-P525WLJL, NP-CG6500UL, NP-CG6500WL, NP-CG6700UL, NP-P605UL, NP-P605UL+, NP-P605ULG, NP-P605ULJL, NP-CA4120X, NP-CA4160W, NP-CA4160X, NP-CA4200U, NP-CA4200W, NP-CA4202W, NP-CA4260X, NP-CA4300X, NP-CA4355X, NP-CD2100U, NP-CD2120X, NP-CD2300X, NP-CR2100X, NP-CR2170W, NP-CR2170X, NP-CR2200U, NP-CR2200W, NP-CR2280X, NP-CR2310X, NP-CR2350X, NP-MC302XG, NP-MC332WG, NP-MC332WJL, NP-MC342XG, NP-MC372X, NP-MC372XG, NP-MC382W, NP-MC382WG, NP-MC422XG, NP-ME342UG, NP-ME372W, NP-ME372WG, NP-ME372WJL, NP-ME382U, NP-ME382UG, NP-ME382UJL, NP-ME402X, NP-ME402XG, NP-ME402XJL, NP-CB4500XL, NP-CG6400UL, NP-CG6400WL, NP-CG6500XL, NP-PE455UL, NP-PE455ULG, NP-PE455WL, NP-PE455WLG, NP-PE505XLG, NP-CB4600U, NP-CF6600U, NP-P474U, NP-P554U, NP-P554U+, NP-P554UG, NP-P554UJL, NP-CG6600UL, NP-P547UL, NP-P547ULG, NP-P547ULJL, NP-P607UL+, NP-P627UL, NP-P627UL+, NP-P627ULG, NP-P627ULJL, NP-PV710UL-B, NP-PV710UL-B1, NP-PV710UL-W, NP-PV710UL-W+, NP-PV710UL-W1, NP-PV730UL-BJL, NP-PV730UL-WJL, NP-PV800UL-B, NP-PV800UL-B+, NP-PV800UL-B1, NP-PV800UL-BJL, NP-PV800UL-W, NP-PV800UL-W+, NP-PV800UL-W1, NP-PV800UL-WJL, NP-CA4200X, NP-CA4265X, NP-CA4300U, NP-CA4300W, NP-CA4305X, NP-CA4400X, NP-CD2125X, NP-CD2200W, NP-CD2300U, NP-CD2310X, NP-CR2105X, NP-CR2200X, NP-CR2205W, NP-CR2300U, NP-CR2300W, NP-CR2315X, NP-CR2400X, NP-MC333XG, NP-MC363XG, NP-MC393WJL, NP-MC423W, NP-MC423WG, NP-MC453X, NP-MC453X, NP-MC453XG, NP-MC453XJL, NP-ME383WG, NP-ME403U, NP-ME403UG, NP-ME403UJL, NP-ME423W, NP-ME423WG, NP-ME423WJL, NP-ME453X, NP-ME453XG, NP-CB4400USL, NP-CB4400WSL, NP-CB4510UL, NP-CB4510WL, NP-CB4510XL, NP-CB4550USL, NP-CB6700UL, NP-CG6510UL, NP-PE456USL, NP-PE456USLG, NP-PE456USLJL, NP-PE456WSLG, NP-PE506UL, NP-PE506ULG, NP-PE506ULJL, NP-PE506WL, NP-PE506WLG, NP-PE506WLJL) allows an attacker to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition via SNMP service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 02:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>