<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 07:46:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-39579 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contains an incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability. A local high privileged att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39579</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contains an incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability. A local high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain root-level access.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 07:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8276 | WPZOOM Portfolio Lite – Filterable Portfolio Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via align Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8276</link><description>The WPZOOM Portfolio Lite – Filterable Portfolio Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘align’ attribute within the 'wp:wpzoom-blocks' Gutenberg block in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 07:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39578 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.1 contains a UNIX symbolic link (symlink) following vulnerability. A local high privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39578</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.1 contains a UNIX symbolic link (symlink) following vulnerability. A local high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to denial of service, information tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 07:36:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44945 | netfilter: nfnetlink: Initialise extack before use in ACKs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44945</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nfnetlink: Initialise extack before use in ACKs

Add missing extack initialisation when ACKing BATCH_BEGIN and BATCH_END.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 06:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3886 | tagDiv Composer &amp;lt;= 5.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via envato_code[]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3886</link><description>The tagDiv Composer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘envato_code[]’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping within the on_ajax_check_envato_code function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 04:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5212 | tagDiv Composer &amp;lt;= 5.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via envato_code[]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5212</link><description>The tagDiv Composer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘envato_code[]’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping within the on_ajax_register_forum_user function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 04:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7435 | Attire &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7435</link><description>The Attire theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6 via deserialization of untrusted input. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 02:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39747 | IBM Sterling Connect:Direct Web Services information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39747</link><description>IBM Sterling Connect:Direct Web Services 6.0, 6.1, 6.2, and 6.3 uses default credentials for potentially critical functionality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 02:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8006 | NULL pointer dereference in libpcap before 1.10.5 with remote packet capture support</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8006</link><description>Remote packet capture support is disabled by default in libpcap.  When a user builds libpcap with remote packet capture support enabled, one of the functions that become available is pcap_findalldevs_ex().  One of the function arguments can be a filesystem path, which normally means a directory with input data files.  When the specified path cannot be used as a directory, the function receives NULL from opendir(), but does not check the return value and passes the NULL value to readdir(), which causes a NULL pointer derefence.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 01:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45304 | OwnableTwoStep allows a pending owner to accept ownership after the original owner has renounced ownership in cairo-contracts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45304</link><description>Cairo-Contracts are OpenZeppelin Contracts written in Cairo for Starknet, a decentralized ZK Rollup. This vulnerability can lead to unauthorized ownership transfer, contrary to the original owner's intention of leaving the contract without an owner. It introduces a security risk where an unintended party (pending owner) can gain control of the contract after the original owner has renounced ownership. This could also be used by a malicious owner to simulate leaving a contract without an owner, to later regain ownership by previously having proposed himself as a pending owner. This issue has been addressed in release version 0.16.0. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 23:56:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7256 | Double-free in libpcap before 1.10.5 with remote packet capture support.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7256</link><description>In affected libpcap versions during the setup of a remote packet capture the internal function sock_initaddress() calls getaddrinfo() and possibly freeaddrinfo(), but does not clearly indicate to the caller function whether freeaddrinfo() still remains to be called after the function returns.  This makes it possible in some scenarios that both the function and its caller call freeaddrinfo() for the same allocated memory block.  A similar problem was reported in Apple libpcap, to which Apple assigned CVE-2023-40400.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 23:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6586 | Lightdash version 0.1024.6 allows users with the necessary permissions, such as Administrator or Editor, to create and share dashboards. A d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6586</link><description>Lightdash version 0.1024.6 allows users with the necessary permissions, such as Administrator or Editor, to create and share dashboards. A dashboard that contains HTML elements which point to a threat actor controlled source can trigger an SSRF request when exported, via a POST request to /api/v1/dashboards//export. The forged request contains the value of the exporting user’s session token. A threat actor could obtain the session token of any user who exports the dashboard. The obtained session token can be used to perform actions as the victim on the application, resulting in session takeover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 22:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6585 | Multiple stored cross-site scripting (“XSS”) vulnerabilities in the markdown dashboard and dashboard comment functionality of Lightdash vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6585</link><description>Multiple stored cross-site scripting (“XSS”) vulnerabilities in the markdown dashboard and dashboard comment functionality of Lightdash version 0.1024.6 allows remote authenticated threat actors to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable web pages. A threat actor could potentially exploit this vulnerability to store malicious JavaScript which executes in the context of a user’s session with the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 22:31:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44682 | ShopXO 6.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the backend that allows attackers to execute code by changing POST parameters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44682</link><description>ShopXO 6.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the backend that allows attackers to execute code by changing POST parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 21:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44684 | TpMeCMS 1.3.3.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /h.php/page?ref=addtabs via the "Title," "Images," and "Content" fields.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44684</link><description>TpMeCMS 1.3.3.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /h.php/page?ref=addtabs via the "Title," "Images," and "Content" fields.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 21:55:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44683 | Seacms v13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via admin-video.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44683</link><description>Seacms v13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via admin-video.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 21:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8347 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System Master.php delete_record sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8347</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function delete_record of the file /classes/Master.php?f=delete_record. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 21:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8348 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System Master.php delete_category sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8348</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function delete_category of the file /classes/Master.php?f=delete_category. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 21:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8285 | Kroxylicious: missing upstream kafka tls hostname verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8285</link><description>A flaw was found in Kroxylicious. When establishing the connection with the upstream Kafka server using a TLS secured connection, Kroxylicious fails to properly verify the server's hostname, resulting in an insecure connection. For a successful attack to be performed, the attacker needs to perform a Man-in-the-Middle attack or compromise any external systems, such as DNS or network routing configuration. This issue is considered a high complexity attack, with additional high privileges required, as the attack would need access to the Kroxylicious configuration or a peer system. The result of a successful attack impacts both data integrity and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 21:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8346 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System SystemSettings.php update_settings_info sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8346</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. Affected is the function update_settings_info of the file /classes/SystemSettings.php?f=update_settings. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 20:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38868 | Incorrect Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38868</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Endpoint Central affected by Incorrect authorization vulnerability while isolating the devices.This issue affects Endpoint Central: before 11.3.2406.08 and before 11.3.2400.15</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 17:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21658 | Insufficient control of region value length in discourse-calendar</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21658</link><description>discourse-calendar is a discourse plugin which adds the ability to create a dynamic calendar in the first post of a topic. The limit on region value length is too generous. This allows a malicious actor to cause a Discourse instance to use excessive bandwidth and disk space. This issue has been patched in main the main branch. There are no workarounds for this vulnerability. Please upgrade as soon as possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 17:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6204 | SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6204</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Exchange Reporter Plus versions before 5715 are vulnerable to SQL Injection in the reports module.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 17:23:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45047 | Potential mXSS vulnerability due to improper HTML escaping in svelte</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45047</link><description>svelte performance oriented web framework. A potential mXSS vulnerability exists in Svelte for versions up to but not including 4.2.19. Svelte improperly escapes HTML on server-side rendering. The assumption is that attributes will always stay as such, but in some situation the final DOM tree rendered on browsers is different from what Svelte expects on server-side rendering. This may be leveraged to perform XSS attacks, and a type of the XSS is known as mXSS (mutation XSS). More specifically, this can occur when injecting malicious content into an attribute within a `noscript` tag. This issue has been addressed in release version 4.2.19. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 17:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8345 | SourceCodester Music Gallery Site Users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8345</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /classes/Users.php?f=delete. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 17:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8344 | Campcodes Supplier Management System edit_area.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8344</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Supplier Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit_area.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 16:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44918 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component admin_datarelate.php of SeaCMS v12.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44918</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component admin_datarelate.php of SeaCMS v12.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 16:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8235 | Libvirt: crash of virtinterfaced via virconnectlistinterfaces()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8235</link><description>A flaw was found in libvirt. A refactor of the code fetching the list of interfaces for multiple APIs introduced a corner case on platforms where allocating 0 bytes of memory results in a NULL pointer. This corner case would lead to a NULL-pointer dereference and subsequent crash of virtinterfaced. This issue could allow clients connecting to the read-only socket to crash the virtinterfaced daemon.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 16:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44916 | Vulnerability in admin_ip.php in Seacms v13.1, when action=set, allows attackers to control IP parameters that are written to the data/admin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44916</link><description>Vulnerability in admin_ip.php in Seacms v13.1, when action=set, allows attackers to control IP parameters that are written to the data/admin/ip.php file and could result in arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 16:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8343 | SourceCodester Sentiment Based Movie Rating System User Registration Users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8343</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Sentiment Based Movie Rating System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /classes/Users.php?f=save_client of the component User Registration Handler. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 16:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8342 | SourceCodester Petshop Management System add_client.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8342</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Petshop Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /controllers/add_client.php. The manipulation of the argument image_profile leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 15:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8340 | SourceCodester Electric Billing Management System Actions.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8340</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Electric Billing Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /Actions.php?a=login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 15:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8341 | SourceCodester Petshop Management System add_user.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8341</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Petshop Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /controllers/add_user.php. The manipulation of the argument avatar leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 15:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8338 | HFO4 shudong-share File Extension fileReceive.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8338</link><description>A vulnerability was found in HFO4 shudong-share 2.4.7. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /includes/fileReceive.php of the component File Extension Handler. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 14:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8339 | SourceCodester Electric Billing Management System Connection Code ?page=tracks sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8339</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Electric Billing Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /?page=tracks of the component Connection Code Handler. The manipulation of the argument code leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 14:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8336 | SourceCodester Music Gallery Site Master.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8336</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /php-music/classes/Master.php?f=delete_music. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 13:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8337 | SourceCodester Contact Manager with Export to VCF index.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8337</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Contact Manager with Export to VCF 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file index.html. The manipulation of the argument contact_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 13:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8334 | master-nan Sweet-CMS log.go LogHandler neutralization for logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8334</link><description>A vulnerability was found in master-nan Sweet-CMS up to 5f441e022b8876f07cde709c77b5be6d2f262e3f. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function LogHandler of the file middleware/log.go. The manipulation leads to improper output neutralization for logs. The attack may be initiated remotely. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The identifier of the patch is 2024c370e6c78b07b358c9d4257fa5d1be732c38. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 13:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8335 | OpenRapid RapidCMS runlogon.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8335</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in OpenRapid RapidCMS up to 1.3.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /resource/runlogon.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 13:03:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8260 | OPA SMB Force-Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8260</link><description>A SMB force-authentication vulnerability exists in all versions of OPA for Windows prior to v0.68.0. The vulnerability exists because of improper input validation, allowing a user to pass an arbitrary SMB share instead of a Rego file as an argument to OPA CLI or to one of the OPA Go library’s functions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8332 | master-nan Sweet-CMS index sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8332</link><description>A vulnerability was found in master-nan Sweet-CMS up to 5f441e022b8876f07cde709c77b5be6d2f262e3f. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /table/index. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The name of the patch is 146359646a5a90cb09156dbd0013b7df77f2aa6c. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8331 | OpenRapid RapidCMS user-move-run.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8331</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OpenRapid RapidCMS up to 1.3.1. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/user/user-move-run.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:20:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48944 | sched: Fix yet more sched_fork() races</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48944</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

sched: Fix yet more sched_fork() races

Where commit 4ef0c5c6b5ba ("kernel/sched: Fix sched_fork() access an
invalid sched_task_group") fixed a fork race vs cgroup, it opened up a
race vs syscalls by not placing the task on the runqueue before it
gets exposed through the pidhash.

Commit 13765de8148f ("sched/fair: Fix fault in reweight_entity") is
trying to fix a single instance of this, instead fix the whole class
of issues, effectively reverting this commit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 10:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7122 | Elementor Addon Elements &amp;lt;= 1.13.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7122</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 09:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7858 | Media Library Folders &amp;lt;= 8.2.3 - Missing Authorization on Various Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7858</link><description>The Media Library Folders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to missing capability checks on several AJAX functions in the media-library-plus.php file in all versions up to, and including, 8.2.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to perform several actions related to managing media files and folder along with controlling settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 09:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8252 | Clean Login &amp;lt;= 1.14.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8252</link><description>The Clean Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.14.5 via the 'template' attribute of the clean-login-register shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 09:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8274 | WP Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 10.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8274</link><description>The WP Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters from 'timeline_obj' in all versions up to, and including, 10.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 09:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44944 | netfilter: ctnetlink: use helper function to calculate expect ID</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44944</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: ctnetlink: use helper function to calculate expect ID

Delete expectation path is missing a call to the nf_expect_get_id()
helper function to calculate the expectation ID, otherwise LSB of the
expectation object address is leaked to userspace.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 08:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8319 | Tourfic &amp;lt;= 2.11.20 - Cross-Site Request Forgery in Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8319</link><description>The Tourfic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.11.20. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the tf_order_status_email_resend_function,  tf_visitor_details_edit_function, tf_checkinout_details_edit_function, tf_order_status_edit_function, tf_order_bulk_action_edit_function, tf_remove_room_order_ids, and tf_delete_old_review_fields functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to resend order status emails, update visitor/order details, edit check-in/out details, edit order status, perform bulk order status updates, remove room order IDs, and delete old review fields, respectively, via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 07:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8016 | The Events Calendar Pro &amp;lt;= 7.0.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) PHP Object Injection to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8016</link><description>The Events Calendar Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 7.0.2 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'filters' parameter in widgets. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. The additional presence of a POP chain allows attackers to execute code remotely. In certain configurations, this can be exploitable by lower level users. We confirmed that this plugin installed with Elementor makes it possible for users with contributor-level access and above to exploit this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 06:59:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34577 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in WRC-X3000GS2-B, WRC-X3000GS2-W, and WRC-X3000GS2A-B due to improper processing of input values ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34577</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in WRC-X3000GS2-B, WRC-X3000GS2-W, and WRC-X3000GS2A-B due to improper processing of input values in easysetup.cgi. If a user views a malicious web page while logged in to the product, an arbitrary script may be executed on the user's web browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 06:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39300 | Missing authentication vulnerability exists in Telnet function of WAB-I1750-PS v1.5.10 and earlier. When Telnet function of the product is e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39300</link><description>Missing authentication vulnerability exists in Telnet function of WAB-I1750-PS v1.5.10 and earlier. When Telnet function of the product is enabled, a remote attacker may login to the product without authentication and alter the product's settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 06:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42412 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in WAB-I1750-PS and WAB-S1167-PS due to improper processing of input values in menu.cgi. If a user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42412</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in WAB-I1750-PS and WAB-S1167-PS due to improper processing of input values in menu.cgi. If a user views a malicious web page while logged in to the product, an arbitrary script may be executed on the user's web browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 06:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3673 | Web Directory Free &amp;lt; 1.7.3 - Unauthenticated LFI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3673</link><description>The Web Directory Free WordPress plugin before 1.7.3 does not validate a parameter before using it in an include(), which could lead to Local File Inclusion issues.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 06:17:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2694 | Betheme &amp;lt;= 27.5.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2694</link><description>The Betheme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 27.5.6 via deserialization of untrusted input of the 'mfn-page-items' post meta value. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 04:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3998 | Betheme | Responsive Multipurpose WordPress &amp;amp; WooCommerce Theme &amp;lt;= 27.5.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3998</link><description>The Betheme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several of the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 27.5.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 04:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5879 | HubSpot – CRM, Email Marketing, Live Chat, Forms &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;lt;= 11.1.22 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HubSpot Meeting Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5879</link><description>The HubSpot – CRM, Email Marketing, Live Chat, Forms &amp; Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'url' attribute of the HubSpot Meeting Widget in all versions up to, and including, 11.1.22 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 04:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4401 | Elementor Addon Elements &amp;lt;= 1.13.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via id and eae_slider_animation Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4401</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ and 'eae_slider_animation' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 03:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5024 | MemberPress &amp;lt;= 1.11.29 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via mepr_screenname and mepr_key Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5024</link><description>The Memberpress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'mepr_screenname' and 'mepr_key' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.11.29 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 03:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5061 | Enfold &amp;lt;= 6.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wrapper_class and class Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5061</link><description>The Enfold - Responsive Multi-Purpose Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘wrapper_class’ and 'class' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 03:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5784 | Tutor LMS Pro &amp;lt;= 2.7.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5784</link><description>The Tutor LMS  Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized administrative actions execution due to a missing capability checks on multiple functions like treport_quiz_atttempt_delete and tutor_gc_class_action in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with the subscriber-level access and above, to preform an administrative actions on the site, like comments, posts or users deletion, viewing notifications, etc.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 03:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8330 | Gether Technology 6SHR System - Unrestricted File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8330</link><description>6SHR system from Gether Technology does not properly validate uploaded file types, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to upload web shell scripts and use them to execute arbitrary system commands on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45490 | An issue was discovered in libexpat before 2.6.3. xmlparse.c does not reject a negative length for XML_ParseBuffer.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45490</link><description>An issue was discovered in libexpat before 2.6.3. xmlparse.c does not reject a negative length for XML_ParseBuffer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45491 | An issue was discovered in libexpat before 2.6.3. dtdCopy in xmlparse.c can have an integer overflow for nDefaultAtts on 32-bit platforms (w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45491</link><description>An issue was discovered in libexpat before 2.6.3. dtdCopy in xmlparse.c can have an integer overflow for nDefaultAtts on 32-bit platforms (where UINT_MAX equals SIZE_MAX).</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45492 | An issue was discovered in libexpat before 2.6.3. nextScaffoldPart in xmlparse.c can have an integer overflow for m_groupSize on 32-bit plat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45492</link><description>An issue was discovered in libexpat before 2.6.3. nextScaffoldPart in xmlparse.c can have an integer overflow for m_groupSize on 32-bit platforms (where UINT_MAX equals SIZE_MAX).</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8327 | HWA JIUH DIGITAL TECHNOLOGY Easy test Online Learning and Testing Platform - SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8327</link><description>Easy test

Online Learning and Testing Platform from HWA JIUH DIGITAL TECHNOLOGY does not properly validate a specific page parameter, allowing remote attackers with regular privilege to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8328 | HWA JIUH DIGITAL TECHNOLOGY Easy test Online Learning and Testing Platform - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8328</link><description>Easy test Online Learning and Testing Platform from HWA JIUH DIGITAL TECHNOLOGY does not properly validate a specific page parameter, allowing remote attackers with regular privilege to inject arbitrary JavaScript code and perform Reflected Cross-site scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8329 | Gether Technology 6SHR System - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8329</link><description>6SHR system from Gether Technology does not properly validate the specific page parameter, allowing remote attackers with regular privilege to inject SQL command to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45488 | One Identity Safeguard for Privileged Passwords before 7.5.2 allows unauthorized access because of an issue related to cookies. This only af...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45488</link><description>One Identity Safeguard for Privileged Passwords before 7.5.2 allows unauthorized access because of an issue related to cookies. This only affects virtual appliance installations (VMware or HyperV). The fixed versions are 7.0.5.1 LTS, 7.4.2, and 7.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:03:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8234 | ** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A command injection vulnerability in the functions formSysCmd(), formUpgradeCert(), and formDelcert() in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8234</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A command injection vulnerability in the functions formSysCmd(), formUpgradeCert(), and formDelcert() in the Zyxel NWA1100-N firmware version 1.00(AACE.1)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some OS commands to access system files on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:46:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2881 | Fault Injection of EdDSA signature in WolfCrypt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2881</link><description>Fault Injection vulnerability in wc_ed25519_sign_msg function in wolfssl/wolfcrypt/src/ed25519.c in WolfSSL wolfssl5.6.6 on Linux/Windows allows remote attacker co-resides in the same system with a victim process to disclose information and escalate privileges via Rowhammer fault injection to the ed25519_key structure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 23:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1545 | Fault Injection of RSA encryption in WolfCrypt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1545</link><description>Fault Injection vulnerability in RsaPrivateDecryption function in wolfssl/wolfcrypt/src/rsa.c in WolfSSL wolfssl5.6.6 on Linux/Windows allows remote attacker co-resides in the same system with a victim process to disclose information and escalate privileges via Rowhammer fault injection to the RsaKey structure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 23:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1543 | AES T-Table sub-cache-line leakage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1543</link><description>The side-channel protected T-Table implementation in wolfSSL up to version 5.6.5 protects against a side-channel attacker with cache-line resolution. In a controlled environment such as Intel SGX, an attacker can gain a per instruction sub-cache-line resolution allowing them to break the cache-line-level protection. For details on the attack refer to:  https://doi.org/10.46586/tches.v2024.i1.457-500</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 22:51:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2502 | Failure to update the tamper reset cause register when a tamper event occurs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2502</link><description>An application can be configured to block boot attempts after consecutive tamper resets are detected, which may not occur as expected.

This is possible because the TAMPERRSTCAUSE register may not be properly updated when a level 4 tamper event (a tamper reset) occurs. This impacts Series 2 HSE-SVH devices, including xG23B, xG24B, xG25B, and xG28B, but does not impact xG21B. To mitigate this issue, upgrade to SE Firmware version 2.2.6 or later.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 22:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6670 | WhatsUp Gold HasErrors SQL Injection Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6670</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2024.0.0, a SQL Injection vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to retrieve the users encrypted password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 22:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6671 | WhatsUp Gold GetStatisticalMonitorList SQL Injection Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6671</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2024.0.0, if the application is configured with only a single user, a SQL Injection vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to retrieve the users encrypted password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 22:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6672 | WhatsUp Gold getMonitorJoin SQL Injection Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6672</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2024.0.0, a SQL Injection vulnerability allows an authenticated low-privileged attacker to achieve privilege escalation by modifying a privileged user's password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 22:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45302 | CRLF Injection in RestSharp&amp;#x27;s `RestRequest.AddHeader` method</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45302</link><description>RestSharp is a Simple REST and HTTP API Client for .NET. The second argument to `RestRequest.AddHeader` (the header value) is vulnerable to CRLF injection. The same applies to `RestRequest.AddOrUpdateHeader` and `RestClient.AddDefaultHeader`. The way HTTP headers are added to a request is via the `HttpHeaders.TryAddWithoutValidation` method which does not check for CRLF characters in the header value. This means that any headers from a `RestSharp.RequestHeaders` object are added to the request in such a way that they are vulnerable to CRLF-injection. In general, CRLF-injection into a HTTP header (when using HTTP/1.1) means that one can inject additional HTTP headers or smuggle whole HTTP requests. If an application using the RestSharp library passes a user-controllable value through to a header, then that application becomes vulnerable to CRLF-injection. This is not necessarily a security issue for a command line application like the one above, but if such code were present in a web application then it becomes vulnerable to request splitting (as shown in the PoC) and thus Server Side Request Forgery. Strictly speaking this is a potential vulnerability in applications using RestSharp, not in RestSharp itself, but I would argue that at the very least there needs to be a warning about this behaviour in the RestSharp documentation. RestSharp has addressed this issue in version 112.0.0. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 21:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41349 | unmark 1.9.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via application/views/marks/add_by_url.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41349</link><description>unmark 1.9.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via application/views/marks/add_by_url.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 20:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41346 | openflights commit 5234b5b is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via php/submit.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41346</link><description>openflights commit 5234b5b is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via php/submit.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 20:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41347 | openflights commit 5234b5b is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via php/settings.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41347</link><description>openflights commit 5234b5b is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via php/settings.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 20:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41348 | openflights commit 5234b5b is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via php/alsearch.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41348</link><description>openflights commit 5234b5b is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via php/alsearch.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 20:12:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41358 | phpipam 1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via app\admin\import-export\import-load-data.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41358</link><description>phpipam 1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via app\admin\import-export\import-load-data.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 20:12:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41370 | Organizr v1.90 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via chat/setlike.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41370</link><description>Organizr v1.90 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via chat/setlike.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 20:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41372 | Organizr v1.90 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via chat/settyping.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41372</link><description>Organizr v1.90 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via chat/settyping.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 20:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41368 | RPi-Jukebox-RFID v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via htdocs\inc.setWlanIpMail.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41368</link><description>RPi-Jukebox-RFID v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via htdocs\inc.setWlanIpMail.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 20:12:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41371 | Organizr v1.90 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via api.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41371</link><description>Organizr v1.90 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via api.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 20:12:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41345 | openflights commit 5234b5b is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via php/trip.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41345</link><description>openflights commit 5234b5b is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via php/trip.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 19:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41350 | bjyadmin commit a560fd5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via Public/statics/umeditor1_2_3/php/imageUp.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41350</link><description>bjyadmin commit a560fd5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via Public/statics/umeditor1_2_3/php/imageUp.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 19:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41364 | RPi-Jukebox-RFID v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via htdocs\trackEdit.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41364</link><description>RPi-Jukebox-RFID v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via htdocs\trackEdit.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 19:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41369 | RPi-Jukebox-RFID v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via htdocs\inc.setWifi.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41369</link><description>RPi-Jukebox-RFID v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via htdocs\inc.setWifi.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 19:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41351 | bjyadmin commit a560fd5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via Public/statics/umeditor1_2_3/php/getContent.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41351</link><description>bjyadmin commit a560fd5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via Public/statics/umeditor1_2_3/php/getContent.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 19:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41361 | RPi-Jukebox-RFID v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via htdocs\manageFilesFolders.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41361</link><description>RPi-Jukebox-RFID v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via htdocs\manageFilesFolders.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 19:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41366 | RPi-Jukebox-RFID v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via htdocs\userScripts.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41366</link><description>RPi-Jukebox-RFID v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via htdocs\userScripts.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 19:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41367 | RPi-Jukebox-RFID v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via htdocs\api\playlist\appendFileToPlaylist.p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41367</link><description>RPi-Jukebox-RFID v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via htdocs\api\playlist\appendFileToPlaylist.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 19:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34017 | Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Snap Deploy (Windows) before bui...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34017</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Snap Deploy (Windows) before build 4569.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 19:23:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34018 | Sensitive information disclosure due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Snap Deploy (Windows) befo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34018</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Snap Deploy (Windows) before build 4569.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 19:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34019 | Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Snap Deploy (Windows) before bui...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34019</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Snap Deploy (Windows) before build 4569.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 19:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43920 | WordPress Gutenverse – Gutenberg Blocks – Page Builder for Site Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43920</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jegstudio Gutenverse allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Gutenverse: from n/a through 1.9.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43921 | WordPress Generate Images – Magic Post Thumbnail plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43921</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Magic Post Thumbnail allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Magic Post Thumbnail: from n/a through 5.2.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43947 | WordPress WP Armour Extended plugin &amp;lt;= 1.26 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43947</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Dinesh Karki WP Armour Extended.This issue affects WP Armour Extended: from n/a through 1.26.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43926 | WordPress Beaver Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.3.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43926</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Beaver Builder Team Beaver Builder allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Beaver Builder: from n/a through 2.8.3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43934 | WordPress Collapsing Archives plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43934</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Robert Felty Collapsing Archives allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Collapsing Archives: from n/a through 3.0.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43935 | WordPress WP Delicious – Recipe Plugin for Food Bloggers (formerly Delicious Recipes) plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43935</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Delicious Delicious Recipes – WordPress Recipe Plugin allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Delicious Recipes – WordPress Recipe Plugin: from n/a through 1.6.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43936 | WordPress EmbedPress plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43936</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPDeveloper EmbedPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects EmbedPress: from n/a through 4.0.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43946 | WordPress SKT Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43946</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SKT Themes SKT Blocks – Gutenberg based Page Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects SKT Blocks – Gutenberg based Page Builder: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43948 | WordPress WP Armour Extended plugin &amp;lt;= 1.26 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43948</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dinesh Karki WP Armour Extended.This issue affects WP Armour Extended: from n/a through 1.26.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44930 | Serilog before v2.1.0 was discovered to contain a Client IP Spoofing vulnerability, which allows attackers to falsify their IP addresses by ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44930</link><description>Serilog before v2.1.0 was discovered to contain a Client IP Spoofing vulnerability, which allows attackers to falsify their IP addresses by specifying an arbitrary IP as a value of X-Forwarded-For or Client-Ip headers while performing HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43949 | WordPress GHActivity plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0-alpha - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43949</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Automattic GHActivity allows Stored XSS.This issue affects GHActivity: from n/a through 2.0.0-alpha.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43950 | WordPress Brickscore plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43950</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nextbricks Brickscore allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Brickscore: from n/a through 1.4.2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43951 | WordPress Tempera theme &amp;lt;= 1.8.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43951</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CryoutCreations Tempera allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Tempera: from n/a through 1.8.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43952 | WordPress Esotera theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.5.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43952</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CryoutCreations Esotera allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Esotera: from n/a through 1.2.5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43953 | WordPress Classic Addons – WPBakery Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43953</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Classic Addons Classic Addons – WPBakery Page Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Classic Addons – WPBakery Page Builder: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44779 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the viewname parameter in the index page of vTiger CRM 7.4.0 allows attackers to exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44779</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the viewname parameter in the index page of vTiger CRM 7.4.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43958 | WordPress Into The Dark theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43958</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Gianni Porto IntoTheDark allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects IntoTheDark: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43960 | WordPress Web and WooCommerce Addons for WPBakery Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43960</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Page Builder Addons Web and WooCommerce Addons for WPBakery Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Web and WooCommerce Addons for WPBakery Builder: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43961 | WordPress azurecurve Toggle Show/Hide plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43961</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in azurecurve azurecurve Toggle Show/Hide allows Stored XSS.This issue affects azurecurve Toggle Show/Hide: from n/a through 2.1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43963 | WordPress Visual CSS Style Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43963</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WaspThemes YellowPencil Visual CSS Style Editor allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects YellowPencil Visual CSS Style Editor: from n/a through 7.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44777 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the tag parameter in the index page of vTiger CRM 7.4.0 allows attackers to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44777</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the tag parameter in the index page of vTiger CRM 7.4.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44778 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the parent parameter in the index page of vTiger CRM 7.4.0 allows attackers to execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44778</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the parent parameter in the index page of vTiger CRM 7.4.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 18:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43964 | WordPress DSGVO All in one for WP plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43964</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Michael Leithold DSGVO All in one for WP allows Stored XSS.This issue affects DSGVO All in one for WP: from n/a through 4.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 17:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44776 | An Open Redirect vulnerability in the page parameter of vTiger CRM v7.4.0 allows attackers to redirect users to a malicious site via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44776</link><description>An Open Redirect vulnerability in the page parameter of vTiger CRM v7.4.0 allows attackers to redirect users to a malicious site via a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 17:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44717 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in DedeBIZ v6.3.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44717</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in DedeBIZ v6.3.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 17:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44716 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in DedeBIZ v6.3.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44716</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in DedeBIZ v6.3.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45056 | `fold (xor (shl 1, x), -1) -&amp;gt; (rotl ~1, x)` misoptimization in zksolc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45056</link><description>zksolc is a Solidity compiler for ZKsync. All LLVM versions since 2015 fold `(xor (shl 1, x), -1)` to `(rotl ~1, x)` if run with optimizations enabled. Here `~1` is generated as an unsigned 64 bits number (`2^64-1`). This number is zero-extended to 256 bits on EraVM target while it should have been sign-extended. Thus instead of producing `roti 2^256 - 1, x` the compiler produces `rotl 2^64 - 1, x`. Analysis has shown that no contracts were affected by the date of publishing this advisory. This issue has been addressed in version 1.5.3. Users are advised to upgrade and redeploy all contracts. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 17:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43804 | OS Command Injection via Port Scan Functionality in Roxy-WI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43804</link><description>Roxy-WI is a web interface for managing Haproxy, Nginx, Apache and Keepalived servers. An OS Command Injection vulnerability allows any authenticated user on the application to execute arbitrary code on the web application server via port scanning functionality. User-supplied input is used without validation when constructing and executing an OS command. User supplied JSON POST data is parsed and if "id" JSON key does not exist, JSON value supplied via "ip" JSON key is assigned to the "ip" variable. Later on, "ip" variable which can be controlled by the attacker is used when constructing the cmd and cmd1 strings without any extra validation. Then, server_mod.subprocess_execute function is called on both cmd1 and cmd2. When the definition of the server_mod.subprocess_execute() function is analyzed, it can be seen that subprocess.Popen() is called on the input parameter with shell=True which results in OS Command Injection. This issue has not yet been patched. Users are advised to contact the Roxy-WI to coordinate a fix.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45045 | JavaScript Injection via url encoded values in links in Collabora Office Android</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45045</link><description>Collabora Online is a collaborative online office suite based on LibreOffice technology. In the mobile (Android/iOS) device variants of Collabora Online it was possible to inject JavaScript via url encoded values in links contained in documents. Since the Android JavaScript interface allows access to internal functions, the likelihood that the app could be compromised via this vulnerability is considered high. Non-mobile variants are not affected. Mobile variants should update to the latest version provided by the platform appstore. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35133 | IBM Security Verify Access HTTP open redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35133</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 OIDC Provider could allow a remote attacker to conduct phishing attacks, using an open redirect attack. By persuading a victim to visit a specially crafted Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to spoof the URL displayed to redirect a user to a malicious Web site that would appear to be trusted. This could allow the attacker to obtain highly sensitive information or conduct further attacks against the victim.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44919 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component admin_ads.php of SeaCMS v12.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44919</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component admin_ads.php of SeaCMS v12.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the ad description parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41964 | Insufficient permission checks in the language settings in Kirby CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41964</link><description>Kirby is a CMS targeting designers and editors. Kirby allows to restrict the permissions of specific user roles. Users of that role can only perform permitted actions. Permissions for creating and deleting languages have already existed and could be configured, but were not enforced by Kirby's frontend or backend code. A permission for updating existing languages has not existed before the patched versions. So disabling the languages.* wildcard permission for a role could not have prohibited updates to existing language definitions. The missing permission checks allowed attackers with Panel access to manipulate the language definitions. The problem has been patched in Kirby 3.6.6.6, Kirby 3.7.5.5, Kirby 3.8.4.4, Kirby 3.9.8.2, Kirby 3.10.1.1, and Kirby 4.3.1. Please update to one of these or a later version to fix the vulnerability. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35118 | IBM MaaS360 information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35118</link><description>IBM MaaS360 for Android 6.31 through 8.60 is using hard coded credentials that can be obtained by a user with physical access to the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43943 | WordPress Greenshift Woocommerce Addon plugin &amp;lt; 1.9.8 - Subscriber+ SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43943</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Wpsoul Greenshift Woocommerce Addon allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Greenshift Woocommerce Addon: from n/a before 1.9.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43944 | WordPress Maintenance &amp;amp; Coming Soon Redirect Animation plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - IP Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43944</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Yassine Idrissi Maintenance &amp; Coming Soon Redirect Animation allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Maintenance &amp; Coming Soon Redirect Animation: from n/a through 2.1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43954 | WordPress Droip plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Subscriber+ Settings Change/Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43954</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Themeum Droip allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Droip: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43955 | WordPress Droip plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Download/Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43955</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Themeum Droip allows File Manipulation.This issue affects Droip: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43957 | WordPress Animated Number Counters plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Editor+ Limited Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43957</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Sk. Abul Hasan Animated Number Counters allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Animated Number Counters: from n/a through 1.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43965 | WordPress SendGrid for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43965</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Smackcoders SendGrid for WordPress allows SQL Injection.This issue affects SendGrid for WordPress: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8255 | Path Traversal in Ocean Data Systems Dream Report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8255</link><description>Delta Electronics DTN Soft version 2.0.1 and prior are vulnerable to an attacker achieving remote code execution through a deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43931 | WordPress JobSearch WP Job Board WordPress Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43931</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in eyecix JobSearch allows Object Injection.This issue affects JobSearch: from n/a through 2.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:17:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43939 | WordPress Z Y N I T H plugin &amp;lt;= 7.4.9 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Option Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43939</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in VIICTORY MEDIA LLC Z Y N I T H allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Z Y N I T H: from n/a through 7.4.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:17:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43940 | WordPress Z Y N I T H plugin &amp;lt;= 7.4.9 - Unauthenticated Plugin Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43940</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in VIICTORY MEDIA LLC Z Y N I T H allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Z Y N I T H: from n/a through 7.4.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:17:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43941 | WordPress Propovoice Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.0.3 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43941</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Propovoice Propovoice Pro allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Propovoice Pro: from n/a through 1.7.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:17:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43942 | WordPress Greenshift Query and Meta Addon plugin &amp;lt; 3.9.2 - Subscriber+ SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43942</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Wpsoul Greenshift Query and Meta Addon allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Greenshift Query and Meta Addon: from n/a before 3.9.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:17:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43922 | WordPress NitroPack plugin &amp;lt;= 1.16.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43922</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in NitroPack Inc. NitroPack allows Code Injection.This issue affects NitroPack: from n/a through 1.16.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:17:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43918 | WordPress WBW Product Table PRO plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary SQL Query Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43918</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WBW WBW Product Table PRO allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WBW Product Table PRO: from n/a through 1.9.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:55:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39658 | WordPress Salon Booking System plugin &amp;lt;= 10.7 - Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39658</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Salon Booking System Salon booking system allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Salon booking system: from n/a through 10.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:55:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43132 | WordPress Docket (WooCommerce Collections / Wishlist / Watchlist) plugin &amp;lt; 1.7.0 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43132</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WPWeb Elite Docket (WooCommerce Collections / Wishlist / Watchlist) allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Docket (WooCommerce Collections / Wishlist / Watchlist): from n/a before 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:55:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43144 | WordPress Cost Calculator Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.15 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43144</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in StylemixThemes Cost Calculator Builder allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Cost Calculator Builder: from n/a through 3.2.15.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:55:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43917 | WordPress TI WooCommerce Wishlist plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43917</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in TemplateInvaders TI WooCommerce Wishlist allows SQL Injection.This issue affects TI WooCommerce Wishlist: from n/a through 2.8.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:55:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8303 | dingfanzu CMS getBasicInfo.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8303</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in dingfanzu CMS up to 29d67d9044f6f93378e6eb6ff92272217ff7225c. This affects an unknown part of the file /ajax/getBasicInfo.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8304 | jpress Template Module edit path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8304</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in jpress up to 5.1.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/template/edit of the component Template Module Handler. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39622 | WordPress ListingPro theme &amp;lt;= 2.9.4 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39622</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in CridioStudio ListingPro.This issue affects ListingPro: from n/a through 2.9.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39638 | WordPress Registrations for the Events Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.12.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39638</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Roundup WP Registrations for the Events Calendar allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Registrations for the Events Calendar: from n/a through 2.12.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39653 | WordPress VikRentCar Car Rental Management System plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39653</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in E4J s.R.L. VikRentCar allows SQL Injection.This issue affects VikRentCar: from n/a through 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38793 | WordPress Best Restaurant Menu by Pricelisto plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38793</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in PriceListo Best Restaurant Menu by PriceListo allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Best Restaurant Menu by PriceListo: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38795 | WordPress ListingPro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.4 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38795</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in CridioStudio ListingPro allows SQL Injection.This issue affects ListingPro: from n/a through 2.9.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39620 | WordPress ListingPro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39620</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in CridioStudio ListingPro allows SQL Injection.This issue affects ListingPro: from n/a through 2.9.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38693 | WordPress WP User Frontend plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.7 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38693</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in weDevs WP User Frontend allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WP User Frontend: from n/a through 4.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5057 | WordPress Easy Digital Downloads plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.12 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5057</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Easy Digital Downloads allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Easy Digital Downloads: from n/a through 3.2.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8302 | dingfanzu CMS chpwd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8302</link><description>A vulnerability was found in dingfanzu CMS up to 29d67d9044f6f93378e6eb6ff92272217ff7225c. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /ajax/chpwd.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1056 | Funnel Kit Funnel Builder PRO &amp;lt;= 3.4.5 Authenticated(Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via allow_iframe_tag_in_post</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1056</link><description>The FunnelKit Funnel Builder Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'allow_iframe_tag_in_post' function which uses the 'wp_kses_allowed_html' filter to globally allow script and iframe tags in posts in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 13:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8301 | dingfanzu CMS checkin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8301</link><description>A vulnerability was found in dingfanzu CMS up to 29d67d9044f6f93378e6eb6ff92272217ff7225c. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /ajax/checkin.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 13:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1384 | Premium Portfolio Features for Phlox theme &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1384</link><description>The Premium Portfolio Features for Phlox theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'aux_recent_portfolios_grid' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 13:00:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2541 | Popup Builder &amp;lt;= 4.3.3 - Sensitive Information Exposure via Imported Subscribers CSV File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2541</link><description>The Popup Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.3 via the Subscribers Import feature. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data after an administrator has imported subscribers via a CSV file. This data may include the first name, last name, e-mail address, and potentially other personally identifiable information of subscribers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 13:00:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3679 | Premium SEO Pack – WP SEO Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.001 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3679</link><description>The Premium SEO Pack – WP SEO Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.001. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view limited information from password protected posts through the social meta data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 13:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8296 | FeehiCMS index.php insert unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8296</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FeehiCMS up to 2.1.1 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function insert of the file /admin/index.php?r=user%2Fcreate. The manipulation of the argument User[avatar] leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 13:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8297 | kitsada8621 Digital Library Management System jwt_refresh_token_middleware.go JwtRefreshAuth neutralization for logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8297</link><description>A vulnerability was found in kitsada8621 Digital Library Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function JwtRefreshAuth of the file middleware/jwt_refresh_token_middleware.go. The manipulation of the argument Authorization leads to improper output neutralization for logs. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The name of the patch is 81b3336b4c9240f0bf50c13cb8375cf860d945f1. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 13:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8295 | FeehiCMS index.php createBanner unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8295</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FeehiCMS up to 2.1.1 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function createBanner of the file /admin/index.php?r=banner%2Fbanner-create. The manipulation of the argument BannerForm[img] leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 12:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6551 | GiveWP &amp;lt;= 3.15.1 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6551</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 3.15.1. This is due to the plugin utilizing Symfony and leaving display_errors on within test files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 11:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7895 | Beaver Builder (Lite Version) &amp;lt;= 2.8.3.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via type Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7895</link><description>The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘type’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.3.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 11:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8294 | FeehiCMS index.php update unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8294</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FeehiCMS up to 2.1.1. This affects the function update of the file /admin/index.php?r=friendly-link%2Fupdate. The manipulation of the argument FriendlyLink[image] leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 11:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29723 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SportsNET</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29723</link><description>SQL injection vulnerabilities in SportsNET affecting version 4.0.1. These vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to retrieve, update and delete all information in the database by sending a specially crafted SQL query: https://XXXXXXX.saludydesafio.com/conexiones/ax/openTracExt/, parameter categoria;.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29724 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SportsNET</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29724</link><description>SQL injection vulnerabilities in SportsNET affecting version 4.0.1. These vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to retrieve, update and delete all information in the database by sending a specially crafted SQL query: https://XXXXXXX.saludydesafio.com/ax/registerSp/, parameter idDesafio.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29725 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SportsNET</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29725</link><description>SQL injection vulnerabilities in SportsNET affecting version 4.0.1. These vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to retrieve, update and delete all information in the database by sending a specially crafted SQL query: https://XXXXXXX.saludydesafio.com/app/ax/sort_bloques/, parameter list.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29726 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SportsNET</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29726</link><description>SQL injection vulnerabilities in SportsNET affecting version 4.0.1. These vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to retrieve, update and delete all information in the database by sending a specially crafted SQL query: https://XXXXXXX.saludydesafio.com/app/ax/setAsRead/, parameter id.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29727 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SportsNET</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29727</link><description>SQL injection vulnerabilities in SportsNET affecting version 4.0.1. These vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to retrieve, update and delete all information in the database by sending a specially crafted SQL query:  https://XXXXXXX.saludydesafio.com/app/ax/sendParticipationRemember/ , parameter send.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29728 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SportsNET</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29728</link><description>SQL injection vulnerabilities in SportsNET affecting version 4.0.1. These vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to retrieve, update and delete all information in the database by sending a specially crafted SQL query:  https://XXXXXXX.saludydesafio.com/app/ax/inscribeUsuario/ , parameter idDesafio.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29729 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SportsNET</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29729</link><description>SQL injection vulnerabilities in SportsNET affecting version 4.0.1. These vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to retrieve, update and delete all information in the database by sending a specially crafted SQL query: https://XXXXXXX.saludydesafio.com/app/ax/generateShortURL/, parameter url.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29730 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SportsNET</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29730</link><description>SQL injection vulnerabilities in SportsNET affecting version 4.0.1. These vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to retrieve, update and delete all information in the database by sending a specially crafted SQL query:  https://XXXXXXX.saludydesafio.com/app/ax/consejoRandom/ , parameter idCat;.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29731 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SportsNET</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29731</link><description>SQL injection vulnerabilities in SportsNET affecting version 4.0.1. These vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to retrieve, update and delete all information in the database by sending a specially crafted SQL query:  https://XXXXXXX.saludydesafio.com/app/ax/checkBlindFields/ , parameters idChallenge and idEmpresa.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4442 | tcp: add sanity tests to TCP_QUEUE_SEQ</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4442</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tcp: add sanity tests to TCP_QUEUE_SEQ

Qingyu Li reported a syzkaller bug where the repro
changes RCV SEQ _after_ restoring data in the receive queue.

mprotect(0x4aa000, 12288, PROT_READ)    = 0
mmap(0x1ffff000, 4096, PROT_NONE, MAP_PRIVATE|MAP_FIXED|MAP_ANONYMOUS, -1, 0) = 0x1ffff000
mmap(0x20000000, 16777216, PROT_READ|PROT_WRITE|PROT_EXEC, MAP_PRIVATE|MAP_FIXED|MAP_ANONYMOUS, -1, 0) = 0x20000000
mmap(0x21000000, 4096, PROT_NONE, MAP_PRIVATE|MAP_FIXED|MAP_ANONYMOUS, -1, 0) = 0x21000000
socket(AF_INET6, SOCK_STREAM, IPPROTO_IP) = 3
setsockopt(3, SOL_TCP, TCP_REPAIR, [1], 4) = 0
connect(3, {sa_family=AF_INET6, sin6_port=htons(0), sin6_flowinfo=htonl(0), inet_pton(AF_INET6, "::1", &amp;amp;sin6_addr), sin6_scope_id=0}, 28) = 0
setsockopt(3, SOL_TCP, TCP_REPAIR_QUEUE, [1], 4) = 0
sendmsg(3, {msg_name=NULL, msg_namelen=0, msg_iov=[{iov_base="0x0000000000000003\0\0", iov_len=20}], msg_iovlen=1, msg_controllen=0, msg_flags=0}, 0) = 20
setsockopt(3, SOL_TCP, TCP_REPAIR, [0], 4) = 0
setsockopt(3, SOL_TCP, TCP_QUEUE_SEQ, [128], 4) = 0
recvfrom(3, NULL, 20, 0, NULL, NULL)    = -1 ECONNRESET (Connection reset by peer)

syslog shows:
[  111.205099] TCP recvmsg seq # bug 2: copied 80, seq 0, rcvnxt 80, fl 0
[  111.207894] WARNING: CPU: 1 PID: 356 at net/ipv4/tcp.c:2343 tcp_recvmsg_locked+0x90e/0x29a0

This should not be allowed. TCP_QUEUE_SEQ should only be used
when queues are empty.

This patch fixes this case, and the tx path as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43986 | WordPress E-cab taxi booking manager plugin &amp;lt;=1.0.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43986</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MagePeople Team Taxi Booking Manager for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Taxi Booking Manager for WooCommerce: through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5622 | Untrusted search path vulnerability in the AprolConfigureCCServices of B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5622</link><description>An untrusted search path vulnerability in the AprolConfigureCCServices of B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;= R 4.2.-07P3 and &lt;= R 4.4-00P3 may allow an authenticated local attacker to execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5623 | Untrusted search path vulnerability in B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5623</link><description>An untrusted search path vulnerability in B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;= R 4.4-00P3 may be used by an authenticated local attacker to get other users to execute arbitrary code under their privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5624 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Shift Logbook application of B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5624</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Shift Logbook application of B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;= R 4.4-00P3 may allow a network-based attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the context of the user's browser session</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38304 | Dell PowerEdge Platform, 14G Intel BIOS version(s) prior to 2.22.x, contains an Access of Memory Location After End of Buffer vulnerability....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38304</link><description>Dell PowerEdge Platform, 14G Intel BIOS version(s) prior to 2.22.x, contains an Access of Memory Location After End of Buffer vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 08:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4428 | Sensetive Data Exposure in Menulux Managment Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4428</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Menulux Information Technologies Managment Portal allows Collect Data as Provided by Users.This issue affects Managment Portal: through 21.05.2024.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 07:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43700 | xfpt versions prior to 1.01 fails to handle appropriately some parameters inside the input data, resulting in a stack-based buffer overflow ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43700</link><description>xfpt versions prior to 1.01 fails to handle appropriately some parameters inside the input data, resulting in a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability. When a user of the affected product is tricked to process a specially crafted file, arbitrary code may be executed on the user's environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 07:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5417 | Gutentor &amp;lt; 3.3.6 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5417</link><description>The Gutentor  WordPress plugin before 3.3.6 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 06:10:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6927 | Viral Signup &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6927</link><description>The Viral Signup  WordPress plugin through 2.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 06:10:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7132 | CoBlocks &amp;lt; 3.1.13 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7132</link><description>The Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks  WordPress plugin before 3.1.13 does not escape the content of post embed via one of its block, which could allow users with the capability to publish posts (editor and admin by default) to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 06:10:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3944 | WP To Do &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Task Comments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3944</link><description>The WP To Do plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Comment in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 05:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5987 | WP Accessibility Helper &amp;lt;= 0.6.2.8 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5987</link><description>The WP Accessibility Helper (WAH) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'save_contrast_variations' and 'save_empty_contrast_variations' functions in all versions up to, and including, 0.6.2.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to edit or delete contrast settings.  Please note these issues were patched in 0.6.2.8, though it broke functionality and the vendor has not responded to our follow-ups.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 05:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7606 | Front End Users &amp;lt;= 3.2.28 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7606</link><description>The Front End Users plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'user-search' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.28 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 05:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7607 | Front End Users &amp;lt;= 3.2.28 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Time-Based SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7607</link><description>The Front End Users plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘order’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.28 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 05:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38303 | Dell PowerEdge Platform, 14G Intel BIOS version(s) prior to 2.22.x, contains an Improper Input Validation vulnerability. A high privileged a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38303</link><description>Dell PowerEdge Platform, 14G Intel BIOS version(s) prior to 2.22.x, contains an Improper Input Validation vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 04:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7418 | The Post Grid &amp;lt;= 7.7.11 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7418</link><description>The The Post Grid – Shortcode, Gutenberg Blocks and Elementor Addon for Post Grid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 7.7.11 via the post_query_guten and post_query functions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to extract information from posts that are not public (i.e. draft, future, etc..).</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 04:15:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7856 | MP3 Audio Player – Music Player, Podcast Player &amp;amp; Radio by Sonaar &amp;lt;= 5.7.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7856</link><description>The MP3 Audio Player – Music Player, Podcast Player &amp; Radio by Sonaar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary file deletion due to a missing capability check on the removeTempFiles() function and insufficient path validation on the 'file' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.0.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files which can make remote code execution possible when wp-config.php is deleted.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 04:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-2440 | Theme Editor &amp;lt;= 2.8 - Authenticated (Admin+) PHAR Deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2440</link><description>The Theme Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to deserialization of untrusted input via the 'images_array' parameter in versions up to, and including 2.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with administrative privileges to call files using a PHAR wrapper that will deserialize and call arbitrary PHP Objects that can be used to perform a variety of malicious actions granted a POP chain is also present. It also requires that the attacker is successful in uploading a file with the serialized payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 03:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5857 | Interactive Contact Form and Multi Step Form Builder with Drag &amp;amp; Drop Editor – Funnelforms Free &amp;lt;= 3.7.3.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Media Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5857</link><description>The Interactive Contact Form and Multi Step Form Builder with Drag &amp; Drop Editor – Funnelforms Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the af2_handel_file_remove AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.3.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary media files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 03:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45440 | core/authorize.php in Drupal 11.x-dev allows Full Path Disclosure (even when error logging is None) if the value of hash_salt is file_get_co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45440</link><description>core/authorize.php in Drupal 11.x-dev allows Full Path Disclosure (even when error logging is None) if the value of hash_salt is file_get_contents of a file that does not exist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 03:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41918 | 'Rakuten Ichiba App' for Android 12.4.0 and earlier and 'Rakuten Ichiba App' for iOS 11.7.0 and earlier are vulnerable to improper authoriza...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41918</link><description>'Rakuten Ichiba App' for Android 12.4.0 and earlier and 'Rakuten Ichiba App' for iOS 11.7.0 and earlier are vulnerable to improper authorization in handler for custom URL scheme. An arbitrary site may be displayed on the WebView of the product via Intent from another application installed on the user's device. As a result, the user may be redirected to an unauthorized site, and the user may become a victim of a phishing attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 02:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45436 | extractFromZipFile in model.go in Ollama before 0.1.47 can extract members of a ZIP archive outside of the parent directory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45436</link><description>extractFromZipFile in model.go in Ollama before 0.1.47 can extract members of a ZIP archive outside of the parent directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 02:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7857 | Media Library Folders &amp;lt;= 8.2.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Second-Order SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7857</link><description>The Media Library Folders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to second order SQL Injection via the 'sort_type' parameter of the 'mlf_change_sort_type' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 8.2.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 02:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45435 | Chartist 1.x through 1.3.0 allows Prototype Pollution via the extend function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45435</link><description>Chartist 1.x through 1.3.0 allows Prototype Pollution via the extend function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 02:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>