<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 01:12:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-12350 | JFinalCMS Template TemplateController.java update command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12350</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JFinalCMS 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function update of the file \src\main\java\com\cms\controller\admin\TemplateController.java of the component Template Handler. The manipulation of the argument content leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 01:12:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12351 | JFinalCMS File Content ContentModel.java findPage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12351</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in JFinalCMS 1.0. This affects the function findPage of the file src\main\java\com\cms\entity\ContentModel.java of the component File Content Handler. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 01:12:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12348 | Guizhou Xiaoma Technology jpress Attachment Upload upload AttachmentUtils.isUnSafe cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12348</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Guizhou Xiaoma Technology jpress 5.1.2. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function AttachmentUtils.isUnSafe of the file /commons/attachment/upload of the component Attachment Upload Handler. The manipulation of the argument files[] leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 01:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12349 | JFinalCMS save cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12349</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JFinalCMS 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/tag/save. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 01:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55563 | Bitcoin Core through 27.2 allows transaction-relay jamming via an off-chain protocol attack, a related issue to CVE-2024-52913. For example,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55563</link><description>Bitcoin Core through 27.2 allows transaction-relay jamming via an off-chain protocol attack, a related issue to CVE-2024-52913. For example, the outcome of an HTLC (Hashed Timelock Contract) can be changed because a flood of transaction traffic prevents propagation of certain Lightning channel transactions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 01:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12346 | Talentera byt_cv_manager cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12346</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Talentera up to 20241128 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /app/control/byt_cv_manager. The manipulation of the argument redirect_url leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The provided PoC only works in Mozilla Firefox. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12347 | Guangzhou Huayi Intelligent Technology Jeewms Druid Monitoring Interface index.html improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12347</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Guangzhou Huayi Intelligent Technology Jeewms up to 1.0.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /jeewms_war/webpage/system/druid/index.html of the component Druid Monitoring Interface. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12344 | TP-Link VN020 F3v(T) FTP USER Command memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12344</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TP-Link VN020 F3v(T) TT_V6.2.1021. This affects an unknown part of the component FTP USER Command Handler. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55560 | MailCleaner before 28d913e has default values of ssh_host_dsa_key, ssh_host_rsa_key, and ssh_host_ed25519_key that persist after installatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55560</link><description>MailCleaner before 28d913e has default values of ssh_host_dsa_key, ssh_host_rsa_key, and ssh_host_ed25519_key that persist after installation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12343 | TP-Link VN020 F3v(T) SOAP Request WANIPConnection buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12343</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TP-Link VN020 F3v(T) TT_V6.2.1021. Affected is an unknown function of the file /control/WANIPConnection of the component SOAP Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument NewConnectionType leads to buffer overflow. The attack needs to be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 09:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12342 | TP-Link VN020 F3v(T) Incomplete SOAP Request WANIPConnection denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12342</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TP-Link VN020 F3v(T) TT_V6.2.1021. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /control/WANIPConnection of the component Incomplete SOAP Request Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can only be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 06:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12209 | WP Umbrella: Update Backup Restore &amp;amp; Monitoring &amp;lt;= 2.17.0 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12209</link><description>The WP Umbrella: Update Backup Restore &amp; Monitoring plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.17.0 via the 'filename' parameter of the 'umbrella-restore' action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 05:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53473 | WeGIA 3.2.0 before 3998672 does not verify permission to change a password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53473</link><description>WeGIA 3.2.0 before 3998672 does not verify permission to change a password.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 22:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47107 | IBM QRadar SIEM cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47107</link><description>IBM QRadar SIEM 7.5 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows authenticated users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 14:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41762 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41762</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.5, 11.1, and 11.5 is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 13:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37071 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37071</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.5, 11.1, and 11.5 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service with a specially crafted query due to improper memory allocation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 13:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47115 | IBM AIX command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47115</link><description>IBM AIX 7.2, 7.3 and VIOS 3.1 and 4.1 could allow a local user to execute arbitrary commands on the system due to improper neutralization of input.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 13:15:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11380 | Mini Program API &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11380</link><description>The Mini Program API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'qvideo' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 11:16:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11457 | Feedpress Generator – External RSS Frontend Customizer &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11457</link><description>The Feedpress Generator – External RSS Frontend Customizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tab' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 11:16:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11464 | Easy Code Snippets &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11464</link><description>The Easy Code Snippets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 11:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11501 | Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11501</link><description>The Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.3 via deserialization of untrusted input from wd_gallery_$id parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 11:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11010 | FileOrganizer &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Local JavaScript File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11010</link><description>The FileOrganizer – Manage WordPress and Website Files plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.4 via the 'default_lang' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 09:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11367 | Smoove connector for Elementor forms &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11367</link><description>The Smoove connector for Elementor forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 09:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11374 | TWChat – Send or receive messages from users &amp;lt;= 4.0.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11374</link><description>The TWChat – Send or receive messages from users plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 09:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12128 | Simple Ecommerce Shopping Cart Plugin- Sell products through Paypal &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via monthly_sales_current_year Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12128</link><description>The Simple Ecommerce Shopping Cart Plugin- Sell products through Paypal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘monthly_sales_current_year’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 09:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12253 | Simple Ecommerce Shopping Cart Plugin- Sell products through Paypal &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Update / Data Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12253</link><description>The Simple Ecommerce Shopping Cart Plugin- Sell products through Paypal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the 'save_settings', 'export_csv', and 'simpleecommcart-action' actions in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugins settings and retrieve order and log data (which is also accessible to unauthenticated users).</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 09:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12270 | Beautiful Taxonomy Filters &amp;lt;= 2.4.3 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12270</link><description>The Beautiful taxonomy filters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'selects[0][term]' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 09:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53143 | fsnotify: Fix ordering of iput() and watched_objects decrement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53143</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fsnotify: Fix ordering of iput() and watched_objects decrement

Ensure the superblock is kept alive until we're done with iput().
Holding a reference to an inode is not allowed unless we ensure the
superblock stays alive, which fsnotify does by keeping the
watched_objects count elevated, so iput() must happen before the
watched_objects decrement.
This can lead to a UAF of something like sb-&gt;s_fs_info in tmpfs, but the
UAF is hard to hit because race orderings that oops are more likely, thanks
to the CHECK_DATA_CORRUPTION() block in generic_shutdown_super().

Also, ensure that fsnotify_put_sb_watched_objects() doesn't call
fsnotify_sb_watched_objects() on a superblock that may have already been
freed, which would cause a UAF read of sb-&gt;s_fsnotify_info.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 06:52:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11183 | Simple Side Tab &amp;lt; 2.2.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11183</link><description>The Simple Side Tab WordPress plugin before 2.2.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 06:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10046 | افزونه پیامک ووکامرس Persian WooCommerce SMS &amp;lt;= 7.0.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10046</link><description>The افزونه پیامک ووکامرس Persian WooCommerce SMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 7.0.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11329 | Comfino Payment Gateway &amp;lt;= 4.1.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11329</link><description>The Comfino Payment Gateway plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11353 | SMS for Lead Capture Forms &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Message Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11353</link><description>The SMS for Lead Capture Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the delete_message() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary messages.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11436 | Drag &amp;amp; Drop Builder, Human Face Detector, Pre-built Templates, Spam Protection, User Email Notifications &amp;amp; more! &amp;lt;= 1.4.19 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11436</link><description>The Drag &amp; Drop Builder, Human Face Detector, Pre-built Templates, Spam Protection, User Email Notifications &amp; more! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11451 | Zooom &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11451</link><description>The Zooom plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'zooom' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11904 | 코드엠샵 소셜톡 &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11904</link><description>The 코드엠샵 소셜톡 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'msntt_add_plus_talk' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11943 | 워드프레스 결제 심플페이 – 우커머스 결제 플러그인 &amp;lt;= 5.2.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via add_query_arg Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11943</link><description>The 워드프레스 결제 심플페이 – 우커머스 결제 플러그인 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12026 | Message Filter for Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) New Filter Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12026</link><description>The Message Filter for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the saveFilter() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create new filters.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12115 | Poll Maker &amp;lt;= 5.5.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Poll Duplication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12115</link><description>The Poll Maker – Versus Polls, Anonymous Polls, Image Polls plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the duplicate_poll() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to duplicate polls via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12165 | Mollie for Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 5.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12165</link><description>The Mollie for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12166 | Shortcodes Blocks Creator Ultimate &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;page&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12166</link><description>The Shortcodes Blocks Creator Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12167 | Shortcodes Blocks Creator Ultimate &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via _wpnonce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12167</link><description>The Shortcodes Blocks Creator Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the '_wpnonce' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12257 | CardGate Payments for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12257</link><description>The CardGate Payments for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7894 | If Menu &amp;lt;= 0.19.1 - Missing Authorization to License Key Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7894</link><description>The If Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of the plugin's license key due to a missing capability check on the 'actions' function in versions up to, and including, 0.19.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify delete or modify the license key.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8679 | Library Management System &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8679</link><description>The Library Management System – Manage e-Digital Books Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘value' parameter of the owt_lib_handler AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>