<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:30:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-26365 | Akamai Ghost on Akamai CDN edge servers before 2026-02-06 mishandles processing of custom hop-by-hop HTTP headers, where an incoming request...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26365</link><description>Akamai Ghost on Akamai CDN edge servers before 2026-02-06 mishandles processing of custom hop-by-hop HTTP headers, where an incoming request containing the header "Connection: Transfer-Encoding" could result in a forward request with invalid message framing, depending on the Akamai processing path. This could result in the origin server parsing the request body incorrectly, leading to HTTP request smuggling.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2979 | FastApiAdmin Scheduled Task API controller.py user_avatar_upload_controller unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2979</link><description>A flaw has been found in FastApiAdmin up to 2.2.0. This issue affects the function user_avatar_upload_controller of the file /backend/app/api/v1/module_system/user/controller.py of the component Scheduled Task API. Executing a manipulation can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2978 | FastApiAdmin Scheduled Task API controller.py upload_file_controller unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2978</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in FastApiAdmin up to 2.2.0. This vulnerability affects the function upload_file_controller of the file /backend/app/api/v1/module_system/params/controller.py of the component Scheduled Task API. Performing a manipulation results in unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1367 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1367</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADSelfService Plus versions 6522 and below are vulnerable to authenticated SQL Injection in the search report option.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2977 | FastApiAdmin Scheduled Task API controller.py upload_controller unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2977</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in FastApiAdmin up to 2.2.0. This affects the function upload_controller of the file /backend/app/api/v1/module_common/file/controller.py of the component Scheduled Task API. Such manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2976 | FastApiAdmin Download Endpoint controller.py download_controller information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2976</link><description>A weakness has been identified in FastApiAdmin up to 2.2.0. Affected by this issue is the function download_controller of the file /backend/app/api/v1/module_common/file/controller.py of the component Download Endpoint. This manipulation of the argument file_path causes information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2975 | FastApiAdmin Custom Documentation Endpoint init_app.py reset_api_docs information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2975</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in FastApiAdmin up to 2.2.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function reset_api_docs of the file /backend/app/plugin/init_app.py of the component Custom Documentation Endpoint. The manipulation results in information disclosure. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2974 | AliasVault App Backup aliasvault.xml backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2974</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in AliasVault App up to 0.25.3 on Android/iOS. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file shared_prefs/aliasvault.xml of the component Backup Handler. The manipulation of the argument accessToken/refreshToken/metadata/key_derivation_params/auth_methods leads to exposure of backup file to an unauthorized control sphere. An attack has to be approached locally. The attack is considered to have high complexity. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. Upgrading to version 0.26.0 is able to resolve this issue. The identifier of the patch is 873ecc03f92238e162f98a068ad56069a922b4f6/0bd662320174d8265dfe3b05a04bc13efc960532. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The creator of the software explains: "Because of AliasVault's zero-knowledge encryption design, the tokens stored in aliasvault.xml are API session tokens that cannot decrypt the vault on their own: the master password is required for that. So while this isn't a direct vault compromise risk, there's no reason to include them in backups either."</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2972 | a466350665 Smart-SSO Role Edit UserController.java save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2972</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in a466350665 Smart-SSO up to 2.1.1. This affects the function Save of the file smart-sso-server/src/main/java/openjoe/smart/sso/server/controller/admin/UserController.java of the component Role Edit Page. Executing a manipulation can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2971 | a466350665 Smart-SSO Login login.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2971</link><description>A vulnerability was found in a466350665 Smart-SSO up to 2.1.1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file smart-sso-server/src/main/resources/templates/login.html of the component Login. Performing a manipulation of the argument redirectUri results in cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2969 | datapizza-labs datapizza-ai Jinja2 Template prompt.py ChatPromptTemplate special elements used in a template engine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2969</link><description>A flaw has been found in datapizza-labs datapizza-ai 0.0.2. Affected is the function ChatPromptTemplate of the file datapizza-ai-core/datapizza/modules/prompt/prompt.py of the component Jinja2 Template Handler. This manipulation of the argument Prompt causes improper neutralization of special elements used in a template engine. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2970 | datapizza-labs datapizza-ai cache.py RedisCache deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2970</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in datapizza-labs datapizza-ai 0.0.2. Affected by this vulnerability is the function RedisCache of the file datapizza-ai-cache/redis/datapizza/cache/redis/cache.py. Such manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack requires being on the local network. A high complexity level is associated with this attack. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2967 | Cesanta Mongoose TCP Sequence Number net_builtin.c getpeer verification of source</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2967</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Cesanta Mongoose up to 7.20. This affects the function getpeer of the file /src/net_builtin.c of the component TCP Sequence Number Handler. The manipulation leads to improper verification of source of a communication channel. The attack may be initiated remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is reported as difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2968 | Cesanta Mongoose Poly1305 Authentication Tag tls_chacha20.c mg_chacha20_poly1305_decrypt signature verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2968</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Cesanta Mongoose up to 7.20. This impacts the function mg_chacha20_poly1305_decrypt of the file /src/tls_chacha20.c of the component Poly1305 Authentication Tag Handler. The manipulation results in improper verification of cryptographic signature. The attack may be launched remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is said to be difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2998 | eAI Technologies｜ERP - DLL Hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2998</link><description>ERP developed by eAI Technologies has a DLL Hijacking vulnerability, allowing authenticated local attackers to place a crafted DLL file in the same directory as the program, thereby executing arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2965 | 07FLYCMS/07FLY-CMS/07FlyCRM System Extension edit.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2965</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in 07FLYCMS, 07FLY-CMS and 07FlyCRM up to 1.2.9. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/SysModule/edit.html of the component System Extension Module. Performing a manipulation of the argument Title results in cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. This product is published under multiple names. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2966 | Cesanta Mongoose DNS Transaction ID dns.c mg_sendnsreq random values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2966</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Cesanta Mongoose up to 7.20. The impacted element is the function mg_sendnsreq of the file /src/dns.c of the component DNS Transaction ID Handler. Executing a manipulation of the argument random can lead to insufficiently random values. The attack can be launched remotely. The attack requires a high level of complexity. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2997 | WisdomGarden｜Tronclass - Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2997</link><description>Tronclass developed by WisdomGarden has a Insecure Direct Object Reference vulnerability. After obtaining a course ID, authenticated remote attackers to modify a specific parameter to obtain a course invitation code, thereby joining any course.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24494 | SQL injection vulnerability in Order Up Online Ordering System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24494</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in the /api/integrations/getintegrations endpoint of Order Up Online Ordering System 1.0 allows an unauthenticated attacker to access sensitive backend database data via a crafted store_id parameter in a POST request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2964 | higuma web-audio-recorder-js Dynamic Config Handling WebAudioRecorder.js extend prototype pollution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2964</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in higuma web-audio-recorder-js 0.1/0.1.1. Impacted is the function extend in the library lib/WebAudioRecorder.js of the component Dynamic Config Handling. Such manipulation leads to improperly controlled modification of object prototype attributes. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2962 | D-Link DWR-M960 Scheduled Reboot Configuration Endpoint formDateReboot sub_460F30 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2962</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. This vulnerability affects the function sub_460F30 of the file /boafrm/formDateReboot of the component Scheduled Reboot Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument submit-url results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2963 | Jinher OA C6 OfficeSupplyTypeRight.aspx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2963</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Jinher OA C6 up to 20260210. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /C6/Jhsoft.Web.officesupply/OfficeSupplyTypeRight.aspx. This manipulation of the argument id/offsnum causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2960 | D-Link DWR-M960 formDhcpv6s sub_468D64 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2960</link><description>A flaw has been found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. Affected by this issue is the function sub_468D64 of the file /boafrm/formDhcpv6s. Executing a manipulation of the argument submit-url can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2961 | D-Link DWR-M960 VPN Configuration Endpoint formVpnConfigSetup sub_4196C4 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2961</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. This affects the function sub_4196C4 of the file /boafrm/formVpnConfigSetup of the component VPN Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2588 | Crypt::NaCl::Sodium versions through 2.001 for Perl has an integer overflow flaw on 32-bit systems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2588</link><description>Crypt::NaCl::Sodium versions through 2.001 for Perl has an integer overflow flaw on 32-bit systems.

Sodium.xs casts a STRLEN (size_t) to unsigned long long when passing a length pointer to libsodium functions.  On 32-bit systems size_t is typically 32-bits while an unsigned long long is at least 64-bits.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 23:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2958 | D-Link DWR-M960 formWsc sub_457C5C stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2958</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. Affected is the function sub_457C5C of the file /boafrm/formWsc. Such manipulation of the argument save_apply leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 23:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2959 | D-Link DWR-M960 formNewSchedule sub_44E0F8 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2959</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_44E0F8 of the file /boafrm/formNewSchedule. Performing a manipulation of the argument url results in stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 23:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2957 | qinming99 dst-admin File BackupController.java deleteBackup denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2957</link><description>A weakness has been identified in qinming99 dst-admin up to 1.5.0. This impacts the function deleteBackup of the file src/main/java/com/tugos/dst/admin/controller/BackupController.java of the component File Handler. This manipulation causes denial of service. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 23:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2956 | qinming99 dst-admin restore revertBackup command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2956</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in qinming99 dst-admin up to 1.5.0. This affects the function revertBackup of the file /home/restore. The manipulation of the argument Name results in command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 22:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2954 | Dromara UJCMS ImportDataController import-channel importChanel injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2954</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Dromara UJCMS 10.0.2. Impacted is the function importChanel of the file /api/backend/ext/import-data/import-channel of the component ImportDataController. Performing a manipulation of the argument driverClassName/url results in injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25455 | Web Ofisi E-Ticaret v3 SQL Injection via ara.html</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25455</link><description>Web Ofisi E-Ticaret v3 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the 'a' parameter. Attackers can send GET requests to with malicious 'a' parameter values to extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25456 | Web Ofisi Emlak v2 SQL Injection via ara Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25456</link><description>Web Ofisi Emlak v2 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the 'ara' GET parameter. Attackers can send requests to with time-based SQL injection payloads to extract sensitive database information or cause denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25457 | Web Ofisi Firma v13 SQL Injection via oz Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25457</link><description>Web Ofisi Firma v13 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the 'oz' array parameter. Attackers can send GET requests to category pages with malicious 'oz[]' values using time-based blind SQL injection payloads to extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25458 | Web Ofisi Firma Rehberi v1 SQL Injection via firmalar.html</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25458</link><description>Web Ofisi Firma Rehberi v1 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through GET parameters. Attackers can send requests to with malicious payloads in the 'il', 'kat', or 'kelime' parameters to extract sensitive database information or perform time-based blind SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25459 | Web Ofisi Emlak V2 SQL Injection via emlak-ara.html</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25459</link><description>Web Ofisi Emlak V2 contains multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in the endpoint that allow unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries through GET parameters. Attackers can inject SQL code into parameters like emlak_durumu, emlak_tipi, il, ilce, kelime, and semt to extract sensitive database information or perform time-based blind SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25460 | Web Ofisi Platinum E-Ticaret v5 SQL Injection via q Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25460</link><description>Web Ofisi Platinum E-Ticaret v5 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the 'q' GET parameter. Attackers can send requests to the arama endpoint with malicious 'q' values using time-based SQL injection techniques to extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25461 | Web Ofisi Platinum E-Ticaret v5 SQL Injection via ajax/productsFilterSearch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25461</link><description>Web Ofisi Platinum E-Ticaret v5 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the 'q' parameter. Attackers can send POST requests to the ajax/productsFilterSearch endpoint with malicious 'q' values using time-based blind SQL injection techniques to extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25462 | Web Ofisi Rent a Car v3 SQL Injection via klima Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25462</link><description>Web Ofisi Rent a Car v3 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the 'klima' parameter. Attackers can send GET requests to with malicious 'klima' values to extract sensitive database information or cause denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2952 | Vaelsys HTTP POST Request tree_server.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2952</link><description>A flaw has been found in Vaelsys 4.1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /tree/tree_server.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. This manipulation of the argument xajaxargs causes os command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2953 | Dromara UJCMS Template WebFileTemplateController.delete deleteDirectory path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2953</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dromara UJCMS 101.2. This issue affects the function deleteDirectory of the file WebFileTemplateController.delete of the component Template Handler. Such manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25366 | microASP Portal+ CMS SQL Injection via pagina.phtml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25366</link><description>microASP Portal+ CMS contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL queries by injecting malicious code into the explode_tree parameter. Attackers can send crafted requests to pagina.phtml with SQL injection payloads using extractvalue and concat functions to extract sensitive database information like the current database name.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25391 | Ashop Shopping Cart Software Lastest Latest SQL Injection via bannedcustomers.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25391</link><description>Ashop Shopping Cart Software contains a time-based blind SQL injection vulnerability that allows attackers to manipulate database queries through the blacklistitemid parameter. Attackers can send POST requests to the admin/bannedcustomers.php endpoint with crafted SQL payloads using SLEEP functions to extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25433 | XOOPS CMS 2.5.9 SQL Injection via gerar_pdf.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25433</link><description>XOOPS CMS 2.5.9 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the cid parameter. Attackers can send GET requests to the gerar_pdf.php endpoint with malicious cid values to extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25439 | NoviSmart CMS SQL Injection via Referer HTTP Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25439</link><description>NoviSmart CMS contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL queries by injecting malicious code through the Referer HTTP header field. Attackers can craft requests with time-based SQL injection payloads in the Referer header to extract sensitive database information or cause denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25440 | WebIncorp ERP Every version SQL Injection via product_detail.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25440</link><description>WebIncorp ERP contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the prod_id parameter. Attackers can send GET requests to product_detail.php with malicious prod_id values to extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2947 | rymcu forest User Profile UserInfoController.java updateUserInfo cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2947</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in rymcu forest up to 0.0.5. This affects the function updateUserInfo of the file - src/main/java/com/rymcu/forest/web/api/user/UserInfoController.java of the component User Profile Handler. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25442 | Web Wiz Forums 12.01 SQL Injection via PF Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25442</link><description>Web Wiz Forums 12.01 contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the PF parameter. Attackers can send GET requests to member_profile.asp with malicious PF values to extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25443 | Inventory Webapp SQL Injection via add-item.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25443</link><description>Inventory Webapp contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through GET parameters. Attackers can supply malicious SQL payloads in the name, description, quantity, or cat_id parameters to add-item.php to execute arbitrary database commands.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25446 | DIGIT CENTRIS ERP Every version SQL Injection via datum1 Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25446</link><description>DIGIT CENTRIS ERP contains an SQL injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through the datum1, datum2, KID, and PID parameters. Attackers can send POST requests to /korisnikinfo.php with malicious SQL syntax in these parameters to extract or modify sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25450 | Dolibarr ERP/CRM 10.0.1 SQL Injection via card.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25450</link><description>Dolibarr ERP/CRM 10.0.1 contains multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities that allow authenticated attackers to manipulate database queries by injecting SQL code through POST parameters. Attackers can inject malicious SQL through parameters like actioncode, demand_reason_id, and availability_id in card.php endpoints to extract sensitive database information using boolean-based blind, error-based, and time-based blind techniques.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25452 | Dolibarr ERP/CRM 10.0.1 SQL Injection via elemid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25452</link><description>Dolibarr ERP/CRM 10.0.1 contains an SQL injection vulnerability in the elemid POST parameter of the viewcat.php endpoint that allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL queries. Attackers can submit crafted POST requests with malicious SQL payloads in the elemid parameter to extract sensitive database information using error-based or time-based blind SQL injection techniques.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2945 | JeecgBoot uploadImgByHttp server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2945</link><description>A weakness has been identified in JeecgBoot 3.9.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /sys/common/uploadImgByHttp. Executing a manipulation of the argument fileUrl can lead to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2946 | rymcu forest Article Content/Comments/Portfolio XssUtils.java XssUtils.replaceHtmlCode cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2946</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in rymcu forest up to 0.0.5. Affected by this issue is the function XssUtils.replaceHtmlCode of the file src/main/java/com/rymcu/forest/util/XssUtils.java of the component Article Content/Comments/Portfolio. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2944 | Tosei Online Store Management System ネット店舗管理システム HTTP POST Request monitor.php system os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2944</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tosei Online Store Management System ネット店舗管理システム 1.01. Affected is the function system of the file /cgi-bin/monitor.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. Performing a manipulation of the argument DevId results in os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 11:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2943 | SapneshNaik Student Management System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2943</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SapneshNaik Student Management System up to f4b4f0928f0b5551a28ee81ae7e7fe47d9345318. This impacts an unknown function of the file index.php. Such manipulation of the argument Error leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 10:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2940 | Zaher1307 tiny_web_server URL tiny.c out-of-bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2940</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Zaher1307 tiny_web_server up to 8d77b1044a0ca3a5297d8726ac8aa2cf944d481b. This affects the function tiny_web_server/tiny.c of the file tiny_web_server/tiny.c of the component URL Handler. This manipulation causes out-of-bounds write. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 10:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2939 | itsourcecode Student Management System Add Student add_student cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2939</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Student Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /add_student/ of the component Add Student Module. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 09:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2938 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System update_smtp.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2938</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /srms/script/admin/core/update_smtp.php. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 09:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2385 | The Plus Addons for Elementor – Addons for Elementor, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 6.4.7 - Unauthenticated Email Relay</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2385</link><description>The The Plus Addons for Elementor – Addons for Elementor, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insufficient Verification of Data Authenticity in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.7. This is due to the plugin decrypting and trusting attacker-controlled email_data in an unauthenticated AJAX handler without cryptographic authenticity guarantees. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to tamper with form email routing and redirection values to trigger unauthorized email relay and attacker-controlled redirection via the 'email_data' parameter.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 08:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2934 | YiFang CMS Extended Management D_friendLinkGroup.php update cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2934</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in YiFang CMS up to 2.0.5. This impacts the function update of the file app/db/admin/D_friendLinkGroup.php of the component Extended Management Module. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 08:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2935 | UTT HiPER 810G ConfigExceptMSN strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2935</link><description>A weakness has been identified in UTT HiPER 810G up to 1.7.7-171114. This issue affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/ConfigExceptMSN. Executing a manipulation of the argument remark can lead to buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 08:46:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2932 | YiFang CMS Extended Management D_adPosition.php update cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2932</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in YiFang CMS up to 2.0.5. The impacted element is the function update of the file app/db/admin/D_adPosition.php of the component Extended Management Module. Performing a manipulation of the argument name/index results in cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 07:49:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2933 | YiFang CMS Extended Management D_adManage.php update cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2933</link><description>A weakness has been identified in YiFang CMS up to 2.0.5. This affects the function update of the file app/db/admin/D_adManage.php of the component Extended Management Module. Executing a manipulation of the argument Name can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 07:49:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2930 | Tenda A18 Httpd Service UploadCfg webCgiGetUploadFile stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2930</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda A18 15.13.07.13. The affected element is the function webCgiGetUploadFile of the file /cgi-bin/UploadCfg of the component Httpd Service. Such manipulation of the argument boundary leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1369 | Conditional CAPTCHA &amp;lt;= 4.0.0 - Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1369</link><description>The Conditional CAPTCHA WordPress plugin through 4.0.0 does not validate a parameter before redirecting the user to its value, leading to an Open Redirect issue</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2929 | D-Link DWR-M960 Wireless Access Control Endpoint formWlAc sub_453140 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2929</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. Impacted is the function sub_453140 of the file /boafrm/formWlAc of the component Wireless Access Control Endpoint. This manipulation of the argument submit-url causes stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 05:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2928 | D-Link DWR-M960 WLAN Encryption Configuration Endpoint formWlEncrypt sub_452CCC stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2928</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. This issue affects the function sub_452CCC of the file /boafrm/formWlEncrypt of the component WLAN Encryption Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument submit-url results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 05:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2926 | D-Link DWR-M960 LTE Configuration Endpoint formLteSetup sub_4237AC stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2926</link><description>A flaw has been found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. This affects the function sub_4237AC of the file /boafrm/formLteSetup of the component LTE Configuration Endpoint. Executing a manipulation of the argument submit-url can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 05:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2927 | D-Link DWR-M960 Operation Mode Configuration Endpoint formOpMode sub_462590 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2927</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. This vulnerability affects the function sub_462590 of the file /boafrm/formOpMode of the component Operation Mode Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 05:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2912 | code-projects Online Reviewer System studentresult-view.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2912</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /system/system/students/assessments/results/studentresult-view.php. The manipulation of the argument test_id results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 04:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2913 | libvips source.c vips_source_read_to_memory heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2913</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in libvips up to 8.19.0. The affected element is the function vips_source_read_to_memory of the file libvips/iofuncs/source.c. This manipulation causes heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Patch name: a56feecbe9ed66521d9647ec9fbcd2546eccd7ee. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue. The confirmation of the bugfix mentions: "[T]he impact of this is negligible, since this only affects custom seekable sources larger than 4 GiB (and the crash occurs in user code rather than libvips itself)."</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 04:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2925 | D-Link DWR-M960 Bridge VLAN Configuration Endpoint formBridgeVlan sub_42B5A0 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2925</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. Affected by this issue is the function sub_42B5A0 of the file /boafrm/formBridgeVlan of the component Bridge VLAN Configuration Endpoint. Performing a manipulation of the argument submit-url results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 04:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2910 | Tenda HG9 formPing6 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2910</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda HG9 300001138. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boaform/formPing6. Executing a manipulation of the argument pingAddr can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 04:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2911 | Tenda FH451 GstDhcpSetSer buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2911</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda FH451 up to 1.0.0.9. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/GstDhcpSetSer. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 04:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2906 | Tenda HG9 Samba Configuration Endpoint formSamba stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2906</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda HG9 300001138. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boaform/formSamba of the component Samba Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument sambaCap results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2907 | Tenda HG9 GPON Configuration Endpoint formgponConf stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2907</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda HG9 300001138. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /boaform/formgponConf of the component GPON Configuration Endpoint. This manipulation of the argument fmgpon_loid/fmgpon_loid_password causes stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2908 | Tenda HG9 Loopback Detection Configuration Endpoint formLoopBack stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2908</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda HG9 300001138. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /boaform/formLoopBack of the component Loopback Detection Configuration Endpoint. Such manipulation of the argument Ethtype leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2909 | Tenda HG9 Diagnostic Ping Endpoint formPing stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2909</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda HG9 300001138. This affects an unknown part of the file /boaform/formPing of the component Diagnostic Ping Endpoint. Performing a manipulation of the argument pingAddr results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2905 | Tenda HG9 Wireless Configuration Endpoint formWlanSetup stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2905</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda HG9 300001138. This impacts an unknown function of the file /boaform/formWlanSetup of the component Wireless Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument ssid leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2897 | funadmin Backend index.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2897</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in funadmin up to 7.1.0-rc4. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file app/backend/view/index/index.html of the component Backend Interface. The manipulation of the argument Value leads to cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2898 | funadmin Backend Endpoint AuthCloudService.php getMember deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2898</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in funadmin up to 7.1.0-rc4. This issue affects the function getMember of the file app/common/service/AuthCloudService.php of the component Backend Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument cloud_account results in deserialization. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2903 | skvadrik re2c ast.cc check_and_merge_special_rules null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2903</link><description>A flaw has been found in skvadrik re2c up to 4.4. Impacted is the function check_and_merge_special_rules of the file src/parse/ast.cc. This manipulation causes null pointer dereference. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been published and may be used. Patch name: febeb977936f9519a25d9fbd10ff8256358cdb97. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2904 | UTT HiPER 810G ConfigExceptAli strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2904</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT HiPER 810G 1.7.7-171114. This affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/ConfigExceptAli. Executing a manipulation can lead to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2896 | funadmin Configuration Ajax.php setConfig improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2896</link><description>A weakness has been identified in funadmin up to 7.1.0-rc4. This affects the function setConfig of the file app/backend/controller/Ajax.php of the component Configuration Handler. Executing a manipulation can lead to improper authorization. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 23:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2894 | funadmin forget.html getMember information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2894</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in funadmin up to 7.1.0-rc4. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getMember of the file app/frontend/view/login/forget.html. Such manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 23:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2895 | funadmin Member.php repass password recovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2895</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in funadmin up to 7.1.0-rc4. Affected by this issue is the function repass of the file app/frontend/controller/Member.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument forget_code/vercode results in weak password recovery. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 23:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2889 | CCExtractor mp4.c processmp4 use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2889</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in CCExtractor up to 0.96.5. Affected is the function processmp4 in the library src/lib_ccx/mp4.c. Performing a manipulation results in use after free. The attack is only possible with local access. The exploit is now public and may be used. Upgrading to version 0.96.6 is able to address this issue. The patch is named fd7271bae238ccb3ae8a71304ea64f0886324925. You should upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 22:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2886 | Tenda A21 SetOnlineDevName set_device_name stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2886</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda A21 1.0.0.0. This affects the function set_device_name of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName. This manipulation of the argument devName causes stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 21:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2887 | aardappel lobster idents.h TypeName recursion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2887</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in aardappel lobster up to 2025.4. This impacts the function lobster::TypeName in the library dev/src/lobster/idents.h. Such manipulation leads to uncontrolled recursion. The attack can only be performed from a local environment. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. Upgrading to version 2026.1 will fix this issue. The name of the patch is 8ba49f98ccfc9734ef352146806433a41d9f9aa6. It is advisable to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 21:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2884 | D-Link DWR-M960 WAN Interface Setting formWanConfigSetup sub_41914C stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2884</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. The affected element is the function sub_41914C of the file /boafrm/formWanConfigSetup of the component WAN Interface Setting Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 20:53:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2885 | D-Link DWR-M960 formIpv6Setup sub_469104 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2885</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. The impacted element is the function sub_469104 of the file /boafrm/formIpv6Setup. The manipulation of the argument submit-url results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 20:53:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2882 | D-Link DWR-M960 formDosCfg sub_46385C stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2882</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. This issue affects the function sub_46385C of the file /boafrm/formDosCfg. Performing a manipulation of the argument submit-url results in stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2883 | D-Link DWR-M960 formIpQoS sub_427D74 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2883</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. Impacted is the function sub_427D74 of the file /boafrm/formIpQoS. Executing a manipulation of the argument submit-url can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2881 | D-Link DWR-M960 Advanced Firewall Configuration Endpoint formFirewallAdv sub_425FF8 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2881</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. This vulnerability affects the function sub_425FF8 of the file /boafrm/formFirewallAdv of the component Advanced Firewall Configuration Endpoint. Such manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 19:51:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2877 | Tenda A18 Httpd Service WifiExtraSet strcpy stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2877</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda A18 15.13.07.13. This affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/WifiExtraSet of the component Httpd Service. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto5g leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 19:05:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2874 | Tenda A21 fast_setting_wifi_set form_fast_setting_wifi_set stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2874</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda A21 1.0.0.0. Impacted is the function form_fast_setting_wifi_set of the file /goform/fast_setting_wifi_set. Executing a manipulation of the argument ssid can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2876 | Tenda A18 setBlackRule parse_macfilter_rule stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2876</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda A18 15.13.07.13. This affects the function parse_macfilter_rule of the file /goform/setBlackRule. This manipulation of the argument deviceList causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2873 | Tenda A21 openSchedWifi setSchedWifi stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2873</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda A21 1.0.0.0. This issue affects the function setSchedWifi of the file /goform/openSchedWifi. Performing a manipulation of the argument schedStartTime/schedEndTime results in stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2872 | Tenda A21 MAC Filtering Configuration Endpoint setBlackRule set_device_name stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2872</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda A21 1.0.0.0. This vulnerability affects the function set_device_name of the file /goform/setBlackRule of the component MAC Filtering Configuration Endpoint. Such manipulation of the argument devName/mac leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:16:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2871 | Tenda A21 SetIpMacBind fromSetIpMacBind stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2871</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda A21 1.0.0.0. This affects the function fromSetIpMacBind of the file /goform/SetIpMacBind. This manipulation of the argument list causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2869 | janet-lang janet handleattr specials.c janetc_varset out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2869</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in janet-lang janet up to 1.40.1. Affected by this vulnerability is the function janetc_varset of the file src/core/specials.c of the component handleattr Handler. The manipulation leads to out-of-bounds read. The attack can only be performed from a local environment. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. Upgrading to version 1.41.0 addresses this issue. The identifier of the patch is 2fabc80151a2b8834ee59cda8a70453f848b40e5. The affected component should be upgraded.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2870 | Tenda A21 formSetQosBand set_qosMib_list stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2870</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda A21 1.0.0.0. Affected by this issue is the function set_qosMib_list of the file /goform/formSetQosBand. The manipulation of the argument list results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2867 | itsourcecode Vehicle Management System billaction.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2867</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Vehicle Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /billaction.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:13:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1787 | LearnPress Export Import &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Missing Authentication to Unauthenticated Migrated Course Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1787</link><description>The LearnPress Export Import – WordPress extension for LearnPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'delete_migrated_data' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete course that have been migrated from Tutor LMS. The Tutor LMS plugin must be installed and activated in order to exploit the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27492 | Lettermint Node.js SDK leaks email properties to unintended recipients when client instance is reused</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27492</link><description>Lettermint Node.js SDK is the official Node.js SDK for Lettermint. In versions 1.5.0 and below, email properties (such as to, subject, html, text, and attachments) are not reset between sends when a single client instance is reused across multiple .send() calls. This can cause properties from a previous send to leak into a subsequent one, potentially delivering content or recipient addresses to unintended parties. Applications sending emails to different recipients in sequence — such as transactional flows like password resets or notifications — are affected. This issue has been fixed in version 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:51:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27574 | OneUptime: node:vm sandbox escape in probe allows any project member to achieve RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27574</link><description>OneUptime is a solution for monitoring and managing online services. In versions 9.5.13 and below, custom JavaScript monitor feature uses Node.js's node:vm module (explicitly documented as not a security mechanism) to execute user-supplied code, allowing trivial sandbox escape via a well-known one-liner that grants full access to the underlying process. Because the probe runs with host networking and holds all cluster credentials (ONEUPTIME_SECRET, DATABASE_PASSWORD, REDIS_PASSWORD, CLICKHOUSE_PASSWORD) in its environment variables, and monitor creation is available to the lowest role (ProjectMember) with open registration enabled by default, any anonymous user can achieve full cluster compromise in about 30 seconds. This issue has been fixed in version 10.0.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:51:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27579 | CollabPlatform : CORS Misconfiguration Allows Arbitrary Origin With Credentials Leading to Authenticated Account Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27579</link><description>CollabPlatform is a full-stack, real-time doc collaboration platform. In all versions of CollabPlatform, the Appwrite project used by the application is misconfigured to allow arbitrary origins in CORS responses while also permitting credentialed requests. An attacker-controlled domain can issue authenticated cross-origin requests and read sensitive user account information, including email address, account identifiers, and MFA status. The issue did not have a fix at the time of publication.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:51:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27576 | OpenClaw: ACP prompt-size checks missing in local stdio bridge could reduce responsiveness with very large inputs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27576</link><description>OpenClaw is a personal AI assistant. In versions 2026.2.17 and below, the ACP bridge accepts very large prompt text blocks and can assemble oversized prompt payloads before forwarding them to chat.send. Because ACP runs over local stdio, this mainly affects local ACP clients (for example IDE integrations) that send unusually large inputs. This issue has been fixed in version 2026.2.19.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27488 | OpenClaw hardened cron webhook delivery against SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27488</link><description>OpenClaw is a personal AI assistant. In versions 2026.2.17 and below, Cron webhook delivery in src/gateway/server-cron.ts uses fetch() directly, so webhook targets can reach private/metadata/internal endpoints without SSRF policy checks. This issue was fixed in version 2026.2.19.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27486 | OpenClaw: Process Safety - Unvalidated PID Kill via SIGKILL in Process Cleanup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27486</link><description>OpenClaw is a personal AI assistant. In versions 2026.2.13 and below of the OpenClaw CLI, the process cleanup uses system-wide process enumeration and pattern matching to terminate processes without verifying if they are owned by the current OpenClaw process. On shared hosts, unrelated processes can be terminated if they match the pattern. The CLI runner cleanup helpers can kill processes matched by command-line patterns without validating process ownership. This issue has been fixed in version 2026.2.14.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27487 | OpenClaw: Prevent shell injection in macOS keychain credential write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27487</link><description>OpenClaw is a personal AI assistant. In versions 2026.2.13 and below, when using macOS, the Claude CLI keychain credential refresh path constructed a shell command to write the updated JSON blob into Keychain via security add-generic-password -w .... Because OAuth tokens are user-controlled data, this created an OS command injection risk. This issue has been fixed in version 2026.2.14.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14339 | weMail &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Form Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14339</link><description>The weMail - Email Marketing, Lead Generation, Optin Forms, Email Newsletters, A/B Testing, and Automation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized form deletion in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.7. This is due to the `Forms::permission()` callback only validating the `X-WP-Nonce` header without checking user capabilities. Since the REST nonce is exposed to unauthenticated visitors via the `weMail` JavaScript object on pages with weMail forms, any unauthenticated user can permanently delete all weMail forms by extracting the nonce from the page source and sending a DELETE request to the forms endpoint.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27482 | Ray: Dashboard DELETE endpoints allow unauthenticated browser-triggered DoS (Serve shutdown / job deletion)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27482</link><description>Ray is an AI compute engine. In versions 2.53.0 and below, thedashboard HTTP server blocks browser-origin POST/PUT but does not cover DELETE, and key DELETE endpoints are unauthenticated by default. If the dashboard/agent is reachable (e.g., --dashboard-host=0.0.0.0), a web page via DNS rebinding or same-network access can issue DELETE requests that shut down Serve or delete jobs without user interaction. This is a drive-by availability impact. The fix for this vulnerability is to update to Ray 2.54.0 or higher.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27484 | OpenClaw Discord moderation authorization used untrusted sender identity in tool-driven flows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27484</link><description>OpenClaw is a personal AI assistant. In versions 2026.2.17 and below, the Discord moderation action handling (timeout, kick, ban) uses sender identity from request parameters in tool-driven flows, instead of trusted runtime sender context. In setups where Discord moderation actions are enabled and the bot has the necessary guild permissions, a non-admin user can request moderation actions by spoofing sender identity fields. This issue has been fixed in version 2026.2.18.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27485 | OpenClaw affected by Stored XSS in Control UI via unsanitized assistant name/avatar in inline script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27485</link><description>OpenClaw is a personal AI assistant. In versions 2026.2.17 and below, skills/skill-creator/scripts/package_skill.py (a local helper script used when authors package skills) previously followed symlinks while building .skill archives. If an author runs this script on a crafted local skill directory containing symlinks to files outside the skill root, the resulting archive can include unintended file contents. If exploited, this vulnerability can lead to potential unintentional disclosure of local files from the packaging machine into a generated .skill artifact, but requires local execution of the packaging script on attacker-controlled skill contents. This issue has been fixed in version 2026.2.18.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27480 | Static Web Server: Timing-Based Username Enumeration in Basic Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27480</link><description>Static Web Server (SWS) is a production-ready web server suitable for static web files or assets. In versions 2.1.0 through 2.40.1, a timing-based username enumeration vulnerability in Basic Authentication allows attackers to identify valid users by exploiting early responses for invalid usernames, enabling targeted brute-force or credential-stuffing attacks. SWS checks whether a username exists before verifying the password, causing valid usernames to follow a slower code path (e.g., bcrypt hashing) while invalid usernames receive an immediate 401 response. This timing discrepancy allows attackers to enumerate valid accounts by measuring response-time differences. This issue has been fixed in version 2.41.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27479 | Wallos: SSRF via Redirect Bypass in Logo/Icon URL Fetch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27479</link><description>Wallos is an open-source, self-hostable personal subscription tracker. Versions 4.6.0 and below contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the subscription and payment logo/icon upload functionality. The application validates the IP address of the provided URL before making the request, but allows HTTP redirects (CURLOPT_FOLLOWLOCATION = true), enabling an attacker to bypass the IP validation and access internal resources, including cloud instance metadata endpoints. The getLogoFromUrl() function validates the URL by resolving the hostname and checking if the resulting IP is in a private or reserved range using FILTER_FLAG_NO_PRIV_RANGE | FILTER_FLAG_NO_RES_RANGE. However, the subsequent cURL request is configured with CURLOPT_FOLLOWLOCATION = true and CURLOPT_MAXREDIRS = 3, which means the request will follow HTTP redirects without re-validating the destination IP. This issue has been fixed in version 4.6.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27464 | Metabase: Server-Side Template Injection via Notifications Endpoint Leads to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27464</link><description>Metabase is an open-source data analytics platform. In versions prior to 0.57.13 and versions 0.58.x through 0.58.6, authenticated users are able to retrieve sensitive information from a Metabase instance, including database access credentials. During testing, it was confirmed that a low-privileged user can extract sensitive information including database credentials, into the email body via template evaluation. This issue has been fixed in versions 0.57.13 and 0.58.7. To workaround this issue, users can disable notifications in their Metabase instance to disallow access to the vulnerable endpoints.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27470 | ZoneMinder: Second-Order SQL Injection in `getNearEvents()` via Stored Event Name and Cause Fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27470</link><description>ZoneMinder is a free, open source closed-circuit television software application. In versions 1.36.37 and below and 1.37.61 through 1.38.0, there is a second-order SQL Injection vulnerability in the web/ajax/status.php file within the getNearEvents() function. Event field values (specifically Name and Cause) are stored safely via parameterized queries but are later retrieved and concatenated directly into SQL WHERE clauses without escaping. An authenticated user with Events edit and view permissions can exploit this to execute arbitrary SQL queries.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27469 | Isso: Stored XSS via comment website field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27469</link><description>Isso is a lightweight commenting server written in Python and JavaScript. In commits before 0afbfe0691ee237963e8fb0b2ee01c9e55ca2144, there is a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting the website and author comment fields. The website field was HTML-escaped using quote=False, which left single and double quotes unescaped. Since the frontend inserts the website value directly into a single-quoted href attribute via string concatenation, a single quote in the URL breaks out of the attribute context, allowing injection of arbitrary event handlers (e.g. onmouseover, onclick). The same escaping is missing entirely from the user-facing comment edit endpoint (PUT /id/) and the moderation edit endpoint (POST /id//edit/). This issue has been patched in commit 0afbfe0691ee237963e8fb0b2ee01c9e55ca2144. To workaround, nabling comment moderation (moderation = enabled = true in isso.cfg) prevents unauthenticated users from publishing comments, raising the bar for exploitation, but it does not fully mitigate the issue since a moderator activating a malicious comment would still expose visitors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2864 | feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp/production_ssm PictureController.java pictureDelete path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2864</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp and production_ssm up to 4288d53bd35757b27f2d070057aefb2c07bdd097. This affects the function pictureDelete of the file PictureController.java. Such manipulation of the argument picName leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. This product is distributed under two entirely different names. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2865 | itsourcecode Agri-Trading Online Shopping System HTTP POST Request productcontroller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2865</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Agri-Trading Online Shopping System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file admin/productcontroller.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. Performing a manipulation of the argument Product results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27466 | BigBlueButton: Exposed ClamAV port enables Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27466</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom. In versions 3.0.21 and below, the official documentation for "Server Customization" on Support for ClamAV as presentation file scanner contains instructions that leave a BBB server vulnerable for Denial of Service. The flawed command exposes both ports (3310 and 7357) to the internet. A remote attacker can use this to send complex or large documents to clamd and waste server resources, or shutdown the clamd process. The clamd documentation explicitly warns about exposing this port. Enabling ufw (ubuntu firewall) during install does not help, because Docker routes container traffic through the nat table, which is not managed or restricted by ufw. Rules installed by ufw in the filter table have no effect on docker traffic. In addition, the provided example also mounts /var/bigbluebutton with write permissions into the container, which should not be required. Future vulnerabilities in clamd may allow attackers to manipulate files in that folder. Users are unaffected unless they have opted in to follow the extra instructions from BigBlueButton's documentation. This issue has been fixed in version 3.0.22.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27467 | BigBlueButton: Audio from participants to the server initially unmuted</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27467</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom. In versions 3.0.19 and below, when first joining a session with the microphone muted, the client sends audio to the server regardless of mute state. Media is discarded at the server side, so it isn't audible to any participants, but this may allow for malicious server operators to access audio data. The behavior is only incorrect between joining the meeting and the first time the user unmutes. This issue has been fixed in version 3.0.20.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27206 | Zumba Json Serializer has a potential PHP Object Injection via Unrestricted @type in unserialize()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27206</link><description>Zumba Json Serializer is a library to serialize PHP variables in JSON format. In versions 3.2.2 and below, the library allows deserialization of PHP objects from JSON using a special @type field. The deserializer instantiates any class specified in the @type field without restriction. When processing untrusted JSON input, this behavior may allow an attacker to instantiate arbitrary classes available in the application. If a vulnerable application passes attacker-controlled JSON into JsonSerializer::unserialize() and contains classes with dangerous magic methods (such as __wakeup() or __destruct()), this may lead to PHP Object Injection and potentially Remote Code Execution (RCE), depending on available gadget chains in the application or its dependencies. This behavior is similar in risk profile to PHP's native unserialize() when used without the allowed_classes restriction. Applications are impacted only if untrusted or attacker-controlled JSON is passed into JsonSerializer::unserialize() and the application or its dependencies contain classes that can be leveraged as a gadget chain. This issue has been fixed in version 3.2.3. If an immediate upgrade isn't feasible, mitigate the vulnerability by never deserializing untrusted JSON with JsonSerializer::unserialize(), validating and sanitizing all JSON input before deserialization, and disabling @type-based object instantiation wherever possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27452 | ASN.1 TypeScript Library: Decoding an INTEGER could leak the underlying ArrayBuffer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27452</link><description>ASN.1 TypeScript ESM library, including codecs for Basic Encoding Rules (BER) and Distinguished Encoding Rules (DER). In versions 11.0.5 and below, in some cases, decoding an INTEGER could leak the underlying ArrayBuffer. This issue is expected to be fixed in version 11.0.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27458 | LinkAce: Stored XSS in Atom Feed via CDATA Escape in List Description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27458</link><description>LinkAce is a self-hosted archive to collect website links. Versions 2.4.2 and below have a Stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability through the Atom feed endpoint for lists (/lists/feed). An authenticated user can inject a CDATA-breaking payload into a list description that escapes the XML CDATA section, injects a native SVG element into the Atom XML document, and executes arbitrary JavaScript directly in the browser when the feed URL is visited. No RSS reader or additional rendering context is required — the browser's native XML parser processes the injected SVG and fires the onload event handler. This vulnerability exists because the lists feed template outputs list descriptions using Blade's raw syntax ({!! !!}) without sanitization inside a CDATA block. The critical detail is that because the output sits inside , an attacker can inject the sequence ]]&gt; to close the CDATA section prematurely, then inject arbitrary XML/SVG elements that the browser parses and executes natively as part of the Atom document. This issue has been fixed in version 2.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27471 | ERP: Document access through endpoints due to missing validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27471</link><description>ERP is a free and open source Enterprise Resource Planning tool. In versions up to 15.98.0 and 16.0.0-rc.1 and through 16.6.0, certain endpoints lacked access validation which allowed for unauthorized document access. This issue has been fixed in versions 15.98.1 and 16.6.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2861 | Foswiki Changes/Viewfile/Oops information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2861</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Foswiki up to 2.1.10. The affected element is an unknown function of the component Changes/Viewfile/Oops. The manipulation results in information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.1.11 is sufficient to fix this issue. The patch is identified as 31aeecb58b64/d8ed86b10e46. Upgrading the affected component is recommended.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2863 | feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp/production_ssm FileServiceImpl.java deleteFile path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2863</link><description>A flaw has been found in feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp and production_ssm up to 4288d53bd35757b27f2d070057aefb2c07bdd097. The impacted element is the function deleteFile of the file FileServiceImpl.java. This manipulation causes path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. This product is distributed under two entirely different names. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26045 | Moodle: moodle: improper validation in file restore functionality leading to remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26045</link><description>A flaw was identified in Moodle’s backup restore functionality where specially crafted backup files were not properly validated during processing. If a malicious backup file is restored, it could lead to unintended execution of server-side code. Since restore capabilities are typically available to privileged users, exploitation requires authenticated access. Successful exploitation could result in full compromise of the Moodle server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26046 | Moodle: moodle: improper input sanitization in tex filter administration setting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26046</link><description>A vulnerability was found in a Moodle TeX filter administrative setting where insufficient sanitization of configuration input could allow command injection. On sites where the TeX filter is enabled and ImageMagick is installed, a maliciously crafted setting value entered by an administrator could result in unintended system command execution. While exploitation requires administrative privileges, successful compromise could affect the entire Moodle server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26047 | Moodle: moodle: uncontrolled resource consumption in tex formula editor leading to denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26047</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability was identified in Moodle’s TeX formula editor. When rendering TeX content using mimetex, insufficient execution time limits could allow specially crafted formulas to consume excessive server resources. An authenticated user could abuse this behavior to degrade performance or cause service interruption.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27211 | Cloud Hypervisor: Host File Exfiltration via QCOW Backing File Abuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27211</link><description>Cloud Hypervisor is a Virtual Machine Monitor for Cloud workloads. Versions 34.0 through 50.0 arevulnerable to arbitrary host file exfiltration (constrained by process privileges) when using virtio-block devices backed by raw images. A malicious guest can overwrite its disk header with a crafted QCOW2 structure pointing to a sensitive host path. Upon the next VM boot or disk scan, the image format auto-detection parses this header and serves the host file's contents to the guest. Guest-initiated VM reboots are sufficient to trigger a disk scan and do not cause the Cloud Hypervisor process to exit. Therefore, a single VM can perform this attack without needing interaction from the management stack. Successful exploitation requires the backing image to be either writable by the guest or sourced from an untrusted origin. Deployments utilizing only trusted, read-only images are not affected. This issue has been fixed in version 50.1. To workaround, enable land lock sandboxing and restrict process privileges and access.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27212 | Swiper has a Prototype Pollution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27212</link><description>Swiper is a free and mobile touch slider with hardware accelerated transitions and native behavior. Versions 6.5.1 through 12.1.1 have a Prototype pollution vulnerability. The vulnerability resides in line 94 of shared/utils.mjs, where the indexOf() function is used to check whether user provided input contain forbidden strings. Despite a previous fix that attempted to mitigate prototype pollution by checking whether user input contained a forbidden key, it is still possible to pollute Object.prototype via a crafted input using Array.prototype. The exploit works across Windows and Linux and on Node and Bun runtimes.  Any application that processes attacker-controlled input using this package may be affected  by the following: Authentication Bypass, Denial of Service and RCE. This issue is fixed in version 12.1.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27205 | Flask session does not add `Vary: Cookie` header when accessed in some ways</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27205</link><description>Flask is a web server gateway interface (WSGI) web application framework. In versions 3.1.2 and below, when the session object is accessed, Flask should set the Vary: Cookie header., resulting in a Use of Cache Containing Sensitive Information vulnerability. The logic instructs caches not to cache the response, as it may contain information specific to a logged in user. This is handled in most cases, but some forms of access such as the Python in operator were overlooked. The severity and risk depend on the application being hosted behind a caching proxy that doesn't ignore responses with cookies, not setting a Cache-Control header to mark pages as private or non-cacheable, and accessing the session in a way that only touches keys without reading values or mutating the session. The issue has been fixed in version 3.1.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27210 | Pannellum has a XSS vulnerability in hot spot attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27210</link><description>Pannellum is a lightweight, free, and open source panorama viewer for the web. In versions 3.5.0 through 2.5.6, the hot spot attributes configuration property allowed any attribute to be set, including HTML event handler attributes, allowing for potential XSS attacks. This affects websites hosting the standalone viewer HTML file and any other use of untrusted JSON config files (bypassing the protections of the escapeHTML parameter). As certain events fire without any additional user interaction, visiting a standalone viewer URL that points to a malicious config file — without additional user interaction — is sufficient to trigger the vulnerability and execute arbitrary JavaScript code, which can, for example, replace the contents of the page with arbitrary content and make it appear to be hosted by the website hosting the standalone viewer HTML file. This issue has been fixed in version 2.5.7. To workaround, setting the Content-Security-Policy header to script-src-attr 'none' will block execution of inline event handlers, mitigating this vulnerability. Don't host pannellum.htm on a domain that shares cookies with user authentication to mitigate XSS risk.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27198 | Formwork Improperly Manages Privileges During User Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27198</link><description>Formwork is a flat file-based Content Management System (CMS). In versions 2.0.0 through 2.3.3, the application fails to properly enforce role-based authorization during account creation. Although the system validates that the specified role exists, it does not verify whether the current user has sufficient privileges to assign highly privileged roles such as admin. As a result, an authenticated user with the editor role can create a new account with administrative privileges, leading to full administrative access and complete compromise of the CMS. This issue has been fixed in version 2.3.4.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27199 | Werkzeug safe_join() allows Windows special device names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27199</link><description>Werkzeug is a comprehensive WSGI web application library. Versions 3.1.5 and below, the safe_join function allows Windows device names as filenames if preceded by other path segments. This was previously reported as GHSA-hgf8-39gv-g3f2, but the added filtering failed to account for the fact that safe_join accepts paths with multiple segments, such as example/NUL. The function send_from_directory uses safe_join to safely serve files at user-specified paths under a directory. If the application is running on Windows, and the requested path ends with a special device name, the file will be opened successfully, but reading will hang indefinitely. This issue has been fixed in version 3.1.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27196 | Statamic affected by privilege escalation via stored Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27196</link><description>Statmatic is a Laravel and Git powered content management system (CMS). Versions 5.73.8 and below in addition to 6.0.0-alpha.1 through 6.3.1 have a Stored XSS vulnerability in html fieldtypes which allows authenticated users with field management permissions to inject malicious JavaScript that executes when viewed by higher-privileged users. This issue has been fixed in 6.3.2 and 5.73.9.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27197 | Sentry: Improper Authentication on SAML SSO process allows user identity linking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27197</link><description>Sentry is a developer-first error tracking and performance monitoring tool. Versions 21.12.0 through 26.1.0 have a critical vulnerability in its SAML SSO implementation  which allows an attacker to take over any user account by using a malicious SAML Identity Provider and another organization on the same Sentry instance. Self-hosted users are only at risk if the following criteria is met: ore than one organizations are configured (SENTRY_SINGLE_ORGANIZATION = True), or malicious user has existing access and permissions to modify SSO settings for another organization in a multo-organization instance. This issue has been fixed in version 26.2.0. To workaround this issue, implement user account-based two-factor authentication to prevent an attacker from being able to complete authentication with a victim's user account. Organization administrators cannot do this on a user's behalf, this requires individual users to ensure 2FA has been enabled for their account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2860 | feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp/production_ssm EmployeeController.java improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2860</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp and production_ssm up to 4288d53bd35757b27f2d070057aefb2c07bdd097. Impacted is an unknown function of the file EmployeeController.java. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. This product is distributed under two entirely different names. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27193 | Feathers exposes internal headers via unencrypted session cookie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27193</link><description>Feathersjs is a framework for creating web APIs and real-time applications with TypeScript or JavaScript. In versions 5.0.39 and below, all HTTP request headers are stored in the session cookie, which is signed but not encrypted, exposing internal proxy/gateway headers to clients. The OAuth service stores the complete headers object in the session, then the session is persisted using cookie-session, which base64-encodes the data. While the cookie is signed to prevent tampering, the contents are readable by anyone by simply decoding the base64 value. Under specific deployment configurations (e.g., behind reverse proxies or API gateways), this can lead to exposure of sensitive internal infrastructure details such as API keys, service tokens, and internal IP addresses. This issue has been fixed in version 5.0.40.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27194 | D-Tale affected by Remote Code Execution through the /save-column-filter endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27194</link><description>D-Tale is a visualizer for pandas data structures. Versions prior to 3.20.0 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution through the /save-column-filter endpoint. Users hosting D-Tale publicly can be vulnerable to remote code execution allowing attackers to run malicious code on the server. This issue has been fixed in version 3.20.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27191 | Feathers: Open Redirect in OAuth callback enables account takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27191</link><description>Feathersjs is a framework for creating web APIs and real-time applications with TypeScript or JavaScript. Versions 5.0.39 and below the redirect query parameter is appended to the base origin without validation, allowing attackers to steal access tokens via URL authority injection. This leads to full account takeover, as the attacker obtains the victim's access token and can impersonate them. The application constructs the final redirect URL by concatenating the base origin with the user-supplied redirect parameter. This is exploitable when the origins array is configured and origin values do not end with /. An attacker can supply @attacker.com as the redirect value results in https://target.com@attacker.com#access_token=..., where the browser interprets attacker.com as the host, leading to full account takeover. This issue has been fixed in version 5.0.40.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27192 | Feathers has an origin validation bypass via prefix matching</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27192</link><description>Feathersjs is a framework for creating web APIs and real-time applications with TypeScript or JavaScript. In versions 5.0.39 and below, origin validation uses startsWith() for comparison, allowing attackers to bypass the check by registering a domain that shares a common prefix with an allowed origin.The getAllowedOrigin() function checks if the Referer header starts with any allowed origin, and this comparison is insufficient as it only validates the prefix. This is exploitable when the origins array is configured and an attacker registers a domain starting with an allowed origin string (e.g., https://target.com.attacker.com bypasses https://target.com). On its own, tokens are still redirected to a configured origin. However, in specific scenarios an attacker can initiate the OAuth flow from an unauthorized origin and exfiltrate tokens, achieving full account takeover. This issue has bee fixed in version 5.0.40.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65995 | Apache Airflow: Disclosure of secrets to UI via kwargs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65995</link><description>When a DAG failed during parsing, Airflow’s error-reporting in the UI could include the full kwargs passed to the operators. If those kwargs contained sensitive values (such as secrets), they might be exposed in the UI tracebacks to authenticated users who had permission to view that DAG. 

The issue has been fixed in Airflow 3.1.4 and 2.11.1, and users are strongly advised to upgrade to prevent potential disclosure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27170 | OpenSift: SSRF risk in URL ingestion endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27170</link><description>OpenSift is an AI study tool that sifts through large datasets using semantic search and generative AI. In versions 1.1.2-alpha and below, URL ingest allows overly permissive server-side fetch behavior and can be coerced into requesting unsafe targets. Potential access/probing of private/local network resources from the OpenSift host process when ingesting attacker-controlled URLs. This issue has been fixed in version 1.1.3-alpha. To workaround when using trusted local-only exceptions, use OPENSIFT_ALLOW_PRIVATE_URLS=true with caution.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 02:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27189 | OpenSift: Race-prone local persistence could cause state corruption/loss</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27189</link><description>OpenSift is an AI study tool that sifts through large datasets using semantic search and generative AI. Versions 1.1.2-alpha and below, use non-atomic and insufficiently synchronized local JSON persistence flows, potentially causing concurrent operations to lose updates or corrupt local state across sessions/study/quiz/flashcard/wellness/auth stores. This issue has been fixed in version 1.1.3-alpha.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 02:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>