<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 01:24:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-12198 | dnsmasq Config File util.c parse_hex heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12198</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in dnsmasq up to 2.73rc6. Affected is the function parse_hex of the file src/util.c of the component Config File Handler. The manipulation of the argument i leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 01:24:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12199 | dnsmasq Config File network.c check_servers null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12199</link><description>A vulnerability was found in dnsmasq up to 2.73rc6. Affected by this vulnerability is the function check_servers of the file src/network.c of the component Config File Handler. The manipulation results in null pointer dereference. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 01:24:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12200 | dnsmasq Config File option.c parse_dhcp_opt null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12200</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in dnsmasq up to 2.73rc6. Affected by this issue is the function parse_dhcp_opt of the file src/option.c of the component Config File Handler. This manipulation of the argument m causes null pointer dereference. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 01:24:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10497 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10497</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 17.10 before 18.3.5, 18.4 before 18.4.3, and 18.5 before 18.5.1 that could have allowed an unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial of service condition by sending specially crafted payloads.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 01:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11447 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11447</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 11.0 before 18.3.5, 18.4 before 18.4.3, and 18.5 before 18.5.1 that could have allowed an unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial of service condition by sending GraphQL requests with crafted JSON payloads.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 01:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11971 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11971</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 10.6 before 18.3.5, 18.4 before 18.4.3, and 18.5 before 18.5.1 that could have allowed an authenticated attacker to trigger unauthorized pipeline executions by manipulating commits.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 01:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11974 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11974</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 11.7 before 18.3.5, 18.4 before 18.4.3, and 18.5 before 18.5.1 that could have allowed an unauthenticated attacker to create a denial of service condition by uploading large files to specific API endpoints.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 01:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6601 | Business Logic Errors in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6601</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 18.4 before 18.4.3, and 18.5 before 18.5.1 that under certain conditions could have allowed authenticated users to gain unauthorized project access by exploiting the access request approval workflow.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 01:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11989 | Missing Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11989</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 17.6.0 before 18.3.5, 18.4 before 18.4.3, and 18.5 before 18.5.1 that could have allowed an authenticated attacker to execute unauthorized quick actions by including malicious commands in specific descriptions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 23:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12284 | Lack of Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12284</link><description>Lack of Input Validation in the web UI might lead to potential exploitation.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 16:35:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12285 | Missing Initial Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12285</link><description>Missing Initial Password Change.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 16:35:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12275 | Mail Configuration File Manipulation + Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12275</link><description>Mail Configuration File Manipulation + Command Execution.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 16:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12278 | Logout Functionality not Working</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12278</link><description>Logout Functionality not Working.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 16:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8709 | SQL Injection in langchain-ai/langchain</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8709</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the langchain-ai/langchain repository, specifically in the LangGraph's SQLite store implementation. The affected version is langgraph-checkpoint-sqlite 2.0.10. The vulnerability arises from improper handling of filter operators ($eq, $ne, $gt, $lt, $gte, $lte) where direct string concatenation is used without proper parameterization. This allows attackers to inject arbitrary SQL, leading to unauthorized access to all documents, data exfiltration of sensitive fields such as passwords and API keys, and a complete bypass of application-level security filters.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 05:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55757 | Extension - virtuemart.net - XSS in VirtueMart component 1.0.0 - 4.4.10 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55757</link><description>A unauthenticated reflected XSS vulnerability in VirtueMart 1.0.0-4.4.10 for Joomla was discovered.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:42:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12221 | CSRF Token not Properly Implemented</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12221</link><description>Busybox 1.31.1 - Multiple Known Vulnerabilities.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 16:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12218 | Weak Default Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12218</link><description>Weak Default Credentials.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 16:01:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12219 | Vulnerable Components in Azure Access OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12219</link><description>Vulnerable Components in Azure Access OS.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 16:01:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12220 | Busybox 1.31.1 - Multiple Known Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12220</link><description>Busybox 1.31.1 - Multiple Known Vulnerabilities.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 16:01:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12217 | SNMP Default Community String (public)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12217</link><description>SNMP Default Community String (public).This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 15:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12216 | Malicious / Malformed App can be Installed but not Uninstalled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12216</link><description>Malicious / Malformed App can be Installed but not Uninstalled/may lead to unavailability.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 15:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11897 | The7 — Ultimate WordPress &amp;amp; WooCommerce Theme &amp;lt;= 12.9.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;the7_fancy_title_css&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11897</link><description>The The7 — Website and eCommerce Builder for WordPress theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘ the7_fancy_title_css’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 12.9.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 12:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10488 | Directorist: AI-Powered Business Directory Plugin with Classified Ads Listings &amp;lt;= 8.4.8 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Move</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10488</link><description>The Directorist: AI-Powered Business Directory Plugin with Classified Ads Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file move due to insufficient file path validation in the add_listing_action AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 8.4.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to move arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is moved (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10580 | Widget Options – The #1 WordPress Widget &amp;amp; Block Control Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10580</link><description>The Widget Options – The #1 WordPress Widget &amp; Block Control Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10637 | Social Feed Gallery &amp;lt;= 4.9.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10637</link><description>The Social Feed Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in versions less than, or equal to, 4.9.2. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to exfiltrate Instagram profile and media data from any account the site owner connected to their site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11255 | Password Policy Manager | Password Manager &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Configuration Log Out</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11255</link><description>The Password Policy Manager | Password Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'moppm_ajax' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to log out the site's connection to miniorange.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11497 | Advanced Database Cleaner &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11497</link><description>The Advanced Database Cleaner plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the aDBc_prepare_elements_to_clean() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to alter the keep last setting via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11875 | SpendeOnline.org &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11875</link><description>The SpendeOnline.org plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'spendeonline' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11893 | Charitable – Donation Plugin for WordPress – Fundraising with Recurring Donations &amp;amp; More &amp;lt;= 1.8.8.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11893</link><description>The Charitable – Donation Plugin for WordPress – Fundraising with Recurring Donations &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the donation_ids parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.8.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. Exploitation of the vulnerability requires a paid donation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11976 | FuseWP – WordPress User Sync to Email List &amp;amp; Marketing Automation (Mailchimp, Constant Contact, ActiveCampaign etc.) &amp;lt;= 1.1.23.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Sync Rule Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11976</link><description>The FuseWP – WordPress User Sync to Email List &amp; Marketing Automation (Mailchimp, Constant Contact, ActiveCampaign etc.) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.23.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the save_changes function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add or edit sync rules via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12034 | Fast Velocity Minify &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12034</link><description>The Fast Velocity Minify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4203 | wpForo Forum &amp;lt;= 2.4.8 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via get_members Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4203</link><description>The wpForo Forum plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to error‐based or time-based SQL Injection via the get_members() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.8 due to missing integer validation on the 'offset' and 'row_count' parameters. The function blindly interpolates 'row_count' into a 'LIMIT offset,row_count' clause using esc_sql() rather than enforcing numeric values. MySQL 5.x’s grammar allows a 'PROCEDURE ANALYSE' clause immediately after a LIMIT clause. Unauthenticated attackers controlling 'row_count' can append a stored‐procedure call, enabling error‐based or time‐based blind SQL injection that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8416 | Product Filter by WBW &amp;lt;= 2.9.7 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8416</link><description>The Product Filter by WBW plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'filtersDataBackend' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.7. This is due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8483 | Discussion Board – WordPress Forum Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8483</link><description>The The Discussion Board – WordPress Forum Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.5. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9322 | Stripe Payment Forms &amp;lt;= 8.3.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9322</link><description>The Stripe Payment Forms by WP Full Pay – Accept Credit Card Payments, Donations &amp; Subscriptions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'wpfs-form-name' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10694 | User Feedback – Create Interactive Feedback Form, User Surveys, and Polls in Seconds &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 - Missing Authorization to Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10694</link><description>The User Feedback – Create Interactive Feedback Form, User Surveys, and Polls in Seconds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the `maybe_load_onboarding_wizard` function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to access the onboarding wizard page and view configuration information including the administrator email address.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10737 | Open Source Genesis Framework &amp;lt;= 3.6.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Shortcodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10737</link><description>The Open Source Genesis Framework theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the theme's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11238 | Watu Quiz &amp;lt;= 3.4.4 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HTTP Referer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11238</link><description>The Watu Quiz plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the HTTP Referer header in versions less than, or equal to, 3.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping when the "Save source URL" option is enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever an user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11244 | Password Protected &amp;lt;= 2.7.11 - Unauthenticated Authorization Bypass via IP Address Spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11244</link><description>The Password Protected plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass via IP address spoofing in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.11. This is due to the plugin trusting client-controlled HTTP headers (such as X-Forwarded-For, HTTP_CLIENT_IP, and similar headers) to determine user IP addresses in the `pp_get_ip_address()` function when the "Use transients" feature is enabled. This makes it possible for attackers to bypass authorization by spoofing these headers with the IP address of a legitimately authenticated user, granted the "Use transients" option is enabled (non-default configuration) and the site is not behind a CDN or reverse proxy that overwrites these headers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11269 | Product Filter by WBW &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11269</link><description>The Product Filter by WBW plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'approveNotice' action in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11564 | Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution &amp;lt;= 3.8.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Payment Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11564</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check while verifying webhook signatures on the "verifyAndCreateOrderData" function  
in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass payment verification and mark orders as paid by submitting forged webhook requests with `payment_type` set to 'recurring'.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11879 | GenerateBlocks &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Improper Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Options Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11879</link><description>The GenerateBlocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'get_option_rest' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to read arbitrary WordPress options, including sensitive information such as SMTP credentials, API keys, and other data stored by other plugins.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11888 | ShopEngine Elementor WooCommerce Builder Addon – All in One WooCommerce Solution &amp;lt;= 4.8.4 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Editor+) License Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11888</link><description>The ShopEngine Elementor WooCommerce Builder Addon – All in One WooCommerce Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to an insufficient capability check on the post_deactive() function and post_activate() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to activate and deactivate licenses.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12005 | WP VR – 360 Panorama and Free Virtual Tour Builder For WordPress &amp;lt;= 8.5.41 - Improper Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12005</link><description>The WP VR – 360 Panorama and Free Virtual Tour Builder For WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data in all versions up to, and including, 8.5.41. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to modify sensitive plugin options.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12095 | Simple Registration for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.5.8 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Privilege Escalation via Role Request Approval</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12095</link><description>The Simple Registration for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.8. This is due to missing nonce validation on the role requests admin page handler in the includes/display-role-admin.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to approve pending role requests and escalate user privileges via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6639 | Tutor LMS Pro – eLearning and online course solution &amp;lt;= 3.8.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference to View/Edit Other Assignments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6639</link><description>The Tutor LMS Pro – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3 due to missing validation on a user controlled key when viewing and editing assignments through the tutor_assignment_submit() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view and edit assignment submissions of other students.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6680 | Tutor LMS &amp;lt;= 3.8.3 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6680</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with tutor-level access and above, to view assignments for courses they don't teach which may contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8413 | Listeo &amp;lt;= 2.0.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via soundcloud Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8413</link><description>The Listeo theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `soundcloud` shortcode in version less than, or equal to, 2.0.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8588 | Gutenberg Blocks – PublishPress Blocks Controls, Visibility, Reusable Blocks &amp;lt;= 3.3.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8588</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks – PublishPress Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Marker Title' and 'Marker Description' parameters for the Maps block in versions up to, and including, 3.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level access and above to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8666 | Testimonial Carousel For Elementor &amp;lt;= 11.6.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8666</link><description>The Testimonial Carousel For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple parameters in versions less than, or equal to, 11.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10579 | BackWPup &amp;lt;= 5.5.0 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10579</link><description>The BackWPup – WordPress Backup &amp; Restore Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'backwpup_working' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve access to a back-up's filename while a backup is running. This information has little value on it's own, but could be used to aid in a brute force attack to retrieve back-up contents in limited environments (i.e. NGINX).</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 04:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11823 | ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp;amp; Gutenberg +21 Modules – All in One Solution &amp;lt;= 3.2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11823</link><description>The ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg +21 Modules – All in One Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'button_exist_text' parameter in the 'wishsuite_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 04:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11760 | eRoom – Webinar &amp;amp; Meeting Plugin for Zoom, Google Meet, Microsoft Teams &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11760</link><description>The eRoom – Webinar &amp; Meeting Plugin for Zoom, Google Meet, Microsoft Teams plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to exposure of sensitive information in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.6. This is due to the plugin exposing Zoom SDK secret keys in client-side JavaScript within the meeting view template. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract the sdk_secret value, which should remain server-side, compromising the security of the Zoom integration and allowing attackers to generate valid JWT signatures for unauthorized meeting access.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 02:27:54 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>