<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:26:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-1066 | kalcaddle kodbox Compression zip command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1066</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in kalcaddle kodbox up to 1.61.10. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /?explorer/index/zip of the component Compression Handler. The manipulation results in command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1064 | bastillion-io Bastillion System Management SystemKtrl.java command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1064</link><description>A vulnerability was found in bastillion-io Bastillion up to 4.0.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file src/main/java/io/bastillion/manage/control/SystemKtrl.java of the component System Management Module. Performing a manipulation results in command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1063 | bastillion-io Bastillion Public Key Management System AuthKeysKtrl.java command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1063</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in bastillion-io Bastillion up to 4.0.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file src/main/java/io/bastillion/manage/control/AuthKeysKtrl.java of the component Public Key Management System. Such manipulation leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:25:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1062 | xiweicheng TMS HtmlUtil.java summary server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1062</link><description>A flaw has been found in xiweicheng TMS up to 2.28.0. This affects the function Summary of the file src/main/java/com/lhjz/portal/util/HtmlUtil.java. This manipulation of the argument url causes server-side request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1061 | xiweicheng TMS FileController.java upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1061</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in xiweicheng TMS up to 2.28.0. Affected by this issue is the function Upload of the file src/main/java/com/lhjz/portal/controller/FileController.java. The manipulation of the argument filename results in unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1059 | FeMiner wms chkuser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1059</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in FeMiner wms up to 9cad1f1b179a98b9547fd003c23b07c7594775fa. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /src/chkuser.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery. Therefore, version details for affected or updated releases cannot be specified. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1050 | risesoft-y9 Digital-Infrastructure REST Authenticate Endpoint Y9PlatformUtil.java sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1050</link><description>A flaw has been found in risesoft-y9 Digital-Infrastructure up to 9.6.7. This affects an unknown function of the file source-code/src/main/java/net/risesoft/util/Y9PlatformUtil.java of the component REST Authenticate Endpoint. Executing a manipulation can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1049 | LigeroSmart index.pl cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1049</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in LigeroSmart up to 6.1.26. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /otrs/index.pl. Such manipulation of the argument TicketID leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1048 | LigeroSmart index.pl cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1048</link><description>A weakness has been identified in LigeroSmart up to 6.1.26. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /otrs/index.pl?Action=AgentTicketZoom. This manipulation of the argument TicketID causes cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:18:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15532 | Open5GS Timer resource consumption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15532</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Timer Handler. The manipulation results in resource consumption. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The patch is identified as c7c131f8d2cb1195ada5e0e691b6868ebcd8a845. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15531 | Open5GS context.c sgwc_bearer_add assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15531</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. This vulnerability affects the function sgwc_bearer_add of the file src/sgwc/context.c. The manipulation leads to reachable assertion. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The issue report is flagged as already-fixed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15530 | Open5GS s11-handler.c assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15530</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. This affects the function sgwc_s11_handle_create_indirect_data_forwarding_tunnel_request of the file /src/sgwc/s11-handler.c. Executing a manipulation can lead to reachable assertion. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The issue report is flagged as already-fixed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10484 | Registration &amp;amp; Login with Mobile Phone Number for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10484</link><description>The Registration &amp; Login with Mobile Phone Number for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a users identity prior to authenticating them via the fma_lwp_set_session_php_fun() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to authenticate as any user on the site, including administrators, without a valid password.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14078 | PAYGENT for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Payment Callback Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14078</link><description>The PAYGENT for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6. This is due to missing authorization checks on the paygent_check_webhook function combined with the paygent_permission_callback function unconditionally returning true on line 199. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to manipulate payment callbacks and modify order statuses by sending forged payment notifications via the `/wp-json/paygent/v1/check/` endpoint.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8615 | CubeWP &amp;lt;= 1.1.26 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via cubewp_shortcode_taxonomy Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8615</link><description>The CubeWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's cubewp_shortcode_taxonomy shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0725 | Integrate Dynamics 365 CRM &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Field Mapping Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0725</link><description>The Integrate Dynamics 365 CRM plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12129 | CubeWP – All-in-One Dynamic Content Framework &amp;lt;= 1.1.27 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12129</link><description>The CubeWP – All-in-One Dynamic Content Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.27 via the /cubewp-posts/v1/query-new and /cubewp-posts/v1/query REST API endpoints due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 07:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14478 | Demo Importer Plus &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Authenticated (Author+) Blind XML External Entity Injection via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14478</link><description>The Demo Importer Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to XML External Entity Injection (XXE) in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.9 via the SVG file upload functionality. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to achieve code execution in vulnerable configurations. This only impacts sites on versions of PHP older than 8.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 07:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12984 | Advanced Ads – Ad Manager &amp;amp; AdSense &amp;lt;= 2.0.15 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12984</link><description>The Advanced Ads – Ad Manager &amp; AdSense plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'order' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.15 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 06:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0691 | CM E-Mail Blacklist &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;black_email&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0691</link><description>The CM E-Mail Blacklist – Simple email filtering for safer registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'black_email' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 06:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0808 | Spin Wheel &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Unauthenticated Client-Side Prize Manipulation via &amp;#x27;prize_index&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0808</link><description>The Spin Wheel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to client-side prize manipulation in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.0. This is due to the plugin trusting client-supplied prize selection data without server-side validation or randomization. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to manipulate which prize they win by modifying the 'prize_index' parameter sent to the server, allowing them to always select the most valuable prizes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 06:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0833 | Team Section Block &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Social Network Link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0833</link><description>The Team Section Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's block in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied social network link URLs. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 06:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12168 | Phrase TMS Integration for WordPress &amp;lt;= 4.7.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Log Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12168</link><description>The Phrase TMS Integration for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_delete_log' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 4.7.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete log files.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12825 | User Registration Using Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12825</link><description>The User Registration Using Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'get_cf7_form_data' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve form settings which includes Facebook app secrets.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14029 | Community Events &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Event Approval via &amp;#x27;eventlist&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14029</link><description>The Community Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ajax_admin_event_approval() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to approve arbitrary events via the 'eventlist' parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13725 | Gutenberg Thim Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Read via &amp;#x27;iconSVG&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13725</link><description>The Gutenberg Thim Blocks – Page Builder, Gutenberg Blocks for the Block Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file reads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to insufficient path validation in the server-side rendering of the thim-blocks/icon block. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server via the 'iconSVG' parameter, which can contain sensitive information such as wp-config.php.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14463 | Payment Button for PayPal &amp;lt;= 1.2.3.41 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Order Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14463</link><description>The Payment Button for PayPal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized order creation in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3.41. This is due to the plugin exposing a public AJAX endpoint (`wppaypalcheckout_ajax_process_order`) that processes checkout results without any authentication or server-side verification of the PayPal transaction. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create arbitrary orders on the site with any chosen transaction ID, payment status, product name, amount, or customer information via direct POST requests to the AJAX endpoint, granted they can bypass basic parameter validation. If email sending is enabled, the plugin will also trigger purchase receipt emails to any email address supplied in the request, leading to order database corruption and unauthorized outgoing emails without any real PayPal transaction taking place.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0682 | Church Admin &amp;lt;= 5.0.28 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Blind Server-Side Request Forgery via &amp;#x27;audio_url&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0682</link><description>The Church Admin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.28 due to insufficient validation of user-supplied URLs in the 'audio_url' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0820 | RepairBuddy &amp;lt;= 4.1116 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Signature Upload to Orders</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0820</link><description>The RepairBuddy – Repair Shop CRM &amp; Booking Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference due to missing capability checks on the wc_upload_and_save_signature_handler function in all versions up to, and including, 4.1116. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary signatures to any order in the system, potentially modifying order metadata and triggering unauthorized status changes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:04:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12002 | Feeds for YouTube Pro &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read via Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12002</link><description>The Feeds for YouTube Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file read in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.0 via the 'sby_check_wp_submit' AJAX action. This is due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied data and the use of that data in a file operation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information, granted the 'Save Featured Images' setting is enabled and 'Disable WP Posts' is disabled. Note: This vulnerability only affects the Pro version of Feeds for YouTube.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12718 | Quick Contact Form &amp;lt;= 8.2.6 - Unauthenticated Open Mail Relay</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12718</link><description>The Quick Contact Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Open Mail Relay in all versions up to, and including, 8.2.6. This is due to the 'qcf_validate_form' AJAX endpoint allowing a user controlled parameter to set the 'from' email address. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send emails to arbitrary recipients utilizing the server. The information is limited to the contact form submission details.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14075 | WP Hotel Booking &amp;lt;= 2.2.7 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via &amp;#x27;email&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14075</link><description>The WP Hotel Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.7. This is due to the plugin exposing the 'hotel_booking_fetch_customer_info' AJAX action to unauthenticated users without proper capability checks, relying only on a nonce for protection. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve sensitive customer information including full names, addresses, phone numbers, and email addresses by providing a valid email address and a publicly accessible nonce.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14450 | Wallet System for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.7.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Wallet Balance Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14450</link><description>The Wallet System for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'change_wallet_fund_request_status_callback' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to manipulate wallet withdrawal requests and arbitrarily increase their wallet balance or decrease other users' balances.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14632 | Filr – Secure document library &amp;lt;= 1.2.11 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HTML Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14632</link><description>The Filr – Secure document library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via unrestricted file upload in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.11 due to insufficient file type restrictions in the FILR_Uploader class. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload malicious HTML files containing JavaScript that will execute whenever a user accesses the uploaded file, granted they have permission to create or edit posts with the 'filr' post type.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15403 | RegistrationMagic &amp;lt;= 6.0.7.1 - Privilege Escalation via admin_order</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15403</link><description>The RegistrationMagic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.7.1. This is due to the 'add_menu' function is accessible via the 'rm_user_exists' AJAX action and allows arbitrary updates to the 'admin_order' setting. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to injecting an empty slug into the order parameter, and manipulate the plugin's menu generation logic, and when the admin menu is subsequently built, the plugin adds 'manage_options' capability for the target role. Note: The vulnerability can only be exploited unauthenticated, but further privilege escalation requires at least a subscriber user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0518 | XSS in Secure Access Consoles prior to 14.20</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0518</link><description>CVE-2026-0518 is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in versions of 
Secure Access prior to 14.20. An attacker with administrative privileges
 can interfere with another administrator’s use of the console.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 01:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0519 | Information Disclosure in Secure Access Between 12.70 and 14.20</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0519</link><description>In Secure Access 12.70 and prior to 14.20, the logging 
subsystem may write an unredacted authentication token to logs under 
certain configurations. Any party with access to those logs could read 
the token and reuse it to access an integrated system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 01:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0517 | Denial of Service in Secure Access Servers Prior to 14.20.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0517</link><description>CVE-2026-0517 is a denial-of-service vulnerability in versions of Secure
 Access Server prior to 14.20. An attacker can send a specially crafted packet 
to a server and cause the server to crash</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 01:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22816 | Gradle fails to disable repositories which can expose builds to malicious artifacts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22816</link><description>Gradle is a build automation tool, and its native-platform tool provides Java bindings for native APIs. When resolving dependencies in versions before 9.3.0, some exceptions were not treated as fatal errors and would not cause a repository to be disabled. If a build encountered one of these exceptions, Gradle would continue to the next repository in the list and potentially resolve dependencies from a different repository. If a Gradle build used an unresolvable host name, Gradle would continue to work as long as all dependencies could be resolved from another repository. An unresolvable host name could be caused by allowing a repository's domain name registration to lapse or typo-ing the real domain name. This behavior could allow an attacker to register a service under the host name used by the build and serve malicious artifacts. The attack requires the repository to be listed before others in the build configuration. Gradle has introduced a change in behavior in Gradle 9.3.0 to stop searching other repositories when encountering these errors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22865 | Gradle&amp;#x27;s failure to disable repositories failing to answer can expose builds to malicious artifacts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22865</link><description>Gradle is a build automation tool, and its native-platform tool provides Java bindings for native APIs. When resolving dependencies in versions before 9.3.0, some exceptions were not treated as fatal errors and would not cause a repository to be disabled. If a build encountered one of these exceptions, Gradle would continue to the next repository in the list and potentially resolve dependencies from a different repository. An exception like NoHttpResponseException can indicate transient errors. If the errors persist after a maximum number of retries, Gradle would continue to the next repository. This behavior could allow an attacker to disrupt the service of a repository and leverage another repository to serve malicious artifacts. This attack requires the attacker to have control over a repository after the disrupted repository. Gradle has introduced a change in behavior in Gradle 9.3.0 to stop searching other repositories when encountering these errors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15528 | Open5GS GTPv2 Bearer Response denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15528</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component GTPv2 Bearer Response Handler. Such manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is 98f76e98df35cd6a35e868aa62715db7f8141ac1. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15529 | Open5GS s5c-handler.c sgwc_s5c_handle_create_session_response denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15529</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. Affected by this issue is the function sgwc_s5c_handle_create_session_response of the file src/sgwc/s5c-handler.c. Performing a manipulation results in denial of service. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The patch is named b19cf6a2dbf5d30811be4488bf059c865bd7d1d2. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23745 | node-tar Vulnerable to Arbitrary File Overwrite and Symlink Poisoning via Insufficient Path Sanitization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23745</link><description>node-tar is a Tar for Node.js. The node-tar library (&lt;= 7.5.2) fails to sanitize the linkpath of Link (hardlink) and SymbolicLink entries when preservePaths is false (the default secure behavior). This allows malicious archives to bypass the extraction root restriction, leading to Arbitrary File Overwrite via hardlinks and Symlink Poisoning via absolute symlink targets. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20960 | Microsoft Power Apps Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20960</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21223 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21223</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56451 | Cross site scripting vulnerability in seeyon Zhiyuan A8+ Collaborative Management Software 7.0 via the topValue parameter to the seeyon/main...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56451</link><description>Cross site scripting vulnerability in seeyon Zhiyuan A8+ Collaborative Management Software 7.0 via the topValue parameter to the seeyon/main.do endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23643 | CakePHP PaginatorHelper::limitControl() vulnerable to reflected cross-site-scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23643</link><description>CakePHP is a rapid development framework for PHP. The PaginatorHelper::limitControl() method has a cross-site-scripting vulnerability via query string parameter manipulation. This issue has been fixed in 5.2.12 and 5.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23800 | WordPress Modular DS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23800</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Modular DS modular-connector allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Modular DS: from 2.5.2 before 2.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25297 | Poll, Survey &amp;amp; Quiz Maker Plugin by Opinion Stage &amp;lt; 19.6.25 Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25297</link><description>Poll, Survey &amp; Quiz Maker Plugin by Opinion Stage Wordpress plugin versions prior to 19.6.25 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via multiple parameters due to insufficient input validation and output escaping. An unauthenticated attacker can inject arbitrary script into content that executes when a victim views an affected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10064 | Omni Secure Files &amp;lt; 0.1.14 Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10064</link><description>Omni Secure Files plugin versions prior to 0.1.14 contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the bundled plupload example endpoint. The /wp-content/plugins/omni-secure-files/plupload/examples/upload.php handler allows unauthenticated uploads without enforcing safe file type restrictions, enabling an attacker to place attacker-controlled files under the plugin's uploads directory. This can lead to remote code execution if a server-executable file type is uploaded and subsequently accessed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:15:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23735 | Concurrent Execution using Shared Resource with Improper Synchronization (&amp;#x27;Race Condition&amp;#x27;) in graphql-modules</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23735</link><description>GraphQL Modules is a toolset of libraries and guidelines dedicated to create reusable, maintainable, testable and extendable modules out of your GraphQL server. From 2.2.1 to before 2.4.1 and 3.1.1, when 2 or more parallel requests are made which trigger the same service, the context of the requests is mixed up in the service when the context is injected via @ExecutionContext(). ExecutionContext is often used to pass authentication tokens from incoming requests to services loading data from backend APIs. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.4.1 and 3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:15:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23742 | Skipper arbitrary code execution through lua filters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23742</link><description>Skipper is an HTTP router and reverse proxy for service composition. The default skipper configuration before 0.23.0 was -lua-sources=inline,file. The problem starts if untrusted users can create lua filters, because of -lua-sources=inline , for example through a Kubernetes Ingress resource. The configuration inline allows these user to create a script that is able to read the filesystem accessible to the skipper process and if the user has access to read the logs, they an read skipper secrets. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.23.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23744 | REC in MCPJam inspector due to HTTP Endpoint exposes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23744</link><description>MCPJam inspector is the local-first development platform for MCP servers. Versions 1.4.2 and earlier are vulnerable to remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability, which allows an attacker to send a crafted HTTP request that triggers the installation of an MCP server, leading to RCE. Since MCPJam inspector by default listens on 0.0.0.0 instead of 127.0.0.1, an attacker can trigger the RCE remotely via a simple HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23731 | WeGIA Clickjacking Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23731</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, The web application is vulnerable to clickjacking attacks. The WeGIA application does not send any defensive HTTP headers related to framing protection. In particular, X-Frame-Options is missing andContent-Security-Policy with frame-ancestors directive is not configured. Because of this, an attacker can load any WeGIA page inside a malicious HTML document, overlay deceptive elements, hide real buttons, or force accidental interaction with sensitive workflows. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23728 | WeGIA has an Open Redirect Vulnerability in control.php Endpoint via nextPage Parameter (metodo=listarTodos, nomeClasse=DestinoControle)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23728</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, an Open Redirect vulnerability was identified in the /WeGIA/controle/control.php endpoint of the WeGIA application, specifically through the nextPage parameter when combined with metodo=listarTodos and nomeClasse=DestinoControle. The application fails to validate or restrict the nextPage parameter, allowing attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external websites. This can be abused for phishing attacks, credential theft, malware distribution, and social engineering using the trusted WeGIA domain. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23729 | WeGIA has an Open Redirect Vulnerability in control.php Endpoint via nextPage Parameter (metodo=listarDescricao, nomeClasse=ProdutoControle)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23729</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, an Open Redirect vulnerability was identified in the /WeGIA/controle/control.php endpoint of the WeGIA application, specifically through the nextPage parameter when combined with metodo=listarDescricao and nomeClasse=ProdutoControle. The application fails to validate or restrict the nextPage parameter, allowing attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external websites. This can be abused for phishing attacks, credential theft, malware distribution, and social engineering using the trusted WeGIA domain. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23730 | WeGIA has an Open Redirect Vulnerability in control.php Endpoint via nextPage Parameter (metodo=listarTodos, nomeClasse=ProdutoControle)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23730</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, an Open Redirect vulnerability was identified in the /WeGIA/controle/control.php endpoint of the WeGIA application, specifically through the nextPage parameter when combined with metodo=listarTodos and nomeClasse=ProdutoControle. The application fails to validate or restrict the nextPage parameter, allowing attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external websites. This can be abused for phishing attacks, credential theft, malware distribution, and social engineering using the trusted WeGIA domain. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23724 | WeGIA Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) – atendido_idatendido Parameter on Occurrence Registration Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23724</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the html/atendido/cadastro_ocorrencia.php endpoint of the WeGIA application. The application does not sanitize user-controlled data before rendering it inside the “Atendido” selection dropdown. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23725 | WeGIA Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) – nome Parameter on Adopters Information Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23725</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the html/pet/adotantes/cadastro_adotante.php and html/pet/adotantes/informacao_adotantes.php endpoint of the WeGIA application. The application does not sanitize user-controlled input before rendering it inside the Adopters Information table, allowing persistent JavaScript injection. Any user who visits the page will have the payload executed automatically. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23726 | WeGIA has an Open Redirect Vulnerability in control.php Endpoint via nextPage Parameter (metodo=listarTodos, nomeClasse=TipoEntradaControle)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23726</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, An Open Redirect vulnerability was identified in the /WeGIA/controle/control.php endpoint of the WeGIA application, specifically through the nextPage parameter when combined with metodo=listarTodos and nomeClasse=TipoEntradaControle. The application fails to validate or restrict the nextPage parameter, allowing attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external websites. This can be abused for phishing attacks, credential theft, malware distribution, and social engineering using the trusted WeGIA domain. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23727 | WeGIA has an Open Redirect Vulnerability in control.php Endpoint via nextPage Parameter (metodo=listarTodos, nomeClasse=TipoSaidaControle)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23727</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, an Open Redirect vulnerability was identified in the /WeGIA/controle/control.php endpoint of the WeGIA application, specifically through the nextPage parameter when combined with metodo=listarTodos and nomeClasse=TipoSaidaControle. The application fails to validate or restrict the nextPage parameter, allowing attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external websites. This can be abused for phishing attacks, credential theft, malware distribution, and social engineering using the trusted WeGIA domain. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69581 | An issue was discovered in Chamillo LMS 1.11.2. The Social Network /personal_data endpoint exposes full sensitive user information even afte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69581</link><description>An issue was discovered in Chamillo LMS 1.11.2. The Social Network /personal_data endpoint exposes full sensitive user information even after logout because proper cache-control is missing. Using the browser back button restores all personal data, allowing unauthorized users on the same device to view confidential information. This leads to profiling, impersonation, targeted attacks, and significant privacy risks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23722 | WeGIA has a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability allowing arbitrary code execution and UI redressing.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23722</link><description>WeGIA is a Web Manager for Charitable Institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the WeGIA system, specifically within the html/memorando/insere_despacho.php file. The application fails to properly sanitize or encode user-supplied input via the id_memorando GET parameter before reflecting it into the HTML source (likely inside a</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23723 | WeGIA has a Critical SQL Injection in Atendido_ocorrenciaControle via id_memorando parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23723</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, an authenticated SQL Injection vulnerability was identified in the Atendido_ocorrenciaControle endpoint via the id_memorando parameter. This flaw allows for full database exfiltration, exposure of sensitive PII, and potential arbitrary file reads in misconfigured environments. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:37:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23634 | Pepr Overly Permissive RBAC ClusterRole in Admin Mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23634</link><description>Pepr is a type safe K8s middleware. Prior to 1.0.5 , Pepr defaults to a cluster-admin RBAC configuration and does not explicitly force or enforce least-privilege guidance for module authors. The default behavior exists to make the “getting started” experience smooth: new users can experiment with Pepr and create resources dynamically without needing to pre-configure RBAC. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23645 | SiYuan Vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via Unrestricted SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23645</link><description>SiYuan is self-hosted, open source personal knowledge management software. Prior to 3.5.4-dev2, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in SiYuan Note. The application does not sanitize uploaded SVG files. If a user uploads and views a malicious SVG file (e.g., imported from an untrusted source), arbitrary JavaScript code is executed in the context of their authenticated session. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.5.4-dev2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47816 | Thecus N4800Eco Nas Server Control Panel - Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47816</link><description>Thecus N4800Eco NAS Server Control Panel contains a command injection vulnerability that allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary system commands through user management endpoints. Attackers can inject commands via username and batch user creation parameters to execute shell commands with administrative privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47818 | DupTerminator 1.4.5639.37199 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47818</link><description>DupTerminator 1.4.5639.37199 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by inputting a long character string in the Excluded text box. Attackers can generate a payload of 8000 repeated characters to trigger the application to stop working on Windows 10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47820 | Ubee EVW327 - &amp;#x27;Enable Remote Access&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47820</link><description>Ubee EVW327 contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability that allows attackers to enable remote access without user interaction. Attackers can craft a malicious webpage that automatically submits a form to change router remote access settings to port 8080 without the user's consent.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47821 | RarmaRadio 2.72.8 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47821</link><description>RarmaRadio 2.72.8 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by overflowing network configuration fields with large character buffers. Attackers can generate a 100,000 character buffer and paste it into multiple network settings fields to trigger application instability and potential crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47822 | DiskBoss Service 12.2.18 - &amp;#x27;diskbsa.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47822</link><description>DiskBoss Service 12.2.18 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its binary path configuration that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path by placing malicious executables in potential path locations to gain system-level access during service startup.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47823 | ePowerSvc 6.0.3008.0 - &amp;#x27;ePowerSvc.exe&amp;#x27;  Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47823</link><description>Acer ePowerSvc 6.0.3008.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in the service configuration to inject malicious code that would execute with LocalSystem permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47824 | iDailyDiary 4.30 - Denial of Service (PoC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47824</link><description>iDailyDiary 4.30 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by overflowing the preferences tab name field. Attackers can paste a 2,000,000 character buffer into the default diary tab name to trigger an application crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47825 | Acer Updater Service 1.2.3500.0 - &amp;#x27;UpdaterService.exe&amp;#x27;  Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47825</link><description>Acer Updater Service 1.2.3500.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to execute code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in C:\Program Files\Acer\Acer Updater\ to inject malicious executables that will run with LocalSystem permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47826 | Acer Backup Manager Module 3.0.0.99 - &amp;#x27;IScheduleSvc.exe&amp;#x27;  Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47826</link><description>Acer Backup Manager 3.0.0.99 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the NTI IScheduleSvc service that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in C:\Program Files (x86)\NTI\Acer Backup Manager\ to inject malicious executables that would run with elevated LocalSystem privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47827 | WebSSH for iOS 14.16.10 - &amp;#x27;mashREPL&amp;#x27; Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47827</link><description>WebSSH for iOS 14.16.10 contains a denial of service vulnerability in the mashREPL tool that allows attackers to crash the application by pasting malformed input. Attackers can trigger the vulnerability by copying a 300-character buffer of repeated 'A' characters into the mashREPL input field, causing the application to crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47828 | BOOTP Turbo 2.0.0.1253 - &amp;#x27;bootpt.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47828</link><description>BOOTP Turbo 2.0.0.1253 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configuration. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path to execute arbitrary code with elevated LocalSystem privileges during system startup or reboot.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47829 | DHCP Broadband 4.1.0.1503 - &amp;#x27;dhcpt.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47829</link><description>DHCP Broadband 4.1.0.1503 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its service configuration that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in 'C:\Program Files\DHCP Broadband 4\dhcpt.exe' to inject malicious code that will execute during service startup with LocalSystem permissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47831 | Sandboxie 5.49.7 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47831</link><description>Sandboxie 5.49.7 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by overflowing the container folder input field. Attackers can paste a large buffer of repeated characters into the Sandbox container folder setting to trigger an application crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47832 | Sandboxie Plus 0.7.4 - &amp;#x27;SbieSvc&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47832</link><description>Sandboxie Plus 0.7.4 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the SbieSvc service that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path during system startup or reboot to inject and run malicious executables with LocalSystem permissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47833 | WifiHotSpot 1.0.0.0 - &amp;#x27;WifiHotSpotService.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47833</link><description>WifiHotSpot 1.0.0.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its WifiHotSpotService.exe that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path during system startup or reboot to inject and run malicious executables with LocalSystem permissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47834 | Schlix CMS 2.2.6-6 - &amp;#x27;title&amp;#x27; Persistent Cross-Site Scripting (Authenticated)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47834</link><description>Schlix CMS 2.2.6-6 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows authenticated users to inject malicious scripts into category titles. Attackers can create a new contact category with a script payload that will execute when the page is viewed by other users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47835 | Freeter 1.2.1 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47835</link><description>Freeter 1.2.1 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to store malicious payloads in custom widget titles and files. Attackers can craft malicious files with embedded scripts that execute when victims interact with the application, potentially enabling remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47836 | Markdown Explorer 0.1.1 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47836</link><description>Markdown Explorer 0.1.1 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious code through file uploads and editor inputs. Attackers can upload markdown files with embedded JavaScript payloads to execute remote commands and potentially gain system access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47837 | Markdownify 1.2.0 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47837</link><description>Markdownify 1.2.0 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to store malicious payloads within markdown files. Attackers can upload crafted markdown files with embedded scripts that execute when the file is opened, potentially enabling remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47838 | Markright 1.0 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47838</link><description>Markright 1.0 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to embed malicious payloads in markdown files. Attackers can upload specially crafted markdown files that execute arbitrary JavaScript when opened, potentially enabling remote code execution on the victim's system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47839 | Marky 0.0.1 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47839</link><description>Marky 0.0.1 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into markdown files. Attackers can upload crafted markdown files with embedded JavaScript payloads that execute when the file is opened, potentially enabling remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47840 | Moeditor 0.2.0 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47840</link><description>Moeditor 0.2.0 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to store malicious payloads within markdown files. Attackers can upload specially crafted markdown files with embedded JavaScript that execute when opened, potentially enabling remote code execution on the victim's system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47841 | SnipCommand 0.1.0 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47841</link><description>SnipCommand 0.1.0 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious payloads into command snippets. Attackers can execute arbitrary code by embedding malicious JavaScript that triggers remote command execution through file or title inputs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47842 | StudyMD 0.3.2 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47842</link><description>StudyMD 0.3.2 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into markdown files. Attackers can upload crafted markdown files with embedded JavaScript payloads that execute when the file is opened, potentially enabling remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47844 | Xmind 2020 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47844</link><description>Xmind 2020 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious payloads into mind mapping files or custom headers. Attackers can craft malicious files with embedded JavaScript that execute system commands when opened, enabling remote code execution through mouse interactions or file opening.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47845 | Spy Emergency 25.0.650 -  Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47845</link><description>Spy Emergency 25.0.650 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configurations that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted file paths in SpyEmergencyHealth.exe and SpyEmergencySrv.exe to inject malicious code during system startup or service restart.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47847 | Disk Sorter Server 13.6.12 - &amp;#x27;Disk Sorter Server&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47847</link><description>Disk Sorter Server 13.6.12 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its binary path configuration that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in 'C:\Program Files\Disk Sorter Server\bin\disksrs.exe' to inject malicious executables and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23490 | pyasn1 has a DoS vulnerability in decoder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23490</link><description>pyasn1 is a generic ASN.1 library for Python. Prior to 0.6.2, a Denial-of-Service issue has been found that leads to memory exhaustion from malformed RELATIVE-OID with excessive continuation octets. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23535 | wlc Path traversal: Unsanitized API slugs in download command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23535</link><description>wlc is a Weblate command-line client using Weblate's REST API. Prior to 1.17.2, the multi-translation download could write to an arbitrary location when instructed by a crafted server. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.17.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68924 | In Umbraco UmbracoForms through 8.13.16, an authenticated attacker can supply a malicious WSDL (aka Webservice) URL as a data source for rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68924</link><description>In Umbraco UmbracoForms through 8.13.16, an authenticated attacker can supply a malicious WSDL (aka Webservice) URL as a data source for remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48647 | In cpm_fwtp_msg_handler of cpm/google/lib/tracepoint/cpm_fwtp_ipc.c, there is a possible memory overwrite due to improper input validation. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48647</link><description>In cpm_fwtp_msg_handler of cpm/google/lib/tracepoint/cpm_fwtp_ipc.c, there is a possible memory overwrite due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62291 | In the eap-mschapv2 plugin (client-side) in strongSwan before 6.0.3, a malicious EAP-MSCHAPv2 server can send a crafted message of size 6 th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62291</link><description>In the eap-mschapv2 plugin (client-side) in strongSwan before 6.0.3, a malicious EAP-MSCHAPv2 server can send a crafted message of size 6 through 8, and cause an integer underflow that potentially results in a heap-based buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15032 | CVE-2025-15032: Increased Spoofing risk; custom new window missing about:blank</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15032</link><description>Missing about:blank indicator in custom-sized new windows in Dia before 1.9.0 on macOS could allow an attacker to spoof a trusted domain in the window title and mislead users about the current site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61873 | Best Practical Request Tracker (RT) before 4.4.9, 5.0.9, and 6.0.2 allows CSV Injection via ticket values when TSV export is used.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61873</link><description>Best Practical Request Tracker (RT) before 4.4.9, 5.0.9, and 6.0.2 allows CSV Injection via ticket values when TSV export is used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51602 | mmstu.c in VideoLAN VLC media player before 3.0.22 allows an out-of-bounds read and denial of service via a crafted 0x01 response from an MM...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51602</link><description>mmstu.c in VideoLAN VLC media player before 3.0.22 allows an out-of-bounds read and denial of service via a crafted 0x01 response from an MMS server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43904 | In SchedMD Slurm before 24.11.5, 24.05.8, and 23.11.11, the accounting system can allow a Coordinator to promote a user to Administrator.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43904</link><description>In SchedMD Slurm before 24.11.5, 24.05.8, and 23.11.11, the accounting system can allow a Coordinator to promote a user to Administrator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31510 | In the portal in LemonLDAP::NG before 2.21.0, cross-site scripting (XSS) allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML (int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31510</link><description>In the portal in LemonLDAP::NG before 2.21.0, cross-site scripting (XSS) allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML (into the login page) via the tab parameter, for Choice authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24531 | In OpenSC pam_pkcs11 before 0.6.13, pam_sm_authenticate() wrongly returns PAM_IGNORE in many error situations (such as an error triggered by...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24531</link><description>In OpenSC pam_pkcs11 before 0.6.13, pam_sm_authenticate() wrongly returns PAM_IGNORE in many error situations (such as an error triggered by a smartcard before login), allowing authentication bypass.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24528 | In MIT Kerberos 5 (aka krb5) before 1.22 (with incremental propagation), there is an integer overflow for a large update size to resize() in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24528</link><description>In MIT Kerberos 5 (aka krb5) before 1.22 (with incremental propagation), there is an integer overflow for a large update size to resize() in kdb_log.c. An authenticated attacker can cause an out-of-bounds write and kadmind daemon crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0629 | Authentication Bypass in Password Recovery Feature via Local Web App on Multiple VIGI Cameras</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0629</link><description>Authentication bypass in the password recovery feature of the local web interface across multiple VIGI camera models allows an attacker on the LAN to reset the admin password without verification by manipulating client-side state. Attackers can gain full administrative access to the device, compromising configuration and network security.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44210 | This issue was addressed with improved permissions checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to access user-se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44210</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved permissions checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44238 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. An app may be able to corrupt coproces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44238</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. An app may be able to corrupt coprocessor memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54556 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. A user may be able to view rest...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54556</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. A user may be able to view restricted content from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24089 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. An app may be able to enume...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24089</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. An app may be able to enumerate a user's installed apps.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24090 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. An app may be able to enume...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24090</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. An app may be able to enumerate a user's installed apps.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31186 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in Xcode 16.3. An app may be able to bypass Privacy pref...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31186</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in Xcode 16.3. An app may be able to bypass Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43508 | A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43508</link><description>A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23528 | Dask distributed Vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via Jupyter Proxy and Dashboard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23528</link><description>Dask distributed is a distributed task scheduler for Dask. Prior to 2026.1.0, when Jupyter Lab, jupyter-server-proxy, and Dask distributed are all run together, it is possible to craft a URL which will result in code being executed by Jupyter due to a cross-side-scripting (XSS) bug in the Dask dashboard. It is possible for attackers to craft a phishing URL that assumes Jupyter Lab and Dask may be running on localhost and using default ports. If a user clicks on the malicious link it will open an error page in the Dask Dashboard via the Jupyter Lab proxy which will cause code to be executed by the default Jupyter Python kernel. This vulnerability is fixed in 2026.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23529 | Arbitrary File Read in Google BigQuery Sink connector</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23529</link><description>Kafka Connect BigQuery Connector is an implementation of a sink connector from Apache Kafka to Google BigQuery. Prior to 2.11.0, there is an arbitrary file read in Google BigQuery Sink connector. Aiven's Google BigQuery Kafka Connect Sink connector requires Google Cloud credential configurations for authentication to BigQuery services. During connector configuration, users can supply credential JSON files that are processed by Google authentication libraries. The service fails to validate externally-sourced credential configurations before passing them to the authentication libraries. An attacker can exploit this by providing a malicious credential configuration containing crafted credential_source.file paths or credential_source.url endpoints, resulting in arbitrary file reads or SSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0949 | PEM versions prior to 9.8.1 are affected by a stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that allows users with access to the Manage Ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0949</link><description>PEM versions prior to 9.8.1 are affected by a stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that allows users with access to the Manage Charts menu to inject arbitrary JavaScript when creating a new chart, which is then executed by any user accessing the chart. By default only the superuser and users with pem_admin or pem_super_admin privileges are able to access the Manage Charts menu.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23523 | Dive allows One-click Remote Code Execution through Deep Links for MCP Install</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23523</link><description>Dive is an open-source MCP Host Desktop Application that enables integration with function-calling LLMs. Prior to 0.13.0, crafted deeplink can install an attacker-controlled MCP server configuration without sufficient user confirmation and can lead to arbitrary local command execution on the victim’s machine. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22782 | RustFS RPC signature verification logs shared secret</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22782</link><description>RustFS is a distributed object storage system built in Rust. From &gt;= 1.0.0-alpha.1 to 1.0.0-alpha.79, invalid RPC signatures cause the server to log the shared HMAC secret (and expected signature), which exposes the secret to log readers and enables forged RPC calls. In crates/ecstore/src/rpc/http_auth.rs, the invalid signature branch logs sensitive data. This log line includes secret and expected_signature, both derived from the shared HMAC key. Any invalidly signed request triggers this path. The function is reachable from RPC and admin request handlers. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.0.0-alpha.80.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70746 | Tenda AX-1806 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the timeZone parameter of the fromSetSysTime function. This vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70746</link><description>Tenda AX-1806 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the timeZone parameter of the fromSetSysTime function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29943 | Write what were condition within AMD CPUs may allow an admin-privileged attacker to modify the configuration of the CPU pipeline potentially...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29943</link><description>Write what were condition within AMD CPUs may allow an admin-privileged attacker to modify the configuration of the CPU pipeline potentially resulting in the corruption of the stack pointer inside an SEV-SNP guest.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71020 | Tenda AX-1806 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the security parameter of the sub_4C408 function. This vulnerability al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71020</link><description>Tenda AX-1806 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the security parameter of the sub_4C408 function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21623 | Extension - stackideas.com - Persistent XSS in EasyDiscuss component 1.0.0-5.0.15 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21623</link><description>Lack of input filterung leads to a persistent XSS vulnerability in the forum post handling of the Easy Discuss component for Joomla.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21624 | Extension - stackideas.com - Persistent XSS in EasyDiscuss component 1.0.0-5.0.15 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21624</link><description>Lack of input filterung leads to a persistent XSS vulnerability in the user avatar text handling of the Easy Discuss component for Joomla.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21625 | Extension - stackideas.com - Lack of mime type validation in EasyDiscuss component 1.0.0-5.0.15 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21625</link><description>User provided uploads to the Easy Discuss component for Joomla aren't properly validated. Uploads are purely checked by file extensions, no mime type checks are happening.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68921 | SteelSeries Nahimic 3 1.10.7 allows Directory traversal.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68921</link><description>SteelSeries Nahimic 3 1.10.7 allows Directory traversal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15104 | Nu Html Checker (validator.nu) - Restriction bypass vulnerability allowing local SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15104</link><description>Nu Html Checker (validator.nu) contains a restriction bypass that allows remote attackers to make the server perform arbitrary HTTP/HTTPS requests to internal resources, including localhost services. While the validator implements hostname-based protections to block direct access to localhost and 127.0.0.1, these controls can be bypassed using DNS rebinding techniques or domains that resolve to loopback addresses.This issue affects The Nu Html Checker (vnu): latest (commit 23f090a11bab8d0d4e698f1ffc197a4fe226a9cd).</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0695 | Stored XSS in Time Entry Audit Trail</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0695</link><description>In ConnectWise PSA versions older than 2026.1, Time Entry notes stored in the Time Entry Audit Trail may be rendered without applying output encoding to certain content. Under specific conditions, this may allow stored script code to execute in the context of a user’s browser when the affected content is displayed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0696 | Session Cookies Missing HttpOnly Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0696</link><description>In ConnectWise PSA versions older than 2026.1, certain session cookies were not set with the HttpOnly attribute. In some scenarios, this could allow client-side scripts access to session cookie values.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14510 | ABB Ability OPTIMAX Authentication Bypass in Single-Sign On</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14510</link><description>Incorrect Implementation of Authentication Algorithm vulnerability in ABB ABB Ability OPTIMAX.This issue affects ABB Ability OPTIMAX: 6.1, 6.2, from 6.3.0 before 6.3.1-251120, from 6.4.0 before 6.4.1-251120.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14894 | CVE-2025-14894</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14894</link><description>Livewire Filemanager, commonly used in Laravel applications, contains LivewireFilemanagerComponent.php, which does not perform file type and MIME validation, allowing for RCE through upload of a malicious php file that can then be executed via the /storage/ URL if a commonly performed setup process within Laravel applications has been completed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0612 | CVE-2026-0612</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0612</link><description>The Librarian contains a information leakage vulnerability through the `web_fetch` tool, which can be used to retrieve arbitrary external content provided by an attacker, which can be used to proxy requests through The Librarian infrastructure. The vendor has fixed the vulnerability in all versions of TheLibrarian.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0613 | CVE-2026-0613</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0613</link><description>The Librarian contains an internal port scanning vulnerability, facilitated by the `web_fetch` tool, which can be used with SSRF-style behavior to perform GET requests to internal IP addresses and services, enabling scanning of the Hertzner cloud environment that TheLibrarian uses. The vendor has fixed the vulnerability in all affected versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0615 | CVE-2026-0615</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0615</link><description>The Librarian `supervisord` status page can be retrieved by the `web_fetch` tool, which can be used to retrieve running processes within TheLibrarian backend.  The vendor has fixed the vulnerability in all affected versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0616 | CVE-2026-0616</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0616</link><description>TheLibrarians web_fetch tool can be used to retrieve the Adminer interface content, which can then be used to log into the internal TheLibrarian backend system. The vendor has fixed the vulnerability in all affected versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14435 | Application-Level DoS via infinite re-render loop in user profile handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14435</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.8, 11.1.x &lt;= 11.1.1, 11.0.x &lt;= 11.0.6 fail to prevent infinite re-renders on API errors which allows authenticated users to cause application-level DoS via triggering unbounded component re-render loops.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68675 | Apache Airflow: proxy credentials for various providers might leak in task logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68675</link><description>In Apache Airflow versions before 3.1.6, the proxies and proxy fields within a Connection may include proxy URLs containing embedded authentication information. These fields were not treated as sensitive by default and therefore were not automatically masked in log output. As a result, when such connections are rendered or printed to logs, proxy credentials embedded in these fields could be exposed.

Users are recommended to upgrade to 3.1.6 or later, which fixes this issue</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59870 | Improper management of a static JWT signing secret in the web application, where the secret lacks rotation , introducing a security risk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59870</link><description>HCL MyXalytics v6.7 is affected by improper management of a static JWT signing secret in the web application, where the secret lacks rotation , introducing a security risk</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68438 | Apache Airflow: Secrets in rendered templates could contain parts of sensitive values when truncated</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68438</link><description>In Apache Airflow versions before 3.1.6, when rendered template fields in a Dag exceed [core] max_templated_field_length, sensitive values could be exposed in cleartext in the Rendered Templates UI. This occurred because serialization of those fields used a secrets masker instance that did not include user-registered mask_secret() patterns, so secrets were not reliably masked before truncation and display.

Users are recommended to upgrade to 3.1.6 or later, which fixes this issue</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:20:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14844 | Membership Plugin – Restrict Content &amp;lt;= 3.2.16 - Missing Authentication to Insecure Direct Object Reference and Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14844</link><description>The Membership Plugin – Restrict Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authentication in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.16 via the 'rcp_stripe_create_setup_intent_for_saved_card' function due to missing capability check. Additionally, the plugin does not check a user-controlled key, which makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to leak Stripe SetupIntent client_secret values for any membership.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14822 | DoS from quadratic complexity in model.ParseHashtags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14822</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.8 fail to validate input size before processing hashtags which allows an authenticated attacker to exhaust CPU resources via a single HTTP request containing a post with thousands space-separated tokens</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12006 | Supermicro BMC firmware update validation bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12006</link><description>There is a vulnerability in the Supermicro BMC firmware validation logic at Supermicro MBD-X12STW-F . An attacker can update the system firmware with a specially crafted image.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12007 | Supermicro BMC firmware update validation bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12007</link><description>There is a vulnerability in the Supermicro BMC firmware validation logic at Supermicro MBD-X13SEM-F . An attacker can update the system firmware with a specially crafted image.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14757 | Cost Calculator Builder &amp;lt;= 3.6.9 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Payment Status Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14757</link><description>The Cost Calculator Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unauthenticated Payment Status Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.9 only when used in combination with Cost Calculator Builder PRO. This is due to the complete_payment AJAX action being registered via wp_ajax_nopriv, making it accessible to unauthenticated users, and the complete() function only verifying a nonce without checking user capabilities or order ownership. Since nonces are exposed to all visitors via window.ccb_nonces in the page source, any unauthenticated attacker can mark any order's payment status as "completed" without actual payment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60021 | Apache bRPC: Remote command injection vulnerability in heap builtin service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60021</link><description>Remote command injection vulnerability in heap profiler builtin service in Apache bRPC ((all versions &lt; 1.15.0)) on all platforms allows attacker to inject remote command.



Root Cause: The bRPC heap profiler built-in service (/pprof/heap) does not validate the user-provided extra_options parameter and executes it as a command-line argument. Attackers can execute remote commands using the extra_options parameter..

Affected scenarios: Use the built-in bRPC heap profiler service to perform jemalloc memory profiling.

How to Fix: we provide two methods, you can choose one of them:

1. Upgrade bRPC to version 1.15.0.
2. Apply this patch ( https://github.com/apache/brpc/pull/3101 ) manually.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0913 | User Submitted Posts &amp;lt;= 20260110 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;usp_access&amp;#x27; Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0913</link><description>The User Submitted Posts – Enable Users to Submit Posts from the Front End plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'usp_access' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 20260110 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1004 | Essential Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 6.5.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1004</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to and including 6.5.5 via the 'eael_product_quickview_popup' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve WooCommerce product information for products with draft, pending, or private status, which should normally be restricted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20759 | OS Command Injection vulnerability exists in multiple Network Cameras TRIFORA 3 series provided by TOA Corporation, which may allow a logged...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20759</link><description>OS Command Injection vulnerability exists in multiple Network Cameras TRIFORA 3 series provided by TOA Corporation, which may allow a logged-in user with the low("monitoring user") or higher privilege to execute an arbitrary OS command.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20894 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in multiple Network Cameras TRIFORA 3 series provided by TOA Corporation. If an attacking administ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20894</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in multiple Network Cameras TRIFORA 3 series provided by TOA Corporation. If an attacking administrator configures the affected product with some malicious input, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of a victim administrator who accesses the setting screen.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22876 | Path Traversal vulnerability exists in multiple Network Cameras TRIFORA 3 series provided by TOA Corporation. If this vulnerability is explo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22876</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability exists in multiple Network Cameras TRIFORA 3 series provided by TOA Corporation. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary files on the affected product may be retrieved by a logged-in user with the low("monitoring user") or higher privilege.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14375 | RSS Aggregator – RSS Import, News Feeds, Feed to Post, and Autoblogging &amp;lt;= 5.0.10 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via className</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14375</link><description>The RSS Aggregator – RSS Import, News Feeds, Feed to Post, and Autoblogging plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘className’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 07:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1003 | GetGenie – AI Content Writer with Keyword Research &amp;amp; SEO Tracking Tools &amp;lt;= 4.3.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1003</link><description>The GetGenie plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.0. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to delete a specific post. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to delete any post on the WordPress site, including posts authored by other users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 07:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14793 | DK PDF – WordPress PDF Generator &amp;lt;= 2.3.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14793</link><description>The DK PDF – WordPress PDF Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.0 via the 'addContentToMpdf' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, author level and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:59:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14853 | LEAV Last Email Address Validator &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14853</link><description>The LEAV Last Email Address Validator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions &lt;= 1.7.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the display_settings_page function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0916 | Related Posts by Taxonomy &amp;lt;= 2.7.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;related_posts_by_tax&amp;#x27; Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0916</link><description>The Related Posts by Taxonomy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'related_posts_by_tax' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0939 | Rede Itaú for WooCommerce — Payment PIX, Credit Card and Debit &amp;lt;= 5.1.2 - Unauthenticated Order Status Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0939</link><description>The Rede Itaú for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to order status manipulation due to insufficient verification of data authenticity in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.2. This is due to the plugin failing to verify the authenticity of payment callbacks. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to manipulate WooCommerce order statuses, either marking unpaid orders as paid, or failed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0942 | Rede Itaú for WooCommerce — Payment PIX, Credit Card and Debit &amp;lt;= 5.1.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Rede Order Logs Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0942</link><description>The Rede Itaú for WooCommerce — Payment PIX, Credit Card and Debit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the clearOrderLogs() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete the Rede Order Logs metadata from all WooCommerce orders.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0975 | DIAView - Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0975</link><description>Delta Electronics DIAView has Command Injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23768 | lucy-xss-filter before commit 7c1de6d allows an attacker to induce server-side HEAD requests to arbitrary URLs when the ObjectSecurityListen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23768</link><description>lucy-xss-filter before commit 7c1de6d allows an attacker to induce server-side HEAD requests to arbitrary URLs when the ObjectSecurityListener or EmbedSecurityListener option is enabled and embed or object tags are used with a src attribute missing a file extension.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23769 | lucy-xss-filter before commit e5826c0 allows an attacker to execute malicious JavaScript due to improper sanitization caused by misconfigure...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23769</link><description>lucy-xss-filter before commit e5826c0 allows an attacker to execute malicious JavaScript due to improper sanitization caused by misconfigured default superset rule files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0858 | Versions of the package net.sourceforge.plantuml:plantuml before 1.2026.0 are vulnerable to Stored XSS due to insufficient sanitization of i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0858</link><description>Versions of the package net.sourceforge.plantuml:plantuml before 1.2026.0 are vulnerable to Stored XSS due to insufficient sanitization of interactive attributes in GraphViz diagrams. As a result, a crafted PlantUML diagram can inject malicious JavaScript into generated SVG output, leading to arbitrary script execution in the context of applications that render the SVG.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12641 | Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Role Demotion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12641</link><description>The Awesome Support - WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to missing capability checks in all versions up to, and including, 6.3.6. This is due to the 'wpas_do_mr_activate_user' function not verifying that a user has permission to modify other users' roles, combined with a nonce reuse vulnerability where public registration nonces are valid for privileged actions because all actions share the same nonce namespace. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to demote administrators to low-privilege roles via the 'wpas-do=mr_activate_user' action with a user-controlled 'user_id' parameter, granted they can access the publicly available registration/submit ticket page to extract a valid nonce.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12957 | All-in-One Video Gallery &amp;lt;= 4.5.7 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload via VTT Upload Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12957</link><description>The All-in-One Video Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file upload in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.7. This is due to insufficient file type validation detecting VTT files, allowing double extension files to bypass sanitization while being accepted as a valid VTT file. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14384 | All in One SEO – Powerful SEO Plugin to Boost SEO Rankings &amp;amp; Increase Traffic &amp;lt;= 4.9.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) AI Access Token and Credit Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14384</link><description>The All in One SEO – Powerful SEO Plugin to Boost SEO Rankings &amp; Increase Traffic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the `/aioseo/v1/ai/credits` REST route in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to disclose the global AI access token.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14982 | Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 10.14.11 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14982</link><description>The Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization leading to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 10.14.11. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view all booking records in the database, including personally identifiable information (PII) such as names, email addresses, phone numbers, physical addresses, payment status, booking costs, and booking hashes belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15370 | Shield Security &amp;lt;= 21.0.9 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference to Disable Google Authenticator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15370</link><description>The Shield: Blocks Bots, Protects Users, and Prevents Security Breaches plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 21.0.9 via the MfaGoogleAuthToggle class due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to disable Google Authenticator for any user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15526 | Fancy Product Designer | WooCommerce WordPress &amp;lt;= 6.4.8 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure via &amp;#x27;pdf&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15526</link><description>The Fancy Product Designer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.8. This is due to improper error handling in the PDF upload functionality that exposes server filesystem paths and stack traces in error messages. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15527 | WP Recipe Maker &amp;lt;= 10.2.2 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15527</link><description>The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 10.2.2 via the api_get_post_summary function due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be retrieved. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from posts they may not be able to edit or read otherwise. This also affects password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1000 | MailerLite - WooCommerce integration &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Missing Authorization to Data Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1000</link><description>The MailerLite - WooCommerce integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized data modification and deletion in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.3. This is due to missing capability checks on the resetIntegration() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to reset the plugin's integration settings, delete all plugin options, and drop the plugin's database tables (woo_mailerlite_carts and woo_mailerlite_jobs), resulting in complete loss of plugin data including customer abandoned cart information and sync job history.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1022 | Gotac｜Statistics Database System - Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1022</link><description>Statistics Database System developed by Gotac has an Arbitrary File Read vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit Relative Path Traversal to download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:06:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1023 | Gotac｜Statistics Database System - Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1023</link><description>Statistics Database System developed by Gotac has a Missing Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to directly exploit a specific functionality to query database contents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:06:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1019 | Gotac｜Police Statistics Database System - Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1019</link><description>Police Statistics Database System developed by Gotac has a Missing Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to read, modify, and delete database contents by using a specific functionality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:06:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1020 | Gotac｜Police Statistics Database System - Absolute Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1020</link><description>Police Statistics Database System developed by Gotac has a Absolute Path Traversal vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to enumerate the system file directory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:06:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1021 | Gotac｜Police Statistics Database System - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1021</link><description>Police Statistics Database System developed by Gotac has an Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attacker to upload and execute web shell backdoors, thereby enabling arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:06:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62581 | DIAView - Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62581</link><description>Delta Electronics DIAView has multiple vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62582 | DIAView - Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62582</link><description>Delta Electronics DIAView has multiple vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1018 | Gotac｜Police Statistics Database System - Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1018</link><description>Police Statistics Database System developed by Gotac has an Arbitrary File Read vulnerability, allowing Unauthenticated remote attacker to exploit Absolute Path Traversal to download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61937 | AVEVA Process Optimization Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61937</link><description>The vulnerability, if exploited, could allow an unauthenticated 
miscreant to achieve remote code execution under OS system privileges of
 “taoimr” service, potentially resulting in complete compromise of the  model application server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61943 | AVEVA Process Optimization SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61943</link><description>The vulnerability, if exploited, could allow an authenticated miscreant 
(Process Optimization Standard User) to tamper with queries in Captive 
Historian and achieve code execution under SQL Server administrative 
privileges, potentially resulting in complete compromise of the SQL 
Server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64691 | AVEVA Process Optimization Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64691</link><description>The vulnerability, if exploited, could allow an authenticated miscreant 
(OS standard user) to tamper with TCL Macro scripts and escalate 
privileges to OS system, potentially resulting in complete compromise of
 the model application server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64729 | AVEVA Process Optimization Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64729</link><description>The vulnerability, if exploited, could allow an authenticated miscreant 
(OS Standard User) to tamper with Process Optimization project files, 
embed code, and escalate their privileges to the identity of a victim 
user who subsequently interacts with the project files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64769 | AVEVA Process Optimization Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64769</link><description>The Process Optimization application suite leverages connection 
channels/protocols that by-default are not encrypted and could become 
subject to hijacking or data leakage in certain man-in-the-middle or 
passive inspection scenarios.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65117 | AVEVA Process Optimization Use of Potentially Dangerous Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65117</link><description>The vulnerability, if exploited, could allow an authenticated miscreant 
(Process Optimization Designer User) to embed OLE objects into graphics,
 and escalate their privileges to the identity of a victim user who 
subsequently interacts with the graphical elements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65118 | AVEVA Process Optimization Uncontrolled Search Path Element</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65118</link><description>The vulnerability, if exploited, could allow an authenticated miscreant 
(OS Standard User) to trick Process Optimization services into loading 
arbitrary code and escalate privileges to OS System, potentially 
resulting in complete compromise of the Model Application Server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14237 | Buffer overflow in XPS font parse processing on Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14237</link><description>Buffer overflow in XPS font parse processing on Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code. *: Satera LBP670C Series/Satera MF750C Series firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in Japan.Color imageCLASS LBP630C/Color imageCLASS MF650C Series/imageCLASS LBP230 Series/imageCLASS X LBP1238 II/imageCLASS MF450 Series/imageCLASS X MF1238 II/imageCLASS X MF1643i II/imageCLASS X MF1643iF II firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in US.i-SENSYS LBP630C Series/i-SENSYS MF650C Series/i-SENSYS LBP230 Series/1238P II/1238Pr II/i-SENSYS MF450 Series/i-SENSYS MF550 Series/1238i II/1238iF II/imageRUNNER 1643i II/imageRUNNER 1643iF II firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14231 | Buffer overflow in print job processing by WSD on Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14231</link><description>Buffer overflow in print job processing by WSD on Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code. *: Satera LBP670C Series/Satera MF750C Series firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in Japan.Color imageCLASS LBP630C/Color imageCLASS MF650C Series/imageCLASS LBP230 Series/imageCLASS X LBP1238 II/imageCLASS MF450 Series/imageCLASS X MF1238 II/imageCLASS X MF1643i II/imageCLASS X MF1643iF II firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in US.i-SENSYS LBP630C Series/i-SENSYS MF650C Series/i-SENSYS LBP230 Series/1238P II/1238Pr II/i-SENSYS MF450 Series/i-SENSYS MF550 Series/1238i II/1238iF II/imageRUNNER 1643i II/imageRUNNER 1643iF II firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14232 | Buffer overflow in XML processing of XPS file in Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14232</link><description>Buffer overflow in XML processing of XPS file in Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code. *: Satera LBP670C Series/Satera MF750C Series firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in Japan.Color imageCLASS LBP630C/Color imageCLASS MF650C Series/imageCLASS LBP230 Series/imageCLASS X LBP1238 II/imageCLASS MF450 Series/imageCLASS X MF1238 II/imageCLASS X MF1643i II/imageCLASS X MF1643iF II firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in US.i-SENSYS LBP630C Series/i-SENSYS MF650C Series/i-SENSYS LBP230 Series/1238P II/1238Pr II/i-SENSYS MF450 Series/i-SENSYS MF550 Series/1238i II/1238iF II/imageRUNNER 1643i II/imageRUNNER 1643iF II firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14233 | Invalid free in CPCA file deletion processing on Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14233</link><description>Invalid free in CPCA file deletion processing on Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code. *: Satera LBP670C Series/Satera MF750C Series firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in Japan.Color imageCLASS LBP630C/Color imageCLASS MF650C Series/imageCLASS LBP230 Series/imageCLASS X LBP1238 II/imageCLASS MF450 Series/imageCLASS X MF1238 II/imageCLASS X MF1643i II/imageCLASS X MF1643iF II firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in US.i-SENSYS LBP630C Series/i-SENSYS MF650C Series/i-SENSYS LBP230 Series/1238P II/1238Pr II/i-SENSYS MF450 Series/i-SENSYS MF550 Series/1238i II/1238iF II/imageRUNNER 1643i II/imageRUNNER 1643iF II firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14234 | Buffer overflow in CPCA list processing on Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the netw...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14234</link><description>Buffer overflow in CPCA list processing on Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code. *: Satera LBP670C Series/Satera MF750C Series firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in Japan.Color imageCLASS LBP630C/Color imageCLASS MF650C Series/imageCLASS LBP230 Series/imageCLASS X LBP1238 II/imageCLASS MF450 Series/imageCLASS X MF1238 II/imageCLASS X MF1643i II/imageCLASS X MF1643iF II firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in US.i-SENSYS LBP630C Series/i-SENSYS MF650C Series/i-SENSYS LBP230 Series/1238P II/1238Pr II/i-SENSYS MF450 Series/i-SENSYS MF550 Series/1238i II/1238iF II/imageRUNNER 1643i II/imageRUNNER 1643iF II firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14235 | Buffer overflow in XPS font fpgm data processing on Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14235</link><description>Buffer overflow in XPS font fpgm data processing on Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code. *: Satera LBP670C Series/Satera MF750C Series firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in Japan.Color imageCLASS LBP630C/Color imageCLASS MF650C Series/imageCLASS LBP230 Series/imageCLASS X LBP1238 II/imageCLASS MF450 Series/imageCLASS X MF1238 II/imageCLASS X MF1643i II/imageCLASS X MF1643iF II firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in US.i-SENSYS LBP630C Series/i-SENSYS MF650C Series/i-SENSYS LBP230 Series/1238P II/1238Pr II/i-SENSYS MF450 Series/i-SENSYS MF550 Series/1238i II/1238iF II/imageRUNNER 1643i II/imageRUNNER 1643iF II firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14236 | Buffer overflow in Address Book attribute tag processing on Small Office Multifunction Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the networ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14236</link><description>Buffer overflow in Address Book attribute tag processing on Small Office Multifunction Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code. *: Satera LBP670C Series/Satera MF750C Series firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in Japan.Color imageCLASS LBP630C/Color imageCLASS MF650C Series/imageCLASS LBP230 Series/imageCLASS X LBP1238 II/imageCLASS MF450 Series/imageCLASS X MF1238 II/imageCLASS X MF1643i II/imageCLASS X MF1643iF II firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in US.i-SENSYS LBP630C Series/i-SENSYS MF650C Series/i-SENSYS LBP230 Series/1238P II/1238Pr II/i-SENSYS MF450 Series/i-SENSYS MF550 Series/1238i II/1238iF II/imageRUNNER 1643i II/imageRUNNER 1643iF II firmware v06.02 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36926 | SmarterTools SmarterTrack 7922 -Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36926</link><description>SmarterTrack 7922 contains an information disclosure vulnerability in the Chat Management search form that reveals agent identification details. Attackers can access the vulnerable /Management/Chat/frmChatSearch.aspx endpoint to retrieve agents' first and last names along with their unique identifiers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36927 | DiskPulse 13.6.14 - Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36927</link><description>DiskPulse Enterprise 13.6.14 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configuration that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in 'C:\Program Files\Disk Pulse Enterprise\bin\diskpls.exe' to inject malicious executables and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36928 | Brother BRAgent 1.38 - &amp;#x27;WBA_Agent_Client&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36928</link><description>Brother BRAgent 1.38 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the WBA_Agent_Client service running with LocalSystem privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in C:\Program Files (x86)\Brother\BRAgent\ to inject and execute malicious code with elevated system permissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36929 | Brother BRPrint Auditor 3.0.7 - &amp;#x27;Multiple&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36929</link><description>Brother BRPrint Auditor 3.0.7 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configurations that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted file paths in BrAuSvc and BRPA_Agent services to inject malicious executables and escalate privileges on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36930 | SysGauge 7.9.18 - &amp;#x27; SysGauge Server&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36930</link><description>SysGauge Server 7.9.18 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its binary path configuration that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in 'C:\Program Files\SysGauge Server\bin\sysgaus.exe' to inject malicious executables and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47756 | Laravel Valet 2.0.3 - Local Privilege Escalation (macOS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47756</link><description>Laravel Valet versions 1.1.4 to 2.0.3 contain a local privilege escalation vulnerability that allows users to modify the valet command with root privileges. Attackers can edit the symlinked valet command to execute arbitrary code with root permissions without additional authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47779 | Dolibarr ERP-CRM 14.0.2 - Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) / Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47779</link><description>Dolibarr ERP-CRM 14.0.2 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the ticket creation module that allows low-privilege users to inject malicious scripts. Attackers can craft a specially designed ticket message with embedded JavaScript that triggers when an administrator copies the text, potentially enabling privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47780 | Macro Expert 4.7 - Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47780</link><description>Macro Expert 4.7 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the improperly configured service path to inject malicious executables that will be run with LocalSystem permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47782 | Odine Solutions GateKeeper 1.0 - &amp;#x27;trafficCycle&amp;#x27; SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47782</link><description>Odine Solutions GateKeeper 1.0 contains a SQL injection vulnerability in the trafficCycle API endpoint that allows remote attackers to inject malicious database queries. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability by sending crafted payloads to the /rass/api/v1/trafficCycle/ endpoint to manipulate PostgreSQL database queries and potentially extract sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47783 | Phpwcms 1.9.30 - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47783</link><description>Phpwcms 1.9.30 contains a file upload vulnerability that allows authenticated attackers to upload malicious SVG files with embedded JavaScript. Attackers can upload crafted SVG payloads through the multiple file upload feature to potentially execute cross-site scripting attacks on the platform.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47785 | Ether_MP3_CD_Burner 1.3.8 - Buffer Overflow (SEH)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47785</link><description>Ether MP3 CD Burner 1.3.8 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the registration name field that allows remote code execution. Attackers can craft a malicious payload to overwrite SEH handlers and execute a bind shell on port 3110 by exploiting improper input validation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47786 | Redragon Gaming Mouse - &amp;#x27;REDRAGON_MOUSE.sys&amp;#x27; Denial of Service (PoC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47786</link><description>Redragon Gaming Mouse driver contains a kernel-level vulnerability that allows attackers to trigger a denial of service by sending malformed IOCTL requests. Attackers can send a crafted 2000-byte buffer with specific byte patterns to the REDRAGON_MOUSE device to crash the kernel driver.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47787 | TotalAV 5.15.69 - Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47787</link><description>TotalAV 5.15.69 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in multiple system services running with LocalSystem privileges. Attackers can place malicious executables in specific unquoted path segments to potentially gain SYSTEM-level access by exploiting the service path configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47788 | WebsiteBaker 2.13.0 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) (Authenticated)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47788</link><description>WebsiteBaker 2.13.0 contains an authenticated remote code execution vulnerability that allows users with language editing permissions to execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the language installation endpoint by manipulating language installation parameters to achieve remote code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47789 | Yenkee Hornet Gaming Mouse - &amp;#x27;GM312Fltr.sys&amp;#x27; Denial of Service (PoC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47789</link><description>Yenkee Hornet Gaming Mouse driver GM312Fltr.sys contains a buffer overrun vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the system by sending oversized input. Attackers can exploit the driver by sending a 2000-byte buffer through DeviceIoControl to trigger a kernel-level system crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47790 | Active WebCam 11.5 - Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47790</link><description>Active WebCam 11.5 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the misconfigured service path by placing malicious executables in specific directory locations to gain administrative access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47791 | SmartFTP Client 10.0.2909.0 - &amp;#x27;Multiple&amp;#x27; Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47791</link><description>SmartFTP Client 10.0.2909.0 contains multiple denial of service vulnerabilities that allow attackers to crash the application through specific input manipulation. Attackers can trigger crashes by entering malformed paths, using invalid IP addresses, or clearing connection history in the client's interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47792 | Remote Mouse 4.002 - Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47792</link><description>Remote Mouse 4.002 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted service path in the RemoteMouseService to inject malicious executables and gain administrative access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47793 | Telegram Desktop 2.9.2 - Denial of Service (PoC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47793</link><description>Telegram Desktop 2.9.2 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by sending an oversized message payload. Attackers can generate a 9 million byte buffer and paste it into the messaging interface to trigger an application crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47794 | ZesleCP 3.1.9 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) (Authenticated)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47794</link><description>ZesleCP 3.1.9 contains an authenticated remote code execution vulnerability that allows attackers to create malicious FTP accounts with shell injection payloads. Attackers can exploit the FTP account creation endpoint by injecting a reverse shell command that establishes a network connection to a specified listening host.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47795 | GeoVision Geowebserver 5.3.3 - Local FIle Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47795</link><description>GeoVision GeoWebServer 5.3.3 contains multiple vulnerabilities including local file inclusion, cross-site scripting, and remote code execution through improper input sanitization. Attackers can exploit the WebStrings.srf endpoint by manipulating path traversal and injection parameters to access system files and execute malicious scripts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47796 | Denver Smart Wifi Camera SHC-150 - &amp;#x27;Telnet&amp;#x27; Remote Code Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47796</link><description>Denver SHC-150 Smart Wifi Camera contains a hardcoded telnet credential vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to access a Linux shell. Attackers can connect to port 23 using the default credential to execute arbitrary commands on the camera's operating system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47797 | Leawo Prof. Media 11.0.0.1 - Denial of Service (DoS) (PoC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47797</link><description>Leawo Prof. Media 11.0.0.1 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by supplying an oversized payload in the activation keycode field. Attackers can generate a 6000-byte buffer of repeated characters to trigger an application crash when pasted into the registration interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47798 | NoteBurner 2.35 - Denial Of Service (DoS) (PoC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47798</link><description>NoteBurner 2.35 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the license code input field that allows attackers to crash the application. Attackers can generate a 6000-byte payload and paste it into the 'Name' and 'Code' fields to trigger an application crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47800 | b2evolution 7.2.2 - &amp;#x27;edit account details&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47800</link><description>b2evolution 7.2.2 contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability that allows attackers to modify admin account details without authentication. Attackers can craft a malicious HTML form to submit unauthorized changes to user profiles by tricking victims into loading a specially crafted webpage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47801 | Vianeos OctoPUS 5 - &amp;#x27;login_user&amp;#x27; SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47801</link><description>Vianeos OctoPUS 5 contains a time-based blind SQL injection vulnerability in the 'login_user' parameter during authentication requests. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by crafting malicious POST requests with specially constructed SQL payloads that trigger database sleep functions to extract information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47803 | iFunbox 4.2 - &amp;#x27;Apple Mobile Device Service&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47803</link><description>iFunbox 4.2 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the Apple Mobile Device Service that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can insert a malicious executable into the unquoted service path to run with LocalSystem privileges when the service restarts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47804 | Wise Care 365 5.6.7.568 - &amp;#x27;WiseBootAssistant&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47804</link><description>Wise Care 365 5.6.7.568 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the WiseBootAssistant service running with LocalSystem privileges. Attackers can exploit this by inserting a malicious executable in the service path, which will execute with elevated system privileges when the service restarts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47805 | Disk Savvy 13.6.14 - &amp;#x27;Multiple&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47805</link><description>Disk Savvy 13.6.14 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configuration that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in service binaries to inject malicious executables that will be run with elevated LocalSystem privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47806 | Dup Scout 13.5.28 - &amp;#x27;Multiple&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47806</link><description>Dup Scout 13.5.28 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configuration that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in 'C:\Program Files\Dup Scout Server\bin\dupscts.exe' to inject malicious executables and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47807 | Sync Breeze 13.6.18 - &amp;#x27;Multiple&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47807</link><description>Sync Breeze 13.6.18 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configuration that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in service binaries located in 'Program Files' directories to inject malicious executables and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47808 | Cotonti Siena 0.9.19 - &amp;#x27;maintitle&amp;#x27; Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47808</link><description>Cotonti Siena 0.9.19 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the admin configuration panel's site title parameter. Attackers can inject malicious JavaScript code through the 'maintitle' parameter to execute scripts when administrators view the page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47809 | Disk Sorter Enterprise 13.6.12 - &amp;#x27;Disk Sorter Enterprise&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47809</link><description>Disk Sorter Enterprise 13.6.12 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configuration that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in 'C:\Program Files\Disk Sorter Enterprise\bin\disksrs.exe' to inject malicious executables and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47810 | WibuKey Runtime 6.51 - &amp;#x27;WkSvW32.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47810</link><description>WibuKey Runtime 6.51 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the WkSvW32.exe service that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in 'C:\PROGRAM FILES (X86)\WIBUKEY\SERVER\WkSvW32.exe' to inject malicious executables and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47811 | Grocery crud 1.6.4 - &amp;#x27;order_by&amp;#x27; SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47811</link><description>Grocery Crud 1.6.4 contains a SQL injection vulnerability in the order_by parameter that allows remote attackers to manipulate database queries. Attackers can inject malicious SQL code through the order_by[] parameter in POST requests to the ajax_list endpoint to potentially extract or modify database information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47812 | GravCMS 1.10.7 - Arbitrary YAML Write/Update (Unauthenticated) (2)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47812</link><description>GravCMS 1.10.7 contains an unauthenticated vulnerability that allows remote attackers to write arbitrary YAML configuration and execute PHP code through the scheduler endpoint. Attackers can exploit the admin-nonce parameter to inject base64-encoded payloads and create malicious custom jobs with system command execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47813 | Backup Key Recovery 2.2.7 - Denial of Service (PoC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47813</link><description>Backup Key Recovery 2.2.7 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by overflowing the registration code input field. Attackers can paste a large buffer of 256 repeated characters into the registration key field to trigger application instability and potential crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47814 | NBMonitor 1.6.8 - Denial of Service (PoC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47814</link><description>NBMonitor 1.6.8 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by overflowing the registration code input field. Attackers can paste a 256-character buffer into the registration key field to trigger an application crash and potential system instability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47815 | Nsauditor 3.2.3 - Denial of Service (PoC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47815</link><description>Nsauditor 3.2.3 contains a denial of service vulnerability in the registration code input field that allows attackers to crash the application. Attackers can paste a large buffer of 256 repeated characters into the 'Key' field to trigger an application crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1011 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Altium Support Center Comment Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1011</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Altium Support Center AddComment endpoint due to missing server-side input sanitization. Although the client interface applies HTML escaping, the backend accepts and stores arbitrary HTML and JavaScript supplied via modified POST requests.

The injected content is rendered verbatim when support cases are viewed by other users, including support staff with elevated privileges, allowing execution of arbitrary JavaScript in the victim’s browser context.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1010 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Altium Workflow Engine Allows Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1010</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Altium Workflow Engine due to missing server-side input sanitization in workflow form submission APIs. A regular authenticated user can inject arbitrary JavaScript into workflow data.

When an administrator views the affected workflow, the injected payload executes in the administrator’s browser context, allowing privilege escalation, including creation of new administrator accounts, session token theft, and execution of administrative actions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22864 | Deno has an incomplete fix for command-injection prevention on Windows — case-insensitive extension bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22864</link><description>Deno is a JavaScript, TypeScript, and WebAssembly runtime. Before 2.5.6, a prior patch aimed to block spawning Windows batch/shell files by returning an error when a spawned path’s extension matched .bat or .cmd. That check performs a case-sensitive comparison against lowercase literals and therefore can be bypassed when the extension uses alternate casing (for example .BAT, .Bat, etc.). This vulnerability is fixed in 2.5.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22863 | Deno node:crypto doesn&amp;#x27;t finalize cipher</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22863</link><description>Deno is a JavaScript, TypeScript, and WebAssembly runtime. Before 2.6.0, node:crypto doesn't finalize cipher. The vulnerability allows an attacker to have infinite encryptions. This can lead to naive attempts at brute forcing, as well as more refined attacks with the goal to learn the server secrets. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.6.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:01:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1009 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Altium Forum Leading to Cross-Customer Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1009</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Altium Forum due to missing server-side input sanitization in forum post content. An authenticated attacker can inject arbitrary JavaScript into forum posts, which is stored and executed when other users view the affected post.
Successful exploitation allows the attacker’s payload to execute in the context of the victim’s authenticated Altium 365 session, enabling unauthorized access to workspace data, including design files and workspace settings. Exploitation requires user interaction to view a malicious forum post.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:01:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68671 | lakeFS is Missing Timestamp Validation in S3 Gateway Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68671</link><description>lakeFS is an open-source tool that transforms object storage into a Git-like repositories. LakeFS's S3 gateway does not validate timestamps in authenticated requests, allowing replay attacks. Prior to 1.75.0, an attacker who captures a valid signed request (e.g., through network interception, logs, or compromised systems) can replay that request until credentials are rotated, even after the request is intended to expire. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.75.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22045 | Traefik&amp;#x27;s ACME TLS-ALPN fast path lacks timeouts and close on handshake stall</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22045</link><description>Traefik is an HTTP reverse proxy and load balancer. Prior to 2.11.35 and 3.6.7, there is a potential vulnerability in Traefik ACME TLS certificates' automatic generation: the ACME TLS-ALPN fast path can allow unauthenticated clients to tie up go routines and file descriptors indefinitely when the ACME TLS challenge is enabled. A malicious client can open many connections, send a minimal ClientHello with acme-tls/1, then stop responding, leading to denial of service of the entry point. The vulnerability is fixed in 2.11.35 and 3.6.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1008 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Altium 365 User Profile Fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1008</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the user profile text fields of Altium 365. Insufficient server-side input sanitization allows authenticated users to inject arbitrary HTML and JavaScript payloads using whitespace-based attribute parsing bypass techniques.
The injected payload is persisted and executed when other users view the affected profile page, potentially allowing session token theft, phishing attacks, or malicious redirects. Exploitation requires an authenticated account and user interaction to view the crafted profile.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0915 | getnetbyaddr and getnetbyaddr_r leak stack contents to DNS resovler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0915</link><description>Calling getnetbyaddr or getnetbyaddr_r with a configured nsswitch.conf that specifies the library's DNS backend for networks and queries for a zero-valued network in the GNU C Library version 2.0 to version 2.42 can leak stack contents to the configured DNS resolver.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2011-10041 | Uploadify &amp;lt;= 1.0 Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2011-10041</link><description>Uploadify WordPress plugin versions up to and including 1.0 contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in process_upload.php due to missing file type validation. An unauthenticated remote attacker can upload arbitrary files to the affected WordPress site, which may allow remote code execution by uploading executable content to a web-accessible location.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7334 | Changjetong T+ &amp;lt;= 16.x GetStoreWarehouseByStore Deserialization RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7334</link><description>Changjetong T+ versions up to and including 16.x contain a .NET deserialization vulnerability in an AjaxPro endpoint that can lead to remote code execution. A remote attacker can send a crafted request to /tplus/ajaxpro/Ufida.T.CodeBehind._PriorityLevel,App_Code.ashx?method=GetStoreWarehouseByStore with a malicious JSON body that leverages deserialization of attacker-controlled .NET types to invoke arbitrary methods such as System.Diagnostics.Process.Start. This can result in execution of arbitrary commands in the context of the T+ application service account. Exploitation evidence was observed by the Shadowserver Foundation on 2023-08-19 (UTC).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67822 | A vulnerability in the Provisioning Manager component of Mitel MiVoice MX-ONE 7.3 (7.3.0.0.50) through 7.8 SP1 (7.8.1.0.14) could allow an u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67822</link><description>A vulnerability in the Provisioning Manager component of Mitel MiVoice MX-ONE 7.3 (7.3.0.0.50) through 7.8 SP1 (7.8.1.0.14) could allow an unauthenticated attacker to conduct an authentication bypass attack due to improper authentication mechanisms. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to gain unauthorized access to user or admin accounts in the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67823 | A vulnerability in the Multimedia Email component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.2.0.10 and Mitel CX through 1.1.0.1 could al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67823</link><description>A vulnerability in the Multimedia Email component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.2.0.10 and Mitel CX through 1.1.0.1 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to conduct a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack due to insufficient input validation. A successful exploit requires user interaction where the email channel is enabled. This could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary scripts in the victim's browser or desktop client application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 21:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1002 | Eclipse Vert.x Web static handler file access denial</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1002</link><description>The Vert.x Web static handler component cache can be manipulated to deny the access to static files served by the handler using specifically crafted request URI.


The issue comes from an improper implementation of the C. rule of section 5.2.4 of RFC3986 and is fixed in Vert.x Core component (used by Vert.x Web):  https://github.com/eclipse-vertx/vert.x/pull/5895 



Steps to reproduce
Given a file served by the static handler, craft an URI that introduces a string like bar%2F..%2F after the last / char to deny the access to the URI with an HTTP 404 response. For example https://example.com/foo/index.html can be denied with https://example.com/foo/bar%2F..%2Findex.html

Mitgation
Disabling Static Handler cache fixes the issue.



StaticHandler staticHandler = StaticHandler.create().setCachingEnabled(false);</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67025 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Anycomment anycomment.io 0.4.4 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Anycomment c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67025</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Anycomment anycomment.io 0.4.4 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Anycomment comment section</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:58:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70891 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Phpgurukul Cyber Cafe Management System v1.0 within the user management module. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70891</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Phpgurukul Cyber Cafe Management System v1.0 within the user management module. The application does not properly sanitize or encode user-supplied input submitted via the uadd parameter in the add-users.php endpoint. An authenticated attacker can inject arbitrary JavaScript code that is persistently stored in the database. The malicious payload is triggered when a privileged user clicks the View button on the view-allusers.php page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70892 | Phpgurukul Cyber Cafe Management System v1.0 contains a SQL Injection vulnerability in the user management module. The application fails to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70892</link><description>Phpgurukul Cyber Cafe Management System v1.0 contains a SQL Injection vulnerability in the user management module. The application fails to properly validate user-supplied input in the username parameter of the add-users.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70893 | A time-based blind SQL Injection vulnerability exists in PHPGurukul Cyber Cafe Management System v1.0 within the adminprofile.php endpoint. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70893</link><description>A time-based blind SQL Injection vulnerability exists in PHPGurukul Cyber Cafe Management System v1.0 within the adminprofile.php endpoint. The application fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input provided via the adminname parameter, allowing authenticated attackers to inject arbitrary SQL expressions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21917 | Junos OS: SRX Series: Specifically malformed SSL packet causes FPC crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21917</link><description>An Improper Validation of Syntactic Correctness of Input vulnerability in the Web-Filtering module of Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX Series allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).

If an SRX device configured for UTM Web-Filtering receives a specifically malformed SSL packet, this will cause an FPC crash and restart.
This issue affects Junos OS on SRX Series:



  *  23.2 versions from 23.2R2-S2 before 23.2R2-S5, 
  *  23.4 versions from 23.4R2-S1 before 23.4R2-S5,
  *  24.2 versions before 24.2R2-S2,
  *  24.4 versions before 24.4R1-S3, 24.4R2.


Earlier versions of Junos are also affected, but no fix is available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21918 | Junos OS: SRX and MX Series: When TCP packets occur in a specific sequence flowd crashes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21918</link><description>A Double Free vulnerability in the flow processing daemon (flowd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX and MX Series allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS). On all SRX and MX Series platforms, when during TCP session establishment a specific sequence of packets is encountered a double free happens. This causes flowd to crash and the respective FPC to restart.





This issue affects Junos OS on SRX and MX Series:



  *  all versions before 22.4R3-S7,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2-S3,
  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R2-S4,
  *  24.2 versions before 24.2R2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21920 | Junos OS: SRX Series: If a specific request is processed by the DNS subsystem flowd will crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21920</link><description>An Unchecked Return Value vulnerability in the DNS module of Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX Series allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).




If an SRX Series device configured for DNS processing, receives a specifically formatted DNS request flowd will crash and restart, which causes a service interruption until the process has recovered.

This issue affects Junos OS on SRX Series:



  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R2-S5,
  *  24.2 versions before 24.2R2-S1,
  *  24.4 versions before 24.4R2.






This issue does not affect Junos OS versions before 23.4R1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21921 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: When telemetry collectors are frequently subscribing and unsubscribing to sensors chassisd or rpd will crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21921</link><description>A Use After Free vulnerability in the chassis daemon (chassisd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows a network-based attacker authenticated with low privileges to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).

When telemetry collectors are frequently subscribing and unsubscribing to sensors continuously over a long period of time, telemetry-capable processes like chassisd, rpd or mib2d will crash and restart, which - depending on the process - can cause a complete outage until the system has recovered.

This issue affects:

 Junos OS: 



  *  all versions before 22.4R3-S8,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2-S5,
  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R2;




Junos OS Evolved:



  *  all versions before 22.4R3-S8-EVO,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2-S5-EVO,
  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59960 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: DHCP Option 82 messages from clients being passed unmodified to the DHCP server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59960</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the Juniper DHCP service (jdhcpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows a DHCP client in one subnet to exhaust the address pools of other subnets, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS) on the downstream DHCP server.



By default, the DHCP relay agent inserts its own Option 82 information when forwarding client requests, optionally replacing any Option 82 information provided by the client. When a specific DHCP DISCOVER is received in 'forward-only' mode with Option 82, the device should drop the message unless 'trust-option82' is configured. Instead, the DHCP relay forwards these packets to the DHCP server unmodified, which uses up addresses in the DHCP server's address pool, ultimately leading to address pool exhaustion.

This issue affects Junos OS: 



  *  all versions before 21.2R3-S10,
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S12,
  *  all versions of 22.2,
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S8, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-S5, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R2-S6, 
  *  from 24.2 before 24.2R2-S2, 
  *  from 24.4 before 24.4R2, 
  *  from 25.2 before 25.2R1-S1, 25.2R2.




Junos OS Evolved:



  *  all versions before 21.4R3-S12-EVO, 
  *  all versions of 22.2-EVO,
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S8-EVO, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-S5-EVO, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R2-S6-EVO, 
  *  from 24.2 before 24.2R2-S2-EVO, 
  *  from 24.4 before 24.4R2-EVO, 
  *  from 25.2 before 25.2R1-S1-EVO, 25.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59961 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Unix socket used to control the jdhcpd process is world-writable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59961</link><description>An Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in the Juniper DHCP daemon (jdhcpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows a local, low-privileged user to write to the Unix socket used to manage the jdhcpd process, resulting in complete control over the resource.

This vulnerability allows any low-privileged user logged into the system to connect to the Unix socket and issue commands to manage the DHCP service, in essence, taking administrative control of the local DHCP server or DHCP relay.

This issue affects:
 Junos OS: 
  *  all versions before 21.2R3-S10,
  *  all versions of 22.2,
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S12,
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S8,
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-S5, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R2-S6, 
  *  from 24.2 before 24.2R2-S2, 
  *  from 24.4 before 24.4R2, 
  *  from 25.2 before 25.2R1-S1, 25.2R2; 



Junos OS Evolved: 
  *  all versions before 22.4R3-S8-EVO, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-S5-EVO, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R2-S6-EVO, 
  *  from 24.2 before 24.2R2-S2-EVO, 
  *  from 24.4 before 24.4R2-EVO, 
  *  from 25.2 before 25.2R1-S1-EVO, 25.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60003 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: BGP update with a set of specific attributes causes rpd crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60003</link><description>A Buffer Over-read vulnerability in the routing protocol daemon (rpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).

When an affected device receives a BGP update with a set of specific optional transitive attributes over an established peering session, rpd will crash and restart when attempting to advertise the received information to another peer.
This issue can only happen if one or both of the BGP peers of the receiving session are non-4-byte-AS capable as determined from the advertised capabilities during BGP session establishment. Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved default behavior is 4-byte-AS capable unless this has been specifically disabled by configuring:

[ protocols bgp ... disable-4byte-as ]


Established BGP sessions can be checked by executing:

show bgp neighbor  | match "4 byte AS"


This issue affects:

Junos OS: 

  *  all versions before 22.4R3-S8,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2-S5,
  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R2-S6,
  *  24.2 versions before 24.2R2-S2,
  *  24.4 versions before 24.4R2;


Junos OS Evolved: 

  *  all versions before 22.4R3-S8-EVO,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2-S5-EVO,
  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R2-S6-EVO,
  *  24.2 versions before 24.2R2-S2-EVO,
  *  24.4 versions before 24.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60007 | Junos OS: A specifically crafted &amp;#x27;show chassis&amp;#x27; command causes chassisd to crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60007</link><description>A NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in the chassis daemon (chassisd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX, SRX and EX Series allows a local attacker with low privileges to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).


When a user executes the 'show chassis' command with specifically crafted options, chassisd will crash and restart. Due to this all components but the Routing Engine (RE) in the chassis are reinitialized, which leads to a complete service outage, which the system automatically recovers from.



This issue affects:

Junos OS on MX, SRX and EX Series: 



  *  all versions before 22.4R3-S8,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2-S5,
  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R2-S6,
  *  24.2 versions before 24.2R2-S2,
  *  24.4 versions before 24.4R2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60011 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Optional transitive BGP attribute is modified before propagation to peers causing sessions to flap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60011</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the routing protocol daemon (rpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause an availability impact for downstream devices.

When an affected device receives a specific optional, transitive BGP attribute over an existing BGP session, it will be erroneously modified before propagation to peers. When the attribute is detected as malformed by the peers, these peers will most likely terminate the BGP sessions with the affected devices and thereby cause an availability impact due to the resulting routing churn.

This issue affects:

Junos OS:



  *  all versions before 22.4R3-S8,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2-S5
  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R2-S6,
  *  24.2 versions before 24.2R2-S2,
  *  24.4 versions before 24.4R2;




Junos OS Evolved: 



  *  all versions before 22.4R3-S8-EVO,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2-S5-EVO,
  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R2-S6-EVO,
  *  24.2 versions before 24.2R2-S2-EVO,
  *  24.4 versions before 24.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70890 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Cyber Cafe Management System v1.0. An authenticated attacker can inject arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70890</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Cyber Cafe Management System v1.0. An authenticated attacker can inject arbitrary JavaScript code into the username parameter via the add-users.php endpoint. The injected payload is stored and executed in the victim s browser when the affected page is accessed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0203 | Junos OS: Receipt of a specifically malformed ICMP packet causes an FPC restart</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0203</link><description>An Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in packet processing of Juniper Networks Junos OS allows an unauthenticated, network-adjacent attacker sending a specifically malformed ICMP packet to cause an FPC to crash and restart, resulting in a Denial of Service (DoS).



When an ICMP packet is received with a specifically malformed IP header value, the FPC receiving the packet crashes and restarts. Due to the specific type of malformed packet, adjacent upstream routers would not forward the packet, limiting the attack surface to adjacent networks.

This issue only affects ICMPv4. ICMPv6 is not vulnerable to this issue.

This issue affects Junos OS: 



  *  all versions before 21.2R3-S9, 
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S10, 
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S7, 
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S4, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S5, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-S3, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R2-S3, 
  *  from 24.2 before 24.2R1-S2, 24.2R2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21903 | Junos OS: Subscribing to telemetry sensors at scale causes all FPCs to crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21903</link><description>A Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (pfe) of Juniper Networks Junos OS allows a network-based attacker, authenticated with low privileges to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).



Subscribing to telemetry sensors at scale causes all FPC connections to drop, resulting in an FPC crash and restart.
The issue was not seen when YANG packages for the specific sensors were installed. 



This issue affects Junos OS: 



  *  all versions before 22.4R3-S7,
  *  23.2 version before 23.2R2-S4,
  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21905 | Junos OS: SRX Series, MX Series with MX-SPC3 or MS-MPC: Receipt of multiple specific SIP messages results in flow management process crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21905</link><description>A Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in the SIP application layer gateway (ALG) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX Series and MX Series with MX-SPC3 or MS-MPC allows an unauthenticated network-based attacker sending specific SIP messages over TCP to crash the flow management process, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS).

On SRX Series, and MX Series with MX-SPC3 or MS-MPC service cards, receipt of multiple SIP messages causes the SIP headers to be parsed incorrectly, eventually causing a continuous loop and leading to a watchdog timer expiration, crashing the flowd process on SRX Series and MX Series with MX-SPC3, or mspmand process on MX Series with MS-MPC.

This issue only occurs over TCP. SIP messages sent over UDP cannot trigger this issue.

This issue affects Junos OS on SRX Series and MX Series with MX-SPC3 and MS-MPC:



  *  all versions before 21.2R3-S10, 
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S12, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S8, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-S5, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R2-S6, 
  *  from 24.2 before 24.2R2-S3, 
  *  from 24.4 before 24.4R2-S1, 
  *  from 25.2 before 25.2R1-S1, 25.2R2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21906 | Junos OS: SRX Series: With GRE performance acceleration enabled, receipt of a specific ICMP packet causes the PFE to crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21906</link><description>An Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the packet forwarding engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX Series allows an unauthenticated network-based attacker sending a specific ICMP packet through a GRE tunnel to cause the PFE to crash and restart.

When PowerMode IPsec (PMI) and GRE performance acceleration are enabled and the device receives a specific ICMP packet, a crash occurs in the SRX PFE, resulting in traffic loss. PMI is enabled by default, and GRE performance acceleration can be enabled by running the configuration command shown below. PMI is a mode of operation that provides IPsec performance improvements using Vector Packet Processing.

Note that PMI with GRE performance acceleration is only supported on specific SRX platforms.
This issue affects Junos OS on the SRX Series:



  *  all versions before 21.4R3-S12, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S8, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-S5, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R2-S5, 
  *  from 24.2 before 24.2R2-S3, 
  *  from 24.4 before 24.4R2-S1, 
  *  from 25.2 before 25.2R1-S1, 25.2R2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21907 | Junos Space: TLS/SSL server supports use of static key ciphers (ssl-static-key-ciphers)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21907</link><description>A Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm vulnerability in the TLS/SSL server of Juniper Networks Junos Space allows the use of static key ciphers (ssl-static-key-ciphers), reducing the confidentiality of on-path traffic communicated across the connection. These ciphers also do not support Perfect Forward Secrecy (PFS), affecting the long-term confidentiality of encrypted communications.This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21908 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Use after free vulnerability In 802.1X authentication daemon can cause crash of the dot1xd process</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21908</link><description>A Use After Free vulnerability was identified in the 802.1X authentication daemon (dot1xd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved that could allow an authenticated, network-adjacent attacker flapping a port to crash the dot1xd process, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS), or potentially execute arbitrary code within the context of the process running as root.

The issue is specific to the processing of a change in authorization (CoA) when a port bounce occurs. A pointer is freed but was then referenced later in the same code path. Successful exploitation is outside the attacker's direct control due to the specific timing of the two events required to execute the vulnerable code path.

This issue affects systems with 802.1X authentication port-based network access control (PNAC) enabled.
This issue affects:

Junos OS: 



  *  from 23.2R2-S1 before 23.2R2-S5, 
  *  from 23.4R2 before 23.4R2-S6, 
  *  from 24.2 before 24.2R2-S3, 
  *  from 24.4 before 24.4R2-S1, 
  *  from 25.2 before 25.2R1-S2, 25.2R2; 




Junos OS Evolved: 



  *  from 23.2R2-S1 before 23.2R2-S5-EVO, 
  *  from 23.4R2 before 23.4R2-S6-EVO, 
  *  from 24.2 before 24.2R2-S3-EVO, 
  *  from 24.4 before 24.4R2-S1-EVO, 
  *  from 25.2 before 25.2R1-S2-EVO, 25.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21909 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Receipt of specific IS-IS update packet causes memory leak leading to RPD crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21909</link><description>A Missing Release of Memory after Effective Lifetime vulnerability in the routing protocol daemon (rpd) Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated attacker controlling an adjacent IS-IS neighbor to send a specific update packet causing a memory leak. Continued receipt and processing of these packets will exhaust all available memory, crashing rpd and creating a Denial of Service (DoS) condition.

Memory usage can be monitored through the use of the 'show task memory detail' command. For example:

user@junos&gt; show task memory detail | match ted-infra
  TED-INFRA-COOKIE             25     1072       28     1184       229



user@junos&gt; 

show task memory detail | match ted-infra
  TED-INFRA-COOKIE             31     1360       34     1472       307

This issue affects:

Junos OS: 

  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R1-S2, 23.4R2, 
  *  from 24.1 before 24.1R2; 


Junos OS Evolved: 

  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-EVO, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R1-S2-EVO, 23.4R2-EVO, 
  *  from 24.1 before 24.1R2-EVO.


This issue does not affect Junos OS versions before 23.2R1 or Junos OS Evolved versions before 23.2R1-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21910 | Junos OS: EX4k Series, QFX5k Series: In an EVPN-VXLAN configuration link flaps cause Inter-VNI traffic drop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21910</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the packet forwarding engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on EX4k Series and QFX5k Series platforms allows an unauthenticated network-adjacent attacker flapping an interface to cause traffic between VXLAN Network Identifiers (VNIs) to drop, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS).

On all EX4k and QFX5k platforms, a link flap in an

EVPN-VXLAN configuration Link Aggregation Group (LAG)
results in Inter-VNI traffic dropping when there are multiple load-balanced next-hop routes for the same destination.

This issue is only applicable to systems that support EVPN-VXLAN Virtual Port-Link Aggregation Groups (VPLAG), such as the QFX5110, QFX5120, QFX5200, EX4100, EX4300, EX4400, and EX4650.

Service can only be restored by restarting the affected FPC via the 'request chassis fpc restart slot ' command.

This issue affects Junos OS 

on EX4k and QFX5k Series: 



  *  all versions before 21.4R3-S12, 
  *  all versions of 22.2
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S8, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-S5, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R2-S5, 
  *  from 24.2 before 24.2R2-S3,
  *  from 24.4 before 24.4R2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21911 | Junos OS Evolved: Flapping management interface causes MAC learning on label-switched interfaces to stop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21911</link><description>An Incorrect Calculation vulnerability in the Layer 2 Control

Protocol 

 Daemon (l2cpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated network-adjacent attacker flapping the management interface to cause the learning of new MACs over label-switched interfaces (LSI) to stop while generating a flood of logs, resulting in high CPU usage.

When the issue is seen, the following log message will be generated:

op:1 flag:0x6 mac:xx:xx:xx:xx:xx:xx bd:2 ifl:13302 reason:0(REASON_NONE) i-op:6(INTRNL_OP_HW_FORCE_DELETE) status:10 lstatus:10 err:26(GETIFBD_VALIDATE_FAILED) err-reason 4(IFBD_VALIDATE_FAIL_EPOCH_MISMATCH) hw_wr:0x4 ctxsync:0 fwdsync:0  rtt-id:51 p_ifl:0  fwd_nh:0 svlbnh:0 event:- smask:0x100000000 dmask:0x0 mplsmask 0x1 act:0x5800 extf:0x0 pfe-id 0 hw-notif-ifl 13302 programmed-ifl 4294967295 pseudo-vtep underlay-ifl-idx 0 stack:GET_MAC, ALLOCATE_MAC, GET_IFL, GET_IFF, GET_IFBD, STOP, 


This issue affects Junos OS Evolved: 

  *  all versions before 21.4R3-S7-EVO, 
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S4-EVO, 
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S2-EVO, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-S1-EVO, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R1-S2-EVO, 23.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21912 | Junos OS: MX10k Series: &amp;#x27;show system firmware&amp;#x27; CLI command may lead to LC480 or LC2101 line card reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21912</link><description>A Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition vulnerability in the method to collect FPC Ethernet firmware statistics of Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX10k Series allows a local, low-privileged attacker executing the 'show system firmware' CLI command to cause an LC480 or LC2101 line card to reset.

On MX10k Series systems with LC480 or LC2101 line cards, repeated execution of the 'show system firmware' CLI command can cause the line card to crash and restart. Additionally, some time after the line card crashes, chassisd may also crash and restart, generating a core dump.This issue affects Junos OS on MX10k Series: 



  *  all versions before 21.2R3-S10, 
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S9, 
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S7, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S6, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-S2, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R2-S3, 
  *  from 24.2 before 24.2R2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21913 | Junos OS: EX4000: A high volume of traffic destined to the device leads to a crash and restart</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21913</link><description>An Incorrect Initialization of Resource vulnerability in the Internal Device Manager (IDM) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on EX4000 models allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).

On EX4000 models with 48 ports (EX4000-48T, EX4000-48P, EX4000-48MP) a high volume of traffic destined to the device will cause an FXPC crash and restart, which leads to a complete service outage until the device has automatically restarted.




The following reboot reason can be seen in the output of 'show chassis routing-engine' and as a log message:

  reason=0x4000002 reason_string=0x4000002:watchdog + panic with core dump 




This issue affects Junos OS on EX4000-48T, EX4000-48P and EX4000-48MP:



  *  24.4 versions before 24.4R2,
  *  25.2 versions before 25.2R1-S2, 25.2R2.




This issue does not affect versions before 24.4R1 as the first Junos OS version for the EX4000 models was 24.4R1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21914 | Junos OS: SRX Series: A specifically malformed GTP message will cause an FPC crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21914</link><description>An Improper Locking vulnerability in the GTP plugin of Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX Series allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (Dos).

If an SRX Series device receives a specifically malformed GPRS Tunnelling Protocol (GTP) Modify Bearer Request message, a lock is acquired and never released. This results in other threads not being able to acquire a lock themselves, causing a watchdog timeout leading to FPC crash and restart. This issue leads to a complete traffic outage until the device has automatically recovered.

This issue affects Junos OS on SRX Series:

  *  all versions before 22.4R3-S8,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2-S5,
  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R2-S6,
  *  24.2 versions before 24.2R2-S3,
  *  24.4 versions before 24.4R2-S2,
  *  25.2 versions before 25.2R1-S1, 25.2R2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52987 | Paragon Automation: A clickjacking vulnerability in the web server configuration has been addressed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52987</link><description>A clickjacking vulnerability exists in the web portal of Juniper Networks Paragon Automation (Pathfinder, Planner, Insights) due to the application's failure to set appropriate X-Frame-Options and X-Content-Type HTTP headers. This vulnerability allows an attacker to trick users into interacting with the interface under the attacker's control. 

This issue affects all versions of Paragon Automation (Pathfinder, Planner, Insights) before 24.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:21:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59959 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Executing a specific show command leads to an rpd crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59959</link><description>An Untrusted Pointer Dereference vulnerability in the routing protocol daemon (rpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows a local, authenticated attacker with low privileges to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).

When the command 'show route &lt; ( receive-protocol | advertising-protocol ) bgp &gt; detail' is executed, and at least one of the routes in the intended output has specific attributes, this will cause an rpd crash and restart.
'show route ... extensive' is not affected.




This issue affects:

Junos OS: 



  *  all versions before 22.4R3-S8,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2-S5,
  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R2-S5,
  *  24.2 versions before 24.2R2-S2,
  *  24.4 versions before 24.4R2;




Junos OS Evolved:



  *  all versions before 22.4R3-S8-EVO, 
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2-S5-EVO,
  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R2-S6-EVO,
  *  24.2 versions before 24.2R2-S2-EVO,
  *  24.4 versions before 24.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:21:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65368 | SparkyFitness v0.15.8.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via user input and LLM output.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65368</link><description>SparkyFitness v0.15.8.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via user input and LLM output.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:21:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15265 | Svelte 5.46.0  - Hydratable Key Script-Breakout XSS (SSR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15265</link><description>An SSR XSS exists in async hydration when attacker‑controlled keys are passed to hydratable. The key is embedded inside a  to terminate the script and inject arbitrary JavaScript. This enables remote script execution in users' browsers, with potential for session theft and account compromise.
This issue affects Svelte: from 5.46.0 before 5.46.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65349 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Web management interface in Each Italy Wireless Mini Router WIRELESS-N 300M v28K.MiniRo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65349</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Web management interface in Each Italy Wireless Mini Router WIRELESS-N 300M v28K.MiniRouter.20190211 allows attackers to execute arbitrary scripts via a crafted payload due to unsanitized repeater AP SSID value when is displayed in any page at /index.htm.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23746 | Entrust Instant Financial Issuance (IFI) SmartCardController Service .NET Remoting RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23746</link><description>Entrust Instant Financial Issuance (IFI) On Premise software (formerly referred to as CardWizard) versions 5.x, prior to 6.10.5, and prior to 6.11.1 contain an insecure .NET Remoting exposure in the SmartCardController service (DCG.SmartCardControllerService.exe). The service registers a TCP remoting channel with unsafe formatter/settings that permit untrusted remoting object invocation. A remote, unauthenticated attacker who can reach the remoting port can invoke exposed remoting objects to read arbitrary files from the server and coerce outbound authentication, and may achieve arbitrary file write and remote code execution via known .NET Remoting exploitation techniques. This can lead to disclosure of sensitive installation and service-account data and compromise of the affected host.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:56:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23520 | Arcane has a Command Injection in Arcane Updater Lifecycle Labels Enables RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23520</link><description>Arcane provides modern docker management. Prior to 1.13.0, Arcane has a command injection in the updater service. Arcane’s updater service supported lifecycle labels com.getarcaneapp.arcane.lifecycle.pre-update and com.getarcaneapp.arcane.lifecycle.post-update that allowed defining a command to run before or after a container update. The label value is passed directly to /bin/sh -c without sanitization or validation. Because any authenticated user (not limited to administrators) can create projects through the API, an attacker can create a project that specifies one of these lifecycle labels with a malicious command. When an administrator later triggers a container update (either manually or via scheduled update checks), Arcane reads the lifecycle label and executes its value as a shell command inside the container. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.13.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23527 | Request Smuggling (TE.TE) in h3 v1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23527</link><description>H3 is a minimal H(TTP) framework built for high performance and portability. Prior to 1.15.5, there is a critical HTTP Request Smuggling vulnerability. readRawBody is doing a strict case-sensitive check for the Transfer-Encoding header. It explicitly looks for "chunked", but per the RFC, this header should be case-insensitive. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.15.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23622 | CSRF Protection Bypass: Sensitive endpoints accept GET requests, enabling admin account takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23622</link><description>Easy!Appointments is a self hosted appointment scheduler. In 1.5.2 and earlier, application/core/EA_Security.php::csrf_verify() only enforces CSRF for POST requests and returns early for non-POST methods. Several application endpoints perform state-changing operations while accepting parameters from GET (or $_REQUEST), so an attacker can perform CSRF by forcing a victim's browser to issue a crafted GET request. Impact: creation of admin accounts, modification of admin email/password, and full admin account takeover.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23766 | Istio through 1.28.2 allows iptables rule injection for changing firewall behavior via the traffic.sidecar.istio.io/excludeInterfaces annota...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23766</link><description>Istio through 1.28.2 allows iptables rule injection for changing firewall behavior via the traffic.sidecar.istio.io/excludeInterfaces annotation. NOTE: the reporter's position is "this doesn't represent a security vulnerability (pod creators can already exclude sidecar injection entirely)."</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48077 | An issue in nanomq v0.22.7 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request. The number of data packets received in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48077</link><description>An issue in nanomq v0.22.7 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request. The number of data packets received in the recv-q queue of the Nanomq process continues to increase, causing the nanomq broker to fall into a deadlock and be unable to provide normal services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23511 | ZITADEL has a user enumeration vulnerability in Login UIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23511</link><description>ZITADEL is an open source identity management platform. Prior to 4.9.1 and 3.4.6, a user enumeration vulnerability has been discovered in Zitadel's login interfaces. An unauthenticated attacker can exploit this flaw to confirm the existence of valid user accounts by iterating through usernames and userIDs. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.9.1 and 3.4.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23519 | RustCrypto cmov: thumbv6m-none-eabi compiler emits non-constant time assembly when using cmovnz</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23519</link><description>RustCrypto CMOV provides conditional move CPU intrinsics which are guaranteed on major platforms to execute in constant-time and not be rewritten as branches by the compiler. Prior to 0.4.4, the thumbv6m-none-eabi (Cortex M0, M0+ and M1) compiler emits non-constant time assembly when using cmovnz (portable version). This vulnerability is fixed in 0.4.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22775 | devalue vulnerable to denial of service due to memory/CPU exhaustion in devalue.parse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22775</link><description>Svelte devalue is a JavaScript library that serializes values into strings when JSON.stringify isn't sufficient for the job. From 5.1.0 to 5.6.1, certain inputs can cause devalue.parse to consume excessive CPU time and/or memory, potentially leading to denial of service in systems that parse input from untrusted sources. This affects applications using devalue.parse on externally-supplied data. The root cause is the ArrayBuffer hydration expecting base64 encoded strings as input, but not checking the assumption before decoding the input. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.6.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0227 | PAN-OS: Firewall Denial of Service (DoS) in GlobalProtect Gateway and Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0227</link><description>A vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) to the firewall. Repeated attempts to trigger this issue results in the firewall entering into maintenance mode.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22249 | Docmost affected by an Arbitrary File Write via Zip Import Feature (ZipSlip)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22249</link><description>Docmost is an open-source collaborative wiki and documentation software. From 0.21.0 to before 0.24.0, Docmost is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Write via Zip Import Feature (ZipSlip). In apps/server/src/integrations/import/utils/file.utils.ts, there are no validation on filename. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.24.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22774 | devalue vulnerable to denial of service due to memory exhaustion in devalue.parse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22774</link><description>Svelte devalue is a JavaScript library that serializes values into strings when JSON.stringify isn't sufficient for the job. From 5.3.0 to 5.6.1, certain inputs can cause devalue.parse to consume excessive CPU time and/or memory, potentially leading to denial of service in systems that parse input from untrusted sources. This affects applications using devalue.parse on externally-supplied data. The root cause is the typed array hydration expecting an ArrayBuffer as input, but not checking the assumption before creating the typed array. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.6.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22803 | SvelteKit has a memory amplification DoS in Remote Functions binary form deserializer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22803</link><description>SvelteKit is a framework for rapidly developing robust, performant web applications using Svelte. From 2.49.0 to 2.49.4, the experimental form remote function uses a binary data format containing a representation of submitted form data. A specially-crafted payload can cause the server to allocate a large amount of memory, causing DoS via memory exhaustion. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.49.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13844 | CWE-415: Double Free vulnerability exists that could cause heap memory corruption when the end user imports a malicious project file (SSD fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13844</link><description>CWE-415: Double Free vulnerability exists that could cause heap memory corruption when the end user imports a malicious project file (SSD file) shared by the attacker into Rapsody.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13845 | CWE-416: Use After Free vulnerability that could cause remote code execution when the end user imports the malicious project file (SSD file)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13845</link><description>CWE-416: Use After Free vulnerability that could cause remote code execution when the end user imports the malicious project file (SSD file) into Rapsody.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67647 | SvelteKit Denial of service and possible SSRF when using prerendering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67647</link><description>SvelteKit is a framework for rapidly developing robust, performant web applications using Svelte. Prior to 2.49.5, SvelteKit is vulnerable to a server side request forgery (SSRF) and denial of service (DoS) under certain conditions. From 2.44.0 through 2.49.4, the vulnerability results in a DoS when your app has at least one prerendered route (export const prerender = true). From 2.19.0 through 2.49.4, the vulnerability results in a DoS when your app has at least one prerendered route and you are using adapter-node without a configured ORIGIN environment variable, and you are not using a reverse proxy that implements Host header validation. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.49.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70303 | A heap overflow in the uncv_parse_config() function of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted MP4 fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70303</link><description>A heap overflow in the uncv_parse_config() function of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted MP4 file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70302 | A heap overflow in the ghi_dmx_declare_opid_bin() function of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70302</link><description>A heap overflow in the ghi_dmx_declare_opid_bin() function of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70299 | A heap overflow in the avi_parse_input_file() function of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted AVI ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70299</link><description>A heap overflow in the avi_parse_input_file() function of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted AVI file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36911 | In key-based pairing, there is a possible ID due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36911</link><description>In key-based pairing, there is a possible ID due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) information disclosure of user's conversations and location with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9014 | Null Pointer Dereference Vulnerability on TL-WR841N</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9014</link><description>A Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability exists in the referer header check of the web portal of TP-Link TL-WR841N v14, caused by improper input validation.  A remote, unauthenticated attacker can exploit this flaw and cause Denial of Service on the web portal service.This issue affects TL-WR841N v14: before 250908.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70307 | A stack overflow in the dump_ttxt_sample function of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70307</link><description>A stack overflow in the dump_ttxt_sample function of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70305 | A stack overflow in the dmx_saf function of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted .saf file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70305</link><description>A stack overflow in the dmx_saf function of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted .saf file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:07:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23494 | Pimcore is Missing Function Level Authorization on &amp;quot;Static Routes&amp;quot; Listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23494</link><description>Pimcore is an Open Source Data &amp; Experience Management Platform. Prior to 12.3.1 and 11.5.14, the application fails to enforce proper server-side authorization checks on the API endpoint responsible for reading or listing static routes. In Pimcore, static routes are custom URL patterns defined via the backend interface or the var/config/staticroutes.php file, including details like regex-based patterns, controllers, variables, and priorities. These routes are registered automatically through the PimcoreStaticRoutesBundle and integrated into the MVC routing system. Testing revealed that an authenticated backend user lacking explicit permissions was able to invoke the endpoint (e.g., GET /api/static-routes) and retrieve sensitive route configurations. This vulnerability is fixed in 12.3.1 and 11.5.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:07:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23496 | Pimcore Web2Print Tools Bundle &amp;quot;Favourite Output Channel Configuration&amp;quot; Missing Function Level Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23496</link><description>Pimcore Web2Print Tools Bundle adds tools for web-to-print use cases to Pimcore. Prior to 5.2.2 and 6.1.1, the application fails to enforce proper server-side authorization checks on the API endpoint responsible for managing "Favourite Output Channel Configurations." Testing revealed that an authenticated backend user without explicitely lacking permissions for this feature was still able to successfully invoke the endpoint and modify or retrieve these configurations. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.2.2 and 6.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:07:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62193 | NOAA PMEL Live Access Server (LAS) command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62193</link><description>Sites running NOAA PMEL Live Access Server (LAS) are vulnerable to remote code execution via specially crafted requests that include PyFerret expressions. By leveraging a SPAWN command, unauthenticated attackers can execute arbitrary OS commands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:07:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70298 | GPAC v2.4.0 was discovered to contain an out-of-bounds read in the oggdmx_parse_tags function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70298</link><description>GPAC v2.4.0 was discovered to contain an out-of-bounds read in the oggdmx_parse_tags function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:07:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70656 | Tenda AX-1806 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the mac parameter of the sub_65B5C function. This vulnerability allows ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70656</link><description>Tenda AX-1806 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the mac parameter of the sub_65B5C function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:07:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20047 | Cisco Identity Services Engine Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20047</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) and Cisco ISE Passive Identity Connector (ISE-PIC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:07:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20075 | Cisco Evolved Programmable Network Manager and Cisco Prime Infrastructure Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20075</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Evolved Programmable Network Manager (EPNM) and Cisco Prime Infrastructure could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against users of the interface of an affected system.

This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious code into specific data fields in the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have valid administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:07:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20076 | Cisco Identity Services Engine Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20076</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:07:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23493 | Pimcore ENV Variables and Cookie Informations are exposed in http_error_log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23493</link><description>Pimcore is an Open Source Data &amp; Experience Management Platform. Prior to 12.3.1 and 11.5.14, the http_error_log file stores the $_COOKIE and $_SERVER variables, which means sensitive information such as database passwords, cookie session data, and other details can be accessed or recovered through the Pimcore backend. This vulnerability is fixed in 12.3.1 and 11.5.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:07:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23495 | Pimcore&amp;#x27;s Admin Classic Bundle is Missing Function Level Authorization on &amp;quot;Predefined Properties&amp;quot; Listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23495</link><description>Pimcore's Admin Classic Bundle provides a Backend UI for Pimcore. Prior to 2.2.3 and 1.7.16, the API endpoint for listing Predefined Properties in the Pimcore platform lacks adequate server-side authorization checks. Predefined Properties are configurable metadata definitions (e.g., name, key, type, default value) used across documents, assets, and objects to standardize custom attributes and improve editorial workflows, as documented in Pimcore's official properties guide. Testing confirmed that an authenticated backend user without explicit permissions for property management could successfully call the endpoint and retrieve the complete list of these configurations. The vulnerability is fixed in 2.2.3 and 1.7.16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:07:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66292 | DPanel has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in /api/common/attach/delete interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66292</link><description>DPanel is an open source server management panel written in Go. Prior to 1.9.2, DPanel has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in the /api/common/attach/delete interface. Authenticated users can delete arbitrary files on the server via path traversal. When a user logs into the administrative backend, this interface can be used to delete files. The vulnerability lies in the Delete function within the app/common/http/controller/attach.go file. The path parameter submitted by the user is directly passed to storage.Local{}.GetSaveRealPath and subsequently to os.Remove without proper sanitization or checking for path traversal characters (../). And the helper function in common/service/storage/local.go uses filepath.Join, which resolves ../ but does not enforce a chroot/jail. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.9.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66417 | GLPI  has an unauthenticated SQL injection through the inventory endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66417</link><description>GLPI is a free asset and IT management software package. From 11.0.0, &lt; 11.0.3, an unauthenticated user can perform a SQL injection through the inventory endpoint. This vulnerability is fixed in 11.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70304 | A buffer overflow in the vobsub_get_subpic_duration() function of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70304</link><description>A buffer overflow in the vobsub_get_subpic_duration() function of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70308 | An out-of-bounds read in the GSF demuxer filter component of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted ....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70308</link><description>An out-of-bounds read in the GSF demuxer filter component of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted .gsf file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70310 | A heap overflow in the vorbis_to_intern() function of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted .ogg fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70310</link><description>A heap overflow in the vorbis_to_intern() function of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted .ogg file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22265 | Roxy-WI has a Command Injection via grep parameter in logs.py allows authenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22265</link><description>Roxy-WI is a web interface for managing Haproxy, Nginx, Apache and Keepalived servers. Prior to 8.2.8.2, command injection vulnerability exists in the log viewing functionality that allows authenticated users to execute arbitrary system commands. The vulnerability is in app/modules/roxywi/logs.py line 87, where the grep parameter is used twice - once sanitized and once raw. This vulnerability is fixed in 8.2.8.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22867 | LaSuite Doc affected by Stored XSS via Interlinking Block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22867</link><description>LaSuite Doc is a collaborative note taking, wiki and documentation platform. From 3.8.0 to 4.3.0, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Interlinking feature. When a user creates a link to another document within the editor, the URL of that link is not validated. An attacker with document editing privileges can inject a malicious javascript: URL that executes arbitrary code when other users click on the link. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70309 | A stack overflow in the pcmreframe_flush_packet function of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted WA...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70309</link><description>A stack overflow in the pcmreframe_flush_packet function of GPAC v2.4.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted WAV file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:37:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64516 | GLPI incorrectly authorizes access to documents</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64516</link><description>GLPI is a free asset and IT management software package. Prior to 10.0.21 and 11.0.3, an unauthorized user can access GLPI documents attached to any item (ticket, asset, ...). If the public FAQ is enabled, this unauthorized access can be performed by an anonymous user. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.0.21 and 11.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47752 | AWebServer GhostBuilding 18 - Denial of Service (DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47752</link><description>AWebServer GhostBuilding 18 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows remote attackers to overwhelm the server by sending multiple concurrent HTTP requests. Attackers can generate high-volume requests to multiple endpoints including /mysqladmin to potentially crash or render the service unresponsive.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47753 | phpKF CMS 3.00 Beta y6 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) (Unauthenticated)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47753</link><description>phpKF CMS 3.00 Beta y6 contains an unauthenticated file upload vulnerability that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code by bypassing file extension checks. Attackers can upload a PHP file disguised as a PNG, rename it, and execute system commands through a crafted web shell parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47754 | Arunna 1.0.0 - &amp;#x27;Multiple&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47754</link><description>Arunna 1.0.0 contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability that allows attackers to manipulate user profile settings without authentication. Attackers can craft a malicious form to change user details, including passwords, email, and administrative privileges by tricking authenticated users into submitting the form.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47755 | Oliver Library Server v5 - Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47755</link><description>Oliver Library Server v5 contains a file download vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to access arbitrary system files through unsanitized input in the FileServlet endpoint. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability by manipulating the 'fileName' parameter to download sensitive files from the server's filesystem.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47757 | Chikitsa Patient Management System 2.0.2 - &amp;#x27;plugin&amp;#x27; Remote Code Execution (RCE) (Authenticated)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47757</link><description>Chikitsa Patient Management System 2.0.2 contains an authenticated remote code execution vulnerability in the backup restoration functionality. Authenticated attackers can upload a modified backup zip file with a malicious PHP shell to execute arbitrary system commands on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47758 | Chikitsa Patient Management System 2.0.2 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) (Authenticated)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47758</link><description>Chikitsa Patient Management System 2.0.2 contains an authenticated remote code execution vulnerability that allows attackers to upload malicious PHP plugins through the module upload functionality. Authenticated attackers can generate and upload a ZIP plugin with a PHP backdoor that enables arbitrary command execution on the server through a weaponized PHP script.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47759 | MTPutty 1.0.1.21 - SSH Password Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47759</link><description>MTPutty 1.0.1.21 contains a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability that allows local attackers to view SSH connection passwords through Windows PowerShell process listing. Attackers can run a PowerShell command to retrieve the full command line of MTPutty processes, exposing plaintext SSH credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47760 | TestLink 1.19 - Arbitrary File Download (Unauthenticated)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47760</link><description>TestLink versions 1.16 through 1.19 contain an unauthenticated file download vulnerability in the attachmentdownload.php endpoint. Attackers can download arbitrary files by iterating file IDs through the 'id' parameter with 'skipCheck=1' to bypass access controls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47761 | MilleGPG5 5.7.2 Luglio 2021 (x64) - Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47761</link><description>MilleGPG5 5.7.2 contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability that allows authenticated users to modify service executable files in the MariaDB bin directory. Attackers can replace the mysqld.exe with a malicious executable, which will execute with system privileges when the computer restarts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47762 | HTTPDebuggerPro 9.11 - Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47762</link><description>HTTPDebuggerPro 9.11 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted binary path in the service configuration to inject malicious executables and gain elevated access to the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47763 | Aimeos Laravel ecommerce platform 2021.10 LTS - &amp;#x27;sort&amp;#x27; SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47763</link><description>Aimeos 2021.10 LTS contains a SQL injection vulnerability in the json api 'sort' parameter that allows attackers to inject malicious database queries. Attackers can manipulate the sort parameter to reveal table and column names by sending crafted GET requests to the jsonapi/review endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47764 | AbsoluteTelnet 11.24 - &amp;#x27;Phone&amp;#x27; Denial of Service (PoC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47764</link><description>AbsoluteTelnet 11.24 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows local attackers to crash the application by manipulating DialUp connection and license name fields. Attackers can generate a 1000-character payload and paste it into specific input fields to trigger application crashes and force unexpected termination.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47765 | AbsoluteTelnet 11.24 - &amp;#x27;Username&amp;#x27; Denial of Service (PoC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47765</link><description>AbsoluteTelnet 11.24 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows local attackers to crash the application by manipulating username and error report fields. Attackers can trigger the crash by inserting 1000 characters into the username or email address fields, causing the application to become unresponsive.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47766 | Kmaleon 1.1.0.205 - &amp;#x27;tipocomb&amp;#x27; SQL Injection (Authenticated)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47766</link><description>Kmaleon 1.1.0.205 contains an authenticated SQL injection vulnerability in the 'tipocomb' parameter of kmaleonW.php that allows attackers to manipulate database queries. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability using boolean-based, error-based, and time-based blind SQL injection techniques to potentially extract or manipulate database information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47767 | 10-Strike Network Inventory Explorer Pro 9.31 - &amp;#x27;srvInventoryWebServer&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47767</link><description>10-Strike Network Inventory Explorer Pro 9.31 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the srvInventoryWebServer service running with LocalSystem privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path by placing malicious executables in potential path segments to achieve privilege escalation and execute code with system-level permissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47768 | ImportExportTools NG 10.0.4 - HTML Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47768</link><description>ImportExportTools NG 10.0.4 contains a persistent HTML injection vulnerability in the email export module that allows remote attackers to inject malicious HTML payloads. Attackers can send emails with crafted HTML in the subject that execute during HTML export, potentially compromising user data or session credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47769 | Isshue Shopping Cart 3.5 - &amp;#x27;Title&amp;#x27; Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47769</link><description>Isshue Shopping Cart 3.5 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability in title input fields across stock, customer, and invoice modules. Attackers with privileged user accounts can inject malicious scripts that execute on preview, potentially enabling session hijacking and persistent phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47771 | RDP Manager 4.9.9.3 - Denial-of-Service (PoC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47771</link><description>RDP Manager 4.9.9.3 contains a denial of service vulnerability in connection input fields that allows local attackers to crash the application. Attackers can add oversized entries in Verbindungsname and Server fields to permanently freeze and crash the software, potentially requiring full reinstallation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47772 | 10-Strike Network Inventory Explorer Pro 9.31 - Buffer Overflow (SEH)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47772</link><description>10-Strike Network Inventory Explorer Pro 9.31 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the text file import functionality that allows remote code execution. Attackers can craft a malicious text file with carefully constructed payload to trigger a reverse shell and execute arbitrary code on the target system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47773 | Dynojet Power Core 2.3.0 - Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47773</link><description>Dynojet Power Core 2.3.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the DJ.UpdateService that allows local authenticated users to potentially execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted binary path by placing malicious executables in the service's file path to gain Local System access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47774 | Kingdia CD Extractor 3.0.2 - Buffer Overflow (SEH)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47774</link><description>Kingdia CD Extractor 3.0.2 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the registration name field that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code. Attackers can craft a malicious payload exceeding 256 bytes to overwrite Structured Exception Handler and gain remote code execution through a bind shell.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47775 | YouTube Video Grabber 1.9.9.1 - Buffer Overflow (SEH)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47775</link><description>YouTube Video Grabber, now referred to as YouTube Downloader, 1.9.9.1 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code by overwriting the Structured Exception Handler. Attackers can craft a malicious payload of 712 bytes with SEH manipulation to trigger a bind shell connection on a specified local port.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47776 | Umbraco v8.14.1 - &amp;#x27;baseUrl&amp;#x27; SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47776</link><description>Umbraco CMS v8.14.1 contains a server-side request forgery vulnerability that allows attackers to manipulate baseUrl parameters in multiple dashboard and help controller endpoints. Attackers can craft malicious requests to the GetContextHelpForPage, GetRemoteDashboardContent, and GetRemoteDashboardCss endpoints to trigger unauthorized server-side requests to external hosts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47777 | Build Smart ERP 21.0817 - &amp;#x27;eidValue&amp;#x27; SQL Injection (Unauthenticated)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47777</link><description>Build Smart ERP 21.0817 contains an unauthenticated SQL injection vulnerability in the 'eidValue' parameter of the login validation endpoint. Attackers can inject stacked SQL queries using payloads like ';WAITFOR DELAY '0:0:3'-- to manipulate database queries and potentially extract or modify database information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47781 | Cmder Console Emulator 1.3.18 - &amp;#x27;Cmder.exe&amp;#x27; Denial of Service (PoC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47781</link><description>Cmder Console Emulator 1.3.18 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability that allows attackers to trigger a denial of service condition through a maliciously crafted .cmd file. Attackers can create a specially constructed .cmd file with repeated characters to overwhelm the console emulator's buffer and crash the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47784 | Cyberfox Web Browser 52.9.1 - Denial of Service (PoC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47784</link><description>Cyberfox Web Browser 52.9.1 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by overflowing the search bar with excessive data. Attackers can generate a 9,000,000 byte payload and paste it into the search bar to trigger an application crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47799 | Visual Tools DVR VX16 4.2.28 - Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47799</link><description>Visual Tools DVR VX16 version 4.2.28 contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability in its Sudo configuration that allows attackers to gain root access. Attackers can exploit the unsafe Sudo settings by using mount commands to bind a shell, enabling unauthorized system-level privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47819 | ProjeQtOr Project Management 9.1.4 - Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47819</link><description>ProjeQtOr Project Management 9.1.4 contains a file upload vulnerability that allows guest users to upload malicious PHP files with arbitrary code execution capabilities. Attackers can upload a PHP script through the profile attachment section and execute system commands by accessing the uploaded file with a specially crafted request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47843 | Tagstoo 2.0.1 - Stored XSS to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47843</link><description>Tagstoo 2.0.1 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious payloads through files or custom tags. Attackers can execute arbitrary JavaScript code to spawn system processes, access files, and perform remote code execution on the victim's computer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67246 | A local information disclosure vulnerability exists in the Ludashi driver before 5.1025 due to a lack of access control in the IOCTL handler...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67246</link><description>A local information disclosure vulnerability exists in the Ludashi driver before 5.1025 due to a lack of access control in the IOCTL handler. This driver exposes a device interface accessible to a normal user and handles attacker-controlled structures containing the lower 4GB of physical addresses. The handler maps arbitrary physical memory via MmMapIoSpace and copies data back to user mode without verifying the caller's privileges or the target address range. This allows unprivileged users to read arbitrary physical memory, potentially exposing kernel data structures, kernel pointers, security tokens, and other sensitive information. This vulnerability can be further exploited to bypass the Kernel Address Space Layout Rules (KASLR) and achieve local privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61973 | A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists during the installation of Epic Games Store via the Microsoft Store. A low-privilege user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61973</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists during the installation of Epic Games Store via the Microsoft Store. A low-privilege user can replace a DLL file during the installation process, which may result in unintended elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67076 | Directory traversal vulnerability in Omnispace Agora Project before 25.10 allowing unauthenticated attackers to read files on the system via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67076</link><description>Directory traversal vulnerability in Omnispace Agora Project before 25.10 allowing unauthenticated attackers to read files on the system via the misc controller and the ExternalGetFile action. Only files with an extension can be read.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67077 | File upload vulnerability in Omnispace Agora Project before 25.10 allowing authenticated, or under certain conditions also guest users, via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67077</link><description>File upload vulnerability in Omnispace Agora Project before 25.10 allowing authenticated, or under certain conditions also guest users, via the UploadTmpFile action.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67078 | Cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Omnispace Agora Project before 25.10 allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code via the notify...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67078</link><description>Cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Omnispace Agora Project before 25.10 allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code via the notify parameter of the file controller used to display errors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67079 | File upload vulnerability in Omnispace Agora Project before 25.10 allowing attackers to execute code through the MSL engine of the Imagick l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67079</link><description>File upload vulnerability in Omnispace Agora Project before 25.10 allowing attackers to execute code through the MSL engine of the Imagick library via crafted PDF file to the file upload and thumbnail functions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67081 | An SQL injection vulnerability in Itflow through 25.06 has been identified in the "role_id" parameter when editing a profile. An attacker wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67081</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability in Itflow through 25.06 has been identified in the "role_id" parameter when editing a profile. An attacker with admin account can exploit this issue via blind SQL injection, allowing for the extraction of arbitrary data from the database. The vulnerability arises from insufficient sanitizing on integer parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67082 | An SQL injection vulnerability in InvoicePlane through 1.6.3 has been identified in "maxQuantity" and "minQuantity" parameters when generati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67082</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability in InvoicePlane through 1.6.3 has been identified in "maxQuantity" and "minQuantity" parameters when generating a report. An authenticated attacker can exploit this issue via error-based SQL injection, allowing for the extraction of arbitrary data from the database. The vulnerability arises from insufficient sanitizing of single quotes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67083 | Directory traversal vulnerability in InvoicePlane through 1.6.3 allows unauthenticated attackers to read files from the server. The ability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67083</link><description>Directory traversal vulnerability in InvoicePlane through 1.6.3 allows unauthenticated attackers to read files from the server. The ability to read files and the file type depends on the web server and its configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67084 | File upload vulnerability in InvoicePlane through 1.6.3 allows authenticated attackers to upload arbitrary PHP files into attachments, which...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67084</link><description>File upload vulnerability in InvoicePlane through 1.6.3 allows authenticated attackers to upload arbitrary PHP files into attachments, which can later be executed remotely, leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70744 | Tenda AX-1806 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the cloneType parameter of the sub_65B5C function. This vulnerability a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70744</link><description>Tenda AX-1806 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the cloneType parameter of the sub_65B5C function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71019 | Tenda AX-1806 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the wanSpeed parameter of the sub_65B5C function. This vulnerability al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71019</link><description>Tenda AX-1806 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the wanSpeed parameter of the sub_65B5C function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0989 | Libxml2: unbounded relaxng include recursion leading to stack overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0989</link><description>A flaw was identified in the RelaxNG parser of libxml2 related to how external schema inclusions are handled. The parser does not enforce a limit on inclusion depth when resolving nested  directives. Specially crafted or overly complex schemas can cause excessive recursion during parsing. This may lead to stack exhaustion and application crashes, creating a denial-of-service risk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0990 | Libxml2: libxml2: denial of service via uncontrolled recursion in xml catalog processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0990</link><description>A flaw was found in libxml2, an XML parsing library. This uncontrolled recursion vulnerability occurs in the xmlCatalogXMLResolveURI function when an XML catalog contains a delegate URI entry that references itself. A remote attacker could exploit this configuration-dependent issue by providing a specially crafted XML catalog, leading to infinite recursion and call stack exhaustion. This ultimately results in a segmentation fault, causing a Denial of Service (DoS) by crashing affected applications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0992 | Libxml2: libxml2: denial of service via crafted xml catalogs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0992</link><description>A flaw was found in the libxml2 library. This uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability occurs when processing XML catalogs that contain repeated  elements pointing to the same downstream catalog. A remote attacker can exploit this by supplying crafted catalogs, causing the parser to redundantly traverse catalog chains. This leads to excessive CPU consumption and degrades application availability, resulting in a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0897 | Denial of Service in Keras via Excessive Memory Allocation in HDF5 Metadata</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0897</link><description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in the HDF5 weight loading component in Google Keras 3.0.0 through 3.13.0 on all platforms allows a remote attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) through memory exhaustion and a crash of the Python interpreter via a crafted .keras archive containing a valid model.weights.h5 file whose dataset declares an extremely large shape.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12895 | Kalium &amp;lt;= 3.29 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Mail Relay via kalium_vc_contact_form_request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12895</link><description>The Kalium 3 | Creative WordPress &amp; WooCommerce Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized email sending due to a missing capability check on the kalium_vc_contact_form_request() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.29. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to use the theme an an open mail relay and send email to arbitrary email addresses on the server's behalf.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13062 | Supreme Modules Lite &amp;lt;= 2.5.62 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload via JSON Upload Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13062</link><description>The Supreme Modules Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file upload in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.62. This is due to insufficient file type validation detecting JSON files, allowing double extension files to bypass sanitization while being accepted as a valid JSON file. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13859 | AffiliateX 1.0.0 - 1.3.9.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Missing Authorization to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via save_customization_settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13859</link><description>The AffiliateX – Amazon Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the save_customization_settings AJAX action in versions 1.0.0 to 1.3.9.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to store arbitrary JavaScript that executes whenever an AffiliateX block renders on the site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22638 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Grafana caused by combining a client path traversal and open redirect. This allows atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22638</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Grafana caused by combining a client path traversal and open redirect. This allows attackers to redirect users to a website that hosts a frontend plugin that will execute arbitrary JavaScript. This vulnerability does not require editor permissions and if anonymous access is enabled, the XSS will work. If the Grafana Image Renderer plugin is installed, it is possible to exploit the open redirect to achieve a full read SSRF. The default Content-Security-Policy (CSP) in Grafana will block the XSS though the `connect-src` directive.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22639 | Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. The Grafana Alerting DingDing integration was not properly protected an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22639</link><description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. The Grafana Alerting DingDing integration was not properly protected and could be exposed to users with Viewer permission. Fixed in versions 10.4.19+security-01, 11.2.10+security-01, 11.3.7+security-01, 11.4.5+security-01, 11.5.5+security-01, 11.6.2+security-01 and 12.0.1+security-01</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22640 | An access control vulnerability was discovered in Grafana OSS where an Organization administrator could permanently delete the Server admini...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22640</link><description>An access control vulnerability was discovered in Grafana OSS where an Organization administrator could permanently delete the Server administrator account. This vulnerability exists in the DELETE /api/org/users/ endpoint. The vulnerability can be exploited when: 1. An Organization administrator exists 2. The Server administrator is either: - Not part of any organization, or - Part of the same organization as the Organization administrator Impact: - Organization administrators can permanently delete Server administrator accounts - If the only Server administrator is deleted, the Grafana instance becomes unmanageable - No super-user permissions remain in the system - Affects all users, organizations, and teams managed in the instance The vulnerability is particularly serious as it can lead to a complete loss of administrative control over the Grafana instance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22641 | This vulnerability in Grafana's datasource proxy API allows authorization checks to be bypassed by adding an extra slash character in the UR...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22641</link><description>This vulnerability in Grafana's datasource proxy API allows authorization checks to be bypassed by adding an extra slash character in the URL path. Users with minimal permissions could gain unauthorized read access to GET endpoints in Alertmanager and Prometheus datasources. The issue primarily affects datasources that implement route-specific permissions, including Alertmanager and certain Prometheus-based datasources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22642 | An open redirect vulnerability has been identified in Grafana OSS organization switching functionality. Prerequisites for exploitation: - Mu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22642</link><description>An open redirect vulnerability has been identified in Grafana OSS organization switching functionality. Prerequisites for exploitation: - Multiple organizations must exist in the Grafana instance - Victim must be on a different organization than the one specified in the URL</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22643 | In Grafana, an excessively long dashboard title or panel name will cause Chromium browsers to become unresponsive due to Improper Input Vali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22643</link><description>In Grafana, an excessively long dashboard title or panel name will cause Chromium browsers to become unresponsive due to Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Grafana. This issue affects Grafana: before 11.6.2 and is fixed in 11.6.2 and higher.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22644 | Certain requests pass the authentication token in the URL as string query parameter, making it vulnerable to theft through server logs, prox...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22644</link><description>Certain requests pass the authentication token in the URL as string query parameter, making it vulnerable to theft through server logs, proxy logs and Referer headers, which could allow an attacker to hijack the user's session and gain unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22645 | The application discloses all used components, versions and license information to unauthenticated actors, giving attackers the opportunity ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22645</link><description>The application discloses all used components, versions and license information to unauthenticated actors, giving attackers the opportunity to target known security vulnerabilities of used components.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22646 | Certain error messages returned by the application expose internal system details that should not be visible to end users, providing attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22646</link><description>Certain error messages returned by the application expose internal system details that should not be visible to end users, providing attackers with valuable reconnaissance information (like file paths, database errors, or software versions) that can be used to map the application's internal structure and discover other, more critical vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0712 | An open redirect vulnerability has been identified in Grafana OSS that can be exploited to achieve XSS attacks. The vulnerability was introd...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0712</link><description>An open redirect vulnerability has been identified in Grafana OSS that can be exploited to achieve XSS attacks. The vulnerability was introduced in Grafana v11.5.0. The open redirect can be chained with path traversal vulnerabilities to achieve XSS. Fixed in versions 12.0.2+security-01, 11.6.3+security-01, 11.5.6+security-01, 11.4.6+security-01 and 11.3.8+security-01</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0713 | A security vulnerability in the /apis/dashboard.grafana.app/* endpoints allows authenticated users to bypass dashboard and folder permission...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0713</link><description>A security vulnerability in the /apis/dashboard.grafana.app/* endpoints allows authenticated users to bypass dashboard and folder permissions. The vulnerability affects all API versions (v0alpha1, v1alpha1, v2alpha1). Impact: - Viewers can view all dashboards/folders regardless of permissions - Editors can view/edit/delete all dashboards/folders regardless of permissions - Editors can create dashboards in any folder regardless of permissions - Anonymous users with viewer/editor roles are similarly affected Organization isolation boundaries remain intact. The vulnerability only affects dashboard access and does not grant access to datasources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22637 | The built-in XY Chart plugin is vulnerable to a DOM XSS vulnerability. A user with Editor permissions is able to modify such a panel in orde...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22637</link><description>The built-in XY Chart plugin is vulnerable to a DOM XSS vulnerability. A user with Editor permissions is able to modify such a panel in order to make it execute arbitrary JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22907 | An attacker may gain unauthorized access to the host filesystem, potentially allowing them to read and modify system data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22907</link><description>An attacker may gain unauthorized access to the host filesystem, potentially allowing them to read and modify system data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22908 | Uploading unvalidated container images may allow remote attackers to gain full access to the system, potentially compromising its integrity ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22908</link><description>Uploading unvalidated container images may allow remote attackers to gain full access to the system, potentially compromising its integrity and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22909 | Certain system functions may be accessed without proper authorization, allowing attackers to start, stop, or delete installed applications, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22909</link><description>Certain system functions may be accessed without proper authorization, allowing attackers to start, stop, or delete installed applications, potentially disrupting system operations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22910 | The device is deployed with weak and publicly known default passwords for certain hidden user levels, increasing the risk of unauthorized ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22910</link><description>The device is deployed with weak and publicly known default passwords for certain hidden user levels, increasing the risk of unauthorized access. This represents a high risk to the integrity of the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22911 | Firmware update files may expose password hashes for system accounts, which could allow a remote attacker to recover credentials and gain un...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22911</link><description>Firmware update files may expose password hashes for system accounts, which could allow a remote attacker to recover credentials and gain unauthorized access to the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22912 | Improper validation of a login parameter may allow attackers to redirect users to malicious websites after authentication. This can lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22912</link><description>Improper validation of a login parameter may allow attackers to redirect users to malicious websites after authentication. This can lead to various risk including stealing credentials from unsuspecting users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22913 | Improper handling of a URL parameter may allow attackers to execute code in a user's browser after login. This can lead to the extraction of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22913</link><description>Improper handling of a URL parameter may allow attackers to execute code in a user's browser after login. This can lead to the extraction of sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22914 | An attacker with limited permissions may still be able to write files to specific locations on the device, potentially leading to system man...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22914</link><description>An attacker with limited permissions may still be able to write files to specific locations on the device, potentially leading to system manipulation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22915 | An attacker with low privileges may be able to read files from specific directories on the device, potentially exposing sensitive informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22915</link><description>An attacker with low privileges may be able to read files from specific directories on the device, potentially exposing sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22916 | An attacker with low privileges may be able to trigger critical system functions such as reboot or factory reset without proper restrictions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22916</link><description>An attacker with low privileges may be able to trigger critical system functions such as reboot or factory reset without proper restrictions, potentially leading to service disruption or loss of configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22917 | Improper input handling in a system endpoint may allow attackers to overload resources, causing a denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22917</link><description>Improper input handling in a system endpoint may allow attackers to overload resources, causing a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22918 | An attacker may exploit missing protection against clickjacking by tricking users into performing unintended actions through maliciously cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22918</link><description>An attacker may exploit missing protection against clickjacking by tricking users into performing unintended actions through maliciously crafted web pages, leading to the extraction of sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22919 | An attacker with administrative access may inject malicious content into the login page, potentially enabling cross-site scripting (XSS) att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22919</link><description>An attacker with administrative access may inject malicious content into the login page, potentially enabling cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks, leading to the extraction of sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22920 | The device's passwords have not been adequately salted, making them vulnerable to password extraction attacks.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22920</link><description>The device's passwords have not been adequately salted, making them vulnerable to password extraction attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0976 | Org.keycloak/keycloak-quarkus-server: keycloak: proxy bypass due to improper handling of matrix parameters in url paths</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0976</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. This improper input validation vulnerability occurs because Keycloak accepts RFC-compliant matrix parameters in URL path segments, while common reverse proxy configurations may ignore or mishandle them. A remote attacker can craft requests to mask path segments, potentially bypassing proxy-level path filtering. This could expose administrative or sensitive endpoints that operators believe are not externally reachable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14457 | Drag and Drop Multiple File Upload for Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 1.3.9.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14457</link><description>The Drag and Drop Multiple File Upload for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing ownership check in the dnd_codedropz_upload_delete() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.9.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary uploaded files when the "Send attachments as links" setting is enabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:20:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14448 | WP-Members Membership Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.4.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Checkbox and Multiple Select User Profile Fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14448</link><description>The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Multiple Checkbox and Multiple Select user profile fields in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 05:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>