<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:40:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-47933 | Argo CD allows cross-site scripting on repositories page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47933</link><description>Argo CD is a declarative, GitOps continuous delivery tool for Kubernetes. Prior to versions 2.13.8, 2.14.13, and 3.0.4, an attacker can perform arbitrary actions on behalf of the victim via the API. Due to the improper filtering of URL protocols in the repository page, an attacker can achieve cross-site scripting with permission to edit the repository. This issue has been patched in versions 2.13.8, 2.14.13, and 3.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5325 | zhilink 智互联(深圳)科技有限公司 ADP Application Developer Platform 应用开发者平台 testService special elements used in a template engine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5325</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in zhilink 智互联(深圳)科技有限公司 ADP Application Developer Platform 应用开发者平台 1.0.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /adpweb/a/ica/api/service/rfa/testService. The manipulation leads to improper neutralization of special elements used in a template engine. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47288 | Discourse Policy plugin private group members visible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47288</link><description>Discourse Policy plugin gives the ability to confirm users have seen or done something. Prior to version 0.1.1, if there was a policy posted to a public topic that was tied to a private group then the group members could be shown to non-group members. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.1. A workaround involves moving any policy topics with private groups to restricted categories.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49350 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49350</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes DB2 Connect Server) 11.1.0 through 11.1.4.7, 11.5.0 through 11.5.9 and 12.1.0 through 12.1.1 is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2518 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2518</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes DB2 Connect Server) 11.5.0 through 11.5.9 and 12.1.0 through 12.1.1 

is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3050 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3050</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes DB2 Connect Server) 11.5.0 through 11.5.9 and 12.1.0 through 12.1.1 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service when using Q replication due to the improper allocation of CPU resources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46701 | Apache Tomcat: Security constraint bypass for CGI scripts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46701</link><description>Improper Handling of Case Sensitivity vulnerability in Apache Tomcat's GCI servlet allows security constraint bypass of security constraints that apply to the pathInfo component of a URI mapped to the CGI servlet.

This issue affects Apache Tomcat: from 11.0.0-M1 through 11.0.6, from 10.1.0-M1 through 10.1.40, from 9.0.0.M1 through 9.0.104.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 11.0.7, 10.1.41 or 9.0.105, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32752 | Dell ThinOS 2502 and prior contain a Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with physical acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32752</link><description>Dell ThinOS 2502 and prior contain a Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with physical access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information Disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48336 | WordPress Course Builder &amp;lt; 3.6.6 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48336</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ThimPress Course Builder allows Object Injection.This issue affects Course Builder: from n/a before 3.6.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5324 | TechPowerUp GPU-Z 0x8000645C IOCTL GPU-Z.sys sub_140001880 memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5324</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in TechPowerUp GPU-Z 2.23.0. Affected is the function sub_140001880 in the library GPU-Z.sys of the component 0x8000645C IOCTL Handler. The manipulation leads to memory leak. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5323 | fossasia open-event-server Mail Verification mail.py send_email_change_user_email reliance on obfuscation or encryption of security-relevant inputs without integrity checking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5323</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in fossasia open-event-server 1.19.1. This issue affects the function send_email_change_user_email of the file /fossasia/open-event-server/blob/development/app/api/helpers/mail.py of the component Mail Verification Handler. The manipulation leads to reliance on obfuscation or encryption of security-relevant inputs without integrity checking. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:27:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41591 | An issue in Open Network Foundation ONOS v2.7.0 allows attackers to create fake IP/MAC addresses and potentially execute a man-in-the-middle...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41591</link><description>An issue in Open Network Foundation ONOS v2.7.0 allows attackers to create fake IP/MAC addresses and potentially execute a man-in-the-middle attack on communications between fake and real hosts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:27:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53423 | An issue in Open Network Foundation ONOS v2.7.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying crafted packets.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53423</link><description>An issue in Open Network Foundation ONOS v2.7.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying crafted packets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:27:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46823 | OpenMRS has Vulnerability in FHIR2 Module Privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46823</link><description>openmrs-module-fhir2 provides the FHIR REST API and related services for OpenMRS, an open medical records system. In versions of the FHIR2 module prior to 2.5.0, privileges were not always correctly checked, which means that unauthorized users may have been able to add or edit data they were not supposed to be able to. All implementers should update to FHIR2 2.5.0 or newer as soon as is feasible to receive a patch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:27:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29632 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Free5gc v.4.0.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the AMF, NGAP, security.go, handl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29632</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Free5gc v.4.0.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the AMF, NGAP, security.go, handler_generated.go, handleInitialUEMessageMain, DecodePlainNasNoIntegrityCheck, GetSecurityHeaderType components</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 17:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51392 | An issue in OpenKnowledgeMaps Headstart v7 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the url parameter of the getPDF.php component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51392</link><description>An issue in OpenKnowledgeMaps Headstart v7 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the url parameter of the getPDF.php component</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 17:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46722 | vLLM has a Weakness in MultiModalHasher Image Hashing Implementation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46722</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). In versions starting from 0.7.0 to before 0.9.0, in the file vllm/multimodal/hasher.py, the MultiModalHasher class has a security and data integrity issue in its image hashing method. Currently, it serializes PIL.Image.Image objects using only obj.tobytes(), which returns only the raw pixel data, without including metadata such as the image’s shape (width, height, mode). As a result, two images of different sizes (e.g., 30x100 and 100x30) with the same pixel byte sequence could generate the same hash value. This may lead to hash collisions, incorrect cache hits, and even data leakage or security risks. This issue has been patched in version 0.9.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46570 | vLLM’s Chunk-Based Prefix Caching Vulnerable to Potential Timing Side-Channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46570</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). Prior to version 0.9.0, when a new prompt is processed, if the PageAttention mechanism finds a matching prefix chunk, the prefill process speeds up, which is reflected in the TTFT (Time to First Token). These timing differences caused by matching chunks are significant enough to be recognized and exploited. This issue has been patched in version 0.9.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48475 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Insufficient Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48475</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.180, the System does not provide a check on which "clients" of the System an authorized user can view and edit, and which ones they cannot. As a result, an authorized user who does not have access to any of the existing mailboxes, as well as to any of the existing conversations, has the ability to view and edit the System's clients. The limitation of client visibility can be implemented by the limit_user_customer_visibility setting, however, in the specified scenarios, there is no check for the presence of this setting. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.180.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48474 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Insufficient Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48474</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.180, the application incorrectly checks user access rights for conversations. Users with show_only_assigned_conversations enabled can assign themselves to an arbitrary conversation from the mailbox to which they have access, thereby bypassing the restriction on viewing conversations. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.180.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48473 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Insufficient Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48473</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.179, when creating a conversation from a message in another conversation, there is no check to ensure that the user has the ability to view this message. Thus, the user can view arbitrary messages from other mailboxes or from other conversations to which they do not have access (access restriction to conversations is implemented by the show_only_assigned_conversations setting, which is also not checked). This issue has been patched in version 1.8.179.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3913 | Team Privacy Settings Authorization Bypass in Mattermost Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3913</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.7.x &lt;= 10.7.0, 10.6.x &lt;= 10.6.2, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.3, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.12 fail to properly validate permissions when changing team privacy settings, allowing team administrators without the 'invite user' permission to access and modify team invite IDs via the /api/v4/teams/:teamId/privacy endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45474 | maccms10 v2025.1000.4047 is vulnerable to Server-side request forgery (SSRF) in Email Settings.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45474</link><description>maccms10 v2025.1000.4047 is vulnerable to Server-side request forgery (SSRF) in Email Settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48389 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Deserialization of Untrusted Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48389</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.178, FreeScout is vulnerable to deserialization of untrusted data due to insufficient validation. Through the set function, a string with a serialized object can be passed, and when getting an option through the get method, deserialization will occur, which will allow arbitrary code execution This issue has been patched in version 1.8.178.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48390 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48390</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.178, FreeScout is vulnerable to code injection due to insufficient validation of user input in the php_path parameter. The backticks characters are not removed, as well as tabulation is not removed. When checking user input, the file_exists function is also called to check for the presence of such a file (folder) in the file system. A user with the administrator role can create a translation for the language, which will create a folder in the file system. Further in tools.php, the user can specify the path to this folder as php_path, which will lead to the execution of code in backticks. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.178.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48471 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48471</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.179, the application does not check or performs insufficient checking of files uploaded to the application. This allows files to be uploaded with the phtml and phar extensions, which can lead to remote code execution if the Apache web server is used. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.179.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48472 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Insufficient Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48472</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.179, there is no check to ensure that the user is disabling notifications for the mailbox to which they already have access. Moreover, the code explicitly implements functionality that if the user does not have access to the mailbox, then after disabling (enabling) notifications for this mailbox, the user will gain access to it. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.179.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48748 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) through v.10.0.7784.0 has a hard-coded password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48748</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) through v.10.0.7784.0 has a hard-coded password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:14:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5321 | aimhubio aim run_view Object query.py RestrictedPythonQuery sandbox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5321</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in aimhubio aim up to 3.29.1. This vulnerability affects the function RestrictedPythonQuery of the file /aim/storage/query.py of the component run_view Object Handler. The manipulation of the argument Query leads to sandbox issue. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:14:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5334 | Exposure of private personal information to an unauthorized actor in the user vaults component of Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager
allows ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5334</link><description>Exposure of private personal information to an unauthorized actor in the user vaults component of Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager
allows an authenticated user to gain unauthorized access to private personal information. 



Under specific circumstances, entries may be unintentionally moved from user vaults to shared vaults when edited by their owners, making them accessible to other users.




This issue affects the following versions :

  *  Remote Desktop Manager Windows 2025.1.34.0 and earlier</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4081 | TCC Bypass via Dylib Substitution in DaVinci Resolve</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4081</link><description>Use of entitlement "com.apple.security.cs.disable-library-validation" and lack of launch and library load constraints allows to substitute a legitimate dylib with malicious one. A local attacker with unprivileged access can execute the application with altered dynamic library successfully bypassing Transparency, Consent, and Control (TCC). Acquired resource access is limited to previously granted permissions by the user. Access to other resources beyond granted-permissions requires user interaction with a system prompt asking for permission.

This issue affects DaVinci Resolve on macOS in all versions.
Last tested version: 19.1.3</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22653 | yasm commit 9defefae was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the yasm_section_bcs_append function at section.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22653</link><description>yasm commit 9defefae was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the yasm_section_bcs_append function at section.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22654 | tcpreplay v4.4.4 was discovered to contain an infinite loop via the tcprewrite function at get.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22654</link><description>tcpreplay v4.4.4 was discovered to contain an infinite loop via the tcprewrite function at get.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33043 | SMM buffer Integrity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33043</link><description>APTIOV contains a vulnerability in BIOS where an attacker may cause an Improper Input Validation locally. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can potentially impact of integrity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46080 | HuoCMS V3.5.1 has a File Upload Vulnerability. An attacker can exploit this flaw to bypass whitelist restrictions and craft malicious files ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46080</link><description>HuoCMS V3.5.1 has a File Upload Vulnerability. An attacker can exploit this flaw to bypass whitelist restrictions and craft malicious files with specific suffixes, thereby gaining control of the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46078 | HuoCMS V3.5.1 and before is vulnerable to file upload, which allows attackers to take control of the target server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46078</link><description>HuoCMS V3.5.1 and before is vulnerable to file upload, which allows attackers to take control of the target server</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5320 | gradio-app gradio CORS is_valid_origin origin validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5320</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in gradio-app gradio up to 5.29.1. This affects the function is_valid_origin of the component CORS Handler. The manipulation of the argument localhost_aliases leads to origin validation error. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37993 | can: m_can: m_can_class_allocate_dev(): initialize spin lock on device probe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37993</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

can: m_can: m_can_class_allocate_dev(): initialize spin lock on device probe

The spin lock tx_handling_spinlock in struct m_can_classdev is not
being initialized. This leads the following spinlock bad magic
complaint from the kernel, eg. when trying to send CAN frames with
cansend from can-utils:

| BUG: spinlock bad magic on CPU#0, cansend/95
|  lock: 0xff60000002ec1010, .magic: 00000000, .owner: /-1, .owner_cpu: 0
| CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 95 Comm: cansend Not tainted 6.15.0-rc3-00032-ga79be02bba5c #5 NONE
| Hardware name: MachineWare SIM-V (DT)
| Call Trace:
| [] dump_backtrace+0x1c/0x24
| [] show_stack+0x28/0x34
| [] dump_stack_lvl+0x4a/0x68
| [] dump_stack+0x14/0x1c
| [] spin_dump+0x62/0x6e
| [] do_raw_spin_lock+0xd0/0x142
| [] _raw_spin_lock_irqsave+0x20/0x2c
| [] m_can_start_xmit+0x90/0x34a
| [] dev_hard_start_xmit+0xa6/0xee
| [] sch_direct_xmit+0x114/0x292
| [] __dev_queue_xmit+0x3b0/0xaa8
| [] can_send+0xc6/0x242
| [] raw_sendmsg+0x1a8/0x36c
| [] sock_write_iter+0x9a/0xee
| [] vfs_write+0x184/0x3a6
| [] ksys_write+0xa0/0xc0
| [] __riscv_sys_write+0x14/0x1c
| [] do_trap_ecall_u+0x168/0x212
| [] handle_exception+0x146/0x152

Initializing the spin lock in m_can_class_allocate_dev solves that
problem.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37994 | usb: typec: ucsi: displayport: Fix NULL pointer access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37994</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: typec: ucsi: displayport: Fix NULL pointer access

This patch ensures that the UCSI driver waits for all pending tasks in the
ucsi_displayport_work workqueue to finish executing before proceeding with
the partner removal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37995 | module: ensure that kobject_put() is safe for module type kobjects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37995</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

module: ensure that kobject_put() is safe for module type kobjects

In 'lookup_or_create_module_kobject()', an internal kobject is created
using 'module_ktype'. So call to 'kobject_put()' on error handling
path causes an attempt to use an uninitialized completion pointer in
'module_kobject_release()'. In this scenario, we just want to release
kobject without an extra synchronization required for a regular module
unloading process, so adding an extra check whether 'complete()' is
actually required makes 'kobject_put()' safe.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37996 | KVM: arm64: Fix uninitialized memcache pointer in user_mem_abort()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37996</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

KVM: arm64: Fix uninitialized memcache pointer in user_mem_abort()

Commit fce886a60207 ("KVM: arm64: Plumb the pKVM MMU in KVM") made the
initialization of the local memcache variable in user_mem_abort()
conditional, leaving a codepath where it is used uninitialized via
kvm_pgtable_stage2_map().

This can fail on any path that requires a stage-2 allocation
without transition via a permission fault or dirty logging.

Fix this by making sure that memcache is always valid.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37997 | netfilter: ipset: fix region locking in hash types</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37997</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: ipset: fix region locking in hash types

Region locking introduced in v5.6-rc4 contained three macros to handle
the region locks: ahash_bucket_start(), ahash_bucket_end() which gave
back the start and end hash bucket values belonging to a given region
lock and ahash_region() which should give back the region lock belonging
to a given hash bucket. The latter was incorrect which can lead to a
race condition between the garbage collector and adding new elements
when a hash type of set is defined with timeouts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37998 | openvswitch: Fix unsafe attribute parsing in output_userspace()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37998</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

openvswitch: Fix unsafe attribute parsing in output_userspace()

This patch replaces the manual Netlink attribute iteration in
output_userspace() with nla_for_each_nested(), which ensures that only
well-formed attributes are processed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37999 | fs/erofs/fileio: call erofs_onlinefolio_split() after bio_add_folio()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37999</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fs/erofs/fileio: call erofs_onlinefolio_split() after bio_add_folio()

If bio_add_folio() fails (because it is full),
erofs_fileio_scan_folio() needs to submit the I/O request via
erofs_fileio_rq_submit() and allocate a new I/O request with an empty
`struct bio`.  Then it retries the bio_add_folio() call.

However, at this point, erofs_onlinefolio_split() has already been
called which increments `folio-&gt;private`; the retry will call
erofs_onlinefolio_split() again, but there will never be a matching
erofs_onlinefolio_end() call.  This leaves the folio locked forever
and all waiters will be stuck in folio_wait_bit_common().

This bug has been added by commit ce63cb62d794 ("erofs: support
unencoded inodes for fileio"), but was practically unreachable because
there was room for 256 folios in the `struct bio` - until commit
9f74ae8c9ac9 ("erofs: shorten bvecs[] for file-backed mounts") which
reduced the array capacity to 16 folios.

It was now trivial to trigger the bug by manually invoking readahead
from userspace, e.g.:

 posix_fadvise(fd, 0, st.st_size, POSIX_FADV_WILLNEED);

This should be fixed by invoking erofs_onlinefolio_split() only after
bio_add_folio() has succeeded.  This is safe: asynchronous completions
invoking erofs_onlinefolio_end() will not unlock the folio because
erofs_fileio_scan_folio() is still holding a reference to be released
by erofs_onlinefolio_end() at the end.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48046 | MICI Network Co. Ltd. NetFax Server Disclosure of Stored Passwords in Cleartext</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48046</link><description>An authenticated user can disclose the cleartext password of a configured SMTP server via an HTTP GET request to the /config.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48047 | MICI Network Co. Ltd. NetFax Server Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48047</link><description>An authenticated user can perform command injection via unsanitized input to the NetFax Server’s ping functionality via the /test.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48045 | MICI Network Co. Ltd. NetFax Server Default Administrator Credentials Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48045</link><description>An unauthenticated HTTP GET request to the /client.php endpoint will disclose the default administrator user credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 12:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48388 | FreeScout Has Insufficient Protection Against CRLF-injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48388</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.178, the application performs insufficient validation of user-supplied data, which is used as arguments to string formatting functions. As a result, an attacker can pass a string containing special symbols (\r, \n, \t)to the application. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.178.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:33:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27151 | redis-check-aof may lead to stack overflow and potential RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27151</link><description>Redis is an open source, in-memory database that persists on disk. In versions starting from 7.0.0 to before 8.0.2, a stack-based buffer overflow exists in redis-check-aof due to the use of memcpy with strlen(filepath) when copying a user-supplied file path into a fixed-size stack buffer. This allows an attacker to overflow the stack and potentially achieve code execution. This issue has been patched in version 8.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52588 | Strapi allows Server-Side Request Forgery in Webhook function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52588</link><description>Strapi is an open-source content management system. Prior to version 4.25.2, inputting a local domain into the Webhooks URL field leads to the application fetching itself, resulting in a server side request forgery (SSRF). This issue has been patched in version 4.25.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4687 | Account pre-hijacking through invite misuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4687</link><description>In Teltonika Networks Remote Management System (RMS), it is possible to perform account pre-hijacking by misusing the invite functionality. If a victim has a pending invite and registers to the platform directly, they are added to the attackers company without their knowledge. The victims account and their company can then be managed by the attacker.This issue affects RMS: before 5.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4670 | Easy Digital Downloads &amp;lt;= 3.3.8.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via edd_receipt Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4670</link><description>The Easy Digital Downloads – eCommerce Payments and Subscriptions made easy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's edd_receipt shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.8.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 08:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5122 | Map Block Leaflet &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via url Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5122</link><description>The Map Block Leaflet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 08:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5286 | Bold Builder &amp;lt;= 5.3.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via additional_settings Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5286</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘additional_settings’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 08:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5273 | All versions of the package mcp-markdownify-server are vulnerable to Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties via the get-markdow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5273</link><description>All versions of the package mcp-markdownify-server are vulnerable to Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties via the get-markdown-file tool. An attacker can craft a prompt that, once accessed by the MCP host, will allow it to read arbitrary files from the host running the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 05:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5276 | All versions of the package mcp-markdownify-server are vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the Markdownify.get() function. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5276</link><description>All versions of the package mcp-markdownify-server are vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the Markdownify.get() function. An attacker can craft a prompt that, once accessed by the MCP host, can invoke the webpage-to-markdown, bing-search-to-markdown, and youtube-to-markdown tools to issue requests and read the responses to attacker-controlled URLs, potentially leaking sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 05:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3755 | Information Disclosure and Denial-of-Service(DoS) Vulnerability in MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3755</link><description>Improper Validation of Specified Index, Position, or Offset in Input vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU modules allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to read information in the product, to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS) condition in MELSOFT connection, or to stop the operation of the CPU module (causing a DoS condtion on the CPU module), by sending specially crafted packets. The product is needed to reset for recovery.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:52:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4583 | Smash Balloon Instagram Feed &amp;lt;= 6.9.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via `data-plugin` Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4583</link><description>The Smash Balloon Social Photo Feed – Easy Social Feeds Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `data-plugin` attribute in all versions up to, and including, 6.9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27706 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Secure Access administrative console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.54</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27706</link><description>CVE-2025-27706 is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the management
 console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.54. Attackers 
with system administrator permissions can interfere with another system 
administrator’s use of the management console when the second 
administrator visits the page. Attack complexity is low, there are no 
preexisting attack requirements, privileges required are high and active
 user interaction is required. There is no impact on confidentiality, 
the impact on integrity is low and there is no impact on availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 21:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27703 | Privilege escalation in the management console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.54</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27703</link><description>CVE-2025-27703 is a privilege escalation vulnerability in the management
 console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.54. Attackers 
with administrative access to a specific subset of privileged features 
in the console can elevate their permissions to access additional 
features in the console. The attack complexity is low, there are no 
preexisting attack requirements; the privileges required are high, and 
there is no user interaction required. The impact to system 
confidentiality is low, the impact to system integrity is high and the 
impact to system availability is low.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 21:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27702 | Permissions bypass in the management console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.54</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27702</link><description>CVE-2025-27702 is a vulnerability in the management console of Absolute 
Secure Access prior to version 13.54. Attackers with administrative 
access to the console and who have been assigned a certain set of 
permissions can bypass those permissions to improperly modify settings. 
The attack complexity is low, there are no preexisting attack 
requirements; the privileges required are high, and there is no user 
interaction required. There is no impact to system confidentiality or 
availability, impact to system integrity is high.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31500 | Best Practical RT (Request Tracker) 5.0 through 5.0.7 allows XSS via JavaScript injection in an Asset name.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31500</link><description>Best Practical RT (Request Tracker) 5.0 through 5.0.7 allows XSS via JavaScript injection in an Asset name.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31501 | Best Practical RT (Request Tracker) 5.0 through 5.0.7 allows XSS via JavaScript injection in an RT permalink.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31501</link><description>Best Practical RT (Request Tracker) 5.0 through 5.0.7 allows XSS via JavaScript injection in an RT permalink.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5256 | Open Redirect vulnerability on user unlock path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5256</link><description>SummaryThis advisory addresses an Open Redirection vulnerability in Mautic's user unlocking endpoint. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to redirect legitimate users to malicious websites, potentially leading to phishing attacks or the delivery of exploit kits.

Open Redirection via returnUrl Parameter: An Open Redirection vulnerability exists in the /s/action/unlock/user.user/0 endpoint. The returnUrl parameter, intended for post-action redirection, is not properly validated. This allows an attacker to craft a URL that, when clicked by a user, redirects them to an arbitrary external website controlled by the attacker.

MitigationUpdate Mautic to a version that properly validates or sanitizes the returnUrl parameter to ensure that redirects only occur to trusted, internal URLs or explicitly whitelisted domains.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30087 | Best Practical RT (Request Tracker) 4.4 through 4.4.7 and 5.0 through 5.0.7 allows XSS via injection of crafted parameters in a search URL.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30087</link><description>Best Practical RT (Request Tracker) 4.4 through 4.4.7 and 5.0 through 5.0.7 allows XSS via injection of crafted parameters in a search URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47055 | Segment cloning doesn&amp;#x27;t have a proper permission check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47055</link><description>SummaryThis advisory addresses a security vulnerability in Mautic related to the segment cloning functionality. This vulnerability allows any authenticated user to clone segments without proper authorization checks.

Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) / Missing Authorization: A missing authorization vulnerability exists in the cloneAction of the segment management. This allows an authenticated user to bypass intended permission restrictions and clone segments even if they lack the necessary permissions to create new ones.

MitigationUpdate Mautic to a version that implements proper authorization checks for the cloneAction within the ListController.php. Ensure that users attempting to clone segments possess the appropriate creation permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47057 | User name enumeration possible due to response time difference on password reset form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47057</link><description>SummaryThis advisory addresses a security vulnerability in Mautic related to the "Forget your password" functionality. This vulnerability could be exploited by unauthenticated users to enumerate valid usernames.

User Enumeration via Timing Attack: A user enumeration vulnerability exists in the "Forget your password" functionality. Differences in response times for existing and non-existing users, combined with a lack of request limiting, allow an attacker to determine the existence of usernames through a timing-based attack.

MitigationPlease update to a version that addresses this timing vulnerability, where password reset responses are normalized to respond at the same time regardless of user existence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57336 | Incorrect access control in M2Soft CROWNIX Report &amp; ERS affected v7.x to v7.4.3.599 and v8.x to v8.0.3.79 allows unauthorized attackers to o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57336</link><description>Incorrect access control in M2Soft CROWNIX Report &amp; ERS affected v7.x to v7.4.3.599 and v8.x to v8.0.3.79 allows unauthorized attackers to obtain Administrator account access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57337 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the opcode 500 functionality of M2Soft CROWNIX Report &amp; ERS v5.x to v5.5.14.1070, v7.x to v7.4.3.9...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57337</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the opcode 500 functionality of M2Soft CROWNIX Report &amp; ERS v5.x to v5.5.14.1070, v7.x to v7.4.3.960, and v8.x to v8.2.0.345 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via supplying a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57338 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in M2Soft CROWNIX Report &amp; ERS v5.x to v5.5.14.1070, v7.x to v7.4.3.960, and v8.x to v8.2.0.345 allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57338</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in M2Soft CROWNIX Report &amp; ERS v5.x to v5.5.14.1070, v7.x to v7.4.3.960, and v8.x to v8.2.0.345 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via supplying a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1461 | Vuetify XSS through &amp;#x27;eventMoreText&amp;#x27; prop of VCalendar</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1461</link><description>Improper neutralization of the value of the 'eventMoreText' property of the 'VCalendar' component in Vuetify allows unsanitized HTML to be inserted into the page. This can lead to a  Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) https://owasp.org/www-community/attacks/xss  attack. The vulnerability occurs because the default Vuetify translator will return the translation key as the translation, if it can't find an actual translation.

This issue affects Vuetify versions greater than or equal to 2.0.0 and less than 3.0.0.

Note:
Version 2.x of Vuetify is End-of-Life and will not receive any updates to address this issue. For more information see  here https://v2.vuetifyjs.com/en/about/eol/ .</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48749 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) v11.0.0.0 and before &amp; after v.11.1.25134.03 inserts Sensitive Information into Sent Da...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48749</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) v11.0.0.0 and before &amp; after v.11.1.25134.03 inserts Sensitive Information into Sent Data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32803 | Insecure file permissions can result in confidential information leakage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32803</link><description>In some cases, Kea log files or lease files may be world-readable.
This issue affects Kea versions 2.4.0 through 2.4.1, 2.6.0 through 2.6.2, and 2.7.0 through 2.7.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47748 | Netwrix Directory Manager v.11.0.0.0 and before &amp; after v.11.1.25134.03 contains a hardcoded password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47748</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager v.11.0.0.0 and before &amp; after v.11.1.25134.03 contains a hardcoded password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48747 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) before and including v.11.0.0.0 and after v.11.1.25134.03 has Incorrect Permission Assi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48747</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) before and including v.11.0.0.0 and after v.11.1.25134.03 has Incorrect Permission Assignment for a Critical Resource.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32801 | Loading a malicious hook library can lead to local privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32801</link><description>Kea configuration and API directives can be used to load a malicious hook library.  Many common configurations run Kea as root, leave the API entry points unsecured by default, and/or place the control sockets in insecure paths.
This issue affects Kea versions 2.4.0 through 2.4.1, 2.6.0 through 2.6.2, and 2.7.0 through 2.7.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32802 | Insecure handling of file paths allows multiple local attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32802</link><description>Kea configuration and API directives can be used to overwrite arbitrary files, subject to permissions granted to Kea.  Many common configurations run Kea as root, leave the API entry points unsecured by default, and/or place the control sockets in insecure paths.
This issue affects Kea versions 2.4.0 through 2.4.1, 2.6.0 through 2.6.2, and 2.7.0 through 2.7.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48746 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) v.11.0.0.0 and before, as well as after v.11.1.25134.03 lacks Authentication for a Crit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48746</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) v.11.0.0.0 and before, as well as after v.11.1.25134.03 lacks Authentication for a Critical Function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48929 | The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 implements authentication through a long-lived credential (e.g., not a token with a short expirat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48929</link><description>The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 implements authentication through a long-lived credential (e.g., not a token with a short expiration time) that can be reused at a later date if discovered by an adversary, as exploited in the wild in May 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48930 | The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 stores certain cleartext information in memory, even though memory content may be accessible to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48930</link><description>The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 stores certain cleartext information in memory, even though memory content may be accessible to an adversary through various avenues, as exploited in the wild in May 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48931 | The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 relies on MD5 for password hashing, which opens up various attack possibilities (including rainbo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48931</link><description>The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 relies on MD5 for password hashing, which opens up various attack possibilities (including rainbow tables) with low computational effort.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48927 | The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 configures Spring Boot Actuator with an exposed heap dump endpoint at a /heapdump URI, as exploit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48927</link><description>The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 configures Spring Boot Actuator with an exposed heap dump endpoint at a /heapdump URI, as exploited in the wild in May 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48928 | The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 is based on a JSP application in which the heap content is roughly equivalent to a "core dump" in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48928</link><description>The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 is based on a JSP application in which the heap content is roughly equivalent to a "core dump" in which a password previously sent over HTTP would be included in this dump, as exploited in the wild in May 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48925 | The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 relies on the client side (e.g., the TM SGNL app) to do MD5 hashing, and then accepts the hash as...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48925</link><description>The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 relies on the client side (e.g., the TM SGNL app) to do MD5 hashing, and then accepts the hash as the authentication credential, as exploited in the wild in May 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48926 | The admin panel in the TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 allows attackers to discover usernames, e-mail addresses, passwords, and telep...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48926</link><description>The admin panel in the TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 allows attackers to discover usernames, e-mail addresses, passwords, and telephone numbers, as exploited in the wild in May 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47056 | Mautic does not shield .env files from web traffic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47056</link><description>SummaryThis advisory addresses a security vulnerability in Mautic where sensitive .env configuration files may be directly accessible via a web browser. This exposure could lead to the disclosure of sensitive information, including database credentials, API keys, and other critical system configurations.

Sensitive Information Disclosure via .env File Exposure: The .env file, which typically contains environment variables and sensitive application configurations, is directly accessible via a web browser due to missing web server configurations that restrict access to such files. This allows an unauthenticated attacker to view the contents of this file by simply navigating to its URL.

MitigationUpdate Mautic to the latest Mautic version.

By default, Mautic does not use .env files for production data.

For Apache users: Ensure your web server is configured to respect .htaccess files.

For Nginx users: As Nginx does not inherently support .htaccess files, you must manually add a configuration block to your Nginx server configuration to deny access to .env files. Add the following to your Nginx configuration for the Mautic site:

location ~ /\.env {
    deny all;
}





After modifying your Nginx configuration, remember to reload or restart your Nginx service for the changes to take effect.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5257 | Predictable Page Indexing Might Lead to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5257</link><description>SummaryThis advisory addresses a security vulnerability in Mautic where unpublished page previews could be accessed by unauthenticated users and potentially indexed by search engines. This could lead to the unintended disclosure of draft content or sensitive information.

Unauthorized Access to Unpublished Page Previews: The page preview functionality for unpublished content, accessible via predictable URLs (e.g., /page/preview/1, /page/preview/2), lacked proper authorization checks. This allowed any unauthenticated user to view content that was not yet intended for public release, and allowed search engines to index these private preview URLs, making the content publicly discoverable.

MitigationMautic has patched this vulnerability by enforcing proper permission checks on preview pages. Users should upgrade to the patched version of Mautic or later.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36572 | Dell PowerStore, version(s) 4.0.0.0, contain(s) an Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in the PowerStore image file. A low privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36572</link><description>Dell PowerStore, version(s) 4.0.0.0, contain(s) an Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in the PowerStore image file. A low privileged attacker with remote access, with the knowledge of the hard-coded credentials, could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain unauthorized access based on the hardcoded account's privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45343 | An issue in Tenda W18E v.2.0 v.16.01.0.11 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the editing functionality of the account module i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45343</link><description>An issue in Tenda W18E v.2.0 v.16.01.0.11 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the editing functionality of the account module in the goform/setmodules route.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 15:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38341 | IBM Sterling Secure Proxy information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38341</link><description>IBM Sterling Secure Proxy 6.0.0.0 through 6.0.3.1, 6.1.0.0 through 6.1.0.0, and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.1 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 15:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51453 | IBM Sterling Secure Proxy directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51453</link><description>IBM Sterling Secure Proxy 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.1 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 15:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3357 | IBM Tivoli Monitoring code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3357</link><description>IBM Tivoli Monitoring 6.3.0.7 through 6.3.0.7 Service Pack 19 could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code due to improper validation of an index value of a dynamically allocated array.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 14:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45997 | Sourcecodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System v.1.0 has a file upload vulnerability. An attacker can upload a PHP file disguis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45997</link><description>Sourcecodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System v.1.0 has a file upload vulnerability. An attacker can upload a PHP file disguised as an image by modifying the Content-Type header to image/jpg.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 14:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4134 | Lack of file validation in Avast Business Antivirus for Linux allows writing untrusted update files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4134</link><description>Lack of file validation in do_update_vps in Avast Business Antivirus for Linux 4.5 on Linux allows local user to spoof or tamper with the update file via an unverified file write.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 13:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40651 | Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in Real Easy Store</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40651</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Real Easy Store. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending the victim a malicious URL using the keyword parameter in /index.php?a=search. This vulnerability can be exploited to steal sensitive user data, such as session cookies, or to perform actions on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 13:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48734 | Apache Commons BeanUtils: PropertyUtilsBean does not suppresses an enum&amp;#x27;s declaredClass property by default</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48734</link><description>Improper Access Control vulnerability in Apache Commons.



A special BeanIntrospector class was added in version 1.9.2. This can be used to stop attackers from using the declared class property of Java enum objects to get access to the classloader. However this protection was not enabled by default. PropertyUtilsBean (and consequently BeanUtilsBean) now disallows declared class level property access by default.





Releases 1.11.0 and 2.0.0-M2 address a potential security issue when accessing enum properties in an uncontrolled way. If an application using Commons BeanUtils passes property paths from an external source directly to the getProperty() method of PropertyUtilsBean, an attacker can access the enum’s class loader via the “declaredClass” property available on all Java “enum” objects. Accessing the enum’s “declaredClass” allows remote attackers to access the ClassLoader and execute arbitrary code. The same issue exists with PropertyUtilsBean.getNestedProperty().
Starting in versions 1.11.0 and 2.0.0-M2 a special BeanIntrospector suppresses the “declaredClass” property. Note that this new BeanIntrospector is enabled by default, but you can disable it to regain the old behavior; see section 2.5 of the user's guide and the unit tests.

This issue affects Apache Commons BeanUtils 1.x before 1.11.0, and 2.x before 2.0.0-M2.Users of the artifact commons-beanutils:commons-beanutils

 1.x are recommended to upgrade to version 1.11.0, which fixes the issue.


Users of the artifact org.apache.commons:commons-beanutils2

 2.x are recommended to upgrade to version 2.0.0-M2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 13:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5277 | aws-mcp-server MCP server is vulnerable to command injection. An attacker can craft a prompt that once accessed by the MCP client will run a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5277</link><description>aws-mcp-server MCP server is vulnerable to command injection. An attacker can craft a prompt that once accessed by the MCP client will run arbitrary commands on the host system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 13:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4493 | Improper privilege assignment in PAM JIT privilege sets in Devolutions 
Server allows a PAM user to perform PAM JIT 
requests on unauthorize...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4493</link><description>Improper privilege assignment in PAM JIT privilege sets in Devolutions 
Server allows a PAM user to perform PAM JIT 
requests on unauthorized groups by exploiting a user interface issue.


This issue affects the following versions : 

  *  Devolutions Server 2025.1.3.0 through 2025.1.7.0
  *  Devolutions Server 2024.3.15.0 and earlier</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 13:02:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5299 | SourceCodester Client Database Management System user_order_customer_update.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5299</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Client Database Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /user_order_customer_update.php. The manipulation of the argument uploaded_file_cancelled leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 12:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5297 | SourceCodester Computer Store System main.c Add stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5297</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Computer Store System 1.0. This issue affects the function Add of the file main.c. The manipulation of the argument laptopcompany/RAM/Processor leads to stack-based buffer overflow. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5298 | Campcodes Online Hospital Management System betweendates-detailsreports.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5298</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes Online Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/betweendates-detailsreports.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3864 | Connection pool exhaustion in hackney</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3864</link><description>Hackney fails to properly release HTTP connections to the pool after handling 307 Temporary Redirect responses. Remote attackers can exploit this to exhaust connection pools, causing denial of service in applications using the library.
Fix for this issue has been included in 1.24.0 release.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5295 | FreeFloat FTP Server PORT Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5295</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component PORT Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40673 | Missing Authorization in DinoRANK</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40673</link><description>A Missing Authorization vulnerability has been found in DinoRANK. This 
vulnerability allows an attacker to access invoices of any user via 
accessing endpoint '/facturas/YYYY-MM/SDRYYMM-XXXXX.pdf' because there 
is no access control. The pdf filename can be obtained via OSINT, 
insecure network traffic or brute force.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1753 | Command Injection in LLama-Index CLI in run-llama/llama_index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1753</link><description>LLama-Index CLI version v0.12.20 contains an OS command injection vulnerability. The vulnerability arises from the improper handling of the `--files` argument, which is directly passed into `os.system`. An attacker who controls the content of this argument can inject and execute arbitrary shell commands. This vulnerability can be exploited locally if the attacker has control over the CLI arguments, and remotely if a web application calls the LLama-Index CLI with a user-controlled filename. This issue can lead to arbitrary code execution on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4963 | WP Extended &amp;lt;= 3.0.15 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4963</link><description>The WP Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5287 | Likes and Dislikes Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5287</link><description>The Likes and Dislikes Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'post' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27522 | Apache InLong: JDBC Vulnerability during verification processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27522</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache InLong.

This issue affects Apache InLong: from 1.13.0 through 2.1.0. This vulnerability is a secondary mining bypass for CVE-2024-26579. Users are advised to upgrade to Apache InLong's 2.2.0 or cherry-pick [1] to solve it.

[1] 

 https://github.com/apache/inlong/pull/11732</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27526 | Apache InLong: JDBC Vulnerability For URLEncode and backspace bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27526</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache InLong.

This issue affects Apache InLong: from 1.13.0 through 2.1.0. This vulnerability which can lead to JDBC Vulnerability URLEncdoe and backspace bypass. Users are advised to upgrade to Apache InLong's 2.2.0 or cherry-pick [1] to solve it.

[1]  https://github.com/apache/inlong/pull/11747</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27528 | Apache InLong: JDBC Vulnerability for Invisible Character Bypass Leading to Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27528</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache InLong.

This issue affects Apache InLong: from 1.13.0 through 2.1.0. 

This
vulnerability allows attackers to bypass the security mechanisms of InLong
JDBC and leads to arbitrary file reading. Users are advised to upgrade to Apache InLong's 2.2.0 or cherry-pick [1] to solve it.

[1]  https://github.com/apache/inlong/pull/11747</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22252 | A missing authentication for critical function in Fortinet FortiProxy versions 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, FortiSwitchManager version 7.2.5, and Fo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22252</link><description>A missing authentication for critical function in Fortinet FortiProxy versions 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, FortiSwitchManager version 7.2.5, and FortiOS versions 7.4.4 through 7.4.6 and version 7.6.0 may allow an attacker with knowledge of an existing admin account to access the device as a valid admin via an authentication bypass.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24473 | A exposure of sensitive system information to an unauthorized control sphere in Fortinet FortiClientWindows versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.1 may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24473</link><description>A exposure of sensitive system information to an unauthorized control sphere in Fortinet FortiClientWindows versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.1 may allow an unauthorized remote attacker to view application information via navigation to a hosted webpage, if Windows is configured to accept incoming connections to port 8053 (non-default setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46777 | A insertion of sensitive information into log file in Fortinet FortiPortal versions 7.4.0, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.5, and versions 7.0.0 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46777</link><description>A insertion of sensitive information into log file in Fortinet FortiPortal versions 7.4.0, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.5, and versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.9 may allow an authenticated attacker with at least read-only admin permissions to view encrypted secrets via the FortiPortal System Log.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47294 | A integer overflow or wraparound in Fortinet FortiOS versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.7, versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.14 may allow a remote unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47294</link><description>A integer overflow or wraparound in Fortinet FortiOS versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.7, versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.14 may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to crash the csfd daemon via a specially crafted request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54020 | A missing authorization in Fortinet FortiManager versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.1, and versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.7 may allow an authenticated a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54020</link><description>A missing authorization in Fortinet FortiManager versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.1, and versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.7 may allow an authenticated attacker to overwrite global threat feeds via crafted update requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 07:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25251 | An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability [CWE-863] in FortiClient Mac 7.4.0 through 7.4.2, 7.2.0 through 7.2.8, 7.0.0 through 7.0.14 may all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25251</link><description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability [CWE-863] in FortiClient Mac 7.4.0 through 7.4.2, 7.2.0 through 7.2.8, 7.0.0 through 7.0.14 may allow a local attacker to escalate privileges via crafted XPC messages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 07:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47295 | A buffer over-read in Fortinet FortiOS versions 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.7, and versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.14 may all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47295</link><description>A buffer over-read in Fortinet FortiOS versions 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.7, and versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.14 may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to crash the FGFM daemon via a specially crafted request, under rare conditions that are outside of the attacker's control.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 07:56:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5082 | WP Attachments &amp;lt;= 5.0.12 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via attachment_id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5082</link><description>The WP Attachments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘attachment_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 07:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4009 | Unauthenticated Arbitrary Command Injection in Evertz SVDN</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4009</link><description>The Evertz SVDN 3080ipx-10G is a High Bandwidth Ethernet Switching Fabric for Video Application. This device exposes a web management interface on port 80. This web management interface can be used by administrators to control product
features, setup network switching, and register license among other features. The application has been developed in PHP with the webEASY SDK, also named ‘ewb’ by Evertz.

This web interface has two endpoints that are vulnerable to arbitrary command injection and the authentication mechanism has a flaw leading to authentication bypass.

Remote unauthenticated attackers can gain arbitrary command execution with elevated privileges ( root ) on affected devices.

This level of access could lead to serious business impact such as the interruption of media streaming, modification of media being streamed, alteration of closed captions being generated, among others.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 07:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4947 | QUIC certificate check skip with wolfSSL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4947</link><description>libcurl accidentally skips the certificate verification for QUIC connections when connecting to a host specified as an IP address in the URL. Therefore, it does not detect impostors or man-in-the-middle attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 06:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5025 | No QUIC certificate pinning with wolfSSL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5025</link><description>libcurl supports *pinning* of the server certificate public key for HTTPS transfers. Due to an omission, this check is not performed when connecting with QUIC for HTTP/3, when the TLS backend is wolfSSL. Documentation says the option works with wolfSSL, failing to specify that it does not for QUIC and HTTP/3. Since pinning makes the transfer succeed if the pin is fine, users could unwittingly connect to an impostor server without noticing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 06:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4800 | MasterStudy LMS Pro &amp;lt;= 4.7.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4800</link><description>The MasterStudy LMS Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to a missing file type validation in the stm_lms_add_assignment_attachment function in all versions up to, and including, 4.7.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server, which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 05:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25025 | IBM Security Guardium information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25025</link><description>IBM Security Guardium 12.0 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 02:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25026 | IBM Security Guardium information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25026</link><description>IBM Security Guardium 12.0 could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive information due to an incorrect authentication check.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 02:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25029 | IBM Security Guardium information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25029</link><description>IBM Security Guardium 12.0 could allow a privileged user to download any file on the system due to improper escaping of input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 02:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45094 | IBM DS8900F and DS8A00 Hardware Management Console (HMC) cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45094</link><description>IBM DS8900F and DS8A00 Hardware Management Console (HMC) is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows a privileged user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 22:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2826 | n affected platforms running Arista EOS, ACL policies may not be enforced. IPv4 ingress ACL, MAC ingress ACL, or IPv6 standard ingress ACL enabled on one or more ethernet or LAG interfaces may result in ACL policies not being enforced for ingress packets.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2826</link><description>n affected platforms running Arista EOS, ACL policies may not be enforced. IPv4 ingress ACL, MAC ingress ACL, or IPv6 standard ingress ACL enabled on one or more ethernet or LAG interfaces may result in ACL policies not being enforced for ingress packets. This can cause incoming packets to incorrectly be allowed or denied. The two symptoms of this issue on the affected release and platform are:

  *  Packets which should be permitted may be dropped and,
  *  Packets which should be dropped may be permitted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 22:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11185 | On affected platforms running Arista EOS, ingress traffic on Layer 2 ports may, under certain conditions, be improperly forwarded to ports associated with different VLANs, resulting in a breach of VLAN isolation and segmentation boundaries.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11185</link><description>On affected platforms running Arista EOS, ingress traffic on Layer 2 ports may, under certain conditions, be improperly forwarded to ports associated with different VLANs, resulting in a breach of VLAN isolation and segmentation boundaries.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 22:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2796 | On affected platforms with hardware IPSec support running Arista EOS with IPsec enabled and anti-replay protection configured, EOS may exhibit unexpected behavior in specific cases. Received duplicate encrypted packets, which should be dropped under normal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2796</link><description>On affected platforms with hardware IPSec support running Arista EOS with IPsec enabled and anti-replay protection configured, EOS may exhibit unexpected behavior in specific cases. Received duplicate encrypted packets, which should be dropped under normal anti-replay protection, will instead be forwarded due to this vulnerability.

Note: this issue does not affect VXLANSec or MACSec encryption functionality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 22:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32440 | NetAlertX Vulnerable to Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32440</link><description>NetAlertX is a network, presence scanner and alert framework. Prior to version 25.4.14, it is possible to bypass the authentication mechanism of NetAlertX to update settings without authentication. An attacker can trigger sensitive functions within util.php by sending crafted requests to /index.php. This issue has been patched in version 25.4.14.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 22:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40911 | Net::CIDR::Set versions 0.10 through 0.13 for Perl does not properly consider leading zero characters in IP CIDR address strings, which could allow attackers to bypass access control that is based on IP addresses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40911</link><description>Net::CIDR::Set versions 0.10 through 0.13 for Perl does not properly handle leading zero characters in IP CIDR address strings, which could allow attackers to bypass access control that is based on IP addresses.

Leading zeros are used to indicate octal numbers, which can confuse users who are intentionally using octal notation, as well as users who believe they are using decimal notation.

Net::CIDR::Set used code from Net::CIDR::Lite, which had a similar vulnerability CVE-2021-47154.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5198 | Stackrox: xss in stackrox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5198</link><description>A flaw was found in Stackrox, where it is vulnerable to Cross-site scripting (XSS) if the script code is included in a small subset of table cells. The only known potential exploit is if the script is included in the name of a Kubernetes “Role” object* that is applied to a secured cluster. This object can be used by a user with access to the cluster or through a compromised third-party product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5222 | Icu: stack buffer overflow in the srbroot::addtag function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5222</link><description>A stack buffer overflow was found in Internationl components for unicode (ICU ). While running the genrb binary, the 'subtag' struct overflowed at the SRBRoot::addTag function. This issue may lead to memory corruption and local arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5278 | Coreutils: heap buffer under-read in gnu coreutils sort via key specification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5278</link><description>A flaw was found in GNU Coreutils. The sort utility's begfield() function is vulnerable to a heap buffer under-read. The program may access memory outside the allocated buffer if a user runs a crafted command using the traditional key format. A malicious input could lead to a crash or leak sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5063 | Use after free in Compositing in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.55 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5063</link><description>Use after free in Compositing in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.55 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5064 | Inappropriate implementation in Background Fetch API in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.55 allowed a remote attacker to leak cross-origin ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5064</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Background Fetch API in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.55 allowed a remote attacker to leak cross-origin data via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5065 | Inappropriate implementation in FileSystemAccess API in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.55 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5065</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in FileSystemAccess API in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.55 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5066 | Inappropriate implementation in Messages in Google Chrome on Android prior to 137.0.7151.55 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5066</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Messages in Google Chrome on Android prior to 137.0.7151.55 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5067 | Inappropriate implementation in Tab Strip in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.55 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5067</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Tab Strip in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.55 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5280 | Out of bounds write in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.55 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5280</link><description>Out of bounds write in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.55 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5281 | Inappropriate implementation in BFCache in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.55 allowed a remote attacker to potentially obtain user informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5281</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in BFCache in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.55 allowed a remote attacker to potentially obtain user information via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5283 | Use after free in libvpx in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.55 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5283</link><description>Use after free in libvpx in Google Chrome prior to 137.0.7151.55 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5279 | Issue with Amazon Redshift Python Connector and the BrowserAzureOAuth2CredentialsProvider plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5279</link><description>When the Amazon Redshift Python Connector is configured with the BrowserAzureOAuth2CredentialsProvider plugin, the driver skips the SSL certificate validation step for the Identity Provider. An insecure connection could allow an actor to intercept the token exchange process and retrieve an access token.

This issue has been addressed in driver version 2.1.7. Users should upgrade to address this issue and ensure any forked or derivative code is patched to incorporate the new fixes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46173 | code-projects Online Exam Mastering System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the name field in the feedback form.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46173</link><description>code-projects Online Exam Mastering System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the name field in the feedback form.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 19:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45529 | An arbitrary file read vulnerability in the ReadTextAsynchronous function of SSCMS v7.3.1 allows attackers to read arbitrary files via sendi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45529</link><description>An arbitrary file read vulnerability in the ReadTextAsynchronous function of SSCMS v7.3.1 allows attackers to read arbitrary files via sending a crafted GET request to /cms/templates/templatesAssetsEditor.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 19:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13966 | ZKTeco BioTime default password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13966</link><description>ZKTeco BioTime allows unauthenticated attackers to enumerate usernames and log in as any user with a password unchanged from the default value '123456'. Users should change their passwords (located under the Attendance Settings tab as "Self-Password").</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 18:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45475 | maccms10 v2025.1000.4047 is vulnerable to Server-Side request forgery (SSRF) in Friend Link Management.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45475</link><description>maccms10 v2025.1000.4047 is vulnerable to Server-Side request forgery (SSRF) in Friend Link Management.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 17:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5252 | PHPGurukul News Portal Project edit-subadmin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5252</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul News Portal Project 4.1. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit-subadmin.php. The manipulation of the argument emailid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 17:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49197 | An issue was discovered in Wi-Fi in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 980, 850, 1080, 1280, 1330, 1380, 1480, W920, W93...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49197</link><description>An issue was discovered in Wi-Fi in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 980, 850, 1080, 1280, 1330, 1380, 1480, W920, W930, and W1000. Lack of a boundary check in STOP_KEEP_ALIVE_OFFLOAD leads to out-of-bounds access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 17:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49196 | An issue was discovered in the GPU in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1480 and 2400. Type confusion leads to a Denial of Service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49196</link><description>An issue was discovered in the GPU in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1480 and 2400. Type confusion leads to a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 17:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22377 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22377</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, 9110, W920, W930, W1000, Modem 5123, Modem 5300, Modem 5400. A Heap-based Out-of-Bounds Write exists in the GPRS protocol implementation because of a mismatch between the actual length of the payload and the length declared within the payload.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 17:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5250 | PHPGurukul News Portal Project edit-category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5250</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul News Portal Project 4.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-category.php. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 17:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5251 | PHPGurukul News Portal Project edit-subcategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5251</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul News Portal Project 4.1. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit-subcategory.php. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 17:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23247 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary, where a failure to check the length of a buffer coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23247</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary, where a failure to check the length of a buffer could allow a user to cause the tool to crash or execute arbitrary code by passing in a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 16:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48057 | Icinga 2 certificate renewal might incorrectly renew an invalid certificate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48057</link><description>Icinga 2 is a monitoring system which checks the availability of network resources, notifies users of outages, and generates performance data for reporting. Prior to versions 2.12.12, 2.13.12, and 2.14.6, the VerifyCertificate() function can be tricked into incorrectly treating certificates as valid. This allows an attacker to send a malicious certificate request that is then treated as a renewal of an already existing certificate, resulting in the attacker obtaining a valid certificate that can be used to impersonate trusted nodes. This only occurs when Icinga 2 is built with OpenSSL older than version 1.1.0. This issue has been patched in versions 2.12.12, 2.13.12, and 2.14.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 16:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5249 | PHPGurukul News Portal Project add-category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5249</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul News Portal Project 4.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/add-category.php. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 16:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5248 | PHPGurukul Company Visitor Management System bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5248</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Company Visitor Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 16:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56193 | There is a possible disclosure of Bluetooth adapter details due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local information disclosure wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56193</link><description>There is a possible disclosure of Bluetooth adapter details due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 15:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27700 | There is a possible bypass of carrier restrictions due to an unusual root cause. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no ad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27700</link><description>There is a possible bypass of carrier restrictions due to an unusual root cause. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 15:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27701 | In the function process_crypto_cmd, the values of ptrs[i] can be potentially equal to NULL which is valid value after calling slice_map_arra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27701</link><description>In the function process_crypto_cmd, the values of ptrs[i] can be potentially equal to NULL which is valid value after calling slice_map_array(). Later this values will be derefenced without prior NULL check, which can lead to local Temporary DoS or OOB Read, leading to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 15:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48370 | auth-js Vulnerable to Insecure Path Routing from Malformed User Input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48370</link><description>auth-js is an isomorphic Javascript library for Supabase Auth. Prior to version 2.69.1, the library functions getUserById, deleteUser, updateUserById, listFactors and deleteFactor did not require the user supplied values to be valid UUIDs. This could lead to a URL path traversal, resulting in the wrong API function being called. Implementations that follow security best practice and validate user controlled inputs, such as the userId are not affected by this. This issue has been patched in version 2.69.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 15:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2236 | Exposure of Sensitive System Information vulnerability during configuration affecting OpenText Advanced Authentication.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2236</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in OpenText Advanced Authentication allows Information Elicitation. The vulnerability could reveal sensitive information while managing and configuring of the external services.

This issue affects Advanced Authentication versions before 6.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 15:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48383 | Django-Select2 Vulnerable to Widget Instance Secret Cache Key Leaking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48383</link><description>Django-Select2 is a Django integration for Select2. Prior to version 8.4.1, instances of HeavySelect2Mixin subclasses like the ModelSelect2MultipleWidget and ModelSelect2Widget can leak secret access tokens across requests. This can allow users to access restricted query sets and restricted data. This issue has been patched in version 8.4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 15:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5247 | Gowabby HFish url.go LoadUrl improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5247</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Gowabby HFish 0.1. This issue affects the function LoadUrl of the file \view\url.go. The manipulation of the argument r leads to improper authentication. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 15:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3704 | WordPress Volunteer Sign Up Sheets plugin &amp;lt; 5.5.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3704</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DBAR Productions Volunteer Sign Up Sheets allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Volunteer Sign Up Sheets: from n/a before 5.5.5.

The patch is available exclusively on GitHub at  https://github.com/dbarproductions/pta-volunteer-sign-up-sheets , as the vendor encounters difficulties using SVN to deploy to the WordPress.org repository.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 14:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5245 | GNU Binutils objdump debug.c debug_type_samep memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5245</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in GNU Binutils up to 2.44. This affects the function debug_type_samep of the file /binutils/debug.c of the component objdump. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 14:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5246 | Campcodes Online Hospital Management System query-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5246</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Campcodes Online Hospital Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /hms/admin/query-details.php. The manipulation of the argument adminremark leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 14:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48796 | Gimp: stack-based buffer overflows in file-ico</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48796</link><description>A flaw was found in GIMP. The GIMP ani_load_image() function is vulnerable to a stack-based overflow. If a user opens.ANI files, GIMP may be used to store more information than the capacity allows. This flaw allows a malicious ANI file to trigger arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 14:35:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48797 | Gimp: multiple heap buffer overflows in tga parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48797</link><description>A flaw was found in GIMP when processing certain TGA image files. If a user opens one of these image files that has been specially crafted by an attacker, GIMP can be tricked into making serious memory errors, potentially leading to crashes and causing a heap buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 14:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48798 | Gimp: multiple use after free in xcf parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48798</link><description>A flaw was found in GIMP when processing XCF image files. If a user opens one of these image files that has been specially crafted by an attacker, GIMP can be tricked into making serious memory errors, potentially leading to crashes and causing use-after-free issues.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 14:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5244 | GNU Binutils ld elflink.c elf_gc_sweep memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5244</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GNU Binutils up to 2.44. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function elf_gc_sweep of the file bfd/elflink.c of the component ld. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.45 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 13:22:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5262 | A double-free could have occurred in `vpx_codec_enc_init_multi` after a failed allocation when initializing the encoder for WebRTC. This cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5262</link><description>A double-free could have occurred in `vpx_codec_enc_init_multi` after a failed allocation when initializing the encoder for WebRTC. This could have caused memory corruption and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 139, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.24, and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5263 | Error handling for script execution was incorrectly isolated from web content, which could have allowed cross-origin leak attacks. This vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5263</link><description>Error handling for script execution was incorrectly isolated from web content, which could have allowed cross-origin leak attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 139, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.24, and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5264 | Due to insufficient escaping of the newline character in the “Copy as cURL” feature, an attacker could trick a user into using this command,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5264</link><description>Due to insufficient escaping of the newline character in the “Copy as cURL” feature, an attacker could trick a user into using this command, potentially leading to local code execution on the user's system. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 139, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.24, and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5265 | Due to insufficient escaping of the ampersand character in the “Copy as cURL” feature, an attacker could trick a user into using this comman...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5265</link><description>Due to insufficient escaping of the ampersand character in the “Copy as cURL” feature, an attacker could trick a user into using this command, potentially leading to local code execution on the user's system.
*This bug only affects Firefox for Windows. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 139, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.24, and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5266 | Script elements loading cross-origin resources generated load and error events which leaked information enabling XS-Leaks attacks. This vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5266</link><description>Script elements loading cross-origin resources generated load and error events which leaked information enabling XS-Leaks attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 139 and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5267 | A clickjacking vulnerability could have been used to trick a user into leaking saved payment card details to a malicious page. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5267</link><description>A clickjacking vulnerability could have been used to trick a user into leaking saved payment card details to a malicious page. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 139 and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5268 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 138, Thunderbird 138, Firefox ESR 128.10, and Thunderbird 128.10. Some of these bugs showed evidence o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5268</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 138, Thunderbird 138, Firefox ESR 128.10, and Thunderbird 128.10. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 139 and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5269 | Memory safety bug present in Firefox ESR 128.10, and Thunderbird 128.10. This bug showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5269</link><description>Memory safety bug present in Firefox ESR 128.10, and Thunderbird 128.10. This bug showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort this could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 128.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5270 | In certain cases, SNI could have been sent unencrypted even when encrypted DNS was enabled. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 139.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5270</link><description>In certain cases, SNI could have been sent unencrypted even when encrypted DNS was enabled. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 139.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5271 | Previewing a response in Devtools ignored CSP headers, which could have allowed content injection attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5271</link><description>Previewing a response in Devtools ignored CSP headers, which could have allowed content injection attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 139.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5272 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 138 and Thunderbird 138. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5272</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 138 and Thunderbird 138. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 139.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5117 | Property 1.0.5 - 1.0.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Author+) Privilege Escalation via property_package_user_role Metadata in PayPal Registration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5117</link><description>The Property plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check on the use of the property_package_user_role metadata in versions 1.0.5 to 1.0.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author‐level access and above, to elevate their privileges to that of an administrator by creating a package post whose property_package_user_role is set to administrator and then submitting the PayPal registration form.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 11:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4412 | TCC Bypass via Dylib Loading in Viscosity.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4412</link><description>On macOS systems, by utilizing a Launch Agent and loading the viscosity_openvpn process from the application bundle, it is possible to load a dynamic library with Viscosity's TCC (Transparency, Consent, and Control) identity. The acquired resource access is limited without entitlements such as access to the camera or microphone. Only user-granted permissions for file resources apply. Access to other resources beyond granted-permissions requires user interaction with a system prompt asking for permission.

This issue was fixed in version 1.11.5 of Viscosity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 10:20:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41653 | Weidmueller: Denial-of-Service Vulnerability in the web server functionality of Industrial Ethernet Switches</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41653</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit a denial-of-service vulnerability in the device's web server functionality by sending a specially crafted HTTP request with a malicious header, potentially causing the server to crash or become unresponsive.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 08:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41649 | Weidmueller: Out-of-Bounds Write Vulnerability in Industrial Ethernet Switches</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41649</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit insufficient input validation to write data beyond the bounds of a buffer, potentially leading to a denial-of-service condition for the devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 08:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41650 | Weidmueller: Denial-of-Service Vulnerability in Industrial Ethernet Switches</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41650</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit input validation in cmd services of the devices, allowing them to disrupt system operations and potentially cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 08:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41651 | Weidmueller: Missing Authentication Vulnerability in Industrial Ethernet Switches</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41651</link><description>Due to missing authentication on a critical function of the devices an unauthenticated remote attacker can execute arbitrary commands, potentially enabling unauthorized upload or download of configuration files and leading to full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 08:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41652 | Weidmueller: Authentication Bypass Vulnerability in Industrial Ethernet Switches</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41652</link><description>The devices are vulnerable to an authentication bypass due to flaws in the authorization mechanism. An unauthenticated remote attacker could exploit this weakness by performing brute-force attacks to guess valid credentials or by using MD5 collision techniques to forge authentication hashes, potentially compromising the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 08:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2407 | Missing Authentication &amp;amp; Authorization in Web-API allows adversary unrestricted access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2407</link><description>Missing Authentication &amp; Authorization in Web-API in Mobatime AMX MTAPI v6 on IIS allows adversaries to unrestricted access via the network. The vulnerability is fixed in Version 1.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 08:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23393 | Reflected XSS in spacewalk-java</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23393</link><description>A Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in  spacewalk-java allows execution of arbitrary Javascript code on users machines.This issue affects Container suse/manager/5.0/x86_64/server:5.0.4.7.19.1: from ? before 5.0.24-150600.3.25.1; SUSE Manager Server Module 4.3: from ? before 4.3.85-150400.3.105.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 07:30:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38866 | Livestatus Injection in dynmaps</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38866</link><description>Improper neutralization of input in Nagvis before version 1.9.47 which can lead to livestatus injection</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 07:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47090 | XSS via WYSIWYG editor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47090</link><description>Improper neutralization of input in Nagvis before version 1.9.47 which can lead to XSS</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 07:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5232 | PHPGurukul Student Study Center Management System report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5232</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Student Study Center Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/report.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 05:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48382 | Fess has Insecure Temporary File Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48382</link><description>Fess is a deployable Enterprise Search Server. Prior to version 14.19.2, the createTempFile() method in org.codelibs.fess.helper.SystemHelper creates temporary files without explicitly setting restrictive permissions. This could lead to potential information disclosure, allowing unauthorized local users to access sensitive data contained in these files. This issue primarily affects environments where Fess is deployed in a shared or multi-user context. Typical single-user or isolated deployments have minimal or negligible practical impact. This issue has been patched in version 14.19.2. A workaround for this issue involves ensuring local access to the environment running Fess is restricted to trusted users only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 04:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5231 | PHPGurukul Company Visitor Management System forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5231</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Company Visitor Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 04:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48054 | Radashi Vulnerable to Improperly Controlled Modification of Object Prototype Attributes (&amp;#x27;Prototype Pollution&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48054</link><description>Radashi is a TypeScript utility toolkit. Prior to version 12.5.1, the set function within the Radashi library is vulnerable to prototype pollution. If an attacker can control parts of the path argument to the set function, they could potentially modify the prototype of all objects in the JavaScript runtime, leading to unexpected behavior, denial of service, or even remote code execution in some specific scenarios. This issue has been patched in version 12.5.1. A workaround for this issue involves sanitizing the path argument provided to the set function to ensure that no part of the path string is __proto__, prototype, or constructor.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 04:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48827 | vBulletin 5.0.0 through 5.7.5 and 6.0.0 through 6.0.3 allows unauthenticated users to invoke protected API controllers' methods when running...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48827</link><description>vBulletin 5.0.0 through 5.7.5 and 6.0.0 through 6.0.3 allows unauthenticated users to invoke protected API controllers' methods when running on PHP 8.1 or later, as demonstrated by the /api.php?method=protectedMethod pattern.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 04:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48828 | Certain vBulletin versions might allow attackers to execute arbitrary PHP code by abusing Template Conditionals in the template engine. By c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48828</link><description>Certain vBulletin versions might allow attackers to execute arbitrary PHP code by abusing Template Conditionals in the template engine. By crafting template code in an alternative PHP function invocation syntax, such as the "var_dump"("test") syntax, attackers can bypass security checks and execute arbitrary PHP code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 04:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5230 | PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System bwdates-report-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5230</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/bwdates-report-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 04:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48742 | The installer in SIGB PMB before 8.0.1.2 allows remote code execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48742</link><description>The installer in SIGB PMB before 8.0.1.2 allows remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 03:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5229 | Campcodes Online Hospital Management System view-patient.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5229</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Hospital Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/view-patient.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 03:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26211 | Gibbon before 29.0.00 allows CSRF.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26211</link><description>Gibbon before 29.0.00 allows CSRF.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 03:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5227 | PHPGurukul Small CRM manage-tickets.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5227</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Small CRM 3.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/manage-tickets.php. The manipulation of the argument aremark leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 03:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5228 | D-Link DI-8100 jhttpd login.cgi httpd_get_parm stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5228</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-8100 up to 20250523. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function httpd_get_parm of the file /login.cgi of the component jhttpd. The manipulation of the argument notify leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can only be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 03:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48743 | SIGB PMB before 8.0.1.2 allows SQL injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48743</link><description>SIGB PMB before 8.0.1.2 allows SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 03:04:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48744 | In SIGB PMB before 8.0.1.2, attackers can achieve Local File Inclusion and remote code execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48744</link><description>In SIGB PMB before 8.0.1.2, attackers can achieve Local File Inclusion and remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 03:04:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5225 | Campcodes Advanced Online Voting System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5225</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes Advanced Online Voting System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument voter leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 03:04:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5226 | PHPGurukul Small CRM change-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5226</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Small CRM 3.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/change-password.php. The manipulation of the argument oldpass leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 03:04:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4682 | Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp;amp; Templates &amp;lt;= 5.4.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Slider and Post Carousel Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4682</link><description>The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HTML attributes in Slider and Post Carousel widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 03:04:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4683 | MStore API – Create Native Android &amp;amp; iOS Apps On The Cloud &amp;lt;= 4.17.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Posts Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4683</link><description>The MStore API – Create Native Android &amp; iOS Apps On The Cloud plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the create_blog function in all versions up to, and including, 4.17.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create new posts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 03:04:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5221 | FreeFloat FTP Server QUOTE Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5221</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the component QUOTE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 03:04:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5224 | Campcodes Online Hospital Management System add-doctor.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5224</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Online Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/add-doctor.php. The manipulation of the argument Doctorspecialization leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 03:04:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33079 | IBM Controller information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33079</link><description>IBM Controller 11.0.0, 11.0.1, and 11.1.0 application could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive credentials that may be inadvertently included within the source code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 03:04:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5220 | FreeFloat FTP Server GET Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5220</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component GET Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 03:04:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5218 | FreeFloat FTP Server LITERAL Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5218</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component LITERAL Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 01:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5219 | FreeFloat FTP Server ASCII Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5219</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component ASCII Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 01:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5216 | PHPGurukul Student Record System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5216</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 01:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5217 | FreeFloat FTP Server RMDIR Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5217</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component RMDIR Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 01:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5215 | D-Link DCS-5020L ptdc.cgi websReadEvent stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5215</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in D-Link DCS-5020L 1.01_B2. This affects the function websReadEvent of the file /rame/ptdc.cgi. The manipulation of the argument Authorization leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 01:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>