<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 12:54:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-27192 | WordPress Configure SMTP Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27192</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Scott Reilly Configure SMTP allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Configure SMTP: from n/a through 3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 12:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27193 | WordPress PayU India plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27193</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PayU PayU India allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects PayU India: from n/a through 3.8.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 12:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27196 | WordPress postMash – custom post order plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27196</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Joel Starnes postMash – custom post order allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects postMash – custom post order: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 12:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6725 | Openstack-designate: bind keys are world readable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6725</link><description>An access-control flaw was found in the OpenStack Designate component where private configuration information including access keys to BIND were improperly made world readable. A malicious attacker with access to any container could exploit this flaw to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 12:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23944 | Apache ZooKeeper: Information disclosure in persistent watcher handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23944</link><description>Information disclosure in persistent watchers handling in Apache ZooKeeper due to missing ACL check. It allows an attacker to monitor child znodes by attaching a persistent watcher (addWatch command) to a parent which the attacker has already access to. ZooKeeper server doesn't do ACL check when the persistent watcher is triggered and as a consequence, the full path of znodes that a watch event gets triggered upon is exposed to the owner of the watcher. It's important to note that only the path is exposed by this vulnerability, not the data of znode, but since znode path can contain sensitive information like user name or login ID, this issue is potentially critical.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.9.2, 3.8.4 which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 10:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27987 | WordPress Give plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27987</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GiveWP Give allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Give: from n/a through 3.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 10:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28752 | Apache CXF SSRF Vulnerability using the Aegis databinding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28752</link><description>A SSRF vulnerability using the Aegis DataBinding in versions of Apache CXF before 4.0.4, 3.6.3 and 3.5.8 allows an attacker to perform SSRF style attacks on webservices that take at least one parameter of any type. Users of other data bindings (including the default databinding) are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 10:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2490 | Tenda AC18 openSchedWifi setSchedWifi stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2490</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setSchedWifi of the file /goform/openSchedWifi. The manipulation of the argument schedStartTime/schedEndTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256897 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2445 | Reflected XSS in Mattermost Jira plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2445</link><description>Mattermost Jira plugin versions shipped with Mattermost versions 8.1.x before 8.1.10, 9.2.x before 9.2.6, 9.3.x before 9.3.2, and 9.4.x before 9.4.3 fail to escape user-controlled outputs when generating HTML pages, which allows an attacker to perform reflected cross-site scripting attacks against the users of the Mattermost server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2446 | Mattermost versions 8.1.x before 8.1.10, 9.2.x before 9.2.6, 9.3.x before 9.3.2, and 9.4.x before 9.4.3 fail to limit the number of @-mentio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2446</link><description>Mattermost versions 8.1.x before 8.1.10, 9.2.x before 9.2.6, 9.3.x before 9.3.2, and 9.4.x before 9.4.3 fail to limit the number of @-mentions processed per message, allowing an authenticated attacker to crash the client applications of other users via large, crafted messages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:22:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2450 | Mattermost versions 8.1.x before 8.1.10, 9.2.x before 9.2.6, 9.3.x before 9.3.2, and 9.4.x before 9.4.3 fail to correctly verify account own...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2450</link><description>Mattermost versions 8.1.x before 8.1.10, 9.2.x before 9.2.6, 9.3.x before 9.3.2, and 9.4.x before 9.4.3 fail to correctly verify account ownership when switching from email to SAML authentication, allowing an authenticated attacker to take over other user accounts via a crafted switch request under specific conditions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:22:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24975 |  Denial of Service for mobile app users due to automatic code highlighting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24975</link><description>Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in Mattermost Mobile versions before 2.13.0 fails to limit the size of the code block that will be processed by the syntax highlighter, allowing an attacker to send a very large code block and crash the mobile app.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28053 | Resource Exhaustion via the Invitation Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28053</link><description>Resource Exhaustion in Mattermost Server versions 8.1.x before 8.1.10 fails to limit the size of the payload that can be read and parsed allowing an attacker to send a very large email payload and crash the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2488 | Tenda AC18 SetPptpServerCfg formSetPPTPServer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2488</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function formSetPPTPServer of the file /goform/SetPptpServerCfg. The manipulation of the argument startIP leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256895. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2489 | Tenda AC18 SetNetControlList formSetQosBand stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2489</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. Affected is the function formSetQosBand of the file /goform/SetNetControlList. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256896. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2487 | Tenda AC18 SetOnlineDevName formSetDeviceName stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2487</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formSetDeviceName of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName. The manipulation of the argument devName/mac leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256894 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 08:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2486 | Tenda AC18 QuickIndex formQuickIndex stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2486</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function formQuickIndex of the file /goform/QuickIndex. The manipulation of the argument PPPOEPassword leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256893 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 08:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28353 | There is a command injection vulnerability in the TRENDnet TEW-827DRU router with firmware version 2.10B01. An attacker can inject commands ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28353</link><description>There is a command injection vulnerability in the TRENDnet TEW-827DRU router with firmware version 2.10B01. An attacker can inject commands into the post request parameters usapps.config.smb_admin_name in the apply.cgi interface, thereby gaining root shell privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28354 | There is a command injection vulnerability in the TRENDnet TEW-827DRU router with firmware version 2.10B01. An attacker can inject commands ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28354</link><description>There is a command injection vulnerability in the TRENDnet TEW-827DRU router with firmware version 2.10B01. An attacker can inject commands into the post request parameters usapps.@smb[%d].username in the apply.cgi interface, thereby gaining root shell privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27756 | An issue in GLPI v.10.0.12 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive informat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27756</link><description>An issue in GLPI v.10.0.12 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the title field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:04:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2483 | Surya2Developer Hostel Management Service Password Change change-password.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2483</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Surya2Developer Hostel Management Service 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /change-password.php of the component Password Change Handler. The manipulation of the argument oldpassword leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256889 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:04:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2485 | Tenda AC18 SetSpeedWan formSetSpeedWan stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2485</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formSetSpeedWan of the file /goform/SetSpeedWan. The manipulation of the argument speed_dir leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256892. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:04:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1795 | The HUSKY – Products Filter for WooCommerce Professional plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'name' parameter in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1795</link><description>The HUSKY – Products Filter for WooCommerce Professional plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'name' parameter in the woof shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.5.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1796 | The HUSKY – Products Filter for WooCommerce Professional plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1796</link><description>The HUSKY – Products Filter for WooCommerce Professional plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'woof' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as 'swoof_slug'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2399 | The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2399</link><description>The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.23 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2482 | Surya2Developer Hostel Management Service HTTP POST Request check_availability.php observable response discrepancy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2482</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Surya2Developer Hostel Management Service 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /check_availability.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument oldpassword leads to observable response discrepancy. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256891.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2480 | MHA Sistemas arMHAzena Executa Page sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2480</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in MHA Sistemas arMHAzena 9.6.0.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Executa Page. The manipulation of the argument Companhia/Planta/Agente de/Agente até leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256888. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2481 | Surya2Developer Hostel Management System manage-students.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2481</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Surya2Developer Hostel Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/manage-students.php. The manipulation of the argument del leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256890 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25227 | SQL Injection vulnerability in ABO.CMS version 5.8, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial of service (DoS), esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25227</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in ABO.CMS version 5.8, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial of service (DoS), escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information via the tb_login parameter in admin login page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 05:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2478 | BradWenqiang HR Background Management register selectAll sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2478</link><description>A vulnerability was found in BradWenqiang HR 2.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function selectAll of the file /bishe/register of the component Background Management. The manipulation of the argument userName leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256886 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 05:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2479 | MHA Sistemas arMHAzena Cadastro Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2479</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in MHA Sistemas arMHAzena 9.6.0.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Cadastro Page. The manipulation of the argument Query leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256887. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 05:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2180 | Zemana AntiLogger v2.74.204.664 - Kernel Memory Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2180</link><description>Zemana AntiLogger v2.74.204.664 is vulnerable to a Memory Information Leak vulnerability by triggering the 0x80002020 IOCTL code of the zam64.sys and zamguard64.sys drivers</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 04:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2204 | Zemana AntiLogger v2.74.204.664 - Denial of Service (DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2204</link><description>Zemana AntiLogger v2.74.204.664 is vulnerable to a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability by triggering the 0x80002004 and 0x80002010 IOCTL codes of the zam64.sys and zamguard64.sys drivers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 04:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26454 | A Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Healthcare-Chatbot through 9b7058a can occur via a crafted payload to the email1 or pwd1 parameter i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26454</link><description>A Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Healthcare-Chatbot through 9b7058a can occur via a crafted payload to the email1 or pwd1 parameter in login.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26540 | A heap-based buffer overflow in Clmg before 3.3.3 can occur via a crafted file to cimg_library::CImg&lt;unsigned char&gt;::_load_analyze.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26540</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow in Clmg before 3.3.3 can occur via a crafted file to cimg_library::CImg&lt;unsigned char&gt;::_load_analyze.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0803 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0803</link><description>Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute malicious code on a target product by sending a specially crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1915 | Incorrect Pointer Scaling vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a remote u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1915</link><description>Incorrect Pointer Scaling vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute malicious code on a target product by sending a specially crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1916 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1916</link><description>Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute malicious code on a target product by sending a specially crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1917 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1917</link><description>Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute malicious code on a target product by sending a specially crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0802 | Incorrect Pointer Scaling vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a remote u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0802</link><description>Incorrect Pointer Scaling vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series and MELSEC-L Series CPU modules allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to read arbitrary information from a target product or execute malicious code on a target product by sending a specially crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1853 | Zemana AntiLogger v2.74.204.664 - Arbitrary Process Termination</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1853</link><description>Zemana AntiLogger v2.74.204.664 is vulnerable to an Arbitrary Process Termination vulnerability by triggering the 0x80002048 IOCTL code of the zam64.sys and zamguard64.sys drivers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 22:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26163 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26163</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 22:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26246 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26246</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 22:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26475 | An issue in radareorg radare2 v.0.9.7 through v.5.8.6 and fixed in v.5.8.8 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the grub...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26475</link><description>An issue in radareorg radare2 v.0.9.7 through v.5.8.6 and fixed in v.5.8.8 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the grub_sfs_read_extent function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 21:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42286 | There is a PHP file inclusion vulnerability in the template configuration of eyoucms v1.6.4, allowing attackers to execute code or system co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42286</link><description>There is a PHP file inclusion vulnerability in the template configuration of eyoucms v1.6.4, allowing attackers to execute code or system commands through a carefully crafted malicious payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 21:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2249 | The LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the LinkWrapper attribute foun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2249</link><description>The LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the LinkWrapper attribute found in several widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping the user supplied attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 21:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50677 | An issue in NETGEAR-DGND4000 v.1.1.00.15_1.00.15 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the next_file parameter to the /setup.c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50677</link><description>An issue in NETGEAR-DGND4000 v.1.1.00.15_1.00.15 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the next_file parameter to the /setup.cgi component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 21:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26503 | Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability in Greek Universities Network Open eClass v.3.15 and earlier allows attackers to run arbitrary code v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26503</link><description>Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability in Greek Universities Network Open eClass v.3.15 and earlier allows attackers to run arbitrary code via upload of crafted file to certbadge.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 21:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0860 | Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information in Softing edgeConnector and edgeAggregator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0860</link><description>The affected product is vulnerable to a cleartext transmission of sensitive information vulnerability, which may allow an attacker to capture packets to craft their own requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 21:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2256 | The oik plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes such as bw_contact_button and bw_butto...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2256</link><description>The oik plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes such as bw_contact_button and bw_button shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 20:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1713 | Plv8 Deferred Trigger Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1713</link><description>A user who can create objects in a database with plv8 3.2.1 installed is able to cause deferred triggers to execute as the Superuser during autovacuum.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 20:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24562 | Security headers not set in vantage6-UI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24562</link><description>vantage6-UI is the official user interface for the vantage6 server. In affected versions a number of security headers are not set. This issue has been addressed in commit `68dfa6614` which is expected to be included in future releases. Users are advised to upgrade when a new release is made. While an upgrade path is not available users may modify the docker image build to insert the headers into nginx.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28423 | Airflow-Diagrams v2.1.0 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the unsafe_load function at cli.py. This vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28423</link><description>Airflow-Diagrams v2.1.0 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the unsafe_load function at cli.py. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted YML file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28424 | zenml v0.55.4 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the load function at /materializers/cloudpickle_materializ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28424</link><description>zenml v0.55.4 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the load function at /materializers/cloudpickle_materializer.py. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28425 | greykite v1.0.0 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the load_obj function at /templates/pickle_utils.py. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28425</link><description>greykite v1.0.0 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the load_obj function at /templates/pickle_utils.py. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23823 | CORS settings overly permissive in vantage6</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23823</link><description>vantage6 is an open source framework built to enable, manage and deploy privacy enhancing technologies like Federated Learning and Multi-Party Computation. The vantage6 server has no restrictions on CORS settings. It should be possible for people to set the allowed origins of the server.  The impact is limited because v6 does not use session cookies. This issue has been addressed in commit `70bb4e1d8` and is expected to ship in subsequent releases. Users are advised to upgrade as soon as a new release is available. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24770 | Username timing attack on recover password/MFA token in vantage6</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24770</link><description>vantage6 is an open source framework built to enable, manage and deploy privacy enhancing technologies like Federated Learning and Multi-Party Computation. Much like GHSA-45gq-q4xh-cp53, it is possible to find which usernames exist in vantage6 by calling the API routes `/recover/lost` and `/2fa/lost`. These routes send emails to users if they have lost their password or MFA token. This issue has been addressed in commit `aecfd6d0e` and is expected to ship in subsequent releases. Users are advised to upgrade as soon as a new release is available. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22346 | IBM i privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22346</link><description>Db2 for IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 infrastructure could allow a local user to gain elevated privileges due to an unqualified library call. A malicious actor could cause user-controlled code to run with administrator privilege.  IBM X-Force ID:  280203.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27265 | IBM Integration Bus for z/OS cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27265</link><description>IBM Integration Bus for z/OS 10.1 through 10.1.0.3 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.  IBM X-Force ID:  284564.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27266 | IBM Maximo Application Suite XML external entity injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27266</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite 7.6.1.3 is vulnerable to an XML External Entity Injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.  IBM X-Force ID:  284566.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27301 | Privilege Escalation Abusing installer in SupportApp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27301</link><description>Support App is an opensource application specialized in managing Apple devices. It's possible to abuse a vulnerability inside the postinstall installer script to make the installer execute arbitrary code as root. The cause of the vulnerability is the fact that the shebang `#!/bin/zsh` is being used. When the installer is executed it asks for the users password to be executed as root. However, it'll still be using the $HOME of the user and therefore loading the file  `$HOME/.zshenv` when the `postinstall` script is executed.
An attacker could add malicious code to `$HOME/.zshenv` and it will be executed when the app is installed. An attacker may leverage this vulnerability to escalate privilege on the system. This issue has been addressed in version 2.5.1 Rev 2. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42938 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iTunes 12.13.1 for Windows. A local attacker may be able to elevate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42938</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iTunes 12.13.1 for Windows. A local attacker may be able to elevate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28181 | Arbitrary method invocation turbo_boost-commands </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28181</link><description>turbo_boost-commands is a set of commands to help you build robust reactive applications with Rails &amp; Hotwire. TurboBoost Commands has existing protections in place to guarantee that only public methods on Command classes can be invoked; however, the existing checks aren't as robust as they should be. It's possible for a sophisticated attacker to invoke more methods than should be permitted depending on the the strictness of authorization checks that individual applications enforce. Being able to call some of these methods can have security implications. Commands verify that the class must be a `Command` and that the method requested is defined as a public method; however, this isn't robust enough to guard against all unwanted code execution. The library should more strictly enforce which methods are considered safe before allowing them to be executed. This issue has been addressed in versions 0.1.3, and 0.2.2. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should see the repository GHSA for workaround advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 17:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28849 | Proxy-Authorization header kept across hosts in follow-redirects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28849</link><description>follow-redirects is an open source, drop-in replacement for Node's `http` and `https` modules that automatically follows redirects. In affected versions follow-redirects only clears authorization header during cross-domain redirect, but keep the proxy-authentication header which contains credentials too. This vulnerability may lead to credentials leak, but has been addressed in version 1.15.6. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 17:11:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22655 | Protection mechanism failure in some 3rd and 4th Generation Intel(R) Xeon(R) Processors when using Intel(R) SGX or Intel(R) TDX may allow a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22655</link><description>Protection mechanism failure in some 3rd and 4th Generation Intel(R) Xeon(R) Processors when using Intel(R) SGX or Intel(R) TDX may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27502 | Insertion of sensitive information into log file for some Intel(R) Local Manageability Service software before version 2316.5.1.2 may allow ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27502</link><description>Insertion of sensitive information into log file for some Intel(R) Local Manageability Service software before version 2316.5.1.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28389 | Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) CSME installer software before version 2328.5.5.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28389</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) CSME installer software before version 2328.5.5.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28746 | Information exposure through microarchitectural state after transient execution from some register files for some Intel(R) Atom(R) Processor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28746</link><description>Information exposure through microarchitectural state after transient execution from some register files for some Intel(R) Atom(R) Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32282 | Race condition in BIOS firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32282</link><description>Race condition in BIOS firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32633 | Improper input validation in the Intel(R) CSME installer software before version 2328.5.5.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32633</link><description>Improper input validation in the Intel(R) CSME installer software before version 2328.5.5.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32666 | On-chip debug and test interface with improper access control in some 4th Generation Intel(R) Xeon(R) Processors when using Intel(R) SGX or ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32666</link><description>On-chip debug and test interface with improper access control in some 4th Generation Intel(R) Xeon(R) Processors when using Intel(R) SGX or Intel(R) TDX may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35191 | Uncontrolled resource consumption for some Intel(R) SPS firmware versions may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35191</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption for some Intel(R) SPS firmware versions may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38575 | Non-transparent sharing of return predictor targets between contexts in some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authorized user to potentially...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38575</link><description>Non-transparent sharing of return predictor targets between contexts in some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authorized user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39368 | Protection mechanism failure of bus lock regulator for some Intel(R) Processors may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable deni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39368</link><description>Protection mechanism failure of bus lock regulator for some Intel(R) Processors may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43490 | Incorrect calculation in microcode keying mechanism for some Intel(R) Xeon(R) D Processors with Intel(R) SGX may allow a privileged user to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43490</link><description>Incorrect calculation in microcode keying mechanism for some Intel(R) Xeon(R) D Processors with Intel(R) SGX may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50168 | Pega Platform from 6.x to 8.8.4 is affected by an XXE issue with PDF Generation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50168</link><description>Pega Platform from 6.x to 8.8.4 is affected by an XXE issue with PDF Generation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 15:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25139 | In TP-Link Omada er605 1.0.1 through (v2.6) 2.2.3, a cloud-brd binary is susceptible to an integer overflow that leads to a heap-based buffe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25139</link><description>In TP-Link Omada er605 1.0.1 through (v2.6) 2.2.3, a cloud-brd binary is susceptible to an integer overflow that leads to a heap-based buffer overflow. After heap shaping, an attacker can achieve code execution in the context of the cloud-brd binary that runs at the root level. This is fixed in ER605(UN)_v2_2.2.4 Build 020240119.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 15:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25156 | Path traversal in GoAnywhere MFT 7.4.1 and Earlier</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25156</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in GoAnywhere MFT prior to 7.4.2 which allows attackers to circumvent endpoint-specific permission checks in the GoAnywhere Admin and Web Clients.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 14:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28323 | The bwdates-report-result.php file in Phpgurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System 3.1 contains a potential security vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28323</link><description>The bwdates-report-result.php file in Phpgurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System 3.1 contains a potential security vulnerability related to user input validation. The script retrieves user-provided date inputs without proper validation, making it susceptible to SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 13:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28417 | Webedition CMS 9.2.2.0 has a Stored XSS vulnerability via /webEdition/we_cmd.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28417</link><description>Webedition CMS 9.2.2.0 has a Stored XSS vulnerability via /webEdition/we_cmd.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 13:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28418 | Webedition CMS 9.2.2.0 has a File upload vulnerability via /webEdition/we_cmd.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28418</link><description>Webedition CMS 9.2.2.0 has a File upload vulnerability via /webEdition/we_cmd.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 13:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1623 | Insufficient session timeout vulnerability in Sagemcom router</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1623</link><description>Insufficient session timeout vulnerability in the FAST3686 V2 Vodafone router from Sagemcom. This vulnerability could allow a local attacker to access the administration panel without requiring login credentials. This vulnerability is possible because the 'Login.asp and logout.asp' files do not handle session details correctly.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 12:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28383 | Tenda AX12 v1.0 v22.03.01.16 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid parameter in the sub_431CF0 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28383</link><description>Tenda AX12 v1.0 v22.03.01.16 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid parameter in the sub_431CF0 function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 12:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0311 | A malicious insider can bypass the existing policy of Skyhigh Client Proxy without a valid release code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0311</link><description>A malicious insider can bypass the existing policy of Skyhigh Client Proxy without a valid release code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 09:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0312 | A malicious insider can uninstall Skyhigh Client Proxy without a valid uninstall password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0312</link><description>A malicious insider can uninstall Skyhigh Client Proxy without a valid uninstall password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 09:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0313 | A malicious insider exploiting this vulnerability can circumvent existing security controls put in place by the organization. On the contrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0313</link><description>A malicious insider exploiting this vulnerability can circumvent existing security controls put in place by the organization. On the contrary, if the victim is legitimately using the temporary bypass to reach out to the Internet for retrieving application and system updates, a remote device could target it and undo the bypass, thereby denying the victim access to the update service, causing it to fail.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 09:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28746 | Apache Airflow: Ignored Airflow Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28746</link><description>Apache Airflow, versions 2.8.0 through 2.8.2, has a vulnerability that allows an authenticated user with limited permissions to access resources such as variables, connections, etc from the UI which they do not have permission to access. 

Users of Apache Airflow are recommended to upgrade to version 2.8.3 or newer to mitigate the risk associated with this vulnerability</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 08:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27986 | WordPress Livemesh Addons for Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 8.3.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27986</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Livemesh Elementor Addons by Livemesh allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Elementor Addons by Livemesh: from n/a through 8.3.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 08:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22397 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') in the SonicOS SSLVPN portal allows a remote authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22397</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') in the SonicOS SSLVPN portal allows a remote authenticated attacker as a firewall 'admin' user to store and execute arbitrary JavaScript code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22398 | An improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (Path Traversal) vulnerability in SonicWall Email Security Appliance could al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22398</link><description>An improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (Path Traversal) vulnerability in SonicWall Email Security Appliance could allow a remote attacker with administrative privileges to conduct a directory traversal attack and delete arbitrary files from the appliance file system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28391 | SQL injection vulnerability in FME Modules quickproducttable module for PrestaShop v.1.2.1 and before, allows a remote attacker to escalate ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28391</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in FME Modules quickproducttable module for PrestaShop v.1.2.1 and before, allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges and obtain information via the readCsv(), displayAjaxProductChangeAttr, displayAjaxProductAddToCart, getSearchProducts, and displayAjaxProductSku methods.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:24:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1882 | Server-side resource injection in PaperCut NG/MF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1882</link><description>This vulnerability allows an already authenticated admin user to create a malicious payload that could be leveraged for remote code execution on the server hosting the PaperCut NG/MF application server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1883 | Reflected XSS in PaperCut NG/MF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1883</link><description>This is a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in the PaperCut NG/MF application server. An attacker can exploit this weakness by crafting a malicious URL that contains a script. When an unsuspecting user clicks on this malicious link, it could potentially lead to limited loss of confidentiality, integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1884 | Server Side Request Forgery in PaperCut NG/MF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1884</link><description>This is a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the PaperCut NG/MF server-side module that  allows an attacker to induce the server-side application to make HTTP requests to an arbitrary domain of the attacker's choosing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22396 | An Integer-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SonicOS via IPSec allows a remote attacker in specific conditions to cause Denial of S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22396</link><description>An Integer-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SonicOS via IPSec allows a remote attacker in specific conditions to cause Denial of Service (DoS) and potentially execute arbitrary code by sending a specially crafted IKEv2 payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28390 | An issue in Advanced Plugins ultimateimagetool module for PrestaShop before v.2.2.01, allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges and ob...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28390</link><description>An issue in Advanced Plugins ultimateimagetool module for PrestaShop before v.2.2.01, allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via Improper Access Control.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1221 | Improper access controls on APIs on Linux and macOS in PaperCut NG/MF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1221</link><description>This vulnerability potentially allows files on a PaperCut NG/MF server to be exposed using a specifically formed payload against the impacted API endpoint. The attacker must carry out some reconnaissance to gain knowledge of a system token. This CVE only affects Linux and macOS PaperCut NG/MF servers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1222 | Incorrect authorization controls in PaperCut NG/MF APIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1222</link><description>This allows attackers to use a maliciously formed API request to gain access to an API authorization level with elevated privileges. This applies to a small subset of PaperCut NG/MF API calls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1223 |  Improper authorization controls in PaperCut NG/MF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1223</link><description>This vulnerability potentially allows unauthorized enumeration of information from the embedded device APIs. An attacker must already have existing knowledge of some combination of valid usernames, device names and an internal system key. For such an attack to be successful the system must be in a specific runtime state.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1654 | Unauthorized write operations in PaperCut NG/MF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1654</link><description>This vulnerability potentially allows unauthorized write operations which may lead to remote code execution. An attacker must already have authenticated admin access and knowledge of both an internal system identifier and details of another valid user to exploit this.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28388 | SQL injection vulnerability in SunnyToo stproductcomments module for PrestaShop v.1.0.5 and before, allows a remote attacker to escalate pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28388</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in SunnyToo stproductcomments module for PrestaShop v.1.0.5 and before, allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the StProductCommentClass::getListcomments method.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25653 | Broken Access Control in the Report functionality of Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4 allows unprivileged users, when Unlimited Admin Mode is ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25653</link><description>Broken Access Control in the Report functionality of Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4 allows unprivileged users, when Unlimited Admin Mode is enabled, to view system reports and modify custom reports via the Report functionality in the Web UI.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25652 | In Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4, it is possible for a user (with access to the Report functionality) to gain unauthorized access to remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25652</link><description>In Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4, it is possible for a user (with access to the Report functionality) to gain unauthorized access to remote sessions created by legitimate users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25649 | In Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4, it is possible for an attacker (with Administrator access to the Secret Server machine) to read the follo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25649</link><description>In Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4, it is possible for an attacker (with Administrator access to the Secret Server machine) to read the following data from a memory dump: the decrypted master key, database credentials (when SQL Server Authentication is enabled), the encryption key of RabbitMQ queue messages, and session cookies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25651 | User enumeration can occur in the Authentication REST API in Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4. This allows a remote attacker to determine whet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25651</link><description>User enumeration can occur in the Authentication REST API in Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4. This allows a remote attacker to determine whether a user is valid because of a difference in responses from the /oauth2/token endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25650 | Insecure key exchange between Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4 and the Distributed Engine 8.4.3 allows a PAM administrator to obtain the Symme...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25650</link><description>Insecure key exchange between Delinea PAM Secret Server 11.4 and the Distributed Engine 8.4.3 allows a PAM administrator to obtain the Symmetric Key (used to encrypt RabbitMQ messages) via crafted payloads to the /pre-authenticate, /authenticate, and /execute-and-respond REST API endpoints. This makes it possible for a PAM administrator to impersonate the Engine and exfiltrate sensitive information from the messages published in the RabbitMQ exchanges, without being audited in the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25228 | Vinchin Backup and Recovery 7.2 and Earlier is vulnerable to Authenticated Remote Code Execution (RCE) via the getVerifydiyResult function i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25228</link><description>Vinchin Backup and Recovery 7.2 and Earlier is vulnerable to Authenticated Remote Code Execution (RCE) via the getVerifydiyResult function in ManoeuvreHandler.class.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28251 | Cross-site websocket hijacking in Querybook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28251</link><description>Querybook is a Big Data Querying UI, combining collocated table metadata and a simple notebook interface. Querybook's datadocs functionality works by using a Websocket Server. The client talks to this WSS whenever updating/deleting/reading any cells as well as for watching the live status of query executions. Currently the CORS setting allows all origins, which could result in cross-site websocket hijacking and allow attackers to read/edit/remove datadocs of the user. This issue has been addressed in version 3.32.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 23:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-11862 | Insecure renegotiation in SSL protocol caused Denial of service attack in Privileged Account Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11862</link><description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in OpenText NetIQ Privileged Account Manager on Linux, Windows, 64 bit allows Flooding.This issue affects NetIQ Privileged Account Manager: before 3.7.0.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 21:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2079 | The WPBakery Page Builder Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'per_line_mo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2079</link><description>The WPBakery Page Builder Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'per_line_mobile' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 21:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2242 | The Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘active-tab’ parameter in all versions up to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2242</link><description>The Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘active-tab’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 21:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38534 | Improper authentication vulnerability in OpenText™ Exceed Turbo X affecting versions 12.5.0 and 12.5.1. The vulnerability could allow disclo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38534</link><description>Improper authentication vulnerability in OpenText™ Exceed Turbo X affecting versions 12.5.0 and 12.5.1. The vulnerability could allow disclosure of restricted information in unauthenticated RPC.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 21:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38535 | Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key vulnerability in OpenText™ Exceed Turbo X affecting versions 12.5.1 and 12.5.2. The vulnerability could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38535</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key vulnerability in OpenText™ Exceed Turbo X affecting versions 12.5.1 and 12.5.2. The vulnerability could compromise the cryptographic keys.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 21:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38536 | HTML injection in OpenText™ Exceed Turbo X affecting version 12.5.1. The vulnerability could result in Cross site scripting.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38536</link><description>HTML injection in OpenText™ Exceed Turbo X affecting version 12.5.1. The vulnerability could result in Cross site scripting.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 21:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27703 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Leantime 3.0.6 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the to-do title parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27703</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Leantime 3.0.6 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the to-do title parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 21:22:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28662 | A Cross Site Scripting vulnerability exists in Piwigo before 14.3.0 script because of missing sanitization in create_tag in admin/include/fu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28662</link><description>A Cross Site Scripting vulnerability exists in Piwigo before 14.3.0 script because of missing sanitization in create_tag in admin/include/functions.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 21:22:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50726 | Users with `create` but not `override` privileges can perform local sync in argo-cd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50726</link><description>Argo CD is a declarative, GitOps continuous delivery tool for Kubernetes. "Local sync" is an Argo CD feature that allows developers to temporarily override an Application's manifests with locally-defined manifests. Use of the feature should generally be limited to highly-trusted users, since it allows the user to bypass any merge protections in git. An improper validation bug allows users who have `create` privileges but not `override` privileges to sync local manifests on app creation. All other restrictions, including AppProject restrictions are still enforced. The only restriction which is not enforced is that the manifests come from some approved git/Helm/OCI source. The bug was introduced in 1.2.0-rc1 when the local manifest sync feature was added. The bug has been patched in Argo CD versions 2.10.3, 2.9.8, and 2.8.12. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may mitigate the risk of branch protection bypass by removing `applications, create` RBAC access. The only way to eliminate the issue without removing RBAC access is to upgrade to a patched version.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28175 | Cross-site scripting on application summary component in argo-cd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28175</link><description>Argo CD is a declarative, GitOps continuous delivery tool for Kubernetes. Due to the improper URL protocols filtering of links specified in the `link.argocd.argoproj.io` annotations in the application summary component, an attacker can achieve cross-site scripting with elevated permissions. All unpatched versions of Argo CD starting with v1.0.0 are vulnerable to a cross-site scripting (XSS) bug allowing a malicious user to inject a javascript: link in the UI. When clicked by a victim user, the script will execute with the victim's permissions (up to and including admin). This vulnerability allows an attacker to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of the victim via the API, such as creating, modifying, and deleting Kubernetes resources. A patch for this vulnerability has been released in Argo CD versions v2.10.3 v2.9.8, and v2.8.12. There are no completely-safe workarounds besides upgrading. The safest alternative, if upgrading is not possible, would be to create a Kubernetes admission controller to reject any resources with an annotation starting with link.argocd.argoproj.io or reject the resource if the value use an improper URL protocol. This validation will need to be applied in all clusters managed by ArgoCD.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22167 | SanDisk PrivateAccess DLL Hijacking Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22167</link><description>A potential DLL hijacking vulnerability in the SanDisk PrivateAccess application for Windows that could lead to arbitrary code execution in the context of the system user. This vulnerability is only exploitable locally if an attacker has access to a copy of the user's vault or has already gained access into a user's system. This attack is limited to the system in context and cannot be propagated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27097 | Potential log injection in reset user endpoint in ckan</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27097</link><description>A user endpoint didn't perform filtering on an incoming parameter, which was added directly to the application log. This could lead to an attacker injecting false log entries or corrupt the log file format. This has been fixed in the CKAN versions 2.9.11 and 2.10.4. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should override the `/user/reset` endpoint to filter the `id` parameter in order to exclude newlines.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41505 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Add Student's Profile Picture function of Student Enrollment In PHP v1.0 allows attackers to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41505</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Add Student's Profile Picture function of Student Enrollment In PHP v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PHP file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41504 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Student Enrollment In PHP 1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the Student Search function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41504</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Student Enrollment In PHP 1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the Student Search function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24105 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Code-projects Computer Science Time Table System 1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via adminFormvali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24105</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Code-projects Computer Science Time Table System 1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via adminFormvalidation.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27102 | Improper isolation of server file access in github.com/pterodactyl/wings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27102</link><description>Wings is the server control plane for Pterodactyl Panel. This vulnerability impacts anyone running the affected versions of Wings. The vulnerability can potentially be used to access files and directories on the host system. The full scope of impact is exactly unknown, but reading files outside of a server's base directory (sandbox root) is possible. In order to use this exploit, an attacker must have an existing "server" allocated and controlled by Wings. Details on the exploitation of this vulnerability are embargoed until March 27th, 2024 at 18:00 UTC. In order to mitigate this vulnerability, a full rewrite of the entire server filesystem was necessary. Because of this, the size of the patch is massive, however effort was made to reduce the amount of breaking changes. Users are advised to update to version 1.11.9. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28193 | Disclosure of Spotify API Access Tokens to Guest Users Using Public Tokens in your_spotify</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28193</link><description>your_spotify is an open source, self hosted Spotify tracking dashboard. YourSpotify version &lt;1.8.0 allows users to create a public token in the settings, which can be used to provide guest-level access to the information of that specific user in YourSpotify. The /me API endpoint discloses Spotify API access and refresh tokens to guest users. Attackers with access to a public token for guest access to YourSpotify can therefore obtain access to Spotify API tokens of YourSpotify users. As a consequence, attackers may extract profile information, information about listening habits, playlists and other information from the corresponding Spotify profile. In addition, the attacker can pause and resume playback in the Spotify app at will. This issue has been resolved in version 1.8.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36238 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in Bagisto v.1.5.1 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the invoice ID parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36238</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in Bagisto v.1.5.1 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the invoice ID parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:22:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25250 | SQL Injection vulnerability in code-projects Agro-School Management System 1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the Login page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25250</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in code-projects Agro-School Management System 1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the Login page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:22:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28192 | NoSQL Injection Leading to Authentication Bypass in your_spotify</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28192</link><description>your_spotify is an open source, self hosted Spotify tracking dashboard. YourSpotify version &lt;1.8.0 is vulnerable to NoSQL injection in the public access token processing logic. Attackers can fully bypass the public token authentication mechanism, regardless if a public token has been generated before or not, without any user interaction or prerequisite knowledge. This vulnerability allows an attacker to fully bypass the public token authentication mechanism, regardless if a public token has been generated before or not, without any user interaction or prerequisite knowledge. This issue has been addressed in version 1.8.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:22:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24692 | Zoom Rooms Client for Windows - Race Condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24692</link><description>Race condition in the installer for Zoom Rooms Client for Windows before version 5.17.5 may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 19:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24693 | Zoom Rooms Client for Windows - Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24693</link><description>Improper access control in the installer for Zoom Rooms Client for Windows before version 5.17.5 may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 19:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0800 | Authentication Bypass via wizardLogin in Arcserve Unified Data Protection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0800</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in Arcserve Unified Data Protection 9.2 and 8.1 in edge-app-base-webui.jar!com.ca.arcserve.edge.app.base.ui.server.servlet.ImportNodeServlet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 19:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0801 | Unauthenticated DoS in Arcserve Unified Data Protection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0801</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in Arcserve Unified Data Protection 9.2 and 8.1 in ASNative.dll.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 19:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0799 | Authentication Bypass via wizardLogin in Arcserve Unified Data Protection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0799</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in Arcserve Unified Data Protection 9.2 and 8.1 in the edge-app-base-webui.jar!com.ca.arcserve.edge.app.base.ui.server.EdgeLoginServiceImpl.doLogin() function within wizardLogin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 19:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28194 | Authentication Bypass Because of Hardcoded JWT Secret in your_spotify</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28194</link><description>your_spotify is an open source, self hosted Spotify tracking dashboard. YourSpotify versions &lt; 1.8.0 use a hardcoded JSON Web Token (JWT) secret to sign authentication tokens. Attackers can use this well-known value to forge valid authentication tokens for arbitrary users. This vulnerability allows attackers to bypass authentication and authenticate as arbitrary YourSpotify users, including admin users. This issue has been addressed in version 1.8.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 18:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2403 | Improper cleanup in temporary file handling component in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.1.12 and
earlier on Windows allows an attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2403</link><description>Improper cleanup in temporary file handling component in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.1.12 and
earlier on Windows allows an attacker that compromised a user endpoint, under specific circumstances, to access sensitive information via residual files in the temporary directory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 18:19:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2418 | SourceCodester Best POS Management System view_order.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2418</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best POS Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /view_order.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256705 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 18:19:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2431 | GlobalProtect App: Local User Can Disable GlobalProtect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2431</link><description>An issue in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app enables a non-privileged user to disable the GlobalProtect app in configurations that allow a user to disable GlobalProtect with a passcode.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 18:00:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2432 | GlobalProtect App: Local Privilege Escalation (PE) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2432</link><description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution requires that the local user is able to successfully exploit a race condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 18:00:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2433 | PAN-OS: Improper Privilege Management Vulnerability in Panorama Software Leads to Availability Loss</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2433</link><description>An improper authorization vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-only administrator to upload files using the web interface and completely fill one of the disk partitions with those uploaded files, which prevents the ability to log into the web interface or to download PAN-OS, WildFire, and content images. 



This issue affects only the web interface of the management plane; the dataplane is unaffected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 18:00:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28195 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in API and login in your_spotify</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28195</link><description>your_spotify is an open source, self hosted Spotify tracking dashboard. YourSpotify versions &lt; 1.9.0 do not protect the API and login flow against Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF). Attackers can use this to execute CSRF attacks on victims, allowing them to retrieve, modify or delete data on the affected YourSpotify instance. Using repeated CSRF attacks, it is also possible to create a new user on the victim instance and promote the new user to instance administrator if a legitimate administrator visits a website prepared by an attacker. Note: Real-world exploitability of this vulnerability depends on the browser version and browser settings in use by the victim. This issue has been addressed in version 1.9.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28196 | Clickjacking in your_spotify</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28196</link><description>your_spotify is an open source, self hosted Spotify tracking dashboard. YourSpotify version &lt; 1.9.0 does not prevent other pages from displaying it in an iframe and is thus vulnerable to clickjacking. Clickjacking can be used to trick an existing user of YourSpotify to trigger actions, such as allowing signup of other users or deleting the current user account. Clickjacking works by opening the target application in an invisible iframe on an attacker-controlled site and luring a victim to visit the attacker page and interacting with it. By positioning elements over the invisible iframe, a victim can be tricked into triggering malicious or destructive actions in the invisible iframe, while they think they interact with a totally different site altogether. When a victim visits an attacker-controlled site while they are logged into YourSpotify, they can be tricked into performing actions on their YourSpotify instance without their knowledge. These actions include allowing signup of other users or deleting the current user account, resulting in a high impact to the integrity of YourSpotify. This issue has been addressed in version 1.9.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0173 | Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS and Dell Precision Rack BIOS contain an improper parameter initialization vulnerability. A local low privileged a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0173</link><description>Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS and Dell Precision Rack BIOS contain an improper parameter initialization vulnerability. A local low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to read the contents of non-SMM stack memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20262 | A vulnerability in the Secure Copy Protocol (SCP) and SFTP feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20262</link><description>A vulnerability in the Secure Copy Protocol (SCP) and SFTP feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to create or overwrite files in a system directory, which could lead to a denial of service (DoS) condition. The attacker would require valid user credentials to perform this attack.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper validation of SCP and SFTP CLI input parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and issuing SCP or SFTP CLI commands with specific parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to impact the functionality of the device, which could lead to a DoS condition. The device may need to be manually rebooted to recover.&#13;
&#13; Note: This vulnerability is exploitable only when a local user invokes SCP or SFTP commands at the Cisco IOS XR CLI. A local user with administrative privileges could exploit this vulnerability remotely.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:51:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20315 | A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on MPLS interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20315</link><description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on MPLS interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20318 | A vulnerability in the Layer 2 Ethernet services of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the lin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20318</link><description>A vulnerability in the Layer 2 Ethernet services of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the line card network processor to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific Ethernet frames that are received on line cards that have the Layer 2 services feature enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific Ethernet frames through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ingress interface network processor to reset, resulting in a loss of traffic over the interfaces that are supported by the network processor. Multiple resets of the network processor would cause the line card to reset, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20319 | A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20319</link><description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20322 | A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on Pseudowire interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20322</link><description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on Pseudowire interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0154 | Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS and Dell Precision Rack BIOS contain an improper parameter initialization vulnerability. A local low privileged a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0154</link><description>Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS and Dell Precision Rack BIOS contain an improper parameter initialization vulnerability. A local low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to read the contents of non-SMM stack memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20266 | A vulnerability in the DHCP version 4 (DHCPv4) server feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to tr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20266</link><description>A vulnerability in the DHCP version 4 (DHCPv4) server feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a crash of the dhcpd process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability exists because certain DHCPv4 messages are improperly validated when they are processed by an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed DHCPv4 message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a crash of the dhcpd process. While the dhcpd process is restarting, which may take approximately two minutes, DHCPv4 server services are unavailable on the affected device. This could temporarily prevent network access to clients that join the network during that time period and rely on the DHCPv4 server of the affected device.&#13;
&#13; Notes: &#13;
&#13; &#13; Only the dhcpd process crashes and eventually restarts automatically. The router does not reload.&#13; This vulnerability only applies to DHCPv4. DHCP version 6 (DHCPv6) is not affected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20320 | A vulnerability in the SSH client feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco 8000 Series Routers and Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20320</link><description>A vulnerability in the SSH client feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco 8000 Series Routers and Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 540 Series and 5700 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device. &#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are included with the SSH client CLI command. An attacker with low-privileged access to an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by issuing a crafted SSH client command to the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20327 | A vulnerability in the PPP over Ethernet (PPPoE) termination feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco ASR 9000 Series Aggregation Services...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20327</link><description>A vulnerability in the PPP over Ethernet (PPPoE) termination feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco ASR 9000 Series Aggregation Services Routers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the improper handling of malformed PPPoE packets that are received on a router that is running Broadband Network Gateway (BNG) functionality with PPPoE termination on a Lightspeed-based or Lightspeed-Plus-based line card. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted PPPoE packet to an affected line card interface that does not terminate PPPoE. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a DoS condition for PPPoE traffic across the router.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0163 | Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS and Dell Precision Rack BIOS contain a TOCTOU race condition vulnerability. A local low privileged attacker could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0163</link><description>Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS and Dell Precision Rack BIOS contain a TOCTOU race condition vulnerability. A local low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain access to otherwise unauthorized resources.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27953 | WordPress Cryptocurrency Widgets – Price Ticker &amp;amp; Coins List Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.8 is vulnerable to Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27953</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Cool Plugins Cryptocurrency Widgets – Price Ticker &amp; Coins List.This issue affects Cryptocurrency Widgets – Price Ticker &amp; Coins List: from n/a through 2.6.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0162 | Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS and Dell Precision Rack BIOS contain an Improper SMM communication buffer verification vulnerability. A local low...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0162</link><description>Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS and Dell Precision Rack BIOS contain an Improper SMM communication buffer verification vulnerability. A local low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability leading to out-of-bound read/writes to SMRAM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27952 | WordPress Advanced Sermons plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27952</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Codeus Advanced Sermons allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Advanced Sermons: from n/a through 3.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0161 | Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS and Dell Precision Rack BIOS contain an Improper SMM communication buffer verification vulnerability. A local low...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0161</link><description>Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS and Dell Precision Rack BIOS contain an Improper SMM communication buffer verification vulnerability. A local low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability leading to arbitrary writes to SMRAM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25099 | WordPress Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp;amp; donations Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25099</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in David de Boer Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp; donations allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp; donations: from n/a through 4.4.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:29:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25101 | WordPress Maspik – Spam blacklist Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.10.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25101</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in yonifre Maspik – Spam Blacklist allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Maspik – Spam Blacklist: from n/a through 0.10.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:29:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28669 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/freelist_edit.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28669</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/freelist_edit.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:29:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25097 | WordPress TNC PDF viewer Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25097</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeNcode LLC TNC PDF viewer allows Stored XSS.This issue affects TNC PDF viewer: from n/a through 2.8.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28676 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via /dede/article_edit.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28676</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via /dede/article_edit.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28680 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/diy_add.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28680</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/diy_add.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23672 | Apache Tomcat: WebSocket DoS with incomplete closing handshake</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23672</link><description>Denial of Service via incomplete cleanup vulnerability in Apache Tomcat. It was possible for WebSocket clients to keep WebSocket connections open leading to increased resource consumption.This issue affects Apache Tomcat: from 11.0.0-M1 through 11.0.0-M16, from 10.1.0-M1 through 10.1.18, from 9.0.0-M1 through 9.0.85, from 8.5.0 through 8.5.98.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 11.0.0-M17, 10.1.19, 9.0.86 or 8.5.99 which fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26630 | mm: cachestat: fix folio read-after-free in cache walk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26630</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: cachestat: fix folio read-after-free in cache walk

In cachestat, we access the folio from the page cache's xarray to compute
its page offset, and check for its dirty and writeback flags.  However, we
do not hold a reference to the folio before performing these actions,
which means the folio can concurrently be released and reused as another
folio/page/slab.

Get around this altogether by just using xarray's existing machinery for
the folio page offsets and dirty/writeback states.

This changes behavior for tmpfs files to now always report zeroes in their
dirty and writeback counters.  This is okay as tmpfs doesn't follow
conventional writeback cache behavior: its pages get "cleaned" during
swapout, after which they're no longer resident etc.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28679 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via Photo Collection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28679</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via Photo Collection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28683 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via create file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28683</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via create file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24549 | Apache Tomcat: HTTP/2 header handling DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24549</link><description>Denial of Service due to improper input validation vulnerability for HTTP/2 requests in Apache Tomcat. When processing an HTTP/2 request, if the request exceeded any of the configured limits for headers, the associated HTTP/2 stream was not reset until after all of the headers had been processed.This issue affects Apache Tomcat: from 11.0.0-M1 through 11.0.0-M16, from 10.1.0-M1 through 10.1.18, from 9.0.0-M1 through 9.0.85, from 8.5.0 through 8.5.98.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 11.0.0-M17, 10.1.19, 9.0.86 or 8.5.99 which fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:52:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1668 | The Avada | Website Builder For WordPress &amp; WooCommerce theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1668</link><description>The Avada | Website Builder For WordPress &amp; WooCommerce theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to and including 7.11.5 via the form entries page. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to view the contents of all form submissions, including fields that are obfuscated (such as the contact form's "password" field).</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1996 | The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's IHover widget link in all versions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1996</link><description>The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's IHover widget link in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1997 | The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'premium_fbchat_app_id' parameter of the Me...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1997</link><description>The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'premium_fbchat_app_id' parameter of the Messenger Chat Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28681 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/plus_edit.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28681</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/plus_edit.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28682 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/sys_cache_up.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28682</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/sys_cache_up.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2000 | The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'navigation_dots' parameter of the Multi Sc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2000</link><description>The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'navigation_dots' parameter of the Multi Scroll Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2237 | The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Global Badge module in all versions up to, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2237</link><description>The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Global Badge module in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2238 | The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Custom Mouse Cursor module in all versions ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2238</link><description>The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Custom Mouse Cursor module in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2239 | The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Premium Magic Scroll module in all versions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2239</link><description>The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Premium Magic Scroll module in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5663 | The News Announcement Scroll plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5663</link><description>The News Announcement Scroll plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 9.0.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6785 | The Download Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized file download of files added via the plugin in all versions up to, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6785</link><description>The Download Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized file download of files added via the plugin in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.84. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download files added with the plugin (even when privately published).</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6809 | The Custom fields shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's cf shortcode in all versions ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6809</link><description>The Custom fields shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's cf shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied custom post meta values. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6825 | The File Manager and File Manager Pro plugins for WordPress are vulnerable to Directory Traversal in versions up to, and including version 7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6825</link><description>The File Manager and File Manager Pro plugins for WordPress are vulnerable to Directory Traversal in versions up to, and including version 7.2.1 (free version) and 8.3.4 (Pro version) via the target parameter in the  mk_file_folder_manager_action_callback_shortcode function. This makes it possible for attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information and to upload files into directories other than the intended directory for file uploads. The free version requires Administrator access for this vulnerability to be exploitable. The Pro version allows a file manager to be embedded via a shortcode and also allows admins to grant file handling privileges to other user levels, which could lead to this vulnerability being exploited by lower-level users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6880 | The Visual Composer Website Builder, Landing Page Builder, Custom Theme Builder, Maintenance Mode &amp; Coming Soon Pages plugin for WordPress i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6880</link><description>The Visual Composer Website Builder, Landing Page Builder, Custom Theme Builder, Maintenance Mode &amp; Coming Soon Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's custom fields in all versions up to, and including, 45.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6954 | The Download Manager Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6954</link><description>The Download Manager Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.85 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6957 | The Fluent Forms plugin for WordPress by Fluent Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6957</link><description>The Fluent Forms plugin for WordPress by Fluent Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The exploitation level depends on who is granted the right to create forms by an administrator. This level can be as low as contributor, but by default is admin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6969 | The User Shortcodes Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.2 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6969</link><description>The User Shortcodes Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.2 via the user_meta shortcode due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to retrieve potentially sensitive user meta.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7015 | The File Manager Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tb' parameter in all versions up to, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7015</link><description>The File Manager Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tb' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0326 | The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Link Wrapper functionali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0326</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Link Wrapper functionality in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.17 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied links. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0368 | The Hustle – Email Marketing, Lead Generation, Optins, Popups plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0368</link><description>The Hustle – Email Marketing, Lead Generation, Optins, Popups plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 7.8.3 via hardcoded API Keys. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including PII.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0369 | The Bulk Edit Post Titles plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0369</link><description>The Bulk Edit Post Titles plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the bulkUpdatePostTitles function in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access and above, to modify the titles of arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0377 | The LifterLMS – WordPress LMS Plugin for eLearning plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0377</link><description>The LifterLMS – WordPress LMS Plugin for eLearning plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'process_review' function in all versions up to, and including, 7.5.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to publish an unrestricted number of reviews on the site.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0385 | The Categorify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the categorifyAj...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0385</link><description>The Categorify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the categorifyAjaxAddCategory function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to add categories.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0447 | The ArtiBot Free Chat Bot for WordPress WebSites plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0447</link><description>The ArtiBot Free Chat Bot for WordPress WebSites plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the artibot_update function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0449 | The ArtiBot Free Chat Bot for WordPress WebSites plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0449</link><description>The ArtiBot Free Chat Bot for WordPress WebSites plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0591 | The wpDataTables – WordPress Data Table, Dynamic Tables &amp; Table Charts Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0591</link><description>The wpDataTables – WordPress Data Table, Dynamic Tables &amp; Table Charts Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'A' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0592 | The Related Posts for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0592</link><description>The Related Posts for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the handle_create_link() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add related posts to other posts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This ultimately makes it possible for attackers to view draft and password protected posts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0614 | The Events Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0614</link><description>The Events Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0631 | The Duitku Payment Gateway plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0631</link><description>The Duitku Payment Gateway plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the check_duitku_response function in all versions up to, and including, 2.11.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the payment status of orders to failed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0681 | The Page Restriction WordPress (WP) – Protect WP Pages/Post plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to information disclosure in all versions up ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0681</link><description>The Page Restriction WordPress (WP) – Protect WP Pages/Post plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to information disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4. This is due to the plugin not properly restricting access to pages via the REST API when a page has been made private. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view protected pages. The vendor has decided that they will not implement REST API protection on posts and pages and the restrictions will only apply to the front-end of the site. The vendors solution was to add notices throughout the dashboard and recommends installing the WordPress REST API Authentication plugin for REST API coverage.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0683 | The Bulgarisation for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to missing capability checks on several func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0683</link><description>The Bulgarisation for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to missing capability checks on several functions in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.14. This makes it possible for unauthenticated and authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to generate and delete labels.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0687 | The Restrict User Access – Ultimate Membership &amp; Content Protection plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0687</link><description>The Restrict User Access – Ultimate Membership &amp; Content Protection plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.5 via API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain the contents of posts and pages via API.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0700 | The Simple Tweet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Tweet this text value in all versions up to, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0700</link><description>The Simple Tweet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Tweet this text value in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0827 | The Play.ht – Make Your Blog Posts Accessible With Text to Speech Audio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0827</link><description>The Play.ht – Make Your Blog Posts Accessible With Text to Speech Audio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on several functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to invoke those functions via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0828 | The Play.ht – Make Your Blog Posts Accessible With Text to Speech Audio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of functio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0828</link><description>The Play.ht – Make Your Blog Posts Accessible With Text to Speech Audio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of functionality due to a missing capability check on several functions in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or higher, to delete, retrieve, or modify post metadata, retrieve posts contents of protected posts, modify conversion data and delete article audio.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0829 | The Comments Extra Fields For Post,Pages and CPT plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and incl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0829</link><description>The Comments Extra Fields For Post,Pages and CPT plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 5.0. This is due to missing or incorrect capability checks on several ajax actions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or higher, to invoke those actions. As a result, they may modify comment form fields and update plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0830 | The Comments Extra Fields For Post,Pages and CPT plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0830</link><description>The Comments Extra Fields For Post,Pages and CPT plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on several ajax actions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to invoke those actions via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. As a result, they may modify comment form fields and update plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0839 | The FeedWordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2022.0222 due...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0839</link><description>The FeedWordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2022.0222 due to missing validation on the user controlled 'guid' key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view draft posts that may contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0871 | The Beaver Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Icon Widget 'fl_builder_data[node_preview][link...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0871</link><description>The Beaver Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Icon Widget 'fl_builder_data[node_preview][link]' and 'fl_builder_data[settings][link_target]' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0896 | The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the button link parameter ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0896</link><description>The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the button link parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor access or higher to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0897 | The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the image URL parameter in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0897</link><description>The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the image URL parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0898 | The Chat Bubble – Floating Chat with Contact Chat Icons, Messages, Telegram, Email, SMS, Call me back plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0898</link><description>The Chat Bubble – Floating Chat with Contact Chat Icons, Messages, Telegram, Email, SMS, Call me back plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0976 | The WP Event Manager – Events Calendar, Registrations, Sell Tickets with WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0976</link><description>The WP Event Manager – Events Calendar, Registrations, Sell Tickets with WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.41 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1038 | The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via a 'playground...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1038</link><description>The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via a 'playground.wordpress.net' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1071 | The Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1071</link><description>The Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'sorting' parameter in versions 2.1.3 to 2.8.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1074 | The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the audio widget 'link_url...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1074</link><description>The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the audio widget 'link_url' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1080 | The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the via the heading tag in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1080</link><description>The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the via the heading tag in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1083 | The Simple Restrict plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.6 via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1083</link><description>The Simple Restrict plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.6 via the REST API. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers to bypass the plugin's restrictions to extract post titles and content</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1126 | The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1126</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the get_attendees_email_by_event_id() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to to retrieve the attendees list for any event.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1127 | The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1127</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the booking_export_all() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve all event booking which can contain PII.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1158 | The Post Form – Registration Form – Profile Form for User Profiles – Frontend Content Forms for User Submissions (UGC) plugin for WordPress ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1158</link><description>The Post Form – Registration Form – Profile Form for User Profiles – Frontend Content Forms for User Submissions (UGC) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the buddyforms_new_page function in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or higher, to create pages with arbitrary titles. These pages are published.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1176 | The HT Easy GA4 – Google Analytics WordPress Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1176</link><description>The HT Easy GA4 – Google Analytics WordPress Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the login() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the email associated through the plugin with GA4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1203 | The Conversios – Google Analytics 4 (GA4), Meta Pixel &amp; more Via Google Tag Manager For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1203</link><description>The Conversios – Google Analytics 4 (GA4), Meta Pixel &amp; more Via Google Tag Manager For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'valueData' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.9.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1234 | The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via data attribute in all versions up t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1234</link><description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via data attribute in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1237 | The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the flyout_layout attribute in a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1237</link><description>The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the flyout_layout attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.24 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1291 | The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown URL parameter in all versions u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1291</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown URL parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.40 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1293 | The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the embedded media custom block in all versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1293</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the embedded media custom block in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.40 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1296 | The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's block upload in all versions up ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1296</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's block upload in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.40 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1311 | The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the storeImages...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1311</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the storeImages function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.40. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1321 | The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to payment bypass in all versions up to, and inclu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1321</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to payment bypass in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.2. This is due to the plugin allowing unauthenticated users to update the status of order payments. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to book events for free.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1358 | The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.12 via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1358</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.12 via the render function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to include the contents of arbitrary PHP files on the server, which may expose sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1363 | The Easy Accordion – Best Accordion FAQ Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'acco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1363</link><description>The Easy Accordion – Best Accordion FAQ Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'accordion_content_source' attribute in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1365 | The YML for Yandex Market plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the feed_id  parameter in all versions up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1365</link><description>The YML for Yandex Market plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the feed_id  parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1370 | The Maintenance Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the subscribe_do...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1370</link><description>The Maintenance Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the subscribe_download function hooked via AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or higher, to download a csv containing subscriber emails.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1380 | The Relevanssi – A Better Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1380</link><description>The Relevanssi – A Better Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the relevanssi_export_log_check() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.22.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export the query log data. The vendor has indicated that they may look into adding a capability check for proper authorization control, however, this vulnerability is theoretically patched as is.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1383 | The WPvivid Backup for MainWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' parameter in all versions up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1383</link><description>The WPvivid Backup for MainWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.32 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1391 | The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘eae_custom_overlay_switcher’ attribu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1391</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘eae_custom_overlay_switcher’ attribute of the Thumbnail Slider widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1392 | The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'button1_icon' attribute of the Dual ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1392</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'button1_icon' attribute of the Dual Button widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1393 | The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'icon_align' attribute of the Content...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1393</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'icon_align' attribute of the Content Switcher widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1409 | The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1409</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's [reg-select-role] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.15.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1413 | The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown Timer widget in all v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1413</link><description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown Timer widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1414 | The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Call To Action widget in all ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1414</link><description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Call To Action widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1422 | The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the modal popup widget's effect setting i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1422</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the modal popup widget's effect setting in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1452 | The GenerateBlocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.2 via Quer...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1452</link><description>The GenerateBlocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.2 via Query Loop. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to see contents of posts and pages in draft or private status as well as those with scheduled publication dates.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1462 | The Maintenance Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Basic Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8 via the RE...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1462</link><description>The Maintenance Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Basic Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8 via the REST API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view post titles and content when the site is in maintenance mode.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1479 | The WP Show Posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.4 via the w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1479</link><description>The WP Show Posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.4 via the wpsp_display function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor access and above to view the contents of draft, trash, future, private and pending posts and pages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1484 | The Booking for Appointments and Events Calendar – Amelia plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the date ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1484</link><description>The Booking for Appointments and Events Calendar – Amelia plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the date parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.98 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1489 | The SMS Alert Order Notifications – WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1489</link><description>The SMS Alert Order Notifications – WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.9. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the processBulkAction function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete pages and posts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1497 | The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the form widget addr2_width attribute in al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1497</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the form widget addr2_width attribute in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1499 | The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Pricing Table widget in the  $settings[...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1499</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Pricing Table widget in the  $settings['title_tags'] parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1505 | The Academy LMS – eLearning and online course solution for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1505</link><description>The Academy LMS – eLearning and online course solution for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.19. This is due to plugin allowing arbitrary user meta updates through the saved_user_info() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with minimal permissions such as students, to elevate their user role to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1535 | The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1535</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 4.15.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1536 | The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to St...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1536</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's event calendar widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1537 | The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to St...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1537</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Data Table widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1541 | The Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the htm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1541</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the htmlTag attribute in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.23 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1585 | The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1585</link><description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1640 | The Contact Form Builder Plugin: Multi Step Contact Form, Payment Form, Custom Contact Form Plugin by Bit Form plugin for WordPress is vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1640</link><description>The Contact Form Builder Plugin: Multi Step Contact Form, Payment Form, Custom Contact Form Plugin by Bit Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a insufficient user validation on the bitforms_update_form_entry AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify form submissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1642 | The MainWP Dashboard  – WordPress Manager for Multiple Websites Maintenance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1642</link><description>The MainWP Dashboard  – WordPress Manager for Multiple Websites Maintenance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.0.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'posting_bulk' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary posts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1680 | The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Settings URL of the Banner,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1680</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Settings URL of the Banner, Team Members, and Image Scroll widgets in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1684 | The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1684</link><description>The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the contact form file field CSS metabox in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1690 | The TeraWallet – Best WooCommerce Wallet System With Cashback Rewards, Partial Payment, Wallet Refunds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1690</link><description>The TeraWallet – Best WooCommerce Wallet System With Cashback Rewards, Partial Payment, Wallet Refunds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the terawallet_export_user_search() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.10. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to export a list of registered users and their emails.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1691 | The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1691</link><description>The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via file upload form, which allows SVG uploads, in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Note that the patch in 2.6.4 allows SVG uploads but the uploaded SVG files are sanitized.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1723 | The SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters in all versions up to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1723</link><description>The SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.58.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Affected parameters include: $instance['fonts']['title_options']['tag'], $headline_tag, $sub_headline_tag, $feature['icon'].</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1751 | The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the question_id para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1751</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the question_id parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber/student access or higher, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1763 | The Wp Social Login and Register Social Counter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing cap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1763</link><description>The Wp Social Login and Register Social Counter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the /wp_social/v1/ REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable and disable certain providers for the social share and login features.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1772 | The Play.ht – Make Your Blog Posts Accessible With Text to Speech Audio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1772</link><description>The Play.ht – Make Your Blog Posts Accessible With Text to Speech Audio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.4 via deserialization of untrusted input from the play_podcast_data post meta. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1793 | The AWeber – Free Sign Up Form and Landing Page Builder Plugin for Lead Generation and Email Newsletter Growth plugin for WordPress is vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1793</link><description>The AWeber – Free Sign Up Form and Landing Page Builder Plugin for Lead Generation and Email Newsletter Growth plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'post_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 7.3.14 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1806 | The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1806</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 4.15.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1843 | The Auto Affiliate Links plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the aa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1843</link><description>The Auto Affiliate Links plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the aalAddLink function in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or higher, to add arbitrary links to posts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1854 | The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1854</link><description>The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the blockId parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1862 | The WooCommerce Add to Cart Custom Redirect plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1862</link><description>The WooCommerce Add to Cart Custom Redirect plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wcr_dismiss_admin_notice' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to update the values of arbitrary site options to 'dismissed'.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1894 | The Burst Statistics – Privacy-Friendly Analytics for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1894</link><description>The Burst Statistics – Privacy-Friendly Analytics for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'burst_total_pageviews_count' custom meta field in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Note that this exploit only functions if the victim has the 'Show Toolbar when viewing site' option enabled in their profile.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1935 | The Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress – Get More Website Traffic, Email Subscribers, and Social Followers plugin for WordPress is vulner...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1935</link><description>The Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress – Get More Website Traffic, Email Subscribers, and Social Followers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘parent_url’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1950 | The Product Carousel Slider &amp; Grid Ultimate for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1950</link><description>The Product Carousel Slider &amp; Grid Ultimate for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.7 via deserialization of untrusted input via shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1951 | The Logo Showcase Ultimate – Logo Carousel, Logo Slider &amp; Logo Grid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1951</link><description>The Logo Showcase Ultimate – Logo Carousel, Logo Slider &amp; Logo Grid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.8 via deserialization via shortcode of untrusted input. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1985 | The Simple Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Display Name' parameter in all versions up ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1985</link><description>The Simple Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Display Name' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This vulnerability requires social engineering to successfully exploit, and the impact would be very limited due to the attacker requiring a user to login as the user with the injected payload for execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28670 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/freelist_main.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28670</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/freelist_main.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28672 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/media_edit.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28672</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/media_edit.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28677 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/article_keywords_main.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28677</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/article_keywords_main.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2006 | The Post Grid, Slider &amp; Carousel Ultimate – with Shortcode, Gutenberg Block &amp; Elementor Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Obj...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2006</link><description>The Post Grid, Slider &amp; Carousel Ultimate – with Shortcode, Gutenberg Block &amp; Elementor Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.7 via deserialization of untrusted input in the outpost_shortcode_metabox_markup function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2020 | The Calculated Fields Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the form page href parameter in all version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2020</link><description>The Calculated Fields Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the form page href parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.56 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Exploitation requires the professional version or higher.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2028 | The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Covid-19 Stats Widget in all ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2028</link><description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Covid-19 Stats Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2030 | The Database for Contact Form 7, WPforms, Elementor forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2030</link><description>The Database for Contact Form 7, WPforms, Elementor forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2106 | The MasterStudy LMS WordPress Plugin – for Online Courses and Education plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2106</link><description>The MasterStudy LMS WordPress Plugin – for Online Courses and Education plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 3.2.10. This can allow unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including all registered user's username and email addresses which can be used to help perform future attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2126 | The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Registration Form widget in all version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2126</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Registration Form widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.32 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2172 | The Malware Scanner plugin and the Web Application Firewall plugin for WordPress (both by MiniOrange) are vulnerable to privilege escalation...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2172</link><description>The Malware Scanner plugin and the Web Application Firewall plugin for WordPress (both by MiniOrange) are vulnerable to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the mo_wpns_init() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.7.2 (for Malware Scanner) and 2.1.1 (for Web Application Firewall). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers  to escalate their privileges to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2194 | The WP Statistics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the URL search parameter in all versions up to, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2194</link><description>The WP Statistics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the URL search parameter in all versions up to, and including, 14.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2252 | The Droit Elementor Addons – Widgets, Blocks, Templates Library For Elementor Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Sit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2252</link><description>The Droit Elementor Addons – Widgets, Blocks, Templates Library For Elementor Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as URL. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2286 | The Sky Addons for Elementor (Free Templates Library, Live Copy, Animations, Post Grid, Post Carousel, Particles, Sliders, Chart) plugin for...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2286</link><description>The Sky Addons for Elementor (Free Templates Library, Live Copy, Animations, Post Grid, Post Carousel, Particles, Sliders, Chart) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the wrapper link URL value in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2293 | The Site Reviews plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the user display name in all versions up to, and incl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2293</link><description>The Site Reviews plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the user display name in all versions up to, and including, 6.11.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28671 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/stepselect_main.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28671</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/stepselect_main.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28673 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/mychannel_edit.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28673</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/mychannel_edit.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28678 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/article_description_main.ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28678</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/article_description_main.php</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25153 | Remote Code Execution in FileCatalyst Workflow 5.x prior to 5.1.6 Build 114</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25153</link><description>A directory traversal within the ‘ftpservlet’ of the FileCatalyst Workflow Web Portal allows files to be uploaded outside of the intended ‘uploadtemp’ directory with a specially crafted POST request. In situations where a file is successfully uploaded to web portal’s DocumentRoot, specially crafted JSP files could be used to execute code, including web shells.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25154 | Path Traversal in FileCatalyst Direct 3.8.8 and Earlier</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25154</link><description>Improper URL validation leads to path traversal in FileCatalyst Direct 3.8.8 and earlier allowing an encoded payload to cause the web server to return files located outside of the web root which may lead to data leakage.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25155 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in FileCatalyst Direct 3.8.8 and earlier</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25155</link><description>In FileCatalyst Direct 3.8.8 and earlier through 3.8.6, the web server does not properly sanitize illegal characters in a URL which is then displayed on a subsequent error page. A malicious actor could craft a URL which would then execute arbitrary code within an HTML script tag.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52608 | firmware: arm_scmi: Check mailbox/SMT channel for consistency</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52608</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

firmware: arm_scmi: Check mailbox/SMT channel for consistency

On reception of a completion interrupt the shared memory area is accessed
to retrieve the message header at first and then, if the message sequence
number identifies a transaction which is still pending, the related
payload is fetched too.

When an SCMI command times out the channel ownership remains with the
platform until eventually a late reply is received and, as a consequence,
any further transmission attempt remains pending, waiting for the channel
to be relinquished by the platform.

Once that late reply is received the channel ownership is given back
to the agent and any pending request is then allowed to proceed and
overwrite the SMT area of the just delivered late reply; then the wait
for the reply to the new request starts.

It has been observed that the spurious IRQ related to the late reply can
be wrongly associated with the freshly enqueued request: when that happens
the SCMI stack in-flight lookup procedure is fooled by the fact that the
message header now present in the SMT area is related to the new pending
transaction, even though the real reply has still to arrive.

This race-condition on the A2P channel can be detected by looking at the
channel status bits: a genuine reply from the platform will have set the
channel free bit before triggering the completion IRQ.

Add a consistency check to validate such condition in the A2P ISR.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26629 | nfsd: fix RELEASE_LOCKOWNER</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26629</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nfsd: fix RELEASE_LOCKOWNER

The test on so_count in nfsd4_release_lockowner() is nonsense and
harmful.  Revert to using check_for_locks(), changing that to not sleep.

First: harmful.
As is documented in the kdoc comment for nfsd4_release_lockowner(), the
test on so_count can transiently return a false positive resulting in a
return of NFS4ERR_LOCKS_HELD when in fact no locks are held.  This is
clearly a protocol violation and with the Linux NFS client it can cause
incorrect behaviour.

If RELEASE_LOCKOWNER is sent while some other thread is still
processing a LOCK request which failed because, at the time that request
was received, the given owner held a conflicting lock, then the nfsd
thread processing that LOCK request can hold a reference (conflock) to
the lock owner that causes nfsd4_release_lockowner() to return an
incorrect error.

The Linux NFS client ignores that NFS4ERR_LOCKS_HELD error because it
never sends NFS4_RELEASE_LOCKOWNER without first releasing any locks, so
it knows that the error is impossible.  It assumes the lock owner was in
fact released so it feels free to use the same lock owner identifier in
some later locking request.

When it does reuse a lock owner identifier for which a previous RELEASE
failed, it will naturally use a lock_seqid of zero.  However the server,
which didn't release the lock owner, will expect a larger lock_seqid and
so will respond with NFS4ERR_BAD_SEQID.

So clearly it is harmful to allow a false positive, which testing
so_count allows.

The test is nonsense because ... well... it doesn't mean anything.

so_count is the sum of three different counts.
1/ the set of states listed on so_stateids
2/ the set of active vfs locks owned by any of those states
3/ various transient counts such as for conflicting locks.

When it is tested against '2' it is clear that one of these is the
transient reference obtained by find_lockowner_str_locked().  It is not
clear what the other one is expected to be.

In practice, the count is often 2 because there is precisely one state
on so_stateids.  If there were more, this would fail.

In my testing I see two circumstances when RELEASE_LOCKOWNER is called.
In one case, CLOSE is called before RELEASE_LOCKOWNER.  That results in
all the lock states being removed, and so the lockowner being discarded
(it is removed when there are no more references which usually happens
when the lock state is discarded).  When nfsd4_release_lockowner() finds
that the lock owner doesn't exist, it returns success.

The other case shows an so_count of '2' and precisely one state listed
in so_stateid.  It appears that the Linux client uses a separate lock
owner for each file resulting in one lock state per lock owner, so this
test on '2' is safe.  For another client it might not be safe.

So this patch changes check_for_locks() to use the (newish)
find_any_file_locked() so that it doesn't take a reference on the
nfs4_file and so never calls nfsd_file_put(), and so never sleeps.  With
this check is it safe to restore the use of check_for_locks() rather
than testing so_count against the mysterious '2'.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2247 | JFrog Artifactory Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2247</link><description>JFrog Artifactory versions below 7.77.7, 7.82.1, are vulnerable to DOM-based cross-site scripting due to improper handling of the import override mechanism.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1507 | The Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'title_tags' attribute of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1507</link><description>The Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'title_tags' attribute of the Rubix widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.13.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 13:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1508 | The Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'settings['title_tags']' a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1508</link><description>The Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'settings['title_tags']' attribute of the Mercury widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.13.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 13:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28675 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/diy_edit.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28675</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /dede/diy_edit.php</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 13:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28684 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/module_main.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28684</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/module_main.php</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 13:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28665 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/article_add.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28665</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/article_add.php</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 12:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28666 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/media_add.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28666</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/media_add.php</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 12:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28667 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/templets_one_edit.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28667</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/templets_one_edit.php</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 12:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28668 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/mychannel_add.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28668</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/mychannel_add.php</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 12:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28429 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/archives_do.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28429</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/archives_do.php</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 12:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28430 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/catalog_edit.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28430</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/catalog_edit.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 12:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28431 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/catalog_del.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28431</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/catalog_del.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 12:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28432 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/article_edit.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28432</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /dede/article_edit.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 12:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2415 | Command injection vulnerability in Movistar 4G router</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2415</link><description>Command injection vulnerability in Movistar 4G router affecting version ES_WLD71-T1_v2.0.201820. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to execute commands inside the router by making a POST request to the URL '/cgi-bin/gui.cgi'.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 11:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2414 | Unprotected Primary Channel vulnerability in Movistar 4G router</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2414</link><description>The primary channel is unprotected on Movistar 4G router affecting E version S_WLD71-T1_v2.0.201820. This device has the 'adb' service open on port 5555 and provides access to a shell with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 11:24:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2416 | Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Movistar 4G router</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2416</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Movistar's 4G router affecting version ES_WLD71-T1_v2.0.201820. This vulnerability allows an attacker to force an end user to execute unwanted actions in a web application in which they are currently authenticated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 11:24:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1979 | Quarkus: information leak in annotation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1979</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Quarkus. In certain conditions related to the CI process, git credentials could be inadvertently published, which could put the git repository at risk.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 09:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2123 | The Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2123</link><description>The Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the several parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 09:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32335 | IBM Maximo Application Suite information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32335</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite 8.10, 8.11 and IBM Maximo Asset Management 7.6.1.3 stores sensitive information in URL parameters. This may lead to information disclosure if unauthorized parties have access to the URLs via server logs, referrer header or browser history.  IBM X-Force ID:  255075.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 09:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28517 | IBM Sterling Partner Engagement Manager cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28517</link><description>IBM Sterling Partner Engagement Manager 6.1.2, 6.2.0, and 6.2.2 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  250421.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 09:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38723 | Maximo Asset Management cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38723</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite 7.6.1.3 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  262192.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 09:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43043 | IBM Maximo Application Suite information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43043</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite - Maximo Mobile for EAM 8.10 and 8.11 could disclose sensitive information to a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  266875.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 09:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-10123 | Wago: Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input in wbm of multiple products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10123</link><description>An unautheticated remote attacker could send specifically crafted packets to a affected device. If an authenticated user then views that data in a specific page of the web-based management a buffer overflow will be triggered to gain full access of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 08:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25090 | Wago: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation in multiple devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25090</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can use an XSS attack due to improper neutralization of input during web page generation. User interaction is required. This leads to a limited impact of confidentiality and integrity but no impact of availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 08:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26529 | An issue in mz-automation libiec61850 v.1.5.3 and before, allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the mmsServer_hand...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26529</link><description>An issue in mz-automation libiec61850 v.1.5.3 and before, allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the mmsServer_handleDeleteNamedVariableListRequest function of src/mms/iso_mms/server/mms_named_variable_list_service.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 08:09:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28623 | RiteCMS v3.0.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component main_menu/edit_section.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28623</link><description>RiteCMS v3.0.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component main_menu/edit_section.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 07:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27440 | The Toyoko Inn official App for iOS versions prior to 1.13.0 and Toyoko Inn official App for Android versions prior 1.3.14 don't properly ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27440</link><description>The Toyoko Inn official App for iOS versions prior to 1.13.0 and Toyoko Inn official App for Android versions prior 1.3.14 don't properly verify server certificates, which allows a man-in-the-middle attacker to spoof servers and obtain sensitive information via a crafted certificate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 05:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2400 | Use after free in Performance Manager in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.128 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corrupt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2400</link><description>Use after free in Performance Manager in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.128 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 04:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2413 | Intumit SmartRobot - Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2413</link><description>Intumit SmartRobot uses a fixed encryption key for authentication. Remote attackers can use this key to encrypt a string composed of the user's name and timestamp to generate an authentication code. With this authentication code, they can obtain administrator privileges and subsequently execute arbitrary code on the remote server using built-in system functionality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 02:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-10130 | The Team Circle Image Slider With Lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in version 1.0. This is due to m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10130</link><description>The Team Circle Image Slider With Lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in version 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the circle_thumbnail_slider_with_lightbox_image_management_func() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to edit image data which can be used to inject malicious JavaScript, along with deleting images, and uploading malicious files via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 02:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2412 | Heimavista Rpage and Epage - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2412</link><description>The disabling function of the user registration page for Heimavista Rpage and Epage is not properly implemented, allowing remote attackers to complete user registration on sites where user registration is supposed to be disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 02:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4839 | The WP Go Maps for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in versions up to, and including, 9.0.32 due to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4839</link><description>The WP Go Maps for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in versions up to, and including, 9.0.32 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 02:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1582 | The WP Go Maps (formerly WP Google Maps) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpgmza' shortco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1582</link><description>The WP Go Maps (formerly WP Google Maps) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpgmza' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 9.0.32 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 02:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>