<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 06:00:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-4661 | WP Reset &amp;lt;= 2.02 - Missing Authorization to License Key Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4661</link><description>The WP Reset plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the save_ajax function in all versions up to, and including, 2.02. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to modify the value fo the 'License Key' field for the 'Activate Pro License' setting.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 06:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5087 | Minimal Coming Soon – Coming Soon Page &amp;lt;= 2.38 - Missing Authorization to Limited Settings Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5087</link><description>The Minimal Coming Soon – Coming Soon Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the validate_ajax, deactivate_ajax, and save_ajax functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.38. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to edit the license key, which could disable features of the plugin.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 06:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5613 | Formula &amp;lt;= 0.5.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via quality_customizer_notify_dismiss_action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5613</link><description>The Formula theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ parameter in the 'quality_customizer_notify_dismiss_action' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 0.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 06:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5638 | Formula &amp;lt;= 0.5.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via ti_customizer_notify_dismiss_recommended_plugins</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5638</link><description>The Formula theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ parameter in the 'ti_customizer_notify_dismiss_recommended_plugins' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 0.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 06:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3668 | PowerPack Pro for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.10.17 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3668</link><description>The PowerPack Pro for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.17. This is due to the plugin not restricting low privileged users from setting a default role for a registration form. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to create a registration form with administrator set as the default role and then register as an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 04:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5770 | WP Force SSL &amp;amp; HTTPS SSL Redirect &amp;lt;= 1.66 - Missing Authorization to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5770</link><description>The WP Force SSL &amp; HTTPS SSL Redirect plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ajax_save_setting' function in versions up to, and including, 1.66. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, subscriber-level permissions and above, to update the plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 04:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5663 | Cards for Beaver Builder &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Cards Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5663</link><description>The Cards for Beaver Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Cards widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 02:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0444 | GStreamer AV1 Video Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0444</link><description>GStreamer AV1 Video Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of GStreamer. Interaction with this library is required to exploit this vulnerability but attack vectors may vary depending on the implementation.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of tile list data within AV1-encoded video files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22873.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 22:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49223 | Precor touchscreen console P62, P80, and P82 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information because the root password is stor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49223</link><description>Precor touchscreen console P62, P80, and P82 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information because the root password is stored in /etc/passwd. An attacker could exploit this to extract files and obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 20:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49224 | Precor touchscreen console P62, P80, and P82 contains a default SSH public key in the authorized_keys file. A remote attacker could use this...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49224</link><description>Precor touchscreen console P62, P80, and P82 contains a default SSH public key in the authorized_keys file. A remote attacker could use this key to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 20:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7261 | Inappropriate implementation in Google Updator prior to 1.3.36.351 in Google Chrome allowed a local attacker to perform privilege escalation...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7261</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Google Updator prior to 1.3.36.351 in Google Chrome allowed a local attacker to perform privilege escalation via a malicious file. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 20:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1694 | Inappropriate implementation in Google Updator prior to 1.3.36.351 in Google Chrome allowed a local attacker to bypass discretionary access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1694</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Google Updator prior to 1.3.36.351 in Google Chrome allowed a local attacker to bypass discretionary access control via a malicious file. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 20:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49221 | Precor touchscreen console P62, P80, and P82 could allow a remote attacker (within the local network) to bypass security restrictions, and a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49221</link><description>Precor touchscreen console P62, P80, and P82 could allow a remote attacker (within the local network) to bypass security restrictions, and access the service menu, because there is a hard-coded service code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 20:21:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49222 | Precor touchscreen console P82 contains a private SSH key that corresponds to a default public key. A remote attacker could exploit this to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49222</link><description>Precor touchscreen console P82 contains a private SSH key that corresponds to a default public key. A remote attacker could exploit this to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 20:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36811 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the image upload function of aimeos-core v2024.04 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36811</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the image upload function of aimeos-core v2024.04 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PHP file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 19:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36827 | An XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in the ebookmeta.get_metadata function of ebookmeta before v1.2.8 allows attackers to access sens...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36827</link><description>An XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in the ebookmeta.get_metadata function of ebookmeta before v1.2.8 allows attackers to access sensitive information or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via crafted XML input.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 18:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37388 | An XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in the ebookmeta.get_metadata function of lxml before v4.9.1 allows attackers to access sensitive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37388</link><description>An XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in the ebookmeta.get_metadata function of lxml before v4.9.1 allows attackers to access sensitive information or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via crafted XML input.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 18:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5745 | itsourcecode Bakery Online Ordering System unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5745</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Bakery Online Ordering System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/modules/product/controller.php?action=add. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-267414 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 17:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30162 | Invision Community through 4.7.16 allows remote code execution via the applications/core/modules/admin/editor/toolbar.php IPS\core\modules\a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30162</link><description>Invision Community through 4.7.16 allows remote code execution via the applications/core/modules/admin/editor/toolbar.php IPS\core\modules\admin\editor\_toolbar::addPlugin() method. This method handles uploaded ZIP files that are extracted into the applications/core/interface/ckeditor/ckeditor/plugins/ directory without properly verifying their content. This can be exploited by admin users (with the toolbar_manage permission) to write arbitrary PHP files into that directory, leading to execution of arbitrary PHP code in the context of the web server user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 17:19:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31958 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor EExynos 2200, Exynos 1480, Exynos 2400. It lacks a check for the validation of native ha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31958</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor EExynos 2200, Exynos 1480, Exynos 2400. It lacks a check for the validation of native handles, which can result in an Out-of-Bounds Write.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 17:19:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32502 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 850, Exynos 1080, Exynos 2100, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, E...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32502</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 850, Exynos 1080, Exynos 2100, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, Exynos 1330, Exynos W920, Exynos W930. The mobile processor lacks proper reference count checking, which can result in a UAF (Use-After-Free) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 17:19:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30163 | Invision Community before 4.7.16 allow SQL injection via the applications/nexus/modules/front/store/store.php IPS\nexus\modules\front\store\...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30163</link><description>Invision Community before 4.7.16 allow SQL injection via the applications/nexus/modules/front/store/store.php IPS\nexus\modules\front\store\_store::_categoryView() method, where user input passed through the filter request parameter is not properly sanitized before being used to execute SQL queries. This can be exploited by unauthenticated attackers to carry out Blind SQL Injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31959 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 2200, Exynos 1480, Exynos 2400. It lacks a check for the validation of native han...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31959</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 2200, Exynos 1480, Exynos 2400. It lacks a check for the validation of native handles, which can result in code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37163 | SkyScrape Secure API Requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37163</link><description>SkyScrape is a GUI Dashboard for AWS Infrastructure and Managing Resources and Usage Costs.  SkyScrape's API requests are currently unsecured HTTP requests, leading to potential vulnerabilities for the user's temporary credentials and data.  This affects version 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:22:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32503 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 850, Exynos 1080, Exynos 2100, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, E...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32503</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 850, Exynos 1080, Exynos 2100, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, Exynos 1330, Exynos W920, Exynos W930. The mobile processor lacks proper memory deallocation checking, which can result in a UAF (Use-After-Free) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 15:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36773 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Monstra CMS v3.0.4 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted pay...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36773</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Monstra CMS v3.0.4 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Themes parameter at index.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 14:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36788 | Netgear WNR614 JNR1010V2 N300-V1.1.0.54_1.0.1 does not properly set the HTTPOnly flag for cookies. This allows attackers to possibly interce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36788</link><description>Netgear WNR614 JNR1010V2 N300-V1.1.0.54_1.0.1 does not properly set the HTTPOnly flag for cookies. This allows attackers to possibly intercept and access sensitive communications between the router and connected devices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 14:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36790 | Netgear WNR614 JNR1010V2/N300-V1.1.0.54_1.0.1 was discovered to store credentials in plaintext.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36790</link><description>Netgear WNR614 JNR1010V2/N300-V1.1.0.54_1.0.1 was discovered to store credentials in plaintext.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 14:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36787 | An issue in Netgear WNR614 JNR1010V2 N300-V1.1.0.54_1.0.1 allows attackers to bypass authentication and access the administrative interface ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36787</link><description>An issue in Netgear WNR614 JNR1010V2 N300-V1.1.0.54_1.0.1 allows attackers to bypass authentication and access the administrative interface via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 14:22:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36789 | An issue in Netgear WNR614 JNR1010V2/N300-V1.1.0.54_1.0.1 allows attackers to create passwords that do not conform to defined security stand...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36789</link><description>An issue in Netgear WNR614 JNR1010V2/N300-V1.1.0.54_1.0.1 allows attackers to create passwords that do not conform to defined security standards.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 14:22:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36792 | An issue in the implementation of the WPS in Netgear WNR614 JNR1010V2/N300-V1.1.0.54_1.0.1 allows attackers to gain access to the router's p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36792</link><description>An issue in the implementation of the WPS in Netgear WNR614 JNR1010V2/N300-V1.1.0.54_1.0.1 allows attackers to gain access to the router's pin.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 14:22:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37162 | zsa Generates Error Messages Containing Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37162</link><description>zsa is a library for building typesafe server actions in Next.js. All users are impacted. The zsa application transfers the parse error stack from the server to the client in production build mode. This can potentially reveal sensitive information about the server environment, such as the machine username and directory paths. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to gain unauthorized access to sensitive server information. This information could be used to plan further attacks or gain a deeper understanding of the server infrastructure. This has been patched on `0.3.3`.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 14:22:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37160 | Formwork has a Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Description metadata</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37160</link><description>Formwork is a flat file-based Content Management System (CMS). An attackers (requires administrator privilege) to execute arbitrary web scripts by modifying site options via /panel/options/site. This type of attack is suitable for persistence, affecting visitors across all pages (except the dashboard). This vulnerability is fixed in 1.13.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 14:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31878 | IBM i information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31878</link><description>IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 Service Tools Server (SST) is vulnerable to SST user enumeration by a remote attacker.  This vulnerability can be used by a malicious actor to gather information about SST users that can be targeted in further attacks.   IBM X-Force ID:  287538.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 13:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36673 | Sourcecodester Pharmacy/Medical Store Point of Sale System 1.0 is vulnerable SQL Injection via login.php. This vulnerability stems from inad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36673</link><description>Sourcecodester Pharmacy/Medical Store Point of Sale System 1.0 is vulnerable SQL Injection via login.php. This vulnerability stems from inadequate validation of user inputs for the email and password parameters, allowing attackers to inject malicious SQL queries.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 13:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5382 | Master Addons – Free Widgets, Hover Effects, Toggle, Conditions, Animations for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.0.6.1 - Missing Authorization to MA Template Creation or Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5382</link><description>The Master Addons – Free Widgets, Hover Effects, Toggle, Conditions, Animations for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ma-template' REST API route in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create or modify existing Master Addons templates or make settings modifications related to these templates.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5438 | Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Authenticated (Instructor+) Insecure Direct Object Reference to Arbitrary Quiz Attempt Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5438</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.1 via the 'attempt_delete' function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Instructor-level access and above, to delete arbitrary quiz attempts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5542 | Master Addons – Free Widgets, Hover Effects, Toggle, Conditions, Animations for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.0.6.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Navigation Menu Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5542</link><description>The Master Addons – Free Widgets, Hover Effects, Toggle, Conditions, Animations for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Navigation Menu widget of the plugin's Mega Menu extension in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5599 | FileOrganizer &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Sensitive Information Exposure via Directory Listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5599</link><description>The FileOrganizer – Manage WordPress and Website Files plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7 via the 'fileorganizer_ajax_handler' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including backups or other sensitive information if the files have been moved to the built-in Trash folder.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5733 | itsourcecode Online Discussion Forum register_me.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5733</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Discussion Forum 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file register_me.php. The manipulation of the argument eaddress leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-267407.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 11:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5734 | itsourcecode Online Discussion Forum poster.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5734</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Online Discussion Forum 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /members/poster.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-267408.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 11:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4610 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU memory processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4610</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user to make improper GPU memory processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: from r34p0 through r40p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r34p0 through r40p0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 11:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5637 | Market Exporter &amp;lt;= 2.0.19 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5637</link><description>The Market Exporter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'remove_files' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.19. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to use path traversal to delete arbitrary files on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 11:18:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5732 | Clash Proxy Port improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5732</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Clash up to 0.20.1 on Windows. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Proxy Port. The manipulation leads to improper authentication. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to change the configuration settings. VDB-267406 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 10:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5424 | WS Form LITE &amp;lt;= 1.9.217 - Unauthenticated CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5424</link><description>The WS Form LITE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to CSV Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.9.217. This allows unauthenticated attackers to embed untrusted input into exported CSV files, which can result in code execution when these files are downloaded and opened on a local system with a vulnerable configuration.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 09:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5426 | Photo Gallery by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Image Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.8.23 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Zipped SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5426</link><description>The Photo Gallery by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Image Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘svg’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.23 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. By default, this can only be exploited by administrators, but the ability to use and configure Photo Gallery can be extended to contributors on pro versions of the plugin.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 09:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5481 | Photo Gallery by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Image Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.8.23 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Path Traversal via esc_dir Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5481</link><description>The Photo Gallery by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Image Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.23 via the esc_dir function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers to cut and paste (copy) the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information, and to cut (delete) arbitrary directories, including the root WordPress directory. By default this can be exploited by administrators only. In the premium version of the plugin, administrators can give gallery edit permissions to lower level users, which might make this exploitable by users as low as contributors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 09:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5645 | Envo Extra &amp;lt;= 1.8.23 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5645</link><description>The Envo Extra plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘button_css_id’ parameter within the Button widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.23 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 09:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4703 | One Page Express Companion &amp;lt;= 1.6.37 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via one_page_express_contact_form Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4703</link><description>The One Page Express Companion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's one_page_express_contact_form shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.37 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 07:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4488 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.3.976 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4488</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘inline_list’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.3.976 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 07:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4489 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.3.976 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG Uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4489</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘custom_upload_mimes’ function in versions up to, and including, 1.3.976 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 07:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4451 | Colibri Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.0.276 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via colibri_video_player Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4451</link><description>The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's colibri_video_player shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.276 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 07:07:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3288 | Logo Slider &amp;lt; 4.0.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3288</link><description>The Logo Slider  WordPress plugin before 4.0.0 does not validate and escape some of its Slider Settings before outputting them back in attributes, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 06:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4620 | ArForms &amp;lt; 6.6 - Unauthenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4620</link><description>The ARForms - Premium WordPress Form Builder Plugin WordPress plugin before 6.6 allows unauthenticated users to modify uploaded files in such a way that PHP code can be uploaded when an upload file input is included on a form</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 06:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4621 | ArForms &amp;lt; 6.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4621</link><description>The ARForms - Premium WordPress Form Builder Plugin WordPress plugin before 6.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 06:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4756 | WP Backpack &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4756</link><description>The WP Backpack WordPress plugin through 2.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 06:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5003 | WP Stacker &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5003</link><description>The WP Stacker WordPress plugin through 1.8.5 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 06:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6491 | Strong Testimonials &amp;lt;= 3.1.12 - Authenticated(Contributor+) Improper Authorization to Views Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6491</link><description>The Strong Testimonials plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to an improper capability check on the wpmtst_save_view_sticky function in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.12. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to modify favorite views.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 05:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3592 | Quiz And Survey Master – Best Quiz, Exam and Survey Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 9.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3592</link><description>The Quiz And Survey Master – Best Quiz, Exam and Survey Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'question_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 9.0.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 05:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4042 | Post Grid, Form Maker, Popup Maker, WooCommerce Blocks, Post Blocks, Post Carousel - Combo Blocks &amp;lt;= 2.2.80 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Block Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4042</link><description>The Post Grid, Form Maker, Popup Maker, WooCommerce Blocks, Post Blocks, Post Carousel – Combo Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'class' attribute of the menu-wrap-item block in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.80 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 05:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4354 | TablePress – Tables in WordPress made easy &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Authenticated (Author+) Server-Side Request Forgery via DNS Rebind</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4354</link><description>The TablePress – Tables in WordPress made easy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.3 via the get_files_to_import() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services. Due to the complex nature of protecting against DNS rebind attacks in WordPress software, we settled on the developer simply restricting the usage of the URL import functionality to just administrators. While this is not optimal, we feel this poses a minimal risk to most site owners and ideally WordPress core would correct this issue in wp_safe_remote_get() and other functions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 05:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4902 | Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 -Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4902</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘course_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with admin access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 04:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5612 | Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp;amp; WooCommerce Builders &amp;lt;= 5.8.15 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Lightbox and Modal Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5612</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘eael_lightbox_open_btn_icon’ parameter within the Lightbox &amp; Modal widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.8.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 04:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5640 | Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor (Revolution of a slider, Hero Slider, Ecommerce Slider) &amp;lt;= 3.14.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Pacific Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5640</link><description>The Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor (Revolution of a slider, Hero Slider, Ecommerce Slider) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ attribute within the Pacific widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.14.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 04:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36082 | SQL injection vulnerability in Music Store - WordPress eCommerce versions prior to 1.1.14 allows a remote authenticated attacker with an adm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36082</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Music Store - WordPress eCommerce versions prior to 1.1.14 allows a remote authenticated attacker with an administrative privilege to execute arbitrary SQL commands. Information stored in the database may be obtained or altered by the attacker.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 03:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1988 | Post Grid, Form Maker, Popup Maker, WooCommerce Blocks, Post Blocks, Post Carousel – Combo Blocks &amp;lt;= 2.2.80 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1988</link><description>The Post Grid, Form Maker, Popup Maker, WooCommerce Blocks, Post Blocks, Post Carousel – Combo Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tag' attribute in blocks in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.80 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 03:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37383 | Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.7 and 1.6.x before 1.6.7 allows XSS via SVG animate attributes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37383</link><description>Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.7 and 1.6.x before 1.6.7 allows XSS via SVG animate attributes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 03:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37384 | Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.7 and 1.6.x before 1.6.7 allows XSS via list columns from user preferences.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37384</link><description>Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.7 and 1.6.x before 1.6.7 allows XSS via list columns from user preferences.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 03:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37385 | Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.7 and 1.6.x before 1.6.7 on Windows allows command injection via im_convert_path and im_identify_path. NOTE: th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37385</link><description>Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.7 and 1.6.x before 1.6.7 on Windows allows command injection via im_convert_path and im_identify_path. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2020-12641.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 03:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4887 | Qi Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4887</link><description>The Qi Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.2 via the 'behavior' attributes found in the qi_addons_for_elementor_blog_list shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include remote files on the server, resulting in code execution. Please note that this requires an attacker to create a non-existent directory or target an instance where file_exists won't return false with a non-existent directory in the path, in order to successfully exploit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 03:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5425 | WP jQuery Lightbox &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via title Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5425</link><description>The WP jQuery Lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘title’ attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 03:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1768 | Clever Fox &amp;lt;= 25.2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1768</link><description>The Clever Fox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's info box block in all versions up to, and including, 25.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 02:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3987 | WP Mobile Menu – The Mobile-Friendly Responsive Menu &amp;lt;= 2.8.4.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Image Alt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3987</link><description>The WP Mobile Menu – The Mobile-Friendly Responsive Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via image alt text in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 02:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5607 | GDPR CCPA Compliance &amp;amp; Cookie Consent Banner &amp;lt;= 2.7.0 - Missing Authorization to Settings Update and Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5607</link><description>The GDPR CCPA Compliance &amp; Cookie Consent Banner plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on several functions named ajaxUpdateSettings() in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify the plugin's settings, update page content, send arbitrary emails and inject malicious web scripts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 02:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32475 | Dell BIOS contains a missing support for integrity check vulnerability. An attacker with physical access to the system could potentially byp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32475</link><description>Dell BIOS contains a missing support for integrity check vulnerability. An attacker with physical access to the system could potentially bypass security mechanisms to run arbitrary code on the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 02:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6876 | Clever Fox – One Click Website Importer by Nayra Themes &amp;lt;= 25.2.0 - Missing Authorization to arbitrary theme activation via clever-fox-activate-theme</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6876</link><description>The Clever Fox – One Click Website Importer by Nayra Themes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'clever-fox-activate-theme' function in all versions up to, and including, 25.2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access and above, to modify the active theme, including to an invalid value which can take down the site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 02:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1689 | WooCommerce Tools &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+)  Plugin Module Deactivation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1689</link><description>The WooCommerce Tools plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the woocommerce_tool_toggle_module() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to deactivate arbitrary plugin modules.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 02:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4968 | netplan leaks the private key of wireguard to local users. A security fix will be released soon.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4968</link><description>netplan leaks the private key of wireguard to local users. A security fix will be released soon.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 01:02:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37539 | HCL Domino Catalog template is susceptible to a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37539</link><description>The Domino Catalog template is susceptible to a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An attacker with the ability to edit documents in the catalog application/database created from this template can embed a cross site scripting attack.  The attack would be activated by an end user clicking it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 22:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51847 | An issue in obgm and Libcoap v.a3ed466 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via thecoap_context_t function in the src/coap_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51847</link><description>An issue in obgm and Libcoap v.a3ed466 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via thecoap_context_t function in the src/coap_threadsafe.c:297:3 component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 21:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36774 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Monstra CMS v3.0.4 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PHP file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36774</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Monstra CMS v3.0.4 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PHP file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 21:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36775 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Monstra CMS v3.0.4 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted pay...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36775</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Monstra CMS v3.0.4 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the About Me parameter in the Edit Profile page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 21:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4013 | Failure to update BT Mesh Replay Protection List</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4013</link><description>A bug exists in the API, mesh_node_power_off(), which fails to copy the contents of the Replay Protection 
List (RPL) from RAM to NVM before powering down, resulting in the ability to replay unsaved messages. Note that as of June 2024, the Gecko SDK was renamed to the Simplicity SDK, and the versioning scheme 
was changed from Gecko SDK vX.Y.Z to Simplicity SDK YYYY.MM.Patch#.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 21:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22524 | dnspod-sr 0dfbd37 is vulnerable to buffer overflow.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22524</link><description>dnspod-sr 0dfbd37 is vulnerable to buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22525 | dnspod-sr 0dfbd37 contains a SEGV.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22525</link><description>dnspod-sr 0dfbd37 contains a SEGV.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24192 | robdns commit d76d2e6 was discovered to contain a heap overflow via the component block-&gt;filename at /src/zonefile-insertion.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24192</link><description>robdns commit d76d2e6 was discovered to contain a heap overflow via the component block-&gt;filename at /src/zonefile-insertion.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24194 | robdns commit d76d2e6 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the item-&gt;tokens component at /src/conf-parse.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24194</link><description>robdns commit d76d2e6 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the item-&gt;tokens component at /src/conf-parse.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 21:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24195 | robdns commit d76d2e6 was discovered to contain a misaligned address at /src/zonefile-insertion.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24195</link><description>robdns commit d76d2e6 was discovered to contain a misaligned address at /src/zonefile-insertion.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 21:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24198 | smartdns commit 54b4dc was discovered to contain a misaligned address at smartdns/src/util.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24198</link><description>smartdns commit 54b4dc was discovered to contain a misaligned address at smartdns/src/util.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 21:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24199 | smartdns commit 54b4dc was discovered to contain a misaligned address at smartdns/src/dns.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24199</link><description>smartdns commit 54b4dc was discovered to contain a misaligned address at smartdns/src/dns.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 21:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49441 | dnsmasq 2.9 is vulnerable to Integer Overflow via forward_query.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49441</link><description>dnsmasq 2.9 is vulnerable to Integer Overflow via forward_query.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 21:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36823 | The encrypt() function of Ninja Core v7.0.0 was discovered to use a weak cryptographic algorithm, leading to a possible leakage of sensitive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36823</link><description>The encrypt() function of Ninja Core v7.0.0 was discovered to use a weak cryptographic algorithm, leading to a possible leakage of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 21:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32752 | Johnson Controls Software House iStar Pro Door Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32752</link><description>Under certain circumstances communications between the ICU tool and an iSTAR Pro door controller is susceptible to Machine-in-the-Middle attacks which could impact door control and configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 21:00:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36795 | Insecure permissions in Netgear WNR614 JNR1010V2/N300-V1.1.0.54_1.0.1 allows attackers to access URLs and directories embedded within the fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36795</link><description>Insecure permissions in Netgear WNR614 JNR1010V2/N300-V1.1.0.54_1.0.1 allows attackers to access URLs and directories embedded within the firmware via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 21:00:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22074 | Dynamsoft Service 1.8.1025 through 1.8.2013, 1.7.0330 through 1.7.2531, 1.6.0428 through 1.6.1112, 1.5.0625 through 1.5.3116, 1.4.0618 throu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22074</link><description>Dynamsoft Service 1.8.1025 through 1.8.2013, 1.7.0330 through 1.7.2531, 1.6.0428 through 1.6.1112, 1.5.0625 through 1.5.3116, 1.4.0618 through 1.4.1230, and 1.0.516 through 1.3.0115 has Incorrect Access Control. This is fixed in 1.8.2014, 1.7.4212, 1.6.3212, 1.5.31212, 1.4.3212, and 1.3.3212.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 20:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36730 | Improper input validation in OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via inputting negative values i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36730</link><description>Improper input validation in OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via inputting negative values into the oneflow.zeros/ones parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 19:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37154 | Evmos allows unvested token delegations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37154</link><description>Evmos is the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) Hub on the Cosmos Network. Users are able to delegate tokens that have not yet been vested. This affects employees and grantees who have funds managed via `ClawbackVestingAccount`. This affects 18.1.0 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 19:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2359 | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2359</link><description>A vulnerability in the parisneo/lollms-webui version 9.3 allows attackers to bypass intended access restrictions and execute arbitrary code. The issue arises from the application's handling of the `/execute_code` endpoint, which is intended to be blocked from external access by default. However, attackers can exploit the `/update_setting` endpoint, which lacks proper access control, to modify the `host` configuration at runtime. By changing the `host` setting to an attacker-controlled value, the restriction on the `/execute_code` endpoint can be bypassed, leading to remote code execution. This vulnerability is due to improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command (`Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command`).</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 19:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2360 | Path Traversal leading to Remote Code Execution in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2360</link><description>parisneo/lollms-webui is vulnerable to path traversal attacks that can lead to remote code execution due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied input in the 'Database path' and 'PDF LaTeX path' settings. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating these settings to execute arbitrary code on the targeted server. The issue affects the latest version of the software. The vulnerability stems from the application's handling of the 'discussion_db_name' and 'pdf_latex_path' parameters, which do not properly validate file paths, allowing for directory traversal. This vulnerability can also lead to further file exposure and other attack vectors by manipulating the 'discussion_db_name' parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 19:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2965 | Denial-of-Service in LangChain SitemapLoader in langchain-ai/langchain</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2965</link><description>A Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerability exists in the `SitemapLoader` class of the `langchain-ai/langchain` repository, affecting all versions. The `parse_sitemap` method, responsible for parsing sitemaps and extracting URLs, lacks a mechanism to prevent infinite recursion when a sitemap URL refers to the current sitemap itself. This oversight allows for the possibility of an infinite loop, leading to a crash by exceeding the maximum recursion depth in Python. This vulnerability can be exploited to occupy server socket/port resources and crash the Python process, impacting the availability of services relying on this functionality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 19:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3150 | Privilege Escalation in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3150</link><description>In mintplex-labs/anything-llm, a vulnerability exists in the thread update process that allows users with Default or Manager roles to escalate their privileges to Administrator. The issue arises from improper input validation when handling HTTP POST requests to the endpoint `/workspace/:slug/thread/:threadSlug/update`. Specifically, the application fails to validate or check user input before passing it to the `workspace_thread` Prisma model for execution. This oversight allows attackers to craft a Prisma relation query operation that manipulates the `users` model to change a user's role to admin. Successful exploitation grants attackers the highest level of user privileges, enabling them to see and perform all actions within the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 19:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3408 | Authentication Bypass and RCE in man-group/dtale</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3408</link><description>man-group/dtale version 3.10.0 is vulnerable to an authentication bypass and remote code execution (RCE) due to improper input validation. The vulnerability arises from a hardcoded `SECRET_KEY` in the flask configuration, allowing attackers to forge a session cookie if authentication is enabled. Additionally, the application fails to properly restrict custom filter queries, enabling attackers to execute arbitrary code on the server by bypassing the restriction on the `/update-settings` endpoint, even when `enable_custom_filters` is not enabled. This vulnerability allows attackers to bypass authentication mechanisms and execute remote code on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 19:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5124 | Timing Attack Vulnerability in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5124</link><description>A timing attack vulnerability exists in the gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt repository, specifically within the password comparison logic. The vulnerability is present in version 20240310 of the software, where passwords are compared using the '=' operator in Python. This method of comparison allows an attacker to guess passwords based on the timing of each character's comparison. The issue arises from the code segment that checks a password for a particular username, which can lead to the exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor. An attacker exploiting this vulnerability could potentially guess user passwords, compromising the security of the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 19:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5328 | SSRF Vulnerability in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5328</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in the lunary-ai/lunary application, specifically within the endpoint '/auth/saml/tto/download-idp-xml'. The vulnerability arises due to the application's failure to validate user-supplied URLs before using them in server-side requests. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted request to the affected endpoint, allowing them to make unauthorized requests to internal or external resources. This could lead to the disclosure of sensitive information, service disruption, or further attacks against the network infrastructure. The issue affects the latest version of the application as of the report.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 19:15:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45192 | IBM Engineering Requirements Management DOORS Next XML external entity injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45192</link><description>IBM Engineering Requirements Management DOORS Next 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 is vulnerable to an XML External Entity Injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.  IBM X-Force ID:  268758.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2032 | Race Condition Vulnerability in zenml-io/zenml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2032</link><description>A race condition vulnerability exists in zenml-io/zenml versions up to and including 0.55.3, which allows for the creation of multiple users with the same username when requests are sent in parallel. This issue was fixed in version 0.55.5. The vulnerability arises due to insufficient handling of concurrent user creation requests, leading to data inconsistencies and potential authentication problems. Specifically, concurrent processes may overwrite or corrupt user data, complicating user identification and posing security risks. This issue is particularly concerning for APIs that rely on usernames as input parameters, such as PUT /api/v1/users/test_race, where it could lead to further complications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:57:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36732 | An issue in OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) when an empty array is processed with oneflow.te...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36732</link><description>An issue in OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) when an empty array is processed with oneflow.tensordot.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:57:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37153 | Evmos&amp;#x27;s contract balance not updating correctly after interchain transaction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37153</link><description>Evmos is the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) Hub on the Cosmos Network. There is an issue with how to liquid stake using Safe which itself is a contract. The bug only appears when there is a local state change together with an ICS20 transfer in the same function and uses the contract's balance, that is using the contract address as the sender parameter in an ICS20 transfer using the ICS20 precompile. This is in essence the "infinite money glitch" allowing contracts to double the supply of Evmos after each transaction.The issue has been patched in versions &gt;=V18.1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:57:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3404 | Improper Access Control in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3404</link><description>In gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt, specifically the version tagged as 20240121, there exists a vulnerability due to improper access control mechanisms. This flaw allows an authenticated attacker to bypass intended access restrictions and read the `history` files of other users, potentially leading to unauthorized access to sensitive information. The vulnerability is present in the application's handling of access control for the `history` path, where no adequate mechanism is in place to prevent an authenticated user from accessing another user's chat history files. This issue poses a significant risk as it could allow attackers to obtain sensitive information from the chat history of other users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:57:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5187 | Arbitrary File Overwrite in download_model_with_test_data in onnx/onnx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5187</link><description>A vulnerability in the `download_model_with_test_data` function of the onnx/onnx framework, version 1.16.0, allows for arbitrary file overwrite due to inadequate prevention of path traversal attacks in malicious tar files. This vulnerability enables attackers to overwrite any file on the system, potentially leading to remote code execution, deletion of system, personal, or application files, thus impacting the integrity and availability of the system. The issue arises from the function's handling of tar file extraction without performing security checks on the paths within the tar file, as demonstrated by the ability to overwrite the `/home/kali/.ssh/authorized_keys` file by specifying an absolute path in the malicious tar file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:57:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5248 | Improper Access Control in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5248</link><description>In lunary-ai/lunary version 1.2.5, an improper access control vulnerability exists due to a missing permission check in the `GET /v1/users/me/org` endpoint. The platform's role definitions restrict the `Prompt Editor` role to prompt management and project viewing/listing capabilities, explicitly excluding access to user information. However, the endpoint fails to enforce this restriction, allowing users with the `Prompt Editor` role to access the full list of users in the organization. This vulnerability allows unauthorized access to sensitive user information, violating the intended access controls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:57:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1873 | Path Traversal and Denial of Service in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1873</link><description>parisneo/lollms-webui is vulnerable to path traversal and denial of service attacks due to an exposed `/select_database` endpoint in version a9d16b0. The endpoint improperly handles file paths, allowing attackers to specify absolute paths when interacting with the `DiscussionsDB` instance. This flaw enables attackers to create directories anywhere on the system where the application has permissions, potentially leading to denial of service by creating directories with names of critical files, such as HTTPS certificate files, causing server startup failures. Additionally, attackers can manipulate the database path, resulting in the loss of client data by constantly changing the file location to an attacker-controlled location, scattering the data across the filesystem and making recovery difficult.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1880 | OS Command Injection in MacOS Text-To-Speech Class in significant-gravitas/autogpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1880</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability exists in the MacOS Text-To-Speech class MacOSTTS of the significant-gravitas/autogpt project, affecting versions up to v0.5.0. The vulnerability arises from the improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command within the `_speech` method of the MacOSTTS class. Specifically, the use of `os.system` to execute the `say` command with user-supplied text allows for arbitrary code execution if an attacker can inject shell commands. This issue is triggered when the AutoGPT instance is run with the `--speak` option enabled and configured with `TEXT_TO_SPEECH_PROVIDER=macos`, reflecting back a shell injection snippet. The impact of this vulnerability is the potential execution of arbitrary code on the instance running AutoGPT. The issue was addressed in version 5.1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36734 | Improper input validation in OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via inputting a negative value ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36734</link><description>Improper input validation in OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via inputting a negative value into the dim parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36735 | OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 does not display an error or warning when the oneflow.eye parameter is floating.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36735</link><description>OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 does not display an error or warning when the oneflow.eye parameter is floating.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36740 | An issue in OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) when index as a negative number exceeds the rang...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36740</link><description>An issue in OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) when index as a negative number exceeds the range of size.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3149 | SSRF in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3149</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in the upload link feature of mintplex-labs/anything-llm. This feature, intended for users with manager or admin roles, processes uploaded links through an internal Collector API using a headless browser. An attacker can exploit this by hosting a malicious website and using it to perform actions such as internal port scanning, accessing internal web applications not exposed externally, and interacting with the Collector API. This interaction can lead to unauthorized actions such as arbitrary file deletion and limited Local File Inclusion (LFI), including accessing NGINX access logs which may contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3153 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3153</link><description>mintplex-labs/anything-llm is affected by an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in its upload file endpoint, leading to a denial of service (DOS) condition. Specifically, the server can be shut down by sending an invalid upload request. An attacker with the ability to upload documents can exploit this vulnerability to cause a DOS condition by manipulating the upload request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3322 | Path Traversal in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3322</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the 'cyber_security/codeguard' native personality of the parisneo/lollms-webui, affecting versions up to 9.5. The vulnerability arises from the improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory in the 'process_folder' function within 'lollms-webui/zoos/personalities_zoo/cyber_security/codeguard/scripts/processor.py'. Specifically, the function fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input for the 'code_folder_path', allowing an attacker to specify arbitrary paths using '../' or absolute paths. This flaw leads to arbitrary file read and overwrite capabilities in specified directories without limitations, posing a significant risk of sensitive information disclosure and unauthorized file manipulation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3429 | Path Traversal in parisneo/lollms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3429</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms application, specifically within the `sanitize_path_from_endpoint` and `sanitize_path` functions in `lollms_core\lollms\security.py`. This vulnerability allows for arbitrary file reading when the application is running on Windows. The issue arises due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied input, enabling attackers to bypass the path traversal protection mechanisms by crafting malicious input. Successful exploitation could lead to unauthorized access to sensitive files, information disclosure, and potentially a denial of service (DoS) condition by including numerous large or resource-intensive files. This vulnerability affects the latest version prior to 9.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4851 | SSRF Vulnerability in stangirard/quivr</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4851</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in the stangirard/quivr application, version 0.0.204, which allows attackers to access internal networks. The vulnerability is present in the crawl endpoint where the 'url' parameter can be manipulated to send HTTP requests to arbitrary URLs, thereby facilitating SSRF attacks. The affected code is located in the backend/routes/crawl_routes.py file, specifically within the crawl_endpoint function. This issue could allow attackers to interact with internal services that are accessible from the server hosting the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5130 | Incorrect Authorization in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5130</link><description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability exists in lunary-ai/lunary versions up to and including 1.2.2, which allows unauthenticated users to delete any dataset. The vulnerability is due to the lack of proper authorization checks in the dataset deletion endpoint. Specifically, the endpoint does not verify if the provided project ID belongs to the current user, thereby allowing any dataset to be deleted without proper authentication. This issue was fixed in version 1.2.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5278 | Unrestricted File Upload leading to RCE in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5278</link><description>gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt is vulnerable to an unrestricted file upload vulnerability due to insufficient validation of uploaded file types in its `/upload` endpoint. Specifically, the `handle_file_upload` function does not sanitize or validate the file extension or content type of uploaded files, allowing attackers to upload files with arbitrary extensions, including HTML files containing XSS payloads and Python files. This vulnerability, present in the latest version as of 20240310, could lead to stored XSS attacks and potentially result in remote code execution (RCE) on the server hosting the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2928 | Local File Inclusion (LFI) via URI Fragment Parsing in mlflow/mlflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2928</link><description>A Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability was identified in mlflow/mlflow, specifically in version 2.9.2, which was fixed in version 2.11.3. This vulnerability arises from the application's failure to properly validate URI fragments for directory traversal sequences such as '../'. An attacker can exploit this flaw by manipulating the fragment part of the URI to read arbitrary files on the local file system, including sensitive files like '/etc/passwd'. The vulnerability is a bypass to a previous patch that only addressed similar manipulation within the URI's query string, highlighting the need for comprehensive validation of all parts of a URI to prevent LFI attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3095 | SSRF in Langchain Web Research Retriever in langchain-ai/langchain</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3095</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in the Web Research Retriever component of langchain-ai/langchain version 0.1.5. The vulnerability arises because the Web Research Retriever does not restrict requests to remote internet addresses, allowing it to reach local addresses. This flaw enables attackers to execute port scans, access local services, and in some scenarios, read instance metadata from cloud environments. The vulnerability is particularly concerning as it can be exploited to abuse the Web Explorer server as a proxy for web attacks on third parties and interact with servers in the local network, including reading their response data. This could potentially lead to arbitrary code execution, depending on the nature of the local services. The vulnerability is limited to GET requests, as POST requests are not possible, but the impact on confidentiality, integrity, and availability is significant due to the potential for stolen credentials and state-changing interactions with internal APIs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4888 | Arbitrary File Deletion in BerriAI/litellm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4888</link><description>BerriAI's litellm, in its latest version, is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to improper input validation on the `/audio/transcriptions` endpoint. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted request that includes a file path to the server, which then deletes the specified file without proper authorization or validation. This vulnerability is present in the code where `os.remove(file.filename)` is used to delete a file, allowing any user to delete critical files on the server such as SSH keys, SQLite databases, or configuration files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5129 | Privilege Escalation Vulnerability in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5129</link><description>A Privilege Escalation Vulnerability exists in lunary-ai/lunary version 1.2.2, where any user can delete any datasets due to missing authorization checks. The vulnerability is present in the dataset deletion functionality, where the application fails to verify if the user requesting the deletion has the appropriate permissions. This allows unauthorized users to send a DELETE request to the server and delete any dataset by specifying its ID. The issue is located in the datasets.delete function within the datasets index file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5131 | Improper Access Control in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5131</link><description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability exists in the lunary-ai/lunary repository, affecting versions up to and including 1.2.2. The vulnerability allows unauthorized users to view any prompts in any projects by supplying a specific prompt ID to an endpoint that does not adequately verify the ownership of the prompt ID. This issue was fixed in version 1.2.25.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5132 | Business Logic Error in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5132</link><description>In lunary-ai/lunary version 1.2.2, a business logic error allows users to bypass the intended limitations on team member invitations and additions, regardless of their subscription plan. The vulnerability arises due to the lack of validation against the predefined member limits in the SEAT_ALLOWANCE constants during the invitation and joining processes. This issue enables users on any plan, including the free plan, to invite and add more members to a team than allowed, effectively circumventing the system's subscription model. The flaw is located in the backend's handling of user invitations and additions, specifically in the /api/v1/auth/index.ts and /api/v1/users.ts endpoints, where the system fails to check the current number of team members against the allowed limits before proceeding with the invitation and addition operations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0520 | Remote Code Execution due to Full Controlled File Write in mlflow/mlflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0520</link><description>A vulnerability in mlflow/mlflow version 8.2.1 allows for remote code execution due to improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('Command Injection') within the `mlflow.data.http_dataset_source.py` module. Specifically, when loading a dataset from a source URL with an HTTP scheme, the filename extracted from the `Content-Disposition` header or the URL path is used to generate the final file path without proper sanitization. This flaw enables an attacker to control the file path fully by utilizing path traversal or absolute path techniques, such as '../../tmp/poc.txt' or '/tmp/poc.txt', leading to arbitrary file write. Exploiting this vulnerability could allow a malicious user to execute commands on the vulnerable machine, potentially gaining access to data and model information. The issue is fixed in version 2.9.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1881 | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command in significant-gravitas/autogpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1881</link><description>AutoGPT, a component of significant-gravitas/autogpt, is vulnerable to an improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') due to a flaw in its shell command validation function. Specifically, the vulnerability exists in versions v0.5.0 up to but not including 5.1.0. The issue arises from the application's method of validating shell commands against an allowlist or denylist, where it only checks the first word of the command. This allows an attacker to bypass the intended restrictions by crafting commands that are executed despite not being on the allowlist or by including malicious commands not present in the denylist. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary shell commands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22326 | IBM System Storage improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22326</link><description>IBM System Storage DS8900F 89.22.19.0, 89.30.68.0, 89.32.40.0, 89.33.48.0, 89.40.83.0, and 89.40.93.0 could allow a remote user to create an LDAP connection with a valid username and empty password to establish an anonymous connection.    IBM X-Force ID:  279518.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2035 | Improper Authorization in zenml-io/zenml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2035</link><description>An improper authorization vulnerability exists in the zenml-io/zenml repository, specifically within the API PUT /api/v1/users/id endpoint. This vulnerability allows any authenticated user to modify the information of other users, including changing the `active` status of user accounts to false, effectively deactivating them. This issue affects version 0.55.3 and was fixed in version 0.56.2. The impact of this vulnerability is significant as it allows for the deactivation of admin accounts, potentially disrupting the functionality and security of the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2171 | Stored XSS in zenml-io/zenml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2171</link><description>A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the zenml-io/zenml repository, specifically within the 'logo_url' field. By injecting malicious payloads into this field, an attacker could send harmful messages to other users, potentially compromising their accounts. The vulnerability affects version 0.55.3 and was fixed in version 0.56.2. The impact of exploiting this vulnerability could lead to user account compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2213 | Improper Authentication in zenml-io/zenml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2213</link><description>An issue was discovered in zenml-io/zenml versions up to and including 0.55.4. Due to improper authentication mechanisms, an attacker with access to an active user session can change the account password without needing to know the current password. This vulnerability allows for unauthorized account takeover by bypassing the standard password change verification process. The issue was fixed in version 0.56.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2288 | CSRF File Upload Vulnerability in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2288</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the profile picture upload functionality of the Lollms application, specifically in the parisneo/lollms-webui repository, affecting versions up to 7.3.0. This vulnerability allows attackers to change a victim's profile picture without their consent, potentially leading to a denial of service by overloading the filesystem with files. Additionally, this flaw can be exploited to perform a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack, enabling attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the victim's browser session. The issue is resolved in version 9.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2383 | Clickjacking Vulnerability in zenml-io/zenml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2383</link><description>A clickjacking vulnerability exists in zenml-io/zenml versions up to and including 0.55.5 due to the application's failure to set appropriate X-Frame-Options or Content-Security-Policy HTTP headers. This vulnerability allows an attacker to embed the application UI within an iframe on a malicious page, potentially leading to unauthorized actions by tricking users into interacting with the interface under the attacker's control. The issue was addressed in version 0.56.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30373 | Kofax Power PDF JPF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30373</link><description>Kofax Power PDF JPF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22092.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37364 | Ariane Allegro Scenario Player through 2024-03-05, when Ariane Duo kiosk mode is used, allows physically proximate attackers to obtain sensi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37364</link><description>Ariane Allegro Scenario Player through 2024-03-05, when Ariane Duo kiosk mode is used, allows physically proximate attackers to obtain sensitive information (such as hotel invoice content with PII), and potentially create unauthorized room keys, by entering a guest-search quote character and then accessing the underlying Windows OS.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3102 | JSON Injection in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3102</link><description>A JSON Injection vulnerability exists in the `mintplex-labs/anything-llm` application, specifically within the username parameter during the login process at the `/api/request-token` endpoint. The vulnerability arises from improper handling of values, allowing attackers to perform brute force attacks without prior knowledge of the username. Once the password is known, attackers can conduct blind attacks to ascertain the full username, significantly compromising system security.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3166 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3166</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in mintplex-labs/anything-llm, affecting both the desktop application version 1.2.0 and the latest version of the web application. The vulnerability arises from the application's feature to fetch and embed content from websites into workspaces, which can be exploited to execute arbitrary JavaScript code. In the desktop application, this flaw can be escalated to Remote Code Execution (RCE) due to insecure application settings, specifically the enabling of 'nodeIntegration' and the disabling of 'contextIsolation' in Electron's webPreferences. The issue has been addressed in version 1.4.2 of the desktop application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3234 | Path Traversal in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3234</link><description>The gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt application is vulnerable to a path traversal attack due to its use of an outdated gradio component. The application is designed to restrict user access to resources within the `web_assets` folder. However, the outdated version of gradio it employs is susceptible to path traversal, as identified in CVE-2023-51449. This vulnerability allows unauthorized users to bypass the intended restrictions and access sensitive files, such as `config.json`, which contains API keys. The issue affects the latest version of chuanhuchatgpt prior to the fixed version released on 20240305.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3402 | Stored XSS vulnerability in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3402</link><description>A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability existed in version (20240121) of gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt due to inadequate sanitization and validation of model output data. Despite user-input validation efforts, the application fails to properly sanitize or validate the output from the model, allowing for the injection and execution of malicious JavaScript code within the context of a user's browser. This vulnerability can lead to the execution of arbitrary JavaScript code in the context of other users' browsers, potentially resulting in the hijacking of victims' browsers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4320 | Remote Code Execution due to LFI in &amp;#x27;/install_extension&amp;#x27; in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4320</link><description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the '/install_extension' endpoint of the parisneo/lollms-webui application, specifically within the `@router.post("/install_extension")` route handler. The vulnerability arises due to improper handling of the `name` parameter in the `ExtensionBuilder().build_extension()` method, which allows for local file inclusion (LFI) leading to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious `name` parameter that causes the server to load and execute a `__init__.py` file from an arbitrary location, such as the upload directory for discussions. This vulnerability affects the latest version of parisneo/lollms-webui and can lead to remote code execution without requiring user interaction, especially when the application is exposed to an external endpoint or operated in headless mode.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4881 | Path Traversal in parisneo/lollms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4881</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms application, affecting version 9.4.0 and potentially earlier versions, but fixed in version 5.9.0. The vulnerability arises due to improper validation of file paths between Windows and Linux environments, allowing attackers to traverse beyond the intended directory and read any file on the Windows system. Specifically, the application fails to adequately sanitize file paths containing backslashes (`\`), which can be exploited to access the root directory and read, or even delete, sensitive files. This issue was discovered in the context of the `/user_infos` endpoint, where a crafted request using backslashes to reference a file (e.g., `\windows\win.ini`) could result in unauthorized file access. The impact of this vulnerability includes the potential for attackers to access sensitive information such as environment variables, database files, and configuration files, which could lead to further compromise of the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4890 | Blind SQL Injection in berriai/litellm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4890</link><description>A blind SQL injection vulnerability exists in the berriai/litellm application, specifically within the '/team/update' process. The vulnerability arises due to the improper handling of the 'user_id' parameter in the raw SQL query used for deleting users. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious SQL commands through the 'user_id' parameter, leading to potential unauthorized access to sensitive information such as API keys, user information, and tokens stored in the database. The affected version is 1.27.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5133 | Account Takeover via Exposed Recovery Token in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5133</link><description>In lunary-ai/lunary version 1.2.4, an account takeover vulnerability exists due to the exposure of password recovery tokens in API responses. Specifically, when a user initiates the password reset process, the recovery token is included in the response of the `GET /v1/users/me/org` endpoint, which lists all users in a team. This allows any authenticated user to capture the recovery token of another user and subsequently change that user's password without consent, effectively taking over the account. The issue lies in the inclusion of the `recovery_token` attribute in the users object returned by the API.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5186 | Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in imartinez/privategpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5186</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in the file upload section of imartinez/privategpt version 0.5.0. This vulnerability allows attackers to send crafted requests that could result in unauthorized access to the local network and potentially sensitive information. Specifically, by manipulating the 'path' parameter in a file upload request, an attacker can cause the application to make arbitrary requests to internal services, including the AWS metadata endpoint. This issue could lead to the exposure of internal servers and sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5206 | Sensitive Data Leakage in sklearn.feature_extraction.text.TfidfVectorizer in scikit-learn/scikit-learn</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5206</link><description>A sensitive data leakage vulnerability was identified in scikit-learn's TfidfVectorizer, specifically in versions up to and including 1.4.1.post1, which was fixed in version 1.5.0. The vulnerability arises from the unexpected storage of all tokens present in the training data within the `stop_words_` attribute, rather than only storing the subset of tokens required for the TF-IDF technique to function. This behavior leads to the potential leakage of sensitive information, as the `stop_words_` attribute could contain tokens that were meant to be discarded and not stored, such as passwords or keys. The impact of this vulnerability varies based on the nature of the data being processed by the vectorizer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5225 | SQL Injection in berriai/litellm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5225</link><description>An SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the berriai/litellm repository, specifically within the `/global/spend/logs` endpoint. The vulnerability arises due to improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL command. The affected code constructs an SQL query by concatenating an unvalidated `api_key` parameter directly into the query, making it susceptible to SQL Injection if the `api_key` contains malicious data. This issue affects the latest version of the repository. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could lead to unauthorized access, data manipulation, exposure of confidential information, and denial of service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5306 | Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5306</link><description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22930.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5307 | Kofax Power PDF AcroForm Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5307</link><description>Kofax Power PDF AcroForm Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22933.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5478 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in SAML metadata endpoint in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5478</link><description>A Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the SAML metadata endpoint `/auth/saml/${org?.id}/metadata` of lunary-ai/lunary version 1.2.7. The vulnerability arises due to the application's failure to escape or validate the `orgId` parameter supplied by the user before incorporating it into the generated response. Specifically, the endpoint generates XML responses for SAML metadata, where the `orgId` parameter is directly embedded into the XML structure without proper sanitization or validation. This flaw allows an attacker to inject arbitrary JavaScript code into the generated SAML metadata page, leading to potential theft of user cookies or authentication tokens.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5480 | Remote Code Execution in pytorch/pytorch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5480</link><description>A vulnerability in the PyTorch's torch.distributed.rpc framework, specifically in versions prior to 2.2.2, allows for remote code execution (RCE). The framework, which is used in distributed training scenarios, does not properly verify the functions being called during RPC (Remote Procedure Call) operations. This oversight permits attackers to execute arbitrary commands by leveraging built-in Python functions such as eval during multi-cpu RPC communication. The vulnerability arises from the lack of restriction on function calls when a worker node serializes and sends a PythonUDF (User Defined Function) to the master node, which then deserializes and executes the function without validation. This flaw can be exploited to compromise master nodes initiating distributed training, potentially leading to the theft of sensitive AI-related data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5550 | Exposure of Sensitive Information via Arbitrary System Path Lookup in h2oai/h2o-3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5550</link><description>In h2oai/h2o-3 version 3.40.0.4, an exposure of sensitive information vulnerability exists due to an arbitrary system path lookup feature. This vulnerability allows any remote user to view full paths in the entire file system where h2o-3 is hosted. Specifically, the issue resides in the Typeahead API call, which when requested with a typeahead lookup of '/', exposes the root filesystem including directories such as /home, /usr, /bin, among others. This vulnerability could allow attackers to explore the entire filesystem, and when combined with a Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability, could make exploitation of the server trivial.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23793 | Upload of files outside application directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23793</link><description>The file upload feature in OTRS and ((OTRS)) Community Edition has a path traversal vulnerability. This issue permits authenticated agents or customer users to upload potentially harmful files to directories accessible by the web server, potentially leading to the execution of local code like Perl scripts.
This issue affects OTRS: from 7.0.X through 7.0.49, 8.0.X, 2023.X, from 2024.X through 2024.3.2; ((OTRS)) Community Edition: from 6.0.1 through 6.0.34.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2362 | Path Traversal in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2362</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui version 9.3 on the Windows platform. Due to improper validation of file paths between Windows and Linux environments, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability to delete any file on the system. The issue arises from the lack of adequate sanitization of user-supplied input in the 'del_preset' endpoint, where the application fails to prevent the use of absolute paths or directory traversal sequences ('..'). As a result, an attacker can send a specially crafted request to the 'del_preset' endpoint to delete files outside of the intended directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2548 | Path Traversal in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2548</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui application, specifically within the `lollms_core/lollms/server/endpoints/lollms_binding_files_server.py` and `lollms_core/lollms/security.py` files. Due to inadequate validation of file paths between Windows and Linux environments using `Path(path).is_absolute()`, attackers can exploit this flaw to read any file on the system. This issue affects the latest version of LoLLMs running on the Windows platform. The vulnerability is triggered when an attacker sends a specially crafted request to the `/user_infos/{path:path}` endpoint, allowing the reading of arbitrary files, as demonstrated with the `win.ini` file. The issue has been addressed in version 9.5 of the software.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2624 | Path Traversal and Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2624</link><description>A path traversal and arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui application, specifically within the `@router.get("/switch_personal_path")` endpoint in `./lollms-webui/lollms_core/lollms/server/endpoints/lollms_user.py`. The vulnerability arises due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied input for the `path` parameter, allowing an attacker to specify arbitrary file system paths. This flaw enables direct arbitrary file uploads, leakage of `personal_data`, and overwriting of configurations in `lollms-webui`-&gt;`configs` by exploiting the same named directory in `personal_data`. The issue affects the latest version of the application and is fixed in version 9.4. Successful exploitation could lead to sensitive information disclosure, unauthorized file uploads, and potentially remote code execution by overwriting critical configuration files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32873 | evmos allows transferring unvested tokens after delegations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32873</link><description>Evmos is the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) Hub on the Cosmos Network. The spendable balance is not updated properly when delegating vested tokens. The issue allows a clawback vesting account to anticipate the release of unvested tokens.  This vulnerability is fixed in 18.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3099 | Denial of Service and Data Model Poisoning via URL Encoding in mlflow/mlflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3099</link><description>A vulnerability in mlflow/mlflow version 2.11.1 allows attackers to create multiple models with the same name by exploiting URL encoding. This flaw can lead to Denial of Service (DoS) as an authenticated user might not be able to use the intended model, as it will open a different model each time. Additionally, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability to perform data model poisoning by creating a model with the same name, potentially causing an authenticated user to become a victim by using the poisoned model. The issue stems from inadequate validation of model names, allowing for the creation of models with URL-encoded names that are treated as distinct from their URL-decoded counterparts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3110 | Stored XSS leading to admin account takeover in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3110</link><description>A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the mintplex-labs/anything-llm application, affecting versions up to and including the latest before 1.0.0. The vulnerability arises from the application's failure to properly sanitize and validate user-supplied URLs before embedding them into the application UI as external links with custom icons. Specifically, the application does not prevent the inclusion of 'javascript:' protocol payloads in URLs, which can be exploited by a user with manager role to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the context of another user's session. This flaw can be leveraged to steal the admin's authorization token by crafting malicious URLs that, when clicked by the admin, send the token to an attacker-controlled server. The attacker can then use this token to perform unauthorized actions, escalate privileges to admin, or directly take over the admin account. The vulnerability is triggered when the malicious link is opened in a new tab using either the CTRL + left mouse button click or the mouse scroll wheel click, or in some non-updated versions of modern browsers, by directly clicking on the link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5126 | Improper Access Control in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5126</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability exists in the lunary-ai/lunary repository, specifically within the versions.patch functionality for updating prompts. Affected versions include 1.2.2 up to but not including 1.2.25. The vulnerability allows unauthorized users to update prompt details due to insufficient access control checks. This issue was addressed and fixed in version 1.2.25.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5128 | IDOR Vulnerability in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5128</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability was identified in lunary-ai/lunary, affecting versions up to and including 1.2.2. This vulnerability allows unauthorized users to view, update, or delete any dataset_prompt or dataset_prompt_variation within any dataset or project. The issue stems from improper access control checks in the dataset management endpoints, where direct references to object IDs are not adequately secured against unauthorized access. This vulnerability was fixed in version 1.2.25.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5304 | Kofax Power PDF TGA File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5304</link><description>Kofax Power PDF TGA File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TGA files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22920.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5305 | Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5305</link><description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22921.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5552 | ReDoS in kubeflow/kubeflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5552</link><description>kubeflow/kubeflow is vulnerable to a Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) attack due to inefficient regular expression complexity in its email validation mechanism. An attacker can remotely exploit this vulnerability without authentication by providing specially crafted input that causes the application to consume an excessive amount of CPU resources. This vulnerability affects the latest version of kubeflow/kubeflow, specifically within the centraldashboard-angular backend component. The impact of exploiting this vulnerability includes resource exhaustion, and service disruption.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2914 | TarSlip Vulnerability in deepjavalibrary/djl</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2914</link><description>A TarSlip vulnerability exists in the deepjavalibrary/djl, affecting version 0.26.0 and fixed in version 0.27.0. This vulnerability allows an attacker to manipulate file paths within tar archives to overwrite arbitrary files on the target system. Exploitation of this vulnerability could lead to remote code execution, privilege escalation, data theft or manipulation, and denial of service. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of file paths during the extraction of tar files, as demonstrated in multiple occurrences within the library's codebase, including but not limited to the files_util.py and extract_imagenet.py scripts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:24:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4325 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in gradio-app/gradio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4325</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in the gradio-app/gradio version 4.21.0, specifically within the `/queue/join` endpoint and the `save_url_to_cache` function. The vulnerability arises when the `path` value, obtained from the user and expected to be a URL, is used to make an HTTP request without sufficient validation checks. This flaw allows an attacker to send crafted requests that could lead to unauthorized access to the local network or the AWS metadata endpoint, thereby compromising the security of internal servers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:24:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5303 | Kofax Power PDF PSD File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5303</link><description>Kofax Power PDF PSD File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PSD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22919.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5482 | SSRF in add_webpage endpoint in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5482</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in the 'add_webpage' endpoint of the parisneo/lollms-webui application, affecting the latest version. The vulnerability arises because the application does not adequately validate URLs entered by users, allowing them to input arbitrary URLs, including those that target internal resources such as 'localhost' or '127.0.0.1'. This flaw enables attackers to make unauthorized requests to internal or external systems, potentially leading to access to sensitive data, service disruption, network integrity compromise, business logic manipulation, and abuse of third-party resources. The issue is critical and requires immediate attention to maintain the application's security and integrity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1879 | CSRF to RCE in significant-gravitas/autogpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1879</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in significant-gravitas/autogpt version v0.5.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the AutoGPT server. The vulnerability stems from the lack of protections on the API endpoint receiving instructions, enabling an attacker to direct a user running AutoGPT in their local network to a malicious website. This site can then send crafted requests to the AutoGPT server, leading to command execution. The issue is exacerbated by CORS being enabled for arbitrary origins by default, allowing the attacker to read the response of all cross-site queries. This vulnerability was addressed in version 5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30368 | A10 Thunder ADC CsrRequestView Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30368</link><description>A10 Thunder ADC CsrRequestView Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of A10 Thunder ADC. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the CsrRequestView class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of a10user. Was ZDI-CAN-22517.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30369 | A10 Thunder ADC Incorrect Permission Assignment Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30369</link><description>A10 Thunder ADC Incorrect Permission Assignment Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of A10 Thunder ADC. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the installer. The issue results from incorrect permissions on a file. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-22754.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30374 | Luxion KeyShot Viewer KSP File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30374</link><description>Luxion KeyShot Viewer KSP File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Luxion KeyShot Viewer. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of KSP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22449.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30375 | Luxion KeyShot Viewer KSP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30375</link><description>Luxion KeyShot Viewer KSP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Luxion KeyShot Viewer. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of KSP files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22515.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3104 | Remote Code Execution in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3104</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in mintplex-labs/anything-llm due to improper handling of environment variables. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by injecting arbitrary environment variables via the `POST /api/system/update-env` endpoint, which allows for the execution of arbitrary code on the host running anything-llm. The vulnerability is present in the latest version of anything-llm, with the latest commit identified as fde905aac1812b84066ff72e5f2f90b56d4c3a59. This issue has been fixed in version 1.0.0. Successful exploitation could lead to code execution on the host, enabling attackers to read and modify data accessible to the user running the service, potentially leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3504 | Improper Access Control in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3504</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability exists in lunary-ai/lunary versions up to and including 1.2.2, where an admin can update any organization user to the organization owner. This vulnerability allows the elevated user to delete projects within the organization. The issue is resolved in version 1.2.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4889 | Code Injection in berriai/litellm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4889</link><description>A code injection vulnerability exists in the berriai/litellm application, version 1.34.6, due to the use of unvalidated input in the eval function within the secret management system. This vulnerability requires a valid Google KMS configuration file to be exploitable. Specifically, by setting the `UI_LOGO_PATH` variable to a remote server address in the `get_image` function, an attacker can write a malicious Google KMS configuration file to the `cached_logo.jpg` file. This file can then be used to execute arbitrary code by assigning malicious code to the `SAVE_CONFIG_TO_DB` environment variable, leading to full system control. The vulnerability is contingent upon the use of the Google KMS feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4941 | Local File Inclusion in JSON component in gradio-app/gradio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4941</link><description>A local file inclusion vulnerability exists in the JSON component of gradio-app/gradio version 4.25. The vulnerability arises from improper input validation in the `postprocess()` function within `gradio/components/json_component.py`, where a user-controlled string is parsed as JSON. If the parsed JSON object contains a `path` key, the specified file is moved to a temporary directory, making it possible to retrieve it later via the `/file=..` endpoint. This issue is due to the `processing_utils.move_files_to_cache()` function traversing any object passed to it, looking for a dictionary with a `path` key, and then copying the specified file to a temporary directory. The vulnerability can be exploited by an attacker to read files on the remote system, posing a significant security risk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5256 | Sonos Era 100 SMB2 Message Handling Integer Underflow Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5256</link><description>Sonos Era 100 SMB2 Message Handling Integer Underflow Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Sonos Era 100 smart speakers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of SMB2 messages. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an integer underflow before reading from memory. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-22336.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5267 | Sonos Era 100 SMB2 Message Handling Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5267</link><description>Sonos Era 100 SMB2 Message Handling Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sonos Era 100 smart speakers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of SMB2 messages. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-22384.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5268 | Sonos Era 100 SMB2 Message Handling Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5268</link><description>Sonos Era 100 SMB2 Message Handling Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Sonos Era 100 smart speakers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of SMB2 messages. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-22428.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5269 | Sonos Era 100 SMB2 Message Handling Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5269</link><description>Sonos Era 100 SMB2 Message Handling Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sonos Era 100 smart speakers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of SMB2 messages. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-22459.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5301 | Kofax Power PDF PSD File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5301</link><description>Kofax Power PDF PSD File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PSD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22917.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5302 | Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5302</link><description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22918.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5452 | RCE via Property/Class Pollution in lightning-ai/pytorch-lightning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5452</link><description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the lightning-ai/pytorch-lightning library version 2.2.1 due to improper handling of deserialized user input and mismanagement of dunder attributes by the `deepdiff` library. The library uses `deepdiff.Delta` objects to modify application state based on frontend actions. However, it is possible to bypass the intended restrictions on modifying dunder attributes, allowing an attacker to construct a serialized delta that passes the deserializer whitelist and contains dunder attributes. When processed, this can be exploited to access other modules, classes, and instances, leading to arbitrary attribute write and total RCE on any self-hosted pytorch-lightning application in its default configuration, as the delta endpoint is enabled by default.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5505 | NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System UpLoadServlet Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5505</link><description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System UpLoadServlet Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the UpLoadServlet class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-22724.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5506 | Luxion KeyShot Viewer KSP File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5506</link><description>Luxion KeyShot Viewer KSP File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Luxion KeyShot Viewer. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of KSP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22514.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5507 | Luxion KeyShot Viewer KSP File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5507</link><description>Luxion KeyShot Viewer KSP File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Luxion KeyShot Viewer. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of KSP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22266.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5508 | Luxion KeyShot Viewer KSP File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5508</link><description>Luxion KeyShot Viewer KSP File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Luxion KeyShot Viewer. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of KSP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22267.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5509 | Luxion KeyShot BIP File Parsing Uncontrolled Search Path Element Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5509</link><description>Luxion KeyShot BIP File Parsing Uncontrolled Search Path Element Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Luxion KeyShot. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of BIP files. The issue results from loading a library from an unsecured location. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22738.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36736 | An issue in the oneflow.permute component of OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 causes an incorrect calculation when the same dimension operation i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36736</link><description>An issue in the oneflow.permute component of OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 causes an incorrect calculation when the same dimension operation is performed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36737 | Improper input validation in OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via inputting a negative value ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36737</link><description>Improper input validation in OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via inputting a negative value into the oneflow.full parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5277 | Weak Password Recovery Mechanism in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5277</link><description>In lunary-ai/lunary version 1.2.4, a vulnerability exists in the password recovery mechanism where the reset password token is not invalidated after use. This allows an attacker who compromises the recovery token to repeatedly change the password of a victim's account. The issue lies in the backend's handling of the reset password process, where the token, once used, is not discarded or invalidated, enabling its reuse. This vulnerability could lead to unauthorized account access if an attacker obtains the recovery token.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3033 | Improper Authorization in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3033</link><description>An improper authorization vulnerability exists in the mintplex-labs/anything-llm application, specifically within the '/api/v/' endpoint and its sub-routes. This flaw allows unauthenticated users to perform destructive actions on the VectorDB, including resetting the database and deleting specific namespaces, without requiring any authorization or permissions. The issue affects all versions up to and including the latest version, with a fix introduced in version 1.0.0. Exploitation of this vulnerability can lead to complete data loss of document embeddings across all workspaces, rendering workspace chats and embeddable chat widgets non-functional. Additionally, attackers can list all namespaces, potentially exposing private workspace names.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5127 | Improper Access Control in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5127</link><description>In lunary-ai/lunary versions 1.2.2 through 1.2.25, an improper access control vulnerability allows users on the Free plan to invite other members and assign them any role, including those intended for Paid and Enterprise plans only. This issue arises due to insufficient backend validation of roles and permissions, enabling unauthorized users to join a project and potentially exploit roles and permissions not intended for their use. The vulnerability specifically affects the Team feature, where the backend fails to validate whether a user has paid for a plan before allowing them to send invite links with any role assigned. This could lead to unauthorized access and manipulation of project settings or data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36743 | An issue in OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) when an empty array is processed with oneflow.do...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36743</link><description>An issue in OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) when an empty array is processed with oneflow.dot.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:28:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36745 | An issue in OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via inputting a negative value into the oneflow....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36745</link><description>An issue in OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via inputting a negative value into the oneflow.index_select parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:28:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3152 | Privilege Escalation and Local File Inclusion in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3152</link><description>mintplex-labs/anything-llm is vulnerable to multiple security issues due to improper input validation in several endpoints. An attacker can exploit these vulnerabilities to escalate privileges from a default user role to an admin role, read and delete arbitrary files on the system, and perform Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) attacks. The vulnerabilities are present in the `/request-token`, `/workspace/:slug/thread/:threadSlug/update`, `/system/remove-logo`, `/system/logo`, and collector's `/process` endpoints. These issues are due to the application's failure to properly validate user input before passing it to `prisma` functions and other critical operations. Affected versions include the latest version prior to 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:28:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33655 | The DNS protocol in RFC 1035 and updates allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (resource consumption) by arranging for DNS qu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33655</link><description>The DNS protocol in RFC 1035 and updates allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (resource consumption) by arranging for DNS queries to be accumulated for seconds, such that responses are later sent in a pulsing burst (which can be considered traffic amplification in some cases), aka the "DNSBomb" issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36742 | An issue in the oneflow.scatter_nd parameter OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) when index para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36742</link><description>An issue in the oneflow.scatter_nd parameter OneFlow-Inc. Oneflow v0.9.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) when index parameter exceeds the range of shape.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37156 | TokenController formName not sanitized in hidden input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37156</link><description>The SuluFormBundle adds support for creating dynamic forms in Sulu Admin. The TokenController get parameter formName is not sanitized in the returned input field which leads to XSS. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 16:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35178 | Jupyter server on Windows discloses Windows user password hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35178</link><description>The Jupyter Server provides the backend for Jupyter web applications. Jupyter Server on Windows has a vulnerability that lets unauthenticated attackers leak the NTLMv2 password hash of the Windows user running the Jupyter server. An attacker can crack this password to gain access to the Windows machine hosting the Jupyter server, or access other network-accessible machines or 3rd party services using that credential. Or an attacker perform an NTLM relay attack without cracking the credential to gain access to other network-accessible machines. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.14.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 15:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37152 | Unauthenticated Access to sensitive settings in Argo CD</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37152</link><description>Argo CD is a declarative, GitOps continuous delivery tool for Kubernetes. The vulnerability allows unauthorized access to the sensitive settings exposed by  /api/v1/settings endpoint without authentication. All sensitive settings are hidden except passwordPattern. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.11.3, 2.10.12, and 2.9.17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 15:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37150 | Private npm registry support used scope auth token for downloading tarballs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37150</link><description>An issue in `.npmrc` support in Deno 1.44.0 was discovered where Deno would send `.npmrc` credentials for the scope to the tarball URL when the registry provided URLs for a tarball on a different domain. All users relying on .npmrc are potentially affected by this vulnerability if their private registry references tarball URLs at a different domain. This includes usage of deno install subcommand, auto-install for npm: specifiers and LSP usage. It is recommended to upgrade to Deno 1.44.1 and if your private registry ever serves tarballs at a different domain to rotate your registry credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 15:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36399 | Kanboard affected by Project Takeover via IDOR in ProjectPermissionController</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36399</link><description>Kanboard is project management software that focuses on the Kanban methodology. The vuln is in app/Controller/ProjectPermissionController.php function addUser(). The users permission to add users to a project only get checked on the URL parameter project_id. If the user is authorized to add users to this project the request gets processed. The users permission for the POST BODY parameter project_id does not get checked again while processing. An attacker with the 'Project Manager' on a single project may take over any other project. The vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.37.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 15:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36106 | Argo CD allows authenticated users to enumerate clusters by name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36106</link><description>Argo CD is a declarative, GitOps continuous delivery tool for Kubernetes. It’s possible for authenticated users to enumerate clusters by name by inspecting error messages. It’s also possible to enumerate the names of projects with project-scoped clusters if you know the names of the clusters. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.11.3, 2.10.12, and 2.9.17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 15:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34832 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in CubeCart v.6.5.5 and before allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file uploaded to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34832</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in CubeCart v.6.5.5 and before allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file uploaded to the _g and node parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 14:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5684 | ID Charger Connect &amp;amp; Pro - JWT-Null-Algorithm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5684</link><description>An attacker with access to the private network (the charger is connected to) or local access to the Ethernet-Interface can exploit a faulty implementation of the JWT-library in order to bypass the password authentication to the web configuration interface and then has full access as the user would have. However, an attacker will not have developer or admin rights. If the implementation of the JWT-library is wrongly configured to accept "none"-algorithms, the server will pass insecure JWT. A local, unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to bypass the authentication mechanism.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 13:02:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36779 | Sourcecodester Stock Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via editCategories.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36779</link><description>Sourcecodester Stock Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via editCategories.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 13:02:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5675 | Unreliable data deserialization vulnerability in Mentor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5675</link><description>Untrusted data deserialization vulnerability has been found in Mentor - Employee Portal, affecting version 3.83.35. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code, by injecting a malicious payload into the “ViewState” field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 12:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5489 | Wbcom Designs - Custom Font Uploader &amp;lt;= 2.3.4 - Missing Authorization to Font Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5489</link><description>The Wbcom Designs – Custom Font Uploader plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'cfu_delete_customfont' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete any custom font.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 11:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5038 | Colibri Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.0.276 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5038</link><description>The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.276 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 11:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5188 | Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp;amp; WooCommerce Builders &amp;lt;= 5.9.22 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5188</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'get_manual_calendar_events' function in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.22 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 11:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5657 | CraftCMS Plugin - Two-Factor Authentication - Password Hash Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5657</link><description>The CraftCMS plugin Two-Factor Authentication in versions 3.3.1, 3.3.2 and 3.3.3 discloses the password hash of the currently authenticated user after submitting a valid TOTP.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5658 | CraftCMS Plugin - Two-Factor Authentication - TOTP Token Stays Valid After Use</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5658</link><description>The CraftCMS plugin Two-Factor Authentication through 3.3.3 allows reuse of TOTP tokens multiple times within the validity period.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5673 | Cross-Site Scripting in PHP File Manager by Dulldusk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5673</link><description>Vulnerability in Dulldusk's PHP File Manager affecting version 1.7.8. This vulnerability consists of an XSS through the fm_current_dir parameter of index.php. An attacker could send a specially crafted JavaScript payload to an authenticated user and partially hijack their browser session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5259 | MultiVendorX Marketplace – WooCommerce MultiVendor Marketplace Solution &amp;lt;= 4.1.11 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via hover_animation Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5259</link><description>The MultiVendorX Marketplace – WooCommerce MultiVendor Marketplace Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘hover_animation’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 09:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5329 | Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) &amp;lt;= 1.5.109 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Blind SQL Injection via data[addonID] Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5329</link><description>The Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to blind SQL Injection via the ‘data[addonID]’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.109 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 09:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28995 | SolarWinds Serv-U L Directory Transversal Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28995</link><description>SolarWinds Serv-U was susceptible to a directory transversal vulnerability that would allow access to read sensitive files on the host machine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 09:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5221 | Qi Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5221</link><description>The Qi Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's file uploader in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 08:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36393 | SysAid - CWE-89: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command (&amp;#x27;SQL Injection&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36393</link><description>SysAid - CWE-89: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection')</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 08:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36394 | SysAid - CWE-78: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command (&amp;#x27;OS Command Injection&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36394</link><description>SysAid - CWE-78: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 08:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4177 | Host whitelist parser issue in GravityZone Console On-Premise (VA-11554)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4177</link><description>A host whitelist parser issue in the proxy service implemented in the GravityZone Update Server allows an attacker to cause a server-side request forgery. This issue only affects GravityZone Console versions before 6.38.1-2 that are running only on premise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 08:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5665 | Login/Signup Popup ( Inline Form + Woocommerce ) 2.7.1 - 2.7.2 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary Options Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5665</link><description>The Login/Signup Popup ( Inline Form + Woocommerce ) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the ‘export_settings’ function in versions 2.7.1 to 2.7.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read arbitrary options on affected sites.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 07:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3049 | Booth: specially crafted hash can lead to invalid hmac being accepted by booth server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3049</link><description>A flaw was found in Booth, a cluster ticket manager. If a specially-crafted hash is passed to gcry_md_get_algo_dlen(), it may allow an invalid HMAC to be accepted by the Booth server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 05:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5656 | Google CSE &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5656</link><description>The Google CSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0972 | BuddyPress Members Only &amp;lt;= 3.3.5 - Improper Access Control to Sensitive Information Exposure via REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0972</link><description>The BuddyPress Members Only plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.5 via the REST API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the plugin's "All Other Sections On Your Site Will be Opened to Guest" feature (when unset) and view restricted page and post content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1175 | WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp;amp; More &amp;lt;= 16.26.6 - Unauthenticated Payment Deletion via delete_payment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1175</link><description>The WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'delete_payment' function in all versions up to, and including, 16.26.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary payments.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5141 | Rotating Tweets (Twitter widget and shortcode) &amp;lt;= 1.9.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5141</link><description>The Rotating Tweets (Twitter widget and shortcode) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's' 'rotatingtweets' in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5152 | ElementsReady Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 6.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5152</link><description>The ElementsReady Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:10:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5153 | Startklar Elementor Addons &amp;lt;= 1.7.15 - Unauthenticated Path Traversal to Arbitrary Directory Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5153</link><description>The Startklar Elementor Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.15 via the 'dropzone_hash' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to copy the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information, and to delete arbitrary directories, including the root WordPress directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:10:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5161 | Magical Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.1.39 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5161</link><description>The Magical Addons For Elementor ( Header Footer Builder, Free Elementor Widgets, Elementor Templates Library ) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.39 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:10:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5162 | WordPress prettyPhoto &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via url Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5162</link><description>The WordPress prettyPhoto plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2922 | Themesflat Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Widget Tags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2922</link><description>The Themesflat Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via widget tags in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4212 | Themesflat Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4212</link><description>The Themesflat Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's TF Group Image, TF Nav Menu, TF Posts, TF Woo Product Grid, TF Accordion, and TF Image Box widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4364 | Qi Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4364</link><description>The Qi Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's button widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4458 | Themesflat Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via URLs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4458</link><description>The Themesflat Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in several widgets via URL parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4459 | Themesflat Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Widget Titles</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4459</link><description>The Themesflat Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widget's titles in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4608 | SellKit – Funnel builder and checkout optimizer for WooCommerce to sell more, faster &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4608</link><description>The SellKit – Funnel builder and checkout optimizer for WooCommerce to sell more, faster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4707 | Materialis Companion &amp;lt;= 1.3.41 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Store Cross-Site Scripting via materialis_contact_form Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4707</link><description>The Materialis Companion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's materialis_contact_form shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.41 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5449 | WP Dark Mode – WordPress Dark Mode Plugin for Improved Accessibility, Dark Theme, Night Mode, and Social Sharing &amp;lt;= 5.0.4 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5449</link><description>The WP Dark Mode – WordPress Dark Mode Plugin for Improved Accessibility, Dark Theme, Night Mode, and Social Sharing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the wpdm_social_share_save_options function in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5615 | Open Graph &amp;lt;= 1.11.2 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5615</link><description>The Open Graph plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.11.2 via the 'opengraph_default_description' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including partial content of password-protected blog posts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2017 | Countdown, Coming Soon, Maintenance – Countdown &amp;amp; Clock &amp;lt;= 2.7.8 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2017</link><description>The Countdown, Coming Soon, Maintenance – Countdown &amp; Clock plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the conditionsRow and switchCountdown functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject PHP Objects and modify the status of countdowns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6956 | EasyAzon – Amazon Associates Affiliate Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via easyazon-cloaking-locale</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6956</link><description>The EasyAzon – Amazon Associates Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘easyazon-cloaking-locale’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6966 | The Moneytizer &amp;lt;= 9.5.20 - Missing Authorization via multiple AJAX actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6966</link><description>The The Moneytizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data, modification of data, and loss of data due to a missing capability check on multiple AJAX functions in the /core/core_ajax.php file in all versions up to, and including, 9.5.20. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access and above, to update and retrieve billing and bank details, update and reset the plugin's settings, and update languages as well as other lower-severity actions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6968 | The Moneytizer &amp;lt;= 9.5.20 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via multiple AJAX actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6968</link><description>The The Moneytizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 9.5.20. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on multiple AJAX functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to to update and retrieve billing and bank details, update and reset the plugin's settings, and update languages as well as other lower-severity actions via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0910 | Restrict for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Protection Mechanism Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0910</link><description>The Restrict for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6 due to improper restrictions on hidden data that make it accessible through the REST API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract potentially sensitive data from post content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2350 | Clever Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple CAFE Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2350</link><description>The Clever Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the CAFE Icon, CAFE Team Member, and CAFE Slider widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4194 | Album and Image Gallery plus Lightbox &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4194</link><description>The The Album and Image Gallery plus Lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.0. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4705 | Testimonials Widget &amp;lt;= 4.0.4 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via testimonials Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4705</link><description>The Testimonials Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's testimonials shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4788 | Boostify Header Footer Builder for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Missing Authorization to Page/Post Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4788</link><description>The Boostify Header Footer Builder for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the create_bhf_post function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to create pages or posts with arbitrary content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4942 | Custom Dash &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4942</link><description>The Custom Dash plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5001 | Image Hover Effects for Elementor with Lightbox and Flipbox &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via _id, oxi_addons_f_title_tag, and content_description_tag Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5001</link><description>The Image Hover Effects for Elementor with Lightbox and Flipbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the '_id', 'oxi_addons_f_title_tag', and 'content_description_tag' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5179 | Cowidgets – Elementor Addons &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5179</link><description>The Cowidgets – Elementor Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 via the 'item_style' and 'style' parameters. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5224 | Easy Social Like Box – Popup – Sidebar Widget &amp;lt;= 4.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5224</link><description>The Easy Social Like Box – Popup – Sidebar Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'cardoza_facebook_like_box' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5324 | Login/Signup Popup ( Inline Form + Woocommerce ) 2.7.1 - 2.7.2 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5324</link><description>The Login/Signup Popup ( Inline Form + Woocommerce ) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'import_settings' function in versions 2.7.1 to 2.7.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change arbitrary options on affected sites. This can be used to enable new user registration and set the default role for new users to Administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5342 | Simple Image Popup Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5342</link><description>The Simple Image Popup Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'sips_popup' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>