<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:28:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-62225 | Optical Disc Archive Software provided by Sony Corporation registers a Windows service with an unquoted file path. A user with the write per...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62225</link><description>Optical Disc Archive Software provided by Sony Corporation registers a Windows service with an unquoted file path. A user with the write permission on the root directory of the system drive may execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64151 | Multiple Roboticsware products provided by Roboticsware PTE. LTD. register Windows services with unquoted file paths. A user with the write ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64151</link><description>Multiple Roboticsware products provided by Roboticsware PTE. LTD. register Windows services with unquoted file paths. A user with the write permission on the root directory of the system drive may execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10567 | FunnelKit &amp;lt; 3.12.0.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10567</link><description>The FunnelKit  WordPress plugin before 3.12.0.1 does not sanitize user input before echoing it back in some of its checkout-related AJAX actions, allowing attackers to conduct reflected XSS attacks against logged-in users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10873 | Elementinvader Addons for Elementor &amp;lt; 1.4.1 – Unauthenticated Arbitrary Email Sending</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10873</link><description>The ElementInvader Addons for Elementor WordPress plugin before 1.4.1 allows unauthenticated user to send arbitrary e-mails to arbitrary addresses due to missing authorization on the elementinvader_addons_for_elementor_forms_send_form action.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11072 | Download Counter Button &amp;lt;= 1.8.6.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11072</link><description>The MelAbu WP Download Counter Button WordPress plugin through 1.8.6.7 does not validate the path of files to be downloaded, which could allow unauthenticated attacker to read/download arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6027 | Ace User Management &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Subscriber+ Authentication Bypass via Password Rest</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6027</link><description>The Ace User Management WordPress plugin through 2.0.3 does not properly validate that a password reset token is associated with the user who requested it, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber to reset the password of arbitrary accounts, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21071 | Out-of-bounds write in handling opcode in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR Nov-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to write ou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21071</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in handling opcode in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR Nov-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21073 | Insecure default configuration in USB connection mode prior to SMR Nov-2025 Release 1 allows privileged physical attackers to access user da...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21073</link><description>Insecure default configuration in USB connection mode prior to SMR Nov-2025 Release 1 allows privileged physical attackers to access user data. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21074 | Out-of-bounds read in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Nov-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21074</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Nov-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21075 | Out-of-bounds write in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Nov-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21075</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Nov-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21076 | Improper handling of insufficient permissions or privileges in Samsung Account prior to version 15.5.00.18 allows local attackers to access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21076</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permissions or privileges in Samsung Account prior to version 15.5.00.18 allows local attackers to access data in Samsung Account. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21077 | Improper input validation in Samsung Email prior to version 6.2.06.0 allows local attackers to launch arbitrary activity with Samsung Email ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21077</link><description>Improper input validation in Samsung Email prior to version 6.2.06.0 allows local attackers to launch arbitrary activity with Samsung Email privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21078 | Use of insufficiently random value of secretKey in Smart Switch prior to version 3.7.68.6 allows adjacent attackers to access backup data fr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21078</link><description>Use of insufficiently random value of secretKey in Smart Switch prior to version 3.7.68.6 allows adjacent attackers to access backup data from applications.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21079 | Improper input validation in Samsung Members prior to version 5.5.01.3 allows remote attackers to connect arbitrary URL and launch arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21079</link><description>Improper input validation in Samsung Members prior to version 5.5.01.3 allows remote attackers to connect arbitrary URL and launch arbitrary activity with Samsung Members privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11749 | AI Engine &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure to Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11749</link><description>The AI Engine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.3 via the /mcp/v1/ REST API endpoint that exposes the 'Bearer Token' value when 'No-Auth URL' is enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract the bearer token, which can be used to gain access to a valid session and perform many actions like creating a new administrator account, leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 05:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11162 | Spectra &amp;lt;= 2.19.14 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom CSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11162</link><description>The Spectra Gutenberg Blocks – Website Builder for the Block Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Custom CSS in all versions up to, and including, 2.19.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 04:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12197 | The Events Calendar 6.15.1.1 - 6.15.9 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via s</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12197</link><description>The The Events Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to blind SQL Injection via the 's' parameter in versions 6.15.1.1 to 6.15.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 04:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11835 | Paid Membership Subscriptions – Effortless Memberships, Recurring Payments &amp;amp; Content Restriction &amp;lt;= 2.16.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Member Subscription Auto Renewal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11835</link><description>The Paid Membership Subscriptions – Effortless Memberships, Recurring Payments &amp; Content Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability and validation check on the PMS_AJAX_Checkout_Handler::process_payment() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.16.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to trigger stored auto-renew charges for arbitrary members.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 03:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12580 | SMS for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12580</link><description>The SMS for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'paged' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 03:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12582 | Features &amp;lt;= 0.0.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Option Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12582</link><description>The Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'features_revert_option AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 0.0.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to revert options.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 03:04:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8871 | Everest Forms (Pro) &amp;lt;= 1.9.7 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection via PHAR Deserialization in Form Signature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8871</link><description>The Everest Forms (Pro) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.7 via deserialization of untrusted input in the mime_content_type() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. This vulnerability may be exploited by unauthenticated attackers when a form is present on the site with a non-required signature form field along with an image upload field. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present. This vulnerability is only exploitable in PHP versions prior to 8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 03:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12735 | CVE-2025-12735</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12735</link><description>The expr-eval library is a JavaScript expression parser and evaluator designed to safely evaluate mathematical expressions with user-defined variables. However, due to insufficient input validation, an attacker can pass a crafted variables object into the evaluate() function and trigger arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 01:48:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64110 | Cursor: Authentication Bypass Possible via New Cursorignore Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64110</link><description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions 1.7.23 and below, a logic bug allows a malicious agent to read sensitive files that should be protected via cursorignore. An attacker who has already achieved prompt injection, or a malicious model, could create a new cursorignore file which can invalidate the configuration of pre-existing ones. This could allow a malicious agent to read protected files. This issue is fixed in version 2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 23:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64109 | Cursor CLI Beta: Command Injection via Untrusted MCP Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64109</link><description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions and below, a vulnerability in the Cursor CLI Beta allowed an attacker to achieve remote code execution through the MCP (Model Context Protocol) server mechanism by uploading a malicious MCP configuration in .cursor/mcp.json file in a GitHub repository. Once a victim clones the project and opens it using Cursor CLI, the command to run the malicious MCP server is immediately executed without any warning, leading to potential code execution as soon as the command runs. This issue is fixed in version 2025.09.17-25b418f.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 23:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64108 | Cursor&amp;#x27;s Sensitive File Modification can Lead to NTFS Path Quirks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64108</link><description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions 1.7.44 and below, various NTFS path quirks allow a prompt injection attacker to circumvent sensitive file protections and overwrite files which Cursor requires human approval to overwrite. Modification of some of the protected files can lead to RCE. Must be chained with a prompt injection or malicious model attach. Only affects systems supporting NTFS. This issue is fixed in version 2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 23:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59595 | CVE-2025-59595 is an internally discovered denial of service 
vulnerability in versions of Secure Access prior to 14.12. An attacker 
can se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59595</link><description>CVE-2025-59595 is an internally discovered denial of service 
vulnerability in versions of Secure Access prior to 14.12. An attacker 
can send a specially crafted packet to a server in a non-default 
configuration and cause the server to crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59596 | CVE-2025-59596 is a denial-of-service vulnerability in Secure Access 
Windows client versions 12.0 to 14.10 that is addressed in version 
14...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59596</link><description>CVE-2025-59596 is a denial-of-service vulnerability in Secure Access 
Windows client versions 12.0 to 14.10 that is addressed in version 
14.12. If a local networking policy is active, attackers on an adjacent 
network may be able to send a crafted packet and cause the client system
 to crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64106 | Cursor: Speedbump Modal Bypass in MCP Server Deep-Link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64106</link><description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions 1.7.28 and below, an input validation flaw in Cursor's MCP server installation enables specially crafted deep-links to bypass the standard security warnings and conceal executed commands from users if they choose to accept the server. If an attacker is able to convince a victim to navigate to a malicious deeplink, the victim will not see the correct speedbump modal, and if they choose to accept, will execute commands specified by the attackers deeplink.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64107 | Cursor is Vulnerable to Path Manipulation Using Backslashes on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64107</link><description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions 1.7.52 and below, manipulating internal settings may lead to RCE. Cursor detects path manipulation via forward slashes (./.cursor/./././././mcp.json etc.), and requires human approval to complete the operation. However, the same kind of manipulation using backslashes was not correctly detected, allowing an attacker who had already achieved prompt injection or some other level of control to overwrite sensitive editor files without approval on Windows machines. This issue is fixed in version 2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62722 | LinkAce: Stored XSS Vulnerability in Link Title Field Through Social Media Sharing Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62722</link><description>LinkAce is a self-hosted archive to collect website links. In versions 2.3.1 and below, the social media sharing functionality contains a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that allows any authenticated user to inject arbitrary JavaScript by creating a link with malicious HTML in the title field. When a user views the link details page and the shareable links are rendered, the malicious JavaScript executes in their browser. This vulnerability affects multiple sharing services and can be exploited to steal session cookies, perform actions on behalf of users, or deliver malware. This issue is fixed in version 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62720 | LinkAce: Data Exfiltration via Export Functions Allow Access to All Users&amp;#x27; Private Links</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62720</link><description>LinkAce is a self-hosted archive to collect website links. Versions 2.3.1 and below allow any authenticated user to export the entire database of links from all users in the system, including private links that should only be accessible to their owners. The HTML and CSV export functions in the ExportController class retrieve all links without applying any ownership or visibility filtering, effectively bypassing all access controls implemented elsewhere in the application. This issue is fixed in version 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62721 | LinkAce: Authorization Bypass Allows Unauthorized Access to All Private Links, Lists, and Tags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62721</link><description>LinkAce is a self-hosted archive to collect website links. In versions 2.3.1 and below, authenticated RSS feed endpoints in the FeedController class fail to implement proper authorization checks, allowing any authenticated user to access all links, lists, and tags from all users in the system, regardless of their ownership or visibility settings. This issue is fixed in version 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62719 | LinkAce: Limited Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in Keyword Fetching Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62719</link><description>LinkAce is a self-hosted archive to collect website links. In versions 2.3.0 and below, the htmlKeywordsFromUrl function in the FetchController class accepts user-provided URLs and makes HTTP requests to them without validating that the destination is not an internal or private network resource. This Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability allows authenticated attackers to use the application server to perform port scanning and service discovery on internal networks. Practical impact is very limited because the function only extracts content from HTML meta keywords tags, which prevents meaningful data exfiltration from databases, APIs, or cloud metadata endpoints. This issue is fixed in version 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:09:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54496 | Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT-6 Heap-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54496</link><description>A maliciously crafted project file may cause a heap-based buffer 
overflow in 
Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT-6, which may allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54526 | Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT-6 Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54526</link><description>Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT-6 is vulnerable to a stack-based buffer 
overflow while processing a specially crafted project file, which may 
allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:44:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62715 | ClipBucket v5: Stored XSS via Collection Tags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62715</link><description>ClipBucket v5 is an open source video sharing platform. Versions 5.5.2-#147 and below contain a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ClipBucket’s Collection tags feature. An authenticated normal user can create a tag containing HTML or JavaScript, which is later rendered unescaped in collection detail and tag-list pages. As a result, arbitrary JavaScript executes in the browsers of all users who view the affected pages. This issue is fixed in version 5.5.2-#152.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:44:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62520 | MantisBT unauthorized disclosure of private project column configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62520</link><description>Mantis Bug Tracker (MantisBT) is an open source issue tracker. In versions 2.27.1 and below, due to insufficient access-level checks, any non-admin user with access to manage_config_columns_page.php can use the Copy From action to retrieve the columns configuration from a private project they have no access to. This issue is fixed in version 2.27.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56230 | Tencent Docs Desktop 3.9.20 and earlier suffers from Missing SSL Certificate Validation in the update component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56230</link><description>Tencent Docs Desktop 3.9.20 and earlier suffers from Missing SSL Certificate Validation in the update component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62369 | Xibo CMS: Remote Code Execution through module templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62369</link><description>Xibo is an open source digital signage platform with a web content management system (CMS). Versions 4.3.0 and below contain a Remote Code Execution vulnerability in the CMS Developer menu's Module Templating functionality, allowing authenticated users with "System -&gt; Add/Edit custom modules and templates" permissions to manipulate Twig filters and execute arbitrary server-side functions as the web server user. This issue is fixed in version 4.3.1. To workaround this issue, use the 4.1 and 4.2 patch commits.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62507 | Redis: Bug in XACKDEL may lead to stack overflow and potential RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62507</link><description>Redis is an open source, in-memory database that persists on disk. In versions 8.2.0 and above, a user can run the XACKDEL command with multiple ID's and trigger a stack buffer overflow, which may potentially lead to remote code execution. This issue is fixed in version 8.2.3. To workaround this issue without patching the redis-server executable is to prevent users from executing XACKDEL operation. This can be done using ACL to restrict XACKDEL command.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27374 | An issue was discovered in the Secure Boot component in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 10...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27374</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Secure Boot component in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400. The lack of a length check leads to out-of-bounds writes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55155 | MantisBT: Authentication bypass for some passwords due to PHP type juggling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55155</link><description>Mantis Bug Tracker (MantisBT) is an open source issue tracker. In versions 2.27.1 and below, when a user edits their profile to change their e-mail address, the system saves it without validating that it actually belongs to the user. This could result in storing an invalid email address, preventing the user from receiving system notifications. Notifications sent to another person's email address could lead to information disclosure. This issue is fixed in version 2.27.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48076 | Galette is vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48076</link><description>Galette is a membership management web application for non profit organizations. Versions 1.1.5.2 and below allow a user to edit a group name and insert an XSS payload. This issue is fixed in version 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48884 | Galette is vulnerable to XSS through Document Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48884</link><description>Galette is a membership management web application for non profit organizations. In versions 1.1.5.2 and below, Galette's Document Type is vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting. This issue is fixed in version 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52910 | An issue was discovered in the GPU in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400. A Use-After...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52910</link><description>An issue was discovered in the GPU in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400. A Use-After-Free leads to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47776 | MantisBT: Authentication bypass for some passwords due to PHP type juggling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47776</link><description>Mantis Bug Tracker (MantisBT) is an open source issue tracker. Due to incorrect use of loose (==) instead of strict (===) comparison in the authentication code in versions 2.27.1 and below.PHP type juggling will cause certain MD5 hashes matching scientific notation to be interpreted as numbers. Instances using the MD5 login method allow an attacker who knows the victim's username and has access to an account with a password hash that evaluates to zero to log in without knowing the victim's actual password, by using any other password with a hash that also evaluates to zero This issue is fixed in version 2.27.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54335 | An issue was discovered in the GPU driver in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1480, 2400, 1580, 2500. There is a use-after-free in the Xclips...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54335</link><description>An issue was discovered in the GPU driver in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1480, 2400, 1580, 2500. There is a use-after-free in the Xclipse GPU Driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56426 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56426</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, W920, W930, W1000. The lack of a length check leads to out-of-bounds writes via malformed USB packets to the target.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32786 | GLPI Inventory Plugin is Vulnerable to Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32786</link><description>The GLPI Inventory Plugin handles network discovery, inventory, software deployment, and data collection for GLPI agents. Versions 1.5.0 and below are vulnerable to SQL Injection. This issue is fixed in version 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49494 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem. Mishandling of an 5G NRMM packet leads to a Denial of Se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49494</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem. Mishandling of an 5G NRMM packet leads to a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23358 | NVIDIA NVApp for Windows contains a vulnerability in the installer, where a local attacker can cause a search path element issue. A successf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23358</link><description>NVIDIA NVApp for Windows contains a vulnerability in the installer, where a local attacker can cause a search path element issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution and escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33176 | NVIDIA RunAI for all platforms contains a vulnerability where a user could cause an improper restriction of communications channels on an ad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33176</link><description>NVIDIA RunAI for all platforms contains a vulnerability where a user could cause an improper restriction of communications channels on an adjacent network. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to escalation of privileges, data tampering, and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54327 | An issue was discovered in VTS in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54327</link><description>An issue was discovered in VTS in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, 1580, W920, W930, and W1000. Improper input validation in the VTS driver leads to an arbitrary write.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:48:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61431 | A reflected cross-site scripted (XSS) vulnerability in the /jsp/gsfr_feditorHTML.jsp endpoint of Zucchetti ZMaintenance Infinity v4.1 allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61431</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripted (XSS) vulnerability in the /jsp/gsfr_feditorHTML.jsp endpoint of Zucchetti ZMaintenance Infinity v4.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary Javascript in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload into the pHtmlSource parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:28:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12108 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function Survision License Plate Recognition Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12108</link><description>The Survision LPR Camera system does not enforce password protection by default. This allows access to the configuration wizard immediately without a login prompt or credentials check.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 18:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64322 | Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in Salesforce Agentforce Vibes Extension allows Manipulating Writeable C...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64322</link><description>Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in Salesforce Agentforce Vibes Extension allows Manipulating Writeable Configuration Files.This issue affects Agentforce Vibes Extension: before 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 18:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10875 | Improper Neutralization of Input Used for LLM Prompting vulnerability in Salesforce Mulesoft Anypoint Code Builder allows Code Injection.Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10875</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input Used for LLM Prompting vulnerability in Salesforce Mulesoft Anypoint Code Builder allows Code Injection.This issue affects Mulesoft Anypoint Code Builder: before 1.11.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 18:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52513 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 2400, 1580, 2500. A race condition in the HTS driver results in an out-of-bounds ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52513</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 2400, 1580, 2500. A race condition in the HTS driver results in an out-of-bounds write, leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 18:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54334 | An issue was discovered in the NPU driver in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1280, 2200, 1380, 1480, 2400, 1580, 2500. There is a NULL Point...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54334</link><description>An issue was discovered in the NPU driver in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1280, 2200, 1380, 1480, 2400, 1580, 2500. There is a NULL Pointer Dereference of hdev in the __npu_vertex_bootup function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 18:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54325 | An issue was discovered in VTS in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 1080, 1280, 2200, 1380, 1480, 2400, 1580, 2500, W92...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54325</link><description>An issue was discovered in VTS in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 1080, 1280, 2200, 1380, 1480, 2400, 1580, 2500, W920, W930, W1000. A race condition in the VTS driver results in an out-of-bounds read, leading to an information leak.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 18:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54333 | An issue was discovered in NPU in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos through July 2025. There is an Invalid Pointer Dereference of node in the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54333</link><description>An issue was discovered in NPU in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos through July 2025. There is an Invalid Pointer Dereference of node in the get_vs4l_profiler_node function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 17:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54331 | An issue was discovered in NPU in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos through July 2025. There is an Untrusted Pointer Dereference of src_hdr in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54331</link><description>An issue was discovered in NPU in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos through July 2025. There is an Untrusted Pointer Dereference of src_hdr in the copy_ncp_header function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 17:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54332 | An issue was discovered in NPU in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos through July 2025. There is a NULL Pointer Dereference of profiler.node in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54332</link><description>An issue was discovered in NPU in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos through July 2025. There is a NULL Pointer Dereference of profiler.node in the npu_vertex_profileoff function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54323 | An issue was discovered in the camera in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54323</link><description>An issue was discovered in the camera in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, and 1580. Improper debug printing leads to information leakage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54329 | An issue was discovered in NAS in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54329</link><description>An issue was discovered in NAS in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, 1580, 2500, W920, W930, W1000, Modem 5123, Modem 5300, and Modem 5400. The function used to send a multiple-payloads message (including an SMS message) lacks bounds checking, which can lead to a heap overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:46:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54330 | An issue was discovered in NPU in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos through July 2025. There is an Out-of-bounds Read of q-&gt;bufs[] in the __is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54330</link><description>An issue was discovered in NPU in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos through July 2025. There is an Out-of-bounds Read of q-&gt;bufs[] in the __is_done_for_me function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54863 | Insufficiently Protected Credentials in Radiometrics VizAir</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54863</link><description>Radiometrics VizAir is vulnerable to exposure of the system's REST API key through a publicly accessible configuration file. This allows attackers to remotely alter weather data and configurations, automate attacks against multiple instances, and extract sensitive meteorological data, which could potentially compromise airport operations. Additionally, attackers could flood the system with false alerts, leading to a denial-of-service condition and significant disruption to airport operations. Unauthorized remote control over aviation weather monitoring and data manipulation could result in incorrect flight planning and hazardous takeoff and landing conditions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60925 | codeshare v1.0.0 was discovered to contain an information leakage vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60925</link><description>codeshare v1.0.0 was discovered to contain an information leakage vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61945 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function in Radiometrics VizAir</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61945</link><description>Radiometrics VizAir is vulnerable to any remote attacker via access to the admin panel of the VizAir system without authentication. Once inside, the attacker can modify critical weather parameters such as wind shear alerts, inversion depth, and CAPE values, which are essential for accurate weather forecasting and flight safety. This unauthorized access could result in the disabling of vital alerts, causing hazardous conditions for aircraft, and manipulating runway assignments, which could result in mid-air conflicts or runway incursions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61956 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function in Radiometrics VizAir</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61956</link><description>Radiometrics VizAir is vulnerable to a lack of authentication mechanisms for critical functions, such as admin access and API requests. Attackers can modify configurations without authentication, potentially manipulating active runway settings and misleading air traffic control (ATC) and pilots. Additionally, manipulated meteorological data could mislead forecasters and ATC, causing inaccurate flight planning.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63294 | WorkDo HRM SaaS HR and Payroll Tool 8.1 is affected vulnerable to Insecure Permissions. An authenticated user can create leave or resignatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63294</link><description>WorkDo HRM SaaS HR and Payroll Tool 8.1 is affected vulnerable to Insecure Permissions. An authenticated user can create leave or resignation records on behalf of other users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12184 | MeetingList &amp;lt;= 0.11 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12184</link><description>The MeetingList plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 0.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 14:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12682 | Easy Upload Files During Checkout &amp;lt;= 2.9.8 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary JavaScript File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12682</link><description>The Easy Upload Files During Checkout plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary JavaScript file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'file_during_checkout' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary JavaScript files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:55:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12695 | Insecure configuration in DSPy lead to arbitrary file read when running untrusted code inside the sandbox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12695</link><description>The overly permissive sandbox configuration in DSPy allows attackers to steal sensitive files in cases when users build an AI agent which consumes user input and uses the “PythonInterpreter” class.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41335 | Missing Authorization vulnerability in CanalDenuncia.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41335</link><description>A lack of authorisation vulnerability has been detected in CanalDenuncia.app. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access other users' information by sending a POST through the parameters 'id' and ' 'id_sociedad' in '/api/buscarEmpresaById.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41336 | Missing Authorization vulnerability in CanalDenuncia.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41336</link><description>A lack of authorisation vulnerability has been detected in CanalDenuncia.app. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access other users' information by sending a POST through the parameter 'web' in '/backend/api/buscarConfiguracionParametros.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41337 | Missing Authorization vulnerability in CanalDenuncia.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41337</link><description>A lack of authorisation vulnerability has been detected in CanalDenuncia.app. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access other users' information by sending a POST through the parameter 'web' in '/backend/api/buscarSSOParametros.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41338 | Missing Authorization vulnerability in CanalDenuncia.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41338</link><description>A lack of authorisation vulnerability has been detected in CanalDenuncia.app. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access other users' information by sending a POST through the parameters 'id_denuncia' and 'id_user' in '/backend/api/buscarTestigoByIdDenunciaUsuario.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41339 | Missing Authorization vulnerability in CanalDenuncia.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41339</link><description>A lack of authorisation vulnerability has been detected in CanalDenuncia.app. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access other users' information by sending a POST through the parameter 'id_sociedad' in '/backend/api/buscarTipoDenuncia.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41340 | Missing Authorization vulnerability in CanalDenuncia.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41340</link><description>A lack of authorisation vulnerability has been detected in CanalDenuncia.app. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access other users' information by sending a POST through the parameters 'id_tp_denuncia' and 'id_sociedad' in '/backend/api/buscarTipoDenunciabyId.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41341 | Missing Authorization vulnerability in CanalDenuncia.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41341</link><description>A lack of authorisation vulnerability has been detected in CanalDenuncia.app. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access other users' information by sending a POST through the parameters 'id_denuncia' and 'seguro' in '/backend/api/buscarUsuarioByDenuncia.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41342 | Missing Authorization vulnerability in CanalDenuncia.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41342</link><description>A lack of authorisation vulnerability has been detected in CanalDenuncia.app. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access other users' information by sending a POST through the parameter 'id_user' in '/backend/api/buscarUsuarioId.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41343 | Missing Authorization vulnerability in CanalDenuncia.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41343</link><description>A lack of authorisation vulnerability has been detected in CanalDenuncia.app. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access other users' information by sending a POST through the parameter 'email' in '/backend/api/users/searchUserByEmail.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41344 | Missing Authorization vulnerability in CanalDenuncia.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41344</link><description>A lack of authorisation vulnerability has been detected in CanalDenuncia.app. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access other users' information by sending a POST through the parameter 'id_archivo' in '/backend/api/verArchivo.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41345 | Missing Authorization vulnerability in CanalDenuncia.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41345</link><description>A lack of authorisation vulnerability has been detected in CanalDenuncia.app. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access other users' information by sending a POST through the parameters 'id_denuncia' and 'id_user' in '/backend/api/buscarDenunciasById.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41111 | Missing Authorization vulnerability in CanalDenuncia.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41111</link><description>A lack of authorisation vulnerability has been detected in CanalDenuncia.app. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access other users' information by sending a POST through the parameter 'id_denuncia' in '/backend/api/buscarComentariosByDenuncia.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41112 | Missing Authorization vulnerability in CanalDenuncia.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41112</link><description>A lack of authorisation vulnerability has been detected in CanalDenuncia.app. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access other users' information by sending a POST through the parameter 'web' in '/backend/api/buscarConfiguracionParametros2.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41113 | Missing Authorization vulnerability in CanalDenuncia.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41113</link><description>A lack of authorisation vulnerability has been detected in CanalDenuncia.app. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access other users' information by sending a POST through the parameter 'id_denuncia' in '/backend/api/buscarDenunciaByPin.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41114 | Missing Authorization vulnerability in CanalDenuncia.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41114</link><description>A lack of authorisation vulnerability has been detected in CanalDenuncia.app. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access other users' information by sending a POST through the parameters 'id_denuncia' and 'id_user' in '/backend/api/buscarDocumentosByIdDenunciaUsuario.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12045 | Orbit Fox Companion &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Post Taxonomy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12045</link><description>The Orbit Fox: Duplicate Page, Menu Icons, SVG Support, Cookie Notice, Custom Fonts &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the category and tag 'name' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 11:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12493 | ShopLentor &amp;lt;= 3.2.5 - Unauthenticated Local PHP File Inclusion via &amp;#x27;load_template&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12493</link><description>The ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg +21 Modules – All in One Solution (formerly WooLentor) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.5 via the 'load_template' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary .php files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where .php file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 11:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11690 | IDOR vulnerability in the CFMOTO RIDE API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11690</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability exists in the vehicleId parameter, allowing unauthorized access to sensitive information of other users’ vehicles. Exploiting this issue enables an attacker to retrieve data such as GPS coordinates, encryption keys, initialization vectors, model numbers, and fuel statistics belonging to other users, instead of being limited to their own vehicle data. This is a server-side authorization fix.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 10:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20725 | In ims service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege, if...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20725</link><description>In ims service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01671924; Issue ID: MSV-4620.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20726 | In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege, if a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20726</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01672598; Issue ID: MSV-4622.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20727 | In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege, if a UE ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20727</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01672601; Issue ID: MSV-4623.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20728 | In wlan STA driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20728</link><description>In wlan STA driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00447115; Issue ID: MSV-4276.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20729 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20729</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00441512; Issue ID: MSV-4153.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20730 | In preloader, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20730</link><description>In preloader, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10068463; Issue ID: MSV-4141.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20731 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20731</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege (when OceReducedNeighborReport is disabled). User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00441511; Issue ID: MSV-4140.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20732 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20732</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege (when OceReducedNeighborReport is disabled). User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00441510; Issue ID: MSV-4139.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20733 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20733</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00441509; Issue ID: MSV-4138.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20734 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20734</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00441507; Issue ID: MSV-4112.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20735 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20735</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00435349; Issue ID: MSV-4051.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20736 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20736</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00435347; Issue ID: MSV-4049.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20737 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20737</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00435343; Issue ID: MSV-4040.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20738 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20738</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00435342; Issue ID: MSV-4039.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20739 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20739</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00435340; Issue ID: MSV-4038.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20740 | In wlan STA driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a race condition. This could lead to local information disclosure with Use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20740</link><description>In wlan STA driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a race condition. This could lead to local information disclosure with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00435337; Issue ID: MSV-4036.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20741 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20741</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00434422; Issue ID: MSV-3958.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20742 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20742</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00432680; Issue ID: MSV-3949.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20743 | In clkdbg, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a maliciou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20743</link><description>In clkdbg, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10136671; Issue ID: MSV-4651.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20744 | In pda, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20744</link><description>In pda, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10127160; Issue ID: MSV-4542.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20745 | In apusys, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious acto...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20745</link><description>In apusys, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10095441; Issue ID: MSV-4294.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20746 | In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20746</link><description>In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10010441; Issue ID: MSV-3967.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20747 | In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20747</link><description>In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10010443; Issue ID: MSV-3966.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20748 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20748</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00432679; Issue ID: MSV-3950.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20749 | In charger, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20749</link><description>In charger, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09915493; Issue ID: MSV-3800.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 06:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10896 | Multiple Plugins &amp;lt;= Multiple Versions - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Plugin Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10896</link><description>Multiple plugins for WordPress with the Jewel Theme Recommended Plugins Library are vulnerable to Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type via arbitrary plugin installation in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2.3. This is due to missing capability checks on the '*_recommended_upgrade_plugin' function which allows arbitrary plugin URLs to be installed. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access and above to upload arbitrary plugin packages to the affected site's server via a crafted plugin URL, which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11704 | Elegance Menu &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11704</link><description>The Elegance Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.9 via the 'elegance-menu' attribute of the `elegance-menu` shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary .php files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where .php file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11724 | EM Beer Manager &amp;lt;= 3.2.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11724</link><description>The EM Beer Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file upload leading to remote code execution in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.3. This is due to missing file type validation in the EMBM_Admin_Untappd_Import_image() function and missing authorization checks on the wp_ajax_embm-untappd-import action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files including PHP files and execute code on the server granted they can provide a mock HTTP server that responds with specific JSON data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11733 | Footnotes Made Easy &amp;lt;= 3.0.7 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11733</link><description>The Footnotes Made Easy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via plugin settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11753 | Multi-language Responsive Portfolio WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11753</link><description>The Bootstrap Multi-language Responsive Portfolio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11758 | All in One Time Clock Lite – Tracking Employee Time Has Never Been Easier &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Missing Authorization to Page Creation and Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11758</link><description>The All in One Time Clock Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing authorization check in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.3. This is due  to the plugin exposing admin-level AJAX actions to unauthenticated users via wp_ajax_nopriv_ hooks, while relying only on a nonce check without capability checks. This makes it possible for  unauthenticated attackers to create published pages, create shift records with integrity issues, and download time reports containing PII (employee names and work schedules).</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11812 | Reuse Builder &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11812</link><description>The Reuse Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'reuse_builder_single_post_title' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.7. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'style' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11890 | Crypto Payment Gateway with Payeer for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Unauthenticated Payment Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11890</link><description>The Crypto Payment Gateway with Payeer for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to payment bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a payments status through server-side validation though the /wc-api/bp-payeer-gateway-callback endpoint. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update unpaid order statuses to paid resulting in a loss of revenue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12065 | WP Carticon &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12065</link><description>The WP Carticon plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'carticon_js_script' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12156 | Ai Auto Tool Content Writing Assistant (Gemini Writer, ChatGPT ) All in One 2.0.7 - 2.2.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Post Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12156</link><description>The Ai Auto Tool Content Writing Assistant (Gemini Writer, ChatGPT ) All in One plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the save_post_data() function in versions 2.0.7 to 2.2.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create and publish arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12157 | Simple User Capabilities &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Capability Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12157</link><description>The Simple User Capabilities plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_nopriv_reset_capability' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset any user's capabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12158 | Simple User Capabilities &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12158</link><description>The Simple User Capabilities plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check on the suc_submit_capabilities() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to elevate the role of any user account to administrator.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12188 | Posts Navigation Links for Sections and Headings - Free by WP Masters &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12188</link><description>The Posts Navigation Links for Sections and Headings – Free by WP Masters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'wpm_navigation_links_settings' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12350 | DominoKit &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12350</link><description>The DominoKit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the wp_ajax_nopriv_dominokit_option_admin_action AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12369 | Extensions for Leaflet Map &amp;lt;= 4.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12369</link><description>The Extensions for Leaflet Map plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `geojsonmarker` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.7. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12371 | Nari Accountant &amp;lt;= 1.0.12 - Authenticated (Editor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12371</link><description>The Nari Accountant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via account settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12389 | Import Export For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12389</link><description>The Import Export For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the update_setting() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugin's record setting.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12393 | Free Quotation &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12393</link><description>The Free Quotation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12396 | Clubmember &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12396</link><description>The clubmember plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12400 | LMB^Box Smileys &amp;lt;= 3.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12400</link><description>The LMB^Box Smileys plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the manage_page() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12402 | LinkedIn Resume &amp;lt;= 2.00 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12402</link><description>The LinkedIn Resume plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.00. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the linkedinresume_printAdminPage() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12403 | Associados Amazon Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.8 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12403</link><description>The Associados Amazon Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.8. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the brzon_admin_panel() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12410 | SH Contextual Help &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12410</link><description>The SH Contextual Help plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation in the sh_contextual_help_dashboard_widget() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12412 | Top Bar Notification &amp;lt;= 1.12 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12412</link><description>The Top Bar Notification plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.12. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on th tbn_ajax_add() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12413 | Social Media WPCF7 Stop Words &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12413</link><description>The Social Media WPCF7 Stop Words plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the smWpCfSwOptions() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12415 | MapMap &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update and Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12415</link><description>The MapMap plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the admin_shortcode_submit, admin_configuration_submit, and admin_shortcode_delete functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12416 | Pagerank Tools &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12416</link><description>The Pagerank Tools plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.5. This is due to missing nonce validation on the pr_save_settings() function and insufficient input sanitization. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. The injected scripts will execute whenever a user accesses the plugin's settings page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12452 | Visit Counter 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12452</link><description>The Visit Counter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in version 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the widgets.php page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12456 | Centangle Team Showcase &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery To Plugin&amp;#x27;s Settings Modification And Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12456</link><description>The Centangle-Team plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Additionally, due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on cai_name_color parameter, this issue allows to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages, that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12683 | NULL DACL assigned to Named Pipe communicating with SYSTEM Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12683</link><description>The service employed by Everything, running as SYSTEM, communicates with the lower privileged Everything GUI via a named pipe. The named pipe has a NULL DACL and thus provides all users full permission over it; leading to potential Service Denial Of Service or Privilege escalation(only if chained with other elements) for a local low privilege user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11007 | CE21 Suite 2.2.1 - 2.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11007</link><description>The CE21 Suite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin settings update due to a missing capability check on the wp_ajax_nopriv_ce21_single_sign_on_save_api_settings AJAX action in versions 2.2.1 to 2.3.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's API settings including a secret key used for authentication. This allows unauthenticated attackers to create new admin accounts on an affected site.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11008 | CE21 Suite &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure to Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11008</link><description>The CE21 Suite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.1 via the log file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including authentication credentials, which can be used to log in as other users as long as they have used the plugin's custom authentication feature before. This may include administrators, which makes a complete site takeover possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12069 | WP Global Screen Options &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Screen Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12069</link><description>The WP Global Screen Options plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.2. This is due to missing nonce validation on the `updatewpglobalscreenoptions` action handler. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify global screen options for all users via a forged request granted they can trick an administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12070 | ViaAds &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to API Key Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12070</link><description>The ViaAds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1. This is due to missing nonce validation on the `ViaAds_pluginHandler` function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's API key and cookie consent settings via a forged request granted they can trick an administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12401 | Label Plugins &amp;lt;= 0.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12401</link><description>The Label Plugins plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.5. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the label_plugins_options() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27064 | Buffer Over-read in Core Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27064</link><description>Information disclosure while registering commands from clients with diag through diagHal.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27070 | Out-of-bounds Write in Windows Compute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27070</link><description>Memory corruption while performing encryption and decryption commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27074 | Incorrect Calculation of Buffer Size in SCE-Mink</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27074</link><description>Memory corruption while processing a GP command response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47352 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47352</link><description>Memory corruption while processing audio streaming operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47353 | Exposed Dangerous Method or Function in Automotive Software platform based on QNX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47353</link><description>Memory corruption while processing request sent from GVM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47357 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function in SMSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47357</link><description>Information Disclosure when a user-level driver performs QFPROM read or write operations on Fuse regions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47360 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow in Automotive Software platform based on QNX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47360</link><description>Memory corruption while processing client message during device management.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47361 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Automotive Software platform based on QNX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47361</link><description>Memory corruption when triggering a subsystem crash with an out-of-range identifier.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47362 | Buffer Over-read in Automotive Software platform based on QNX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47362</link><description>Information disclosure while processing message from client with invalid payload.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47365 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in Automotive Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47365</link><description>Memory corruption while processing large input data from a remote source via a communication interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47367 | Out-of-bounds Write in WinBlast Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47367</link><description>Memory corruption while accessing a buffer during IOCTL processing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47368 | Buffer Over-read in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47368</link><description>Memory corruption when dereferencing an invalid userspace address in a user buffer during MCDM IOCTL processing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47370 | Reachable Assertion in BT Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47370</link><description>Transient DOS when a remote device sends an invalid connection request during BT connectable LE scan.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12324 | TablePress – Tables in WordPress made easy &amp;lt;= 3.2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12324</link><description>The TablePress – Tables in WordPress made easy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `table` shortcode attributes in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:10:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11841 | Greenshift – animation and page builder blocks &amp;lt;= 12.2.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Chart Data Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11841</link><description>The Greenshift – animation and page builder blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Chart Data attributes in all versions up to, and including, 12.2.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 03:10:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43288 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7. An app may be able to bypass Priva...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43288</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7. An app may be able to bypass Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43309 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26 and iPadOS 26. An attacker with physical access to an iOS de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43309</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26 and iPadOS 26. An attacker with physical access to an iOS device may be able to view notification contents from the Lock Screen.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43322 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43322</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43323 | This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26, tvOS 26, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, watchOS 26. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43323</link><description>This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26, tvOS 26, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, watchOS 26. An app may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43334 | This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43334</link><description>This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43335 | The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43335</link><description>The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43336 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43336</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app with root privileges may be able to access private information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43338 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43338</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26. Processing a maliciously crafted media file may lead to unexpected app termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43345 | A correctness issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 26, watchOS 26, macOS Sonoma 14.8, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43345</link><description>A correctness issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 26, watchOS 26, macOS Sonoma 14.8, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, macOS Sequoia 15.7, visionOS 26, iOS 18.7 and iPadOS 18.7. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43348 | A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may bypass Ga...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43348</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may bypass Gatekeeper checks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43350 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An attacker may be able to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43350</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An attacker may be able to view restricted content from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43360 | The issue was addressed with improved UI. This issue is fixed in iOS 26 and iPadOS 26. Password fields may be unintentionally revealed.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43360</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved UI. This issue is fixed in iOS 26 and iPadOS 26. Password fields may be unintentionally revealed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43361 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in tvOS 26, watchOS 26, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, macOS S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43361</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in tvOS 26, watchOS 26, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, visionOS 26. A malicious app may be able to read kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43364 | A race condition was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8, macOS Sequoia 15.7. An app may be able ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43364</link><description>A race condition was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8, macOS Sequoia 15.7. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43365 | A denial-of-service issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 26 and iPadOS 26. An unprivileged process...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43365</link><description>A denial-of-service issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 26 and iPadOS 26. An unprivileged process may be able to terminate a root processes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43373 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43373</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43376 | A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 26, tvOS 26, watchOS 26, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, vis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43376</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 26, tvOS 26, watchOS 26, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, visionOS 26. A remote attacker may be able to view leaked DNS queries with Private Relay turned on.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43377 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to cause ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43377</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43378 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43378</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43379 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43379</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43380 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43380</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. Parsing a file may lead to an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43382 | A parsing issue in the handling of directory paths was addressed with improved path validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43382</link><description>A parsing issue in the handling of directory paths was addressed with improved path validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43383 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43383</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. Processing a maliciously crafted media file may lead to unexpected app termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43384 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43384</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. Processing a maliciously crafted media file may lead to unexpected app termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43385 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43385</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. Processing a maliciously crafted media file may lead to unexpected app termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43386 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43386</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Processing a maliciously crafted media file may lead to unexpected app termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43387 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. A malicious app may be able to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43387</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. A malicious app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43389 | A privacy issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43389</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43390 | A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43390</link><description>A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43391 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43391</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43392 | The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43392</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. A website may exfiltrate image data cross-origin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43394 | This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43394</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43395 | This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43395</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43396 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. A sandboxed app may be a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43396</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. A sandboxed app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43397 | A permissions issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43397</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43398 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, watc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43398</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43399 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43399</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43401 | A denial-of-service issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. A remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43401</link><description>A denial-of-service issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. A remote attacker may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43405 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43405</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43407 | This issue was addressed with improved entitlements. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, iOS 26...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43407</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved entitlements. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43408 | This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43408</link><description>This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An attacker with physical access may be able to access contacts from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43409 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43409</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43411 | This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43411</link><description>This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43412 | A file quarantine bypass was addressed with additional checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43412</link><description>A file quarantine bypass was addressed with additional checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43413 | An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43413</link><description>An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. A sandboxed app may be able to observe system-wide network connections.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43414 | A permissions issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. A shortcut may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43414</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. A shortcut may be able to access files that are normally inaccessible to the Shortcuts app.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43419 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26, tvOS 26, watchOS 26, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, visionOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43419</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26, tvOS 26, watchOS 26, iOS 26 and iPadOS 26, visionOS 26. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43420 | A race condition was addressed with improved state handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43420</link><description>A race condition was addressed with improved state handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43421 | Multiple issues were addressed by disabling array allocation sinking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43421</link><description>Multiple issues were addressed by disabling array allocation sinking. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43422 | The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An attacker with physical access to a d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43422</link><description>The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An attacker with physical access to a device may be able to disable Stolen Device Protection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43423 | A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, visionOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43423</link><description>A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, visionOS 26.1. An attacker with physical access to an unlocked device paired with a Mac may be able to view sensitive user information in system logging.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43424 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. A malicious HID device may cause an un...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43424</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. A malicious HID device may cause an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43425 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43425</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43426 | A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be able to access se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43426</link><description>A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43427 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43427</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43429 | A buffer overflow was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43429</link><description>A buffer overflow was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43430 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43430</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43431 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43431</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43432 | A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43432</link><description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43433 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43433</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43434 | A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43434</link><description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected Safari crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43435 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43435</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43436 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43436</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to enumerate a user's installed apps.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43438 | A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43438</link><description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected Safari crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43439 | A privacy issue was addressed by removing sensitive data. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43439</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed by removing sensitive data. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43440 | This issue was addressed with improved checks This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43440</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved checks This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43441 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43441</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43442 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be able to ident...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43442</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be able to identify what other apps a user has installed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43443 | This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43443</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43444 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43444</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43445 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43445</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing a maliciously crafted media file may lead to unexpected app termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43446 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43446</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43447 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43447</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43448 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43448</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43449 | The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. A malicious app may be able to tr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43449</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. A malicious app may be able to track users between installs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43450 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be able to learn information a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43450</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be able to learn information about the current camera view before being granted camera access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43452 | This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. Keyboard sugges...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43452</link><description>This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. Keyboard suggestions may display sensitive information on the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43454 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. A device may persistently fail ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43454</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. A device may persistently fail to lock.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43455 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. A maliciou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43455</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. A malicious app may be able to take a screenshot of sensitive information in embedded views.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43457 | A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43457</link><description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected Safari crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43458 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43458</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43459 | An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1. An attacker with physical access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43459</link><description>An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1. An attacker with physical access to a locked Apple Watch may be able to view Live Voicemail.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43460 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An attacker with physical access to a loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43460</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An attacker with physical access to a locked device may be able to view sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43462 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visionOS 26...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43462</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43468 | A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43468</link><description>A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43469 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43469</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43472 | A validation issue was addressed with improved input sanitization. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43472</link><description>A validation issue was addressed with improved input sanitization. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43474 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43474</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or read kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43476 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43476</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43477 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43477</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43478 | A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43478</link><description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43479 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43479</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43480 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43480</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1, watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1. A malicious website may exfiltrate data cross-origin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43481 | This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43481</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43493 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Visiting a malici...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43493</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Visiting a malicious website may lead to address bar spoofing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43495 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be able to monitor keystrokes with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43495</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be able to monitor keystrokes without user permission.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43496 | The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, vis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43496</link><description>The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, visionOS 26.1. Remote content may be loaded even when the 'Load Remote Images' setting is turned off.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43498 | An authorization issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43498</link><description>An authorization issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43499 | This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43499</link><description>This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43500 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of user preferences. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, vis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43500</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of user preferences. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43502 | A privacy issue was addressed by removing sensitive data. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An ap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43502</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed by removing sensitive data. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to bypass certain Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43503 | An inconsistent user interface issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43503</link><description>An inconsistent user interface issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, Safari 26.1, visionOS 26.1. Visiting a malicious website may lead to user interface spoofing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43504 | A buffer overflow was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in Xcode 26.1. A user in a privileged network position ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43504</link><description>A buffer overflow was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in Xcode 26.1. A user in a privileged network position may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43505 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in Xcode 26.1. Processing a maliciously craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43505</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in Xcode 26.1. Processing a maliciously crafted file may lead to heap corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43507 | A privacy issue was addressed by moving sensitive data. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43507</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed by moving sensitive data. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1, visionOS 26.1. An app may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35021 | Abilis CPX Fallback Shell Connection Relay</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35021</link><description>By failing to authenticate three times to an unconfigured Abilis CPX device via SSH, an attacker can login to a restricted shell on the fourth attempt, and from there, relay connections.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46556 | MantisBT is Vulnerable to Denial-of-Service (DoS) attack via Excessive Note Length</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46556</link><description>Mantis Bug Tracker (MantisBT) is an open source issue tracker. Versions 2.27.1 and below allow attackers to permanently corrupt issue activity logs by submitting extremely long notes (tested with 4,788,761 characters) due to a lack of server-side validation of note length. Once such a note is added, the activity stream UI fails to render; therefore, new notes cannot be displayed, effectively breaking all future collaboration on the issue. This issue is fixed in version 2.27.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15054 | Nagios XI &amp;lt; 5.4.0 XSS via jQuery Migrate Library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15054</link><description>Nagios XI versions prior to 5.4.0 are vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) via the jQuery Migrate library. Insufficient validation or escaping of user-supplied input may allow an attacker to inject and execute arbitrary script in the context of a victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 22:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47698 | Nagios XI &amp;lt; 5.8.7 XSS in Core UI Views URL handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47698</link><description>Nagios XI versions prior to 5.8.7 using embedded Nagios Core are vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) via the Core UI’s Views URL handling. Insufficient validation or escaping of user-supplied input may allow an attacker to inject and execute arbitrary script in the context of a victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 22:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13997 | Nagios XI &amp;lt; 2024R1.1.3 Privilege Escalation via Migrate Server Feature to Root on Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13997</link><description>Nagios XI versions prior to 2024R1.1.3 contain a privilege escalation vulnerability in which an authenticated administrator could leverage the Migrate Server feature to obtain root privileges on the underlying XI host. By abusing the migration workflow, an admin-level attacker could execute actions outside the intended security scope of the application, resulting in full control of the operating system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 22:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34501 | Shuffle Master Deck Mate 2 Hard-coded Credentials &amp;amp; Exposed Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34501</link><description>Deck Mate 2 is distributed with static, hard-coded credentials for the root shell and web user interface, while multiple management services (SSH, HTTP, Telnet, SMB, X11) are enabled by default. If an attacker can reach these interfaces - most often through local or near-local access such as connecting to the USB or Ethernet ports beneath the table - the built-in credentials permit administrative login and full control of the system. Once authenticated, an attacker can access firmware utilities, modify controller software, and establish persistent compromise. Remote attack paths via network, cellular, or telemetry links may exist in specific configurations but generally require additional capabilities or operator error. The vendor reports that USB access has been disabled in current firmware builds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 22:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13998 | Nagios XI &amp;lt; 2024R1.1.3 API Keys &amp;amp; Hashed Passwords Authenticated Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13998</link><description>Nagios XI versions prior to 2024R1.1.3, under certain circumstances, disclose sensitive user account information (including API keys and hashed passwords) to authenticated users who should not have access to that data. Exposure of API keys or password hashes could lead to account compromise, abuse of API privileges, or offline cracking attempts. CVE-2024-13995 addresses a similar vulnerability with a potentially incomplete fix for the underlying problem in earlier versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 22:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11193 | A potential vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Tablets that could allow a local authenticated user or application to gain access to s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11193</link><description>A potential vulnerability was reported in some Lenovo Tablets that could allow a local authenticated user or application to gain access to sensitive device specific information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 21:51:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36172 | Multiple security vulnerabilities are addressed with IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation iFixes for 24.0.0-IF007, 24.0.1-IF005 and 25.0.0-IF002</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36172</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation 25.0.0 through 25.0.0 Interim Fix 001, 24.0.1 through 24.0.1 Interim Fix 004, 24.0.0 through 24.0.0 Interim Fix 006, and earlier unsupported releases IBM Business Automation Workflow is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 21:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12657 | Malformed KMIP response may result in access violation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12657</link><description>The KMIP response parser built into mongo binaries is overly tolerant of certain malformed packets, and may parse them into invalid objects. Later reads of this object can result in read access violations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 21:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63293 | FairSketch Rise Ultimate Project Manager &amp; CRM 3.9.4 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions. A remote authenticated user can append comments ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63293</link><description>FairSketch Rise Ultimate Project Manager &amp; CRM 3.9.4 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions. A remote authenticated user can append comments or upload attachments to tickets for which they lack view or edit authorization, due to missing authorization checks in the ticketing/commenting API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 20:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50735 | Directory traversal vulnerability in NextChat thru 2.16.0 due to the WebDAV proxy failing to canonicalize or reject dot path segments in its...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50735</link><description>Directory traversal vulnerability in NextChat thru 2.16.0 due to the WebDAV proxy failing to canonicalize or reject dot path segments in its catch-all route, allowing attackers to gain sensitive information via authenticated or anonymous WebDAV endpoints.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 20:16:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12531 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server is affected by an XML external entity injection (XXE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12531</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7.0.0 through 11.7.1.6 is vulnerable to an XML external entity injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12642 | HTTP Header Smuggling via Trailer Merge</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12642</link><description>lighttpd1.4.80 incorrectly merged trailer fields into headers after http request parsing. This behavior can be exploited to conduct HTTP Header Smuggling attacks.

Successful exploitation may allow an attacker to:

  *  Bypass access control rules
  *  Inject unsafe input into backend logic that trusts request headers
  *  Execute HTTP Request Smuggling attacks under some conditions


This issue affects lighttpd1.4.80</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:46:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63593 | Grav CMS1.7.49.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63593</link><description>Grav CMS1.7.49.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8558 | Insider Threat Management (ITM) Server versions prior to 7.17.2 contain an authentication bypass vulnerability that allows unauthenticated u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8558</link><description>Insider Threat Management (ITM) Server versions prior to 7.17.2 contain an authentication bypass vulnerability that allows unauthenticated users on an adjacent network to perform agent unregistration when the number of registered agents exceeds the licensed limit. Successful exploitation prevents the server from receiving new events from affected agents, resulting in a partial loss of integrity and availability with no impact to confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12463 | Unauthenticated SQL Injection in Guetebruck G-Cam Series Cameras</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12463</link><description>An unauthenticated SQL Injection was discovered within the Geutebruck G-Cam E-Series Cameras through the `Group` parameter in the `/uapi-cgi/viewer/Param.cgi` script. This has been confirmed on the EFD-2130 camera running firmware version 1.12.0.19.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10280 | Incorrect Content Type Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10280</link><description>IdentityIQ
8.5, IdentityIQ 8.4 and all 8.4 patch levels prior to 8.4p4, IdentityIQ 8.3 and
all 8.3 patch levels prior to 8.3p6, and all prior versions allows some
IdentityIQ web services that provide non-HTML content to be accessed via a URL
path that will set the Content-Type to HTML allowing a requesting browser to
interpret content not properly escaped to prevent Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11953 | Command injection in React Native CLI allows remote attackers to perform remote code execution by sending HTTP requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11953</link><description>The Metro Development Server, which is opened by the React Native CLI, binds to external interfaces by default. The server exposes an endpoint that is vulnerable to OS command injection. This allows unauthenticated network attackers to send a POST request to the server and run arbitrary executables. On Windows, the attackers can also execute arbitrary shell commands with fully controlled arguments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50363 | Phpgurukul Maid Hiring Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /maid-hiring.php va the name field.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50363</link><description>Phpgurukul Maid Hiring Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /maid-hiring.php va the name field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63441 | Open Source Social Network (OSSN) 8.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the parameter param` at endpoint u/administrator/frien...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63441</link><description>Open Source Social Network (OSSN) 8.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the parameter param` at endpoint u/administrator/friends.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60785 | A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the Postgres Drivers component of iceScrum v7.54 Pro On-prem allows attackers to execute arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60785</link><description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the Postgres Drivers component of iceScrum v7.54 Pro On-prem allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted HTML page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60503 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the administrative interface of ultimatefosters UltimatePOS 4.8 where input submitted i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60503</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the administrative interface of ultimatefosters UltimatePOS 4.8 where input submitted in the purchase functionality is reflected without proper escaping in the admin log panel page in the 'reference No.' field. This flaw allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of an administrator's browser session, which could lead to session hijacking or other malicious actions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36093 | security vulnerabilities are addressed with IBM Business Automation Insights iFixes for October 2025.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36093</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak For Business Automation 25.0.0, 24.0.1, and 24.0.0 could allow an attacker to access unauthorized content or perform unauthorized actions using man in the middle techniques due to improper access controls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63453 | Car-Booking-System-PHP v.1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /carlux/contact.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63453</link><description>Car-Booking-System-PHP v.1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /carlux/contact.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63452 | Car-Booking-System-PHP v.1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /carlux/forgot-pass.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63452</link><description>Car-Booking-System-PHP v.1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /carlux/forgot-pass.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63450 | Car-Booking-System-PHP v.1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /carlux/booking.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63450</link><description>Car-Booking-System-PHP v.1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /carlux/booking.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63451 | Car-Booking-System-PHP v.1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /carlux/sign-in.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63451</link><description>Car-Booking-System-PHP v.1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /carlux/sign-in.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63449 | Water Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /orders.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63449</link><description>Water Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /orders.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11761 | HP Client Management Script Library – Security Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11761</link><description>A potential security vulnerability has been identified in the HP Client Management Script Library software, which might allow escalation of privilege during the installation process. HP is releasing software updates to mitigate the potential vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36091 | IBM Business Automation Insights unverified ownership</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36091</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak For Business Automation 25.0.0, 24.0.1, and 24.0.0 could allow an authenticated user to cause dashboards to become inaccessible to legitimate users due to invalid ownership assignment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36092 | IBM Business Automation Insights improper input validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36092</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak For Business Automation 25.0.0, 24.0.1, and 24.0.0 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service due to the improper validation of input length.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63446 | Water Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /add_vendor.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63446</link><description>Water Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /add_vendor.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63447 | Water Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /add_customer.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63447</link><description>Water Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /add_customer.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63448 | Water Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /edit_product.php?id=1.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63448</link><description>Water Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /edit_product.php?id=1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63442 | Simple User Management System with PHP-MySQL v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via the Profile Section. The system fails to p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63442</link><description>Simple User Management System with PHP-MySQL v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via the Profile Section. The system fails to properly sanitize user input, allowing attackers to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript when the input is displayed in the browser</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63443 | School Management System PHP v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /login.php via the password parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63443</link><description>School Management System PHP v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /login.php via the password parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45663 | An issue in NetSurf v3.11 causes the application to read uninitialized heap memory when creating a dom_event structure.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45663</link><description>An issue in NetSurf v3.11 causes the application to read uninitialized heap memory when creating a dom_event structure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51317 | An issue in NetSurf v.3.11 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the dom_node_normalize function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51317</link><description>An issue in NetSurf v.3.11 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the dom_node_normalize function</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 14:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29699 | NetSurf 3.11 is vulnerable to Use After Free in dom_node_set_text_content function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29699</link><description>NetSurf 3.11 is vulnerable to Use After Free in dom_node_set_text_content function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 14:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60892 | An issue in Raspberry Pi Imager version 1.9.6 for Windows, affecting its OS customization feature. The imager's 'public-key authentication' ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60892</link><description>An issue in Raspberry Pi Imager version 1.9.6 for Windows, affecting its OS customization feature. The imager's 'public-key authentication' setting unintentionally re-adds a user's id_rsa.pub key from their local Windows machine to the authorized_keys file on the Raspberry Pi, even after the user explicitly deletes the key from the user interface. This creates an unintended attack surface, as it could allow an attacker to use a different key than the intended one to login to the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 14:55:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8900 | Doccure Core &amp;lt; 1.5.4 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8900</link><description>The Doccure Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions up to, and excluding, 1.5.4. This is due to the plugin allowing users who are registering new accounts to set their own role or by supplying 'user_type' field. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to gain elevated privileges by creating an account with the administrator role.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 14:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64294 | WordPress WP Snow Effect plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.15 - Broken Access Control to Notice Dismissal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64294</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in d3wp WP Snow Effect allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects WP Snow Effect: from n/a through 1.1.15.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 13:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12626 | jeecgboot jeewx-boot WxActGoldeneggsPrizesController.java getImgUrl path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12626</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in jeecgboot jeewx-boot up to 641ab52c3e1845fec39996d7794c33fb40dad1dd. This affects the function getImgUrl of the file WxActGoldeneggsPrizesController.java. Performing manipulation of the argument imgurl results in path traversal. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided. The root cause was initially fixed but can be evaded with additional encoding.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 13:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40107 | can: hi311x: fix null pointer dereference when resuming from sleep before interface was enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40107</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

can: hi311x: fix null pointer dereference when resuming from sleep before interface was enabled

This issue is similar to the vulnerability in the `mcp251x` driver,
which was fixed in commit 03c427147b2d ("can: mcp251x: fix resume from
sleep before interface was brought up").

In the `hi311x` driver, when the device resumes from sleep, the driver
schedules `priv-&gt;restart_work`. However, if the network interface was
not previously enabled, the `priv-&gt;wq` (workqueue) is not allocated and
initialized, leading to a null pointer dereference.

To fix this, we move the allocation and initialization of the workqueue
from the `hi3110_open` function to the `hi3110_can_probe` function.
This ensures that the workqueue is properly initialized before it is
used during device resume. And added logic to destroy the workqueue
in the error handling paths of `hi3110_can_probe` and in the
`hi3110_can_remove` function to prevent resource leaks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 12:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0987 | IDOR in CB Project&amp;#x27;s CVLand</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0987</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in CB Project Ltd. Co. CVLand allows Parameter Injection.This issue affects CVLand: from 2.1.0 through 20251103.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 12:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48397 | The privileged user could log in without sufficient credentials after enabling an application protocol.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48397</link><description>The privileged user could log in without sufficient credentials after enabling an application protocol.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 08:44:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12623 | fushengqian fuint Authentication Token ClientSignController.java authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12623</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in fushengqian fuint up to 41e26be8a2c609413a0feaa69bdad33a71ae8032. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file fuint-application/src/main/java/com/fuint/module/clientApi/controller/ClientSignController.java of the component Authentication Token Handler. Such manipulation leads to authorization bypass. The attack may be launched remotely. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product operates on a rolling release basis, ensuring continuous delivery. Consequently, there are no version details for either affected or updated releases.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 08:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48396 | Arbitrary code execution is possible due to improper validation of the file upload functionality in Eaton BLSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48396</link><description>Arbitrary code execution is possible due to improper validation of the file upload functionality in Eaton BLSS.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 08:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12622 | Tenda AC10 SysRunCmd formSysRunCmd buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12622</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda AC10 16.03.10.13. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSysRunCmd of the file /goform/SysRunCmd. This manipulation of the argument getui causes buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 07:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12619 | Tenda A15 openNetworkGateway fromSetWirelessRepeat buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12619</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda A15 15.13.07.13. Affected is the function fromSetWirelessRepeat of the file /goform/openNetworkGateway. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto2_4g results in buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 07:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12503 | Digiwin｜EasyFlow .NET and EasyFlow AiNet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12503</link><description>EasyFlow .NET and EasyFlow AiNet developed by Digiwin has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 06:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12618 | Tenda AC8 DatabaseIniSet buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12618</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.06. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/DatabaseIniSet. The manipulation of the argument Time leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 06:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12617 | itsourcecode Billing System login_crud.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12617</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Billing System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/app/login_crud.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Password can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 04:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12616 | PHPGurukul News Portal settings.py insertion of sensitive information into debugging code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12616</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in PHPGurukul News Portal 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /onps/settings.py. Performing manipulation results in insertion of sensitive information into debugging code. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 04:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12615 | PHPGurukul News Portal settings.py hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12615</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in PHPGurukul News Portal 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /onps/settings.py. Such manipulation of the argument SECRET_KEY leads to use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The attack may be performed from remote. The attack requires a high level of complexity. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 03:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12614 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System admin_class.php delete_payment sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12614</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. Impacted is the function delete_payment of the file /admin_class.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 03:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12611 | Tenda AC21 SetPptpServerCfg formSetPPTPServer buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12611</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda AC21 16.03.08.16. This vulnerability affects the function formSetPPTPServer of the file /goform/SetPptpServerCfg. The manipulation of the argument startIp leads to buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 03:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12612 | Campcodes School Fees Payment Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12612</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes School Fees Payment Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ajax.php. The manipulation results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 03:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12610 | CodeAstro Gym Management System view-progress-report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12610</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in CodeAstro Gym Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/view-progress-report.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 03:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12609 | CodeAstro Gym Management System update-progress.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12609</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Gym Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/update-progress.php. Performing manipulation of the argument id/ini_weight results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 01:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12608 | itsourcecode Online Loan Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12608</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Online Loan Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /manage_user.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 01:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12607 | itsourcecode Online Loan Management System manage_payment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12607</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Online Loan Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /manage_payment.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 01:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>