<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:54:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-51107 | Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the component /mcgs/admin/contactus.php of PHPGURUKUL Medical Card Generation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51107</link><description>Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the component /mcgs/admin/contactus.php of PHPGURUKUL Medical Card Generation System using PHP and MySQL v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the pagetitle, pagedes, and email parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51108 | Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the component /admin/card-bwdates-report.php of PHPGURUKUL Medical Card Genera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51108</link><description>Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the component /admin/card-bwdates-report.php of PHPGURUKUL Medical Card Generation System using PHP and MySQL v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the fromdate and todate parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51360 | An issue in Hospital Management System In PHP V4.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the hms/doctor/edit-profile.php fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51360</link><description>An issue in Hospital Management System In PHP V4.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the hms/doctor/edit-profile.php file</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5114 | easysoft zentaopms Editor index.php edit deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5114</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in easysoft zentaopms 21.5_20250307 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function Edit of the file /index.php?m=editor&amp;amp;f=edit&amp;amp;filePath=cGhhcjovLy9ldGMvcGFzc3dk&amp;amp;action=edit of the component Committer. The manipulation of the argument filePath leads to deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5111 | FreeFloat FTP Server TYPE Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5111</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component TYPE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5112 | FreeFloat FTP Server MGET Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5112</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component MGET Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3580 | An access control vulnerability was discovered in Grafana OSS where an Organization administrator could permanently delete the Server admini...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3580</link><description>An access control vulnerability was discovered in Grafana OSS where an Organization administrator could permanently delete the Server administrator account. This vulnerability exists in the DELETE /api/org/users/ endpoint.

The vulnerability can be exploited when:

1. An Organization administrator exists

2. The Server administrator is either:

   - Not part of any organization, or
   - Part of the same organization as the Organization administrator
Impact:

- Organization administrators can permanently delete Server administrator accounts

- If the only Server administrator is deleted, the Grafana instance becomes unmanageable

- No super-user permissions remain in the system

- Affects all users, organizations, and teams managed in the instance

The vulnerability is particularly serious as it can lead to a complete loss of administrative control over the Grafana instance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5110 | FreeFloat FTP Server VERBOSE Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5110</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component VERBOSE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5109 | FreeFloat FTP Server STATUS Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5109</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component STATUS Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7803 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7803</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 11.6 before 17.10.7, 17.11 before 17.11.3, and 18.0 before 18.0.1. A Discord webhook integration may cause DoS.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9163 | User Interface (UI) Misrepresentation of Critical Information in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9163</link><description>A business logic error in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.1 prior to 17.10.7, 17.11 prior to 17.11.3 and 18.0 prior to 18.0.1 where an attacker can cause a branch name confusion in confidential MRs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31049 | WordPress Dash &amp;lt;= 1.3 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31049</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in themeton Dash allows Object Injection. This issue affects Dash: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31053 | WordPress KBx Pro Ultimate &amp;lt;= 7.9.8 - Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31053</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in quantumcloud KBx Pro Ultimate allows Path Traversal. This issue affects KBx Pro Ultimate: from n/a through 7.9.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31056 | WordPress WhatsCart plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31056</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Techspawn WhatsCart - Whatsapp Abandoned Cart Recovery, Order Notifications, Chat Box, OTP for WooCommerce allows SQL Injection. This issue affects WhatsCart - Whatsapp Abandoned Cart Recovery, Order Notifications, Chat Box, OTP for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31060 | WordPress Capie &amp;lt;= 1.0.40 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31060</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ApusTheme Capie allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Capie: from n/a through 1.0.40.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31064 | WordPress Vizeon - Business Consulting &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31064</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in gavias Vizeon - Business Consulting allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Vizeon - Business Consulting: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31069 | WordPress HotStar – Multi-Purpose Business Theme &amp;lt;= 1.4 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31069</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in themeton HotStar – Multi-Purpose Business Theme allows Object Injection. This issue affects HotStar – Multi-Purpose Business Theme: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31397 | WordPress Bus Ticket Booking with Seat Reservation for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31397</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in smartcms Bus Ticket Booking with Seat Reservation for WooCommerce allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Bus Ticket Booking with Seat Reservation for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31423 | WordPress Umberto &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31423</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in AncoraThemes Umberto allows Object Injection. This issue affects Umberto: from n/a through 1.2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31430 | WordPress The Business &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31430</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in themeton The Business allows Object Injection. This issue affects The Business: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31631 | WordPress Fish House &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31631</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in AncoraThemes Fish House allows Object Injection. This issue affects Fish House: from n/a through 1.2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31632 | WordPress La Boom &amp;lt;= 2.7 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31632</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in SpyroPress La Boom allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects La Boom: from n/a through 2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31633 | WordPress Kiamo - Responsive Business Service WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31633</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in gavias Kiamo - Responsive Business Service WordPress Theme allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Kiamo - Responsive Business Service WordPress Theme: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31636 | WordPress WP Post Modules for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31636</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SaurabhSharma WP Post Modules for Elementor allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Post Modules for Elementor: from n/a through 2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31912 | WordPress Enzio - Responsive Business WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31912</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in gavias Enzio - Responsive Business WordPress Theme allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Enzio - Responsive Business WordPress Theme: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31913 | WordPress Ogami &amp;lt;= 1.53 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31913</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ApusTheme Ogami allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Ogami: from n/a through 1.53.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31914 | WordPress Pixel WordPress Form BuilderPlugin &amp;amp; Autoresponder &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31914</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in kamleshyadav Pixel WordPress Form BuilderPlugin &amp; Autoresponder allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Pixel WordPress Form BuilderPlugin &amp; Autoresponder: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31916 | WordPress JP Students Result Management System Premium plugin 1.1.7 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31916</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in joy2012bd JP Students Result Management System Premium allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects JP Students Result Management System Premium: from 1.1.7 through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31918 | WordPress Simple Business Directory Pro &amp;lt;= 15.4.8 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31918</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in quantumcloud Simple Business Directory Pro allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Simple Business Directory Pro: from n/a through 15.4.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31924 | WordPress Crafts &amp;amp; Arts &amp;lt;= 2.5 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31924</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in designthemes Crafts &amp; Arts allows Object Injection. This issue affects Crafts &amp; Arts: from n/a through 2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31927 | WordPress Acerola &amp;lt;= 1.6.5 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31927</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in themeton Acerola allows Object Injection. This issue affects Acerola: from n/a through 1.6.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32284 | WordPress Pet World &amp;lt;= 2.8 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32284</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in designthemes Pet World allows Object Injection. This issue affects Pet World: from n/a through 2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32285 | WordPress Butcher theme &amp;lt;= 2.40 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32285</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ApusTheme Butcher allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Butcher: from n/a through 2.40.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32286 | WordPress Butcher &amp;lt;= 2.40 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32286</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ApusTheme Butcher allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Butcher: from n/a through 2.40.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32289 | WordPress Yozi &amp;lt;= 2.0.52 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32289</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ApusTheme Yozi allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Yozi: from n/a through 2.0.52.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32292 | WordPress Jarvis – Night Club, Concert, Festival WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.8.11 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32292</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in AncoraThemes Jarvis – Night Club, Concert, Festival WordPress allows Object Injection. This issue affects Jarvis – Night Club, Concert, Festival WordPress: from n/a through 1.8.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32293 | WordPress Finance Consultant &amp;lt;= 2.8 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32293</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in designthemes Finance Consultant allows Object Injection. This issue affects Finance Consultant: from n/a through 2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32294 | WordPress Oxpitan &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32294</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in gavias Oxpitan allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Oxpitan: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32302 | WordPress Winnex &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32302</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in gavias Winnex allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Winnex: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32309 | WordPress Healsoul &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32309</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ThemeMove Healsoul allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Healsoul: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39480 | WordPress Car Dealer &amp;lt;= 1.6.6 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39480</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ThemeMakers Car Dealer allows Object Injection. This issue affects Car Dealer: from n/a through 1.6.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39485 | WordPress GrandTour Theme &amp;lt;= 5.5.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39485</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ThemeGoods Grand Tour | Travel Agency WordPress allows Object Injection. This issue affects Grand Tour | Travel Agency WordPress: from n/a through 5.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39489 | WordPress CouponXL &amp;lt;= 4.5.0 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39489</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in pebas CouponXL allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects CouponXL: from n/a through 4.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39490 | WordPress Backpack Traveler &amp;lt;= 2.7 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39490</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Mikado-Themes Backpack Traveler allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Backpack Traveler: from n/a through 2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39494 | WordPress Wilmër theme &amp;lt; 3.4.2 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39494</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Mikado-Themes Wilmër allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Wilmër: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39495 | WordPress Avantage Theme &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39495</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in BoldThemes Avantage allows Object Injection. This issue affects Avantage: from n/a through 2.4.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39499 | WordPress Medicare Theme &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39499</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in BoldThemes Medicare allows Object Injection. This issue affects Medicare: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39500 | WordPress Goodlayers Hostel Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39500</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in GoodLayers Goodlayers Hostel allows Object Injection. This issue affects Goodlayers Hostel: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39501 | WordPress Goodlayers Hostel Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39501</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in GoodLayers Goodlayers Hostel allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Goodlayers Hostel: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39502 | WordPress Goodlayers Hostel Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39502</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GoodLayers Goodlayers Hostel allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Goodlayers Hostel: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39503 | WordPress Goodlayers Hotel plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.4 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39503</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in GoodLayers Goodlayers Hotel allows Object Injection. This issue affects Goodlayers Hotel: from n/a through 3.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39504 | WordPress Goodlayers Hotel plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39504</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in GoodLayers Goodlayers Hotel allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Goodlayers Hotel: from n/a through 3.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39505 | WordPress Goodlayers Hotel plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39505</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GoodLayers Goodlayers Hotel allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Goodlayers Hotel: from n/a through 3.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39506 | WordPress Nasa Core Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39506</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in NasaTheme Nasa Core allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Nasa Core: from n/a through 6.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39536 | WordPress JobHunt Job Alerts &amp;lt;= 3.6 - Arbitrary Content Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39536</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Chimpstudio JobHunt Job Alerts allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects JobHunt Job Alerts: from n/a through 3.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41377 | Cryptographic vulnerability in Iridium Certus 700</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41377</link><description>Cryptographic vulnerability in Iridium Certus 700. This vulnerability allows a user to retrieve the encryption key, resulting in the loading of malicious firmware.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41378 | Injection vulnerability in Iridium Certus 700</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41378</link><description>The SSID field is not parsed correctly and can be used to inject commands into the hostpad.conf file. This can be exploited by an attacker to extend his knowledge of the system and compromise other devices. The information is filtered by the logs function of the web panel.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41379 | Injection vulnerability in Iridium Certus 700</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41379</link><description>The Intellian C700 web panel allows you to add firewall rules. Each of these rules has an associated ID, but there is a problem when adding a new rule, the ID used to create the database entry may be different from the JSON ID. If the rule needs to be deleted later, the system will use the JSON ID and therefore fail. This can be exploited by an attacker to create rules that cannot be deleted unless the device is reset to factory defaults.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41380 | Injection vulnerability in Iridium Certus 700</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41380</link><description>Iridium Certus 700 version 1.0.1 has an embedded credentials vulnerability in the code. This vulnerability allows a local user to retrieve the SSH hash string.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46437 | WordPress Tayori Form plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46437</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in tayoricom Tayori Form allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Tayori Form: from n/a through 1.2.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46440 | WordPress kStats Reloaded plugin &amp;lt;= 0.7.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46440</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mark kStats Reloaded allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects kStats Reloaded: from n/a through 0.7.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46444 | WordPress Ads Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 4.88 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46444</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in scripteo Ads Pro Plugin allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Ads Pro Plugin: from n/a through 4.88.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46446 | WordPress Libro de Reclamaciones &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46446</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ivanrojas Libro de Reclamaciones allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Libro de Reclamaciones: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46448 | WordPress Document Management System &amp;lt;= 1.24 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46448</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in reifsnyderb Document Management System allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Document Management System: from n/a through 1.24.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46454 | WordPress Meta Keywords &amp;amp; Description &amp;lt;= 0.8 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46454</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in svil4ok Meta Keywords &amp;amp; Description allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Meta Keywords &amp;amp; Description: from n/a through 0.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46455 | WordPress WP HRM LITE &amp;lt;= 1.1 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46455</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in IndigoThemes WP HRM LITE allows SQL Injection. This issue affects WP HRM LITE: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46456 | WordPress Theme Blvd Sliders plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46456</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jason Theme Blvd Sliders allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Theme Blvd Sliders: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46458 | WordPress occupancyplan plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3.0 - CSRF to SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46458</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in x000x occupancyplan allows SQL Injection. This issue affects occupancyplan: from n/a through 1.0.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46460 | WordPress Easy Guide &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46460</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Detheme Easy Guide allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Easy Guide: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46463 | WordPress Mailing Group Listserv &amp;lt;= 3.0.4 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46463</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Yamna Khawaja Mailing Group Listserv allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Mailing Group Listserv: from n/a through 3.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46468 | WordPress Fable Extra &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46468</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in WPFable Fable Extra allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Fable Extra: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46474 | WordPress SEUR Oficial &amp;lt;= 2.2.23 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46474</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in SEUR OFICIAL SEUR Oficial allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects SEUR Oficial: from n/a through 2.2.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46486 | WordPress Nomupay Payment Processing Gateway &amp;lt;= 7.1.7 - Arbitrary File Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46486</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in totalprocessing Nomupay Payment Processing Gateway allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Nomupay Payment Processing Gateway: from n/a through 7.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46487 | WordPress EC Authorize.net plugin &amp;lt;=  0.3.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46487</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sftranna EC Authorize.net allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects EC Authorize.net: from n/a through 0.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46488 | WordPress Visual Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46488</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in dastan800 Visual Builder allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Visual Builder: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46490 | WordPress Crossword Compiler Puzzles &amp;lt;= 5.2 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46490</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in wordwebsoftware Crossword Compiler Puzzles allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Crossword Compiler Puzzles: from n/a through 5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46493 | WordPress Crossword Compiler Puzzles &amp;lt;= 5.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46493</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wordwebsoftware Crossword Compiler Puzzles allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Crossword Compiler Puzzles: from n/a through 5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46515 | WordPress Category Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46515</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in M A Vinoth Kumar Category Widget allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Category Widget: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46518 | WordPress IGIT Related Posts With Thumb Image After Posts &amp;lt;=  4.5.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46518</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in phpaddicted IGIT Related Posts With Thumb Image After Posts allows Stored XSS. This issue affects IGIT Related Posts With Thumb Image After Posts: from n/a through 4.5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46526 | WordPress My Custom Widgets plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46526</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in janekniefeldt My Custom Widgets allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects My Custom Widgets: from n/a through 2.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46527 | WordPress Web3Press – Decentralize Publishing with Writing NFT plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Arbitrary File Read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46527</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in LikeCoin Web3Press allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Web3Press: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46537 | WordPress Section Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46537</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ctltwp Section Widget allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Section Widget: from n/a through 3.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46539 | WordPress Fable Extra &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46539</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WPFable Fable Extra allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Fable Extra: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47438 | WordPress WP Job Portal plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47438</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in wpjobportal WP Job Portal allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects WP Job Portal: from n/a through 2.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47453 | WordPress WP Smart Import &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47453</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Xylus Themes WP Smart Import allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects WP Smart Import: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47458 | WordPress B2i Investor Tools plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47458</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in B2itech B2i Investor Tools allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects B2i Investor Tools: from n/a through 1.0.7.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47461 | WordPress Subaccounts for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.6 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47461</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in mediaticus Subaccounts for WooCommerce allows Authentication Abuse. This issue affects Subaccounts for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.6.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47478 | WordPress ProfileGrid  &amp;lt;= 5.9.5.0 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47478</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Metagauss ProfileGrid  allows SQL Injection. This issue affects ProfileGrid : from n/a through 5.9.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47492 | WordPress Drag and Drop File Upload for Elementor Forms &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47492</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in add-ons.org Drag and Drop File Upload for Elementor Forms allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Drag and Drop File Upload for Elementor Forms: from n/a through 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47512 | WordPress Tainacan plugin &amp;lt;=  0.21.14 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47512</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in tainacan Tainacan allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Tainacan: from n/a through 0.21.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47513 | WordPress Infocob CRM Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47513</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in James Laforge Infocob CRM Forms allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Infocob CRM Forms: from n/a through 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47529 | WordPress Experto CTA Widget – Call To Action, Sticky CTA, Floating Button Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Settings Change Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47529</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in UX Design Experts Experto CTA Widget &amp;#8211; Call To Action, Sticky CTA, Floating Button Plugin allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Experto CTA Widget &amp;#8211; Call To Action, Sticky CTA, Floating Button Plugin: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47530 | WordPress WPFunnels &amp;lt;= 3.5.18 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47530</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in WPFunnels WPFunnels allows Object Injection. This issue affects WPFunnels: from n/a through 3.5.18.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47532 | WordPress CoinPayments.net Payment Gateway for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0.17 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47532</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in CoinPayments CoinPayments.net Payment Gateway for WooCommerce allows Object Injection. This issue affects CoinPayments.net Payment Gateway for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.0.17.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47535 | WordPress Opal Woo Custom Product Variation &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47535</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in wpopal Opal Woo Custom Product Variation allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Opal Woo Custom Product Variation: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47539 | WordPress Eventin &amp;lt;= 4.0.26 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47539</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Themewinter Eventin allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Eventin: from n/a through 4.0.26.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47541 | WordPress Mail Mint &amp;lt;= 1.17.7 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47541</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in WPFunnels Mail Mint allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Mail Mint: from n/a through 1.17.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47558 | WordPress MapSVG plugin &amp;lt;= 8.5.31 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47558</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in RomanCode MapSVG allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects MapSVG: from n/a through 8.5.31.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47568 | WordPress ZoomSounds plugin &amp;lt;= 6.91 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47568</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ZoomIt ZoomSounds allows Object Injection. This issue affects ZoomSounds: from n/a through 6.91.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47575 | WordPress School Management plugin &amp;lt;= 92.0.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47575</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in mojoomla School Management allows SQL Injection. This issue affects School Management: from n/a through 92.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47599 | WordPress Facturante &amp;lt;= 1.11 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47599</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in facturante Facturante allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Facturante: from n/a through 1.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47603 | WordPress belingoGeo &amp;lt;= 1.12.0 - Arbitrary File Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47603</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Belingo belingoGeo allows Path Traversal. This issue affects belingoGeo: from n/a through 1.12.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47611 | WordPress User Meta plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47611</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Khaled User Meta allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects User Meta: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47613 | WordPress School Management System for Wordpress plugin &amp;lt;= 92.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47613</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in mojoomla School Management allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects School Management: from n/a through 92.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47618 | WordPress BMI Adult &amp;amp; Kid Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47618</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mortgage Calculator BMI Adult &amp; Kid Calculator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects BMI Adult &amp; Kid Calculator: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47619 | WordPress 6Storage Rentals &amp;lt;= 2.19.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47619</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in 6Storage 6Storage Rentals allows Path Traversal. This issue affects 6Storage Rentals: from n/a through 2.19.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47631 | WordPress Hospital Management System plugin &amp;lt;= 47.0(20-11-2023) - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47631</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in mojoomla Hospital Management System allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Hospital Management System: from 47.0(20 through 11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47637 | WordPress STAGGS &amp;lt;= 2.11.0 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47637</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in STAGGS STAGGS allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects STAGGS: from n/a through 2.11.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47640 | WordPress Printcart Web to Print Product Designer for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.3.8 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47640</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in printcart Printcart Web to Print Product Designer for WooCommerce allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Printcart Web to Print Product Designer for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47641 | WordPress Printcart Web to Print Product Designer for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.3.8 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47641</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in printcart Printcart Web to Print Product Designer for WooCommerce allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Printcart Web to Print Product Designer for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47642 | WordPress Ajar in5 Embed &amp;lt;= 3.1.5 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47642</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Ajar Productions Ajar in5 Embed allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Ajar in5 Embed: from n/a through 3.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47646 | WordPress PSW Front-end Login &amp;amp; Registration &amp;lt;= 1.13 - Broken Authentication Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47646</link><description>Weak Password Recovery Mechanism for Forgotten Password vulnerability in Gilblas Ngunte Possi PSW Front-end Login &amp;amp; Registration allows Password Recovery Exploitation. This issue affects PSW Front-end Login &amp;amp; Registration: from n/a through 1.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47658 | WordPress ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.2.7 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47658</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in ELEXtensions ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System: from n/a through 3.2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47660 | WordPress WC Affiliate &amp;lt;= 2.9.1 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47660</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Codexpert, Inc WC Affiliate allows Object Injection. This issue affects WC Affiliate: from n/a through 2.9.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47663 | WordPress Hospital Management System plugin &amp;lt;= 47.0(20-11-2023) - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47663</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in mojoomla Hospital Management System allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Hospital Management System: from 47.0(20 through 11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47670 | WordPress WordPress Social Login and Register &amp;lt;= 7.6.10 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47670</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in miniOrange WordPress Social Login and Register allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects WordPress Social Login and Register: from n/a through 7.6.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47671 | WordPress Binary MLM Plan &amp;lt;= 3.0 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47671</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LETSCMS MLM Software Binary MLM Plan allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Binary MLM Plan: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47672 | WordPress miniOrange Discord Integration &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47672</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in miniOrange miniOrange Discord Integration allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects miniOrange Discord Integration: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47673 | WordPress Arconix Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.16 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47673</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in tychesoftwares Arconix Shortcodes allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Arconix Shortcodes: from n/a through 2.1.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47678 | WordPress FunnelCockpit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47678</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FunnelCockpit FunnelCockpit allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects FunnelCockpit: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47680 | WordPress xili-tidy-tags plugin &amp;lt;= 1.12.06 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47680</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Michel - xiligroup dev xili-tidy-tags allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects xili-tidy-tags: from n/a through 1.12.06.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47687 | WordPress StoreKeeper for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 14.4.4 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47687</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in StoreKeeper B.V. StoreKeeper for WooCommerce allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects StoreKeeper for WooCommerce: from n/a through 14.4.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47690 | WordPress Lead Form Data Collection to CRM plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Arbitrary Option Update to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47690</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in smackcoders Lead Form Data Collection to CRM allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Lead Form Data Collection to CRM: from n/a through 3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48241 | WordPress Verge3D plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48241</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Soft8Soft LLC Verge3D allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Verge3D: from n/a through 4.9.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48245 | WordPress Quick Contact Form plugin &amp;lt;= 8.2.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48245</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in fullworks Quick Contact Form  allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Quick Contact Form : from n/a through 8.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48271 | WordPress Leadinfo &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Settings Change Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48271</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Leadinfo Leadinfo allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Leadinfo: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48273 | WordPress WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.3.2 - Arbitrary File Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48273</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in wpjobportal WP Job Portal allows Path Traversal. This issue affects WP Job Portal: from n/a through 2.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48275 | WordPress Visual Header &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48275</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in dastan800 Visual Header allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Visual Header: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48283 | WordPress Majestic Support &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48283</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Majestic Support Majestic Support allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Majestic Support: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48286 | WordPress ReDi Restaurant Reservation plugin &amp;lt;= 24.1209 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48286</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in catkin ReDi Restaurant Reservation allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects ReDi Restaurant Reservation: from n/a through 24.1209.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48287 | WordPress Pix 4x sem juros – Pagaleve &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48287</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Pagaleve Pix 4x sem juros &amp;#8211; Pagaleve allows Object Injection. This issue affects Pix 4x sem juros &amp;#8211; Pagaleve: from n/a through 1.6.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48289 | WordPress Kids Planet &amp;lt;= 2.2.14 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48289</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in AncoraThemes Kids Planet allows Object Injection. This issue affects Kids Planet: from n/a through 2.2.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48292 | WordPress Tourmaster plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.8 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48292</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in GoodLayers Tourmaster allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Tourmaster: from n/a through 5.3.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5107 | Fujian Kelixun xml_cdr_details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5107</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Fujian Kelixun 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /app/xml_cdr/xml_cdr_details.php. The manipulation of the argument uuid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5108 | zongzhige ShopXO ZIP File Payment.php Upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5108</link><description>A vulnerability was found in zongzhige ShopXO 6.5.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function Upload of the file app/admin/controller/Payment.php of the component ZIP File Handler. The manipulation of the argument params leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1123 | Solid Mail – SMTP email and logging made by SolidWP &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Email</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1123</link><description>The Solid Mail – SMTP email and logging made by SolidWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via email Name, Subject, and Body in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5105 | TOZED ZLT W51 Service Port 7777 heap inspection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5105</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOZED ZLT W51 up to 1.4.2 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Service Port 7777. The manipulation leads to improper clearing of heap memory before release. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5106 | Fujian Kelixun Filename fax_view.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5106</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Fujian Kelixun 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /app/fax/fax_view.php of the component Filename Handler. The manipulation of the argument fax_file leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36527 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36527</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8511 are vulnerable to SQL injection while exporting reports.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41407 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41407</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8511 are vulnerable to SQL injection in the OU History report.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3893 | SQL Injection in MegaBIP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3893</link><description>While editing pages managed by MegaBIP a user with high privileges is prompted to give a reasoning for performing this action. Input provided by the the user is not sanitized, leading to SQL Injection vulnerability. 
Version 5.20 of MegaBIP fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:22:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3894 | Stored XSS in MegaBIP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3894</link><description>Text editor embedded into MegaBIP software does not neutralize user input allowing Stored XSS attacks on other users. In order to use the editor high privileges are required.  
Version 5.20 of MegaBIP fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:22:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3895 | Low token entropy in MegaBIP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3895</link><description>Token used for resetting passwords in MegaBIP software are generated using a small space of random values combined with a queryable value.
 It allows an unauthenticated attacker who know user login names to brute force these tokens and change account passwords (including these belonging to administrators). 
Version 5.20 of MegaBIP fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:22:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4379 | Reflected XSS in DobryCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4379</link><description>DobryCMS in versions 2.* and lower is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). Improper input validation in szukaj parameter allows arbitrary JavaScript to be executed on victim's browser when specially crafted URL is opened.

A hotfix for affected versions was released on 29.04.2025. It removes the vulnerability without incrementing the version.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:22:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13945 | Stored Absolute Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13945</link><description>Stored Absolute Path Traversal vulnerabilities in ASPECT could expose sensitive data 
if administrator credentials become compromised.

This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 09:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47149 | The optional feature 'Anti-Virus &amp; Sandbox' of i-FILTER contains an issue with improper pattern file validation. If exploited, the product m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47149</link><description>The optional feature 'Anti-Virus &amp; Sandbox' of i-FILTER contains an issue with improper pattern file validation. If exploited, the product may treat an unauthorized pattern file as an authorized. If the product uses a specially crafted pattern file, information in the server where the product is running may be retrieved, and/or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 09:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5096 | TablePress &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5096</link><description>The TablePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'data-caption', 'data-s-content-padding', 'data-s-title', and 'data-footer' data-attributes in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 08:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48695 | An issue was discovered in CyberDAVA before 1.1.20. A privilege escalation vulnerability allows a low-privileged user to escalate their priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48695</link><description>An issue was discovered in CyberDAVA before 1.1.20. A privilege escalation vulnerability allows a low-privileged user to escalate their privilege by abusing the following API due to the lack of access control: /api/v2/users/user//role/ROLE/ (admin access can be achieved).</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 04:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48708 | gs_lib_ctx_stash_sanitized_arg in base/gslibctx.c in Artifex Ghostscript through 10.05.0 lacks argument sanitization for the # case.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48708</link><description>gs_lib_ctx_stash_sanitized_arg in base/gslibctx.c in Artifex Ghostscript through 10.05.0 lacks argument sanitization for the # case.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 04:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4594 | Tournamatch &amp;lt;= 4.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4594</link><description>The Tournamatch plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'trn-ladder-registration-button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 03:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48701 | openDCIM through 23.04 allows SQL injection in people_depts.php because prepared statements are not used.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48701</link><description>openDCIM through 23.04 allows SQL injection in people_depts.php because prepared statements are not used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 03:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5098 | KL-001-2025-003: Mobile Dynamix PrinterShare Mobile Print Gmail Oauth Token Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5098</link><description>PrinterShare Android application allows the capture of Gmail authentication tokens that can be reused to access a user's Gmail account without proper authorization.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5099 | KL-001-2025-004: Mobile Dynamix PrinterShare Mobile Print Out-of-bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5099</link><description>An Out of Bounds Write occurs when the native library attempts PDF rendering, which can be exploited to achieve memory corruption and potentially arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5100 | KL-001-2025-005: Mobile Dynamix PrinterShare Mobile Print Double-Free Memory Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5100</link><description>A double-free condition occurs during the cleanup of temporary image files, which can be exploited to achieve memory corruption and potentially arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2394 | Ecovacs Home Android and iOS Mobile Applications up to version 3.3.0 contained embedded access keys and secrets for Alibaba Object Storage S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2394</link><description>Ecovacs Home Android and iOS Mobile Applications up to version 3.3.0 contained embedded access keys and secrets for Alibaba Object Storage Service (OSS), leading to sensitive data disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 01:03:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4692 | ABUP IoT Cloud Platform Incorrect Privilege Assignment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4692</link><description>Actors can use a maliciously crafted JavaScript object notation (JSON) web token (JWT) to perform privilege escalation by submitting the malicious JWT to a vulnerable method exposed on the cloud platform. If the exploit is successful, the user can escalate privileges to access any device managed by the 

ABUP Cloud Update Platform.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 23:19:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4338 | Lantronix Device Installer Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4338</link><description>Lantronix Device installer is vulnerable to XML external entity (XXE) attacks in configuration files read from the network device. An attacker could obtain credentials, access these network devices, and modify their configurations. An attacker may also gain access to the host running the Device Installer software or the password hash of the user running the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 23:19:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48371 | OpenFGA Authorization Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48371</link><description>OpenFGA is an authorization/permission engine. OpenFGA versions 1.8.0 through 1.8.12 (corresponding to Helm chart openfga-0.2.16 through openfga-0.2.30 and docker 1.8.0 through 1.8.12) are vulnerable to authorization bypass when certain Check and ListObject calls are executed. Users are affected under four specific conditions: First, calling Check API or ListObjects with an authorization model that has a relationship directly assignable by both type bound public access and userset; second, there are check or list object queries with contextual tuples for the relationship that can be directly assignable by both type bound public access and userset; third, those contextual tuples’s user field is an userset; and finally, type bound public access tuples are not assigned to the relationship. Users should upgrade to version 1.8.13 to receive a patch. The upgrade is backwards compatible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 22:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47181 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Update Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47181</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 22:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4975 | Tapo privilege escalation on shared devices using notifications</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4975</link><description>When a notification relating to low battery appears for a user with whom the device has been shared, tapping the notification grants full access to the power settings of that device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 21:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48374 | zot logs secrets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48374</link><description>zot is ancontainer image/artifact registry based on the Open Container Initiative Distribution Specification. Prior to version 2.1.3 (corresponding to pseudoversion 1.4.4-0.20250522160828-8a99a3ed231f), when using Keycloak as an oidc provider, the clientsecret gets printed into the container stdout logs for an example at container startup. Version 2.1.3 (corresponding to pseudoversion 1.4.4-0.20250522160828-8a99a3ed231f) fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 20:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48372 | Schule Has Insecure OTP Length, is Susceptible to Brute-Force Attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48372</link><description>Schule is open-source school management system software. The generateOTP() function generates a 4-digit numeric One-Time Password (OTP). Prior to version 1.0.1, even if a secure random number generator is used, the short length and limited range (1000–9999) results in only 9000 possible combinations. This small keyspace makes the OTP highly vulnerable to brute-force attacks, especially in the absence of strong rate-limiting or lockout mechanisms. Version 1.0.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 20:44:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48373 | Schule Has Client-Side Role-Based Access Control (RBAC) Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48373</link><description>Schule is open-source school management system software. The application relies on client-side JavaScript (index.js) to redirect users to different panels based on their role. Prior to version 1.0.1, this implementation poses a serious security risk because it assumes that the value of data.role is trustworthy on the client side. Attackers can manipulate JavaScript in the browser (e.g., via browser dev tools or intercepting API responses) and set data.role to any arbitrary value (e.g., "admin"), gaining unauthorized access to restricted areas of the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 20:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5962 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Authentication Endpoint of Multiple WSO2 Products Due to Missing Output Encoding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5962</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the authentication endpoint of multiple WSO2 products due to missing output encoding of user-supplied input. A malicious actor can exploit this vulnerability to inject arbitrary JavaScript into the authentication flow, potentially leading to UI modifications, redirections to malicious websites, or data exfiltration from the browser.

While this issue could allow an attacker to manipulate the user’s browser, session-related sensitive cookies remain protected with the httpOnly flag, preventing session hijacking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40458 | An issue in Ocuco Innovation Tracking.exe v.2.10.24.51 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the modification of TCP packets.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40458</link><description>An issue in Ocuco Innovation Tracking.exe v.2.10.24.51 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the modification of TCP packets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40459 | An issue in Ocuco Innovation APPMANAGER.EXE v.2.10.24.51 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the application manager function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40459</link><description>An issue in Ocuco Innovation APPMANAGER.EXE v.2.10.24.51 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the application manager function</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40460 | An issue in Ocuco Innovation v.2.10.24.51 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the JOBENTRY.EXE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40460</link><description>An issue in Ocuco Innovation v.2.10.24.51 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the JOBENTRY.EXE</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40461 | An issue in Ocuco Innovation v.2.10.24.51 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the STOCKORDERENTRY.EXE component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40461</link><description>An issue in Ocuco Innovation v.2.10.24.51 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the STOCKORDERENTRY.EXE component</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40462 | An issue in Ocuco Innovation v.2.10.24.51 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the SETTINGSVATIGATOR.EXE component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40462</link><description>An issue in Ocuco Innovation v.2.10.24.51 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the SETTINGSVATIGATOR.EXE component</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41195 | An issue in Ocuco Innovation - INNOVASERVICEINTF.EXE v2.10.24.17 allows attackers to bypass authentication and escalate privileges to Admini...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41195</link><description>An issue in Ocuco Innovation - INNOVASERVICEINTF.EXE v2.10.24.17 allows attackers to bypass authentication and escalate privileges to Administrator via a crafted TCP packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41196 | An issue in Ocuco Innovation - REPORTSERVER.EXE v2.10.24.13 allows attackers to bypass authentication and escalate privileges to Administrat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41196</link><description>An issue in Ocuco Innovation - REPORTSERVER.EXE v2.10.24.13 allows attackers to bypass authentication and escalate privileges to Administrator via a crafted TCP packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41197 | An issue in Ocuco Innovation - INVCLIENT.EXE v2.10.24.5 allows attackers to bypass authentication and escalate privileges to Administrator v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41197</link><description>An issue in Ocuco Innovation - INVCLIENT.EXE v2.10.24.5 allows attackers to bypass authentication and escalate privileges to Administrator via a crafted TCP packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41198 | An issue in Ocuco Innovation - REPORTS.EXE v2.10.24.13 allows attackers to bypass authentication and escalate privileges to Administrator vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41198</link><description>An issue in Ocuco Innovation - REPORTS.EXE v2.10.24.13 allows attackers to bypass authentication and escalate privileges to Administrator via a crafted TCP packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41199 | An issue in Ocuco Innovation - JOBMANAGER.EXE v2.10.24.16 allows attackers to bypass authentication and escalate privileges to Administrator...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41199</link><description>An issue in Ocuco Innovation - JOBMANAGER.EXE v2.10.24.16 allows attackers to bypass authentication and escalate privileges to Administrator via a crafted TCP packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7487 | Improper Authentication in WSO2 Identity Server 7.0.0 Allows Bypass of App-Native Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7487</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability exists in WSO2 Identity Server 7.0.0 due to an implementation flaw that allows app-native authentication to be bypassed when an invalid object is passed.

Exploitation of this vulnerability could enable malicious actors to circumvent the client verification mechanism, compromising the integrity of the authentication process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13955 | SQL Injection 2nd Order</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13955</link><description>2nd Order SQL injection vulnerabilities in ASPECT allow unintended access and manipulation of database repositories if administrator credentials become compromised.This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13956 | SSL Verification Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13956</link><description>SSL Verification Bypass vulnerabilities exist in ASPECT if administrator credentials become compromisedThis issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13957 | SSRF Server Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13957</link><description>SSRF Server Side Request Forgery vulnerabilities exist in ASPECT if administrator credentials become compromisedThis issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13958 | Stored Cross Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13958</link><description>Stored Cross Site Scripting vulnerabilities exist in ASPECT if administrator creden-tials become compromisedThis issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51552 | Weak Password Storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51552</link><description>Weak password storage vulnerabilities exist in ASPECT if administrator credentials become compromisedThis issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7103 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in WSO2 Identity Server 7.0.0 Sub-Organization Login Flow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7103</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the sub-organization login flow of WSO2 Identity Server 7.0.0 due to improper input validation. A malicious actor can exploit this vulnerability to inject arbitrary JavaScript into the login flow, potentially leading to UI modifications, redirections to malicious websites, or data exfiltration from the browser.

While this issue could allow an attacker to manipulate the user’s browser, session-related sensitive cookies remain protected with the httpOnly flag, preventing session hijacking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13949 | Log Forging</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13949</link><description>Large content vulnerabilities are present in ASPECT exposing a device to disk overutilization on a system if administrator credentials become compromisedThis issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13950 | Log Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13950</link><description>Log injection vulnerabilities in ASPECT provide attacker access to inject malicious browser scripts if administrator credentials become compromised.This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13951 | One way hash with predictable salt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13951</link><description>One way hash with predictable salt vulnerabilities in ASPECT may expose sensitive information to a potential attackerThis issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13952 | Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13952</link><description>Predictable filename vulnerabilities in ASPECT may expose sensitive information to a potential attacker if administrator credentials become compromisedThis issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13953 | Sensitive Information disclosed in log files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13953</link><description>Sensitive device logger information in ASPECT may be exposed if administrator credentials become compromisedThis issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13954 | Serialization / Deserialization of configuration data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13954</link><description>Serialized configuration information may be disclosed during device commissioning while using ASPECT's configuration toolsetThis issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48848 | LARGECONTENT - device disk overutilization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48848</link><description>Large content vulnerabilities are present in ASPECT exposing a device to disk overutilization on a system if administrator credentials become compromisedThis issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51553 | Predictable Filename</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51553</link><description>Predictable filename vulnerabilities in ASPECT may expose sensitive information to a potential attacker if administrator credentials become compromisedThis issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6914 | Incorrect Authorization in Multiple WSO2 Products via Account Recovery SOAP Admin Service Leading to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6914</link><description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability exists in multiple WSO2 products due to a business logic flaw in the account recovery-related SOAP admin service. A malicious actor can exploit this vulnerability to reset the password of any user account, leading to a complete account takeover, including accounts with elevated privileges.

This vulnerability is exploitable only through the account recovery SOAP admin services exposed via the "/services" context path in affected products. The impact may be reduced if access to these endpoints has been restricted based on the "Security Guidelines for Production Deployment" by disabling exposure to untrusted networks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13946 | Binary Planting / LoadLibrary DLL&amp;#x27;s not Signed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13946</link><description>DLL's are not digitally signed when loaded in ASPECT's configuration toolset exposing the application to binary planting during device commissioning.This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13947 | External System or Configuration Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13947</link><description>Device commissioning parameters in ASPECT may be modified by an external source if administrative credentials become compromisedThis issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13948 | Insecure Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13948</link><description>Windows permissions for ASPECT configuration toolsets are not fully secured allow-ing exposure of configuration informationThis issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13929 | Authenticated Servlet Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13929</link><description>Servlet injection vulnerabilities in ASPECT allow remote code execution if session administrator credentials become compromised.
This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.08.03; NEXUS Series: through 3.08.03; MATRIX Series: through 3.08.03.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13930 | Authenticated Unchecked Loop Condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13930</link><description>An Unchecked Loop Condition in ASPECT provides an attacker the ability to maliciously consume system resources if session administrator credentials become compromised
This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.08.03; NEXUS Series: through 3.08.03; MATRIX Series: through 3.08.03.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13931 | Authenticated Relative Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13931</link><description>Relative Path Traversal vulnerabilities in ASPECT allow access to file resources if session administrator credentials become compromised.
This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.08.03; NEXUS Series: through 3.08.03; MATRIX Series: through 3.08.03.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13928 | Authenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13928</link><description>SQL injection vulnerabilities in ASPECT allow unintended access and manipulation of database repositories if session administrator credentials become compromised.
This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.08.03; NEXUS Series: through 3.08.03; MATRIX Series: through 3.08.03.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30169 | Admin Authorized File Upload and Execute PHP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30169</link><description>File upload and execute vulnerabilities in ASPECT allow PHP script injection if session administrator credentials become compromised.
This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.08.03; NEXUS Series: through 3.08.03; MATRIX Series: through 3.08.03.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30171 | Admin Authorized System File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30171</link><description>System File Deletion vulnerabilities in ASPECT provide attackers access to delete system files if session administrator credentials become compromised.
This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.08.03; NEXUS Series: through 3.08.03; MATRIX Series: through 3.08.03.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30172 | Admin Authorized Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30172</link><description>Remote Code Execution vulnerabilities are present in ASPECT if session administrator credentials become compromised
This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.08.03; NEXUS Series: through 3.08.03; MATRIX Series: through 3.08.03.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30173 | Admin Authorized File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30173</link><description>File upload vulnerabilities are present in ASPECT if session administrator credentials become compromised
This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.08.03; NEXUS Series: through 3.08.03; MATRIX Series: through 3.08.03.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2409 | Admin Authorized System File corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2409</link><description>File corruption vulnerabilities in ASPECT provide attackers access to overwrite sys-tem files if session administrator credentials become compromised
This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.08.03; NEXUS Series: through 3.08.03; MATRIX Series: through 3.08.03.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:45:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2410 | Admin Authorized Port (iptables) manipulation (open/close/disable ports)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2410</link><description>Port manipulation vulnerabilities in ASPECT provide attackers with the ability to con-trol TCP/IP port access if session administrator credentials become compromised.
This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.08.03; NEXUS Series: through 3.08.03; MATRIX Series: through 3.08.03.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30170 | Admin Authorized Exposure of file path, file size or file existence</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30170</link><description>Exposure of file path, file size or file existence vulnerabilities in ASPECT provide attackers access to file system information if session administrator credentials become compromised.
This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.08.03; NEXUS Series: through 3.08.03; MATRIX Series: through 3.08.03.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48369 | GroupOffice vulnerable to Stored XSS in Tasks Comment Section</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48369</link><description>Group-Office is an enterprise customer relationship management and groupware tool. Prior to versions 6.8.119 and 25.0.20, a persistent Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Groupoffice's tasks comment functionality, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript by uploading an file with a crafted filename. When administrators or other users view the task containing this malicious file, the payload executes in their browser context. The application fails to sanitize image filenames before rendering them in the comment. By uploading an image with a crafted filename containing XSS payloads, attackers can steal sensitive information. Versions 6.8.119 and 25.0.20 contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9639 | Authenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9639</link><description>Remote Code Execution vulnerabilities are present in ASPECT if session administra-tor credentials become compromised.
This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.08.03; NEXUS Series: through 3.08.03; MATRIX Series: through 3.08.03.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48066 | wire-webapp has no database deletion on client logout</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48066</link><description>wire-webapp is the web application for the open-source messaging service Wire. A bug fix caused a regression causing an issue with function to delete local data. Instructing the client to delete its local database on user logout does not result in deletion. This is the case for both temporary clients (marking the device as a public computer on login) and regular clients instructing the deletion of all personal information and conversations upon logout. Access to the machine is required to access the data. If encryption-at-rest is used, cryptographic material can't be exported. The underlying issue has been fixed with wire-webapp version 2025-05-14-production.0. In order to mitigate potential impact, the database must be manually deleted on devices where the option "This is a public computer" was used prior to log in or a log out with the request to delete local data with the affected versions has happened before.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48075 | Fiber panics when fiber.Ctx.BodyParser parses invalid range index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48075</link><description>Fiber is an Express-inspired web framework written in Go. Starting in version 2.52.6 and prior to version 2.52.7, `fiber.Ctx.BodyParser` can map flat data to nested slices using `key[idx]value` syntax, but when idx is negative, it causes a panic instead of returning an error stating it cannot process the data. Since this data is user-provided, this could lead to denial of service for anyone relying on this `fiber.Ctx.BodyParser`  functionality. Version 2.52.7 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48366 | GroupOffice&amp;#x27;s Blind Stored XSS in Phone Number Field Enables Forced Redirect and Unauthorized Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48366</link><description>Group-Office is an enterprise customer relationship management and groupware tool. Prior to versions 6.8.119 and 25.0.20, a stored and blind XSS vulnerability exists in the Phone Number field of the user profile within the GroupOffice application. This allows a malicious actor to inject persistent JavaScript payloads, which are triggered in the context of another user when they view the Address Book. Successful exploitation enables actions such as forced redirects, unauthorized fetch requests, or other arbitrary JavaScript execution without user interaction. Versions 6.8.119 and 25.0.20 contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48368 | GroupOffice&amp;#x27;s DOM-Based XSS in all Date Input Fields Allows Arbitrary JavaScript Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48368</link><description>Group-Office is an enterprise customer relationship management and groupware tool. Prior to versions 6.8.119 and 25.0.20, a  DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the GroupOffice application, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the context of the victim's browser. This can lead to session hijacking, defacement, or redirection to malicious sites. The vulnerability can be triggered by injecting a crafted payload into a parameter that is later processed unsafely in the DOM. Versions 6.8.119 and 25.0.20 contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52874 | In Infoblox NETMRI before 7.6.1, authenticated users can perform SQL injection attacks.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52874</link><description>In Infoblox NETMRI before 7.6.1, authenticated users can perform SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48061 | wire-webapp Has Insufficient Session Invalidation after User Logout</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48061</link><description>wire-webapp is the web application for the open-source messaging service Wire. A change caused a regression resulting in sessions not being properly invalidated. A user that logged out of the Wire webapp, could have been automatically logged in again after re-opening the application. This does not happen when the user is logged in as a temporary user by selecting "This is a public computer" during login or the user selects "Delete all your personal information and conversations on this device" upon logout. The underlying issue has been fixed with wire-webapp version 2025-05-20-production.0. As a workaround, this behavior can be prevented by either deleting all information upon logout as well as logging in as a temporary client.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47780 | cli_permissions.conf: deny option does not work for disallowing shell commands</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47780</link><description>Asterisk is an open-source private branch exchange (PBX). Prior to versions 18.26.2, 20.14.1, 21.9.1, and 22.4.1 of Asterisk and versions 18.9-cert14 and 20.7-cert5 of certified-asterisk, trying to disallow shell commands to be run via the Asterisk command line interface (CLI) by configuring `cli_permissions.conf` (e.g. with the config line `deny=!*`) does not work which could lead to a security risk. If an administrator running an Asterisk instance relies on the `cli_permissions.conf` file to work and expects it to deny all attempts to execute shell commands, then this could lead to a security vulnerability. Versions 18.26.2, 20.14.1, 21.9.1, and 22.4.1 of Asterisk and versions 18.9-cert14 and 20.7-cert5 of certified-asterisk fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43596 | MSP360 Backup (for Windows) insecure filesystem permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43596</link><description>An insecure file system permissions vulnerability in MSP360 Backup 8.0 allows a low privileged user to execute commands with SYSTEM level privileges using a specially crafted file with an arbitrary file backup target. Upgrade to MSP360 Backup 8.1.1.19 (released on 2025-05-15).</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45472 | Insecure permissions in autodeploy-layer v1.2.0 allows attackers to escalate privileges and compromise the customer cloud account.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45472</link><description>Insecure permissions in autodeploy-layer v1.2.0 allows attackers to escalate privileges and compromise the customer cloud account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46716 | Sandboxie Arbitrary Kernel Read in SbieDrv.sys API (API_SET_SECURE_PARAM)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46716</link><description>Sandboxie is a sandbox-based isolation software for 32-bit and 64-bit Windows NT-based operating systems. Starting in version 1.3.0 and prior to version 1.15.12, Api_SetSecureParam fails to sanitize incoming pointers, and implicitly trusts that the pointer the user has passed in is safe to read from. SetRegValue then reads an arbitrary address, which can be a kernel pointer, into a HKLM Security SBIE registry value. This can later be retrieved by API_GET_SECURE_PARAM. Version 1.15.12 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47779 | Using malformed From header can forge identity with &amp;quot;;&amp;quot; or NULL in name portion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47779</link><description>Asterisk is an open-source private branch exchange (PBX). Prior to versions 18.26.2, 20.14.1, 21.9.1, and 22.4.1 of Asterisk and versions 18.9-cert14 and 20.7-cert5 of certified-asterisk, SIP requests of the type MESSAGE (RFC 3428) authentication do not get proper alignment. An authenticated attacker can spoof any user identity to send spam messages to the user with their authorization token. Abuse of this security issue allows authenticated attackers to send fake chat messages can be spoofed to appear to come from trusted entities. Even administrators who follow Security best practices and Security Considerations can be impacted. Therefore, abuse can lead to spam and enable social engineering, phishing and similar attacks. Versions 18.26.2, 20.14.1, 21.9.1, and 22.4.1 of Asterisk and versions 18.9-cert14 and 20.7-cert5 of certified-asterisk fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48850 | Authenticated Absolute Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48850</link><description>Absolute File Traversal vulnerabilities in ASPECT allows access and modification of unintended resources.
This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.08.03; NEXUS Series: through 3.08.03; MATRIX Series: through 3.08.03.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48853 | Authenticated Escalation to guest to root</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48853</link><description>An escalation of privilege vulnerability in ASPECT could provide an attacker root access to a server when logged in as a "non" root ASPECT user. This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.08.03; NEXUS Series: through 3.08.03; MATRIX Series: through 3.08.03.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33138 | IBM Aspera Faspex HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33138</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.12 is vulnerable to HTML injection. A remote attacker could inject malicious HTML code, which when viewed, would be executed in the victim's Web browser within the security context of the hosting site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46715 | Sandboxie Arbitrary Kernel Write in SbieDrv.sys API (API_GET_SECURE_PARAM)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46715</link><description>Sandboxie is a sandbox-based isolation software for 32-bit and 64-bit Windows NT-based operating systems. Starting in version 1.3.0 and prior to version 1.15.12. Api_GetSecureParam fails to sanitize incoming pointers, and implicitly trusts that the pointer the user has passed in is safe to write to. GetRegValue then writes the contents of the SBIE registry entry selected to this address. An attacker can pass in a kernel pointer and the driver dumps the registry key contents we requested to it. This can be triggered by anyone on the system, including low integrity windows processes. Version 1.15.12 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33137 | IBM Aspera Faspex data modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33137</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.12 could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive information or perform unauthorized actions on behalf of another user due to client-side enforcement of server-side security.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33136 | IBM Aspera Faspex data modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33136</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.12 could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive information or perform unauthorized actions on behalf of another user due to improper protection of assumed immutable data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45468 | Insecure permissions in fc-stable-diffusion-plus v1.0.18 allows attackers to escalate privileges and compromise the customer cloud account.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45468</link><description>Insecure permissions in fc-stable-diffusion-plus v1.0.18 allows attackers to escalate privileges and compromise the customer cloud account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4366 | Request Smuggling Vulnerability in Pingora</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4366</link><description>A request smuggling vulnerability identified within Pingora’s proxying framework, pingora-proxy, allows malicious HTTP requests to be injected via manipulated request bodies on cache HITs, leading to unauthorized request execution and potential cache poisoning.

Fixed in:  https://github.com/cloudflare/pingora/commit/fda3317ec822678564d641e7cf1c9b77ee3759ff https://github.com/cloudflare/pingora/commit/fda3317ec822678564d641e7cf1c9b77ee3759ff 

Impact: The issue could lead to request smuggling in cases where Pingora’s proxying framework, pingora-proxy, is used for caching allowing an attacker to manipulate headers and URLs in subsequent requests made on the same HTTP/1.1 connection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23182 | UBtech – CWE-203: Observable Discrepancy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23182</link><description>CWE-203: Observable Discrepancy</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23183 | UBtech – CWE-601: URL Redirection to Untrusted Site (&amp;#x27;Open Redirect&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23183</link><description>CWE-601: URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect')</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5081 | Campcodes Cybercafe Management System adminprofile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5081</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Campcodes Cybercafe Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /adminprofile.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2506 | When pglogical attempts to replicate data, it does not verify it is using a replication connection, which means a user with CONNECT access t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2506</link><description>When pglogical attempts to replicate data, it does not verify it is using a replication connection, which means a user with CONNECT access to a database configured for replication can execute the pglogical command to obtain read access to replicated tables. When pglogical runs it should verify it is running on a replication connection but does not perform this check. This vulnerability was introduced in the pglogical 3.x codebase, which is proprietary to EDB. The same code base has been integrated into BDR/PGD 4 and 5.
To exploit the vulnerability the attacker needs at least CONNECT permissions to a database configured for replication and must understand a number of pglogical3/BDR specific commands and be able to decode the binary protocol.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45471 | Insecure permissions in measure-cold-start v1.4.1 allows attackers to escalate privileges and compromise the customer cloud account.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45471</link><description>Insecure permissions in measure-cold-start v1.4.1 allows attackers to escalate privileges and compromise the customer cloud account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5080 | Tenda FH451 webExcptypemanFilter stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5080</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda FH451 1.0.0.9. Affected is the function webExcptypemanFilter of the file /goform/webExcptypemanFilter. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5024 | Gnome-remote-desktop: uncontrolled resource consumption due to malformed rdp pdus</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5024</link><description>A flaw was found in gnome-remote-desktop. Once gnome-remote-desktop listens for RDP connections, an unauthenticated attacker can exhaust system resources and repeatedly crash the process. There may be a resource leak after many attacks, which will also result in gnome-remote-desktop no longer being able to open files even after it is restarted via systemd.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32814 | An issue was discovered in Infoblox NETMRI before 7.6.1. Unauthenticated SQL Injection can occur.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32814</link><description>An issue was discovered in Infoblox NETMRI before 7.6.1. Unauthenticated SQL Injection can occur.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54188 | Infoblox NETMRI before 7.6.1 has a vulnerability allowing remote authenticated users to read arbitrary files with root access.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54188</link><description>Infoblox NETMRI before 7.6.1 has a vulnerability allowing remote authenticated users to read arbitrary files with root access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32813 | An issue was discovered in Infoblox NETMRI before 7.6.1. Remote Unauthenticated Command Injection can occur.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32813</link><description>An issue was discovered in Infoblox NETMRI before 7.6.1. Remote Unauthenticated Command Injection can occur.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32815 | An issue was discovered in Infoblox NETMRI before 7.6.1. Authentication Bypass via a Hardcoded credential can occur.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32815</link><description>An issue was discovered in Infoblox NETMRI before 7.6.1. Authentication Bypass via a Hardcoded credential can occur.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12093 | Improper Validation of Consistency within Input in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12093</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 11.1 before 17.10.7, 17.11 before 17.11.3, and 18.0 before 18.0.1. Improper XPath validation allows modified SAML response to bypass 2FA requirement under specialized conditions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0605 | Weak Authentication in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0605</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.8 before 17.10.7, 17.11 before 17.11.3, and 18.0 before 18.0.1. Group access controls could allow certain users to bypass two-factor authentication requirements.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0679 | Exposure of Private Personal Information to an Unauthorized Actor in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0679</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 17.1 before 17.10.7, 17.11 before 17.11.3, and 18.0 before 18.0.1. Under certain conditions un-authorised users can view full email addresses that should be partially obscured.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0993 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0993</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 17.10.7, 17.11 before 17.11.3, and 18.0 before 18.0.1. This could allow an authenticated attacker to cause a denial of service condition by exhausting server resources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5079 | Campcodes Online Shopping Portal updateorder.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5079</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Shopping Portal 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/updateorder.php. The manipulation of the argument remark leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32915 | Sensitive data exposed during automatic agent updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32915</link><description>Packages downloaded by Checkmk's automatic agent updates on Linux and Solaris have incorrect permissions in Checkmk &lt; 2.4.0p1, &lt; 2.3.0p32, &lt; 2.2.0p42 and &lt;= 2.1.0p49 (EOL). This allows a local attacker to read sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47466 | TagLib before 2.0 allows a segmentation violation and application crash during tag writing via a crafted WAV file in which an id3 chunk is t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47466</link><description>TagLib before 2.0 allows a segmentation violation and application crash during tag writing via a crafted WAV file in which an id3 chunk is the only valid chunk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1110 | Insufficient Granularity of Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1110</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 18.0 before 18.0.1. In certain circumstances, a user with limited permissions could access Job Data via a crafted GraphQL query.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5077 | Campcodes Online Shopping Portal edit-subcategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5077</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Shopping Portal 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit-subcategory.php. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5078 | Campcodes Online Shopping Portal subcategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5078</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Shopping Portal 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/subcategory.php. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2853 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2853</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 17.10.7, 17.11 before 17.11.3, and 18.0 before 18.0.1. A lack of proper validation in GitLab could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3111 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3111</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 10.2 before 17.10.7, 17.11 before 17.11.3, and 18.0 before 18.0.1. A lack of input validation in the Kubernetes integration could allow an authenticated user to cause denial of service..</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4575 | The x509 application adds trusted use instead of rejected use</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4575</link><description>Issue summary: Use of -addreject option with the openssl x509 application adds
a trusted use instead of a rejected use for a certificate.

Impact summary: If a user intends to make a trusted certificate rejected for
a particular use it will be instead marked as trusted for that use.

A copy &amp; paste error during minor refactoring of the code introduced this
issue in the OpenSSL 3.5 version. If, for example, a trusted CA certificate
should be trusted only for the purpose of authenticating TLS servers but not
for CMS signature verification and the CMS signature verification is intended
to be marked as rejected with the -addreject option, the resulting CA
certificate will be trusted for CMS signature verification purpose instead.

Only users which use the trusted certificate format who use the openssl x509
command line application to add rejected uses are affected by this issue.
The issues affecting only the command line application are considered to
be Low severity.

The FIPS modules in 3.5, 3.4, 3.3, 3.2, 3.1 and 3.0 are not affected by this
issue.

OpenSSL 3.4, 3.3, 3.2, 3.1, 3.0, 1.1.1 and 1.0.2 are also not affected by this
issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4979 | Insufficient Granularity of Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4979</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 17.10.7, 17.11 before 17.11.3, and 18.0 before 18.0.1. An attacker may be able to reveal masked or hidden CI variables (that they did not author) in the WebUI, by simply creating their own variable and observing the HTTP response.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5076 | FreeFloat FTP Server SEND Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5076</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component SEND Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3938 | Missing Cryptographic Step</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3938</link><description>Missing Cryptographic Step vulnerability in Tridium Niagara Framework on Windows, Linux, QNX, Tridium Niagara Enterprise Security on Windows, Linux, QNX allows Cryptanalysis. This issue affects Niagara Framework: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11; Niagara Enterprise Security: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11. Tridium recommends upgrading to Niagara Framework and Enterprise Security versions 4.14.2u2, 4.15.u1, or 4.10u.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3939 | Observable Response Discrepancy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3939</link><description>Observable Response Discrepancy vulnerability in Tridium Niagara Framework on Windows, Linux, QNX, Tridium Niagara Enterprise Security on Windows, Linux, QNX allows Cryptanalysis. This issue affects Niagara Framework: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11; Niagara Enterprise Security: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11.Tridium recommends upgrading to Niagara Framework and Enterprise Security versions 4.14.2u2, 4.15.u1, or 4.10u.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3940 | Improper Use of Validation Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3940</link><description>Improper Use of Validation Framework vulnerability in Tridium Niagara Framework on Windows, Linux, QNX, Tridium Niagara Enterprise Security on Windows, Linux, QNX allows Input Data Manipulation. This issue affects Niagara Framework: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11; Niagara Enterprise Security: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11. Tridium recommends upgrading to Niagara Framework and Enterprise Security versions 4.14.2u2, 4.15.u1, or 4.10u.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3941 | Improper Handling of Windows: DATA Alternate Data Stream</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3941</link><description>Improper Handling of Windows ::DATA Alternate Data Stream vulnerability in Tridium Niagara Framework on Windows, Tridium Niagara Enterprise Security on Windows allows Input Data Manipulation. This issue affects Niagara Framework: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11; Niagara Enterprise Security: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11.Tridium recommends upgrading to Niagara Framework and Enterprise Security versions 4.14.2u2, 4.15.u1, or 4.10u.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3942 | Improper Output Neutralization for Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3942</link><description>Improper Output Neutralization for Logs vulnerability in Tridium Niagara Framework on Windows, Linux, QNX, Tridium Niagara Enterprise Security on Windows, Linux, QNX allows Input Data Manipulation. This issue affects Niagara Framework: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11; Niagara Enterprise Security: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11. Tridium recommends upgrading to Niagara Framework and Enterprise Security versions 4.14.2u2, 4.15.u1, or 4.10u.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3943 | Use of GET Request Method With sensitive Query Strings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3943</link><description>Use of GET Request Method With Sensitive Query Strings vulnerability in Tridium Niagara Framework on Windows, Linux, QNX, Tridium Niagara Enterprise Security on Windows, Linux, QNX allows Parameter Injection. This issue affects Niagara Framework: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11; Niagara Enterprise Security: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11. Tridium recommends upgrading to Niagara Framework and Enterprise Security versions 4.14.2u2, 4.15.u1, or 4.10u.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3944 | Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3944</link><description>Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in Tridium Niagara Framework on QNX, Tridium Niagara Enterprise Security on QNX allows File Manipulation. This issue affects Niagara Framework: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11; Niagara Enterprise Security: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11. Tridium recommends upgrading to Niagara Framework and Enterprise Security versions 4.14.2u2, 4.15.u1, or 4.10u.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3945 | Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command (‘Argument Injection’)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3945</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection') vulnerability in Tridium Niagara Framework on QNX, Tridium Niagara Enterprise Security on QNX allows Command Delimiters. This issue affects Niagara Framework: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11; Niagara Enterprise Security: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11. Tridium recommends upgrading to Niagara Framework and Enterprise Security versions 4.14.2u2, 4.15.u1, or 4.10u.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5075 | FreeFloat FTP Server DEBUG Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5075</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component DEBUG Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2272 | Privilege Escalation and Arbitrary code execution in F1E Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2272</link><description>Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability in Forcepoint FIE Endpoint allows Privilege Escalation, Code Injection, Hijacking a privileged process.This issue affects FIE Endpoint: before 25.05.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3936 | Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3936</link><description>Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in Tridium Niagara Framework on Windows, Tridium Niagara Enterprise Security on Windows allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Niagara Framework: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11; Niagara Enterprise Security: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11. Tridium recommends upgrading to Niagara Framework and Enterprise Security versions 4.14.2u2, 4.15.u1, or 4.10u.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3937 | Use of Password Hash with Insufficient Computational Effort</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3937</link><description>Use of Password Hash With Insufficient Computational Effort vulnerability in Tridium Niagara Framework on Windows, Linux, QNX, Tridium Niagara Enterprise Security on Windows, Linux, QNX allows Cryptanalysis. This issue affects Niagara Framework: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11; Niagara Enterprise Security: before 4.14.2, before 4.15.1, before 4.10.11. Tridium recommends upgrading to Niagara Framework and Enterprise Security versions 4.14.2u2, 4.15.u1, or 4.10u.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46713 | Sandboxie has Pool Buffer Overflow in SbieDrv.sys API (API_SET_SECURE_PARAM)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46713</link><description>Sandboxie is a sandbox-based isolation software for 32-bit and 64-bit Windows NT-based operating systems. Starting in version 0.0.1 and prior to 1.15.12, API_SET_SECURE_PARAM may have an arithmetic overflow deep in the memory allocation subsystem that would lead to a smaller allocation than requested, and a buffer overflow. Version 1.15.12 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46714 | Sandboxie has Pool Buffer Overflow in SbieDrv.sys API (API_GET_SECURE_PARAM)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46714</link><description>Sandboxie is a sandbox-based isolation software for 32-bit and 64-bit Windows NT-based operating systems. Starting in version 1.3.0 and prior to 1.15.12, API_GET_SECURE_PARAM has an arithmetic overflow leading to a small memory allocation and then a extremely large copy into the small allocation. Version 1.15.12 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5074 | FreeFloat FTP Server PROMPT Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5074</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component PROMPT Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5073 | FreeFloat FTP Server MKDIR Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5073</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component MKDIR Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:12:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3836 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3836</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions 8510 and prior are vulnerable to authenticated SQL injection in the logon events aggregate report.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41403 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41403</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions 8510 and prior are vulnerable to authenticated SQL injection while fetching service account audit data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3444 | Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3444</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ServiceDesk Plus MSP and SupportCenter Plus versions below 14920 are vulnerable to authenticated Local File Inclusion (LFI) in the Admin module, where help card content is loaded.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25010 | Ericsson RAN Compute and Site Controller 6610 - Improper Input Validation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25010</link><description>Ericsson RAN Compute
and Site Controller 6610 contains in certain configurations a high severity
vulnerability where improper input validation could be exploited leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4280 | TCC Bypass via Inherited Permissions in Bundled Interpreter in Poedit.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4280</link><description>MacOS version of Poedit bundles a Python interpreter that inherits the Transparency, Consent, and Control (TCC) permissions
granted by the user to the main application bundle. An attacker with local user access can
invoke this interpreter with arbitrary commands or scripts, leveraging the
application's previously granted TCC permissions to access user's files in privacy-protected folders without triggering user prompts. Accessing other resources beyond previously granted TCC permissions will prompt the user for approval in the name of Poedit, potentially disguising attacker's malicious intent.

This issue has been fixed in 3.6.3 version of Poedit.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9544 | MapSVG - All Kinds of Maps and Store Locator for WordPress &amp;lt;= 8.6.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9544</link><description>The MapSVG plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 8.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 09:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4405 | Hot Random Image &amp;lt;= 1.9.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via link Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4405</link><description>The Hot Random Image plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘link’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 09:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4419 | Hot Random Image &amp;lt;= 1.9.2 - Path Traversal to Authenticated (Contributor+) Limited Arbitrary Image Access via path Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4419</link><description>The Hot Random Image plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.2 via the 'path' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to access arbitrary images with allowed extensions, outside of the originally intended directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 09:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4123 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Grafana caused by combining a client path traversal and open redirect. This allows atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4123</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Grafana caused by combining a client path traversal and open redirect. This allows attackers to redirect users to a website that hosts a frontend plugin that will execute arbitrary JavaScript. This vulnerability does not require editor permissions and if anonymous access is enabled, the XSS will work. If the Grafana Image Renderer plugin is installed, it is possible to exploit the open redirect to achieve a full read SSRF.

The default Content-Security-Policy (CSP) in Grafana will block the XSS though the `connect-src` directive.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4133 | Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp;amp; Scheduler &amp;lt; 8.4.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4133</link><description>The Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp; Scheduler WordPress plugin before 8.4.0 does not escape the title of posts when outputting them in a dashboard, which could allow users with the contributor role to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 06:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5062 | WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 9.4.2 - PostMessage-Based Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5062</link><description>The WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PostMessage-Based Cross-Site Scripting via the 'customize-store' page in all versions up to, and including, 9.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on PostMessage data. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 03:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2759 | GStreamer Incorrect Permission Assignment Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2759</link><description>GStreamer Incorrect Permission Assignment Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of GStreamer. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the product installer. The issue results from incorrect permissions on folders. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of a target user. Was ZDI-CAN-25448.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 01:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3480 | MedDream WEB DICOM Viewer Cleartext Transmission of Credentials Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3480</link><description>MedDream WEB DICOM Viewer Cleartext Transmission of Credentials Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of MedDream WEB DICOM Viewer. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Web Portal. The issue results from the lack of encryption when transmitting credentials. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose transmitted credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-25842.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 01:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3481 | MedDream PACS Server DICOM File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3481</link><description>MedDream PACS Server DICOM File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of MedDream PACS Server. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DICOM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-25827.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 01:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3482 | MedDream PACS Server DICOM File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3482</link><description>MedDream PACS Server DICOM File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of MedDream PACS Server. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DICOM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-25826.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 01:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3483 | MedDream PACS Server DICOM File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3483</link><description>MedDream PACS Server DICOM File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of MedDream PACS Server. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DICOM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-25825.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 01:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3484 | MedDream PACS Server DICOM File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3484</link><description>MedDream PACS Server DICOM File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of MedDream PACS Server. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DICOM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-25853.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 01:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3486 | Allegra isZipEntryValide Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3486</link><description>Allegra isZipEntryValide Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Allegra. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the isZipEntryValide method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of LOCAL SERVICE. Was ZDI-CAN-25730.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 01:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3881 | eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 check_req.php ntp Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3881</link><description>eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 check_req.php ntp Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 charging stations. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of the ntp parameter provided to the check_req.php endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the www-data user. Was ZDI-CAN-23113.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 01:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3882 | eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 nwcheckexec.php dest Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3882</link><description>eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 nwcheckexec.php dest Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 charging stations. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of the dest parameter provided to the nwcheckexec.php endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the www-data user. Was ZDI-CAN-23114.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 01:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3883 | eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 index.php Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3883</link><description>eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 index.php Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 charging stations. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of GET parameters provided to the index.php endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the www-data user. Was ZDI-CAN-23115.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 01:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3884 | Cloudera Hue Ace Editor Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3884</link><description>Cloudera Hue Ace Editor Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Cloudera Hue. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Ace Editor web application. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-24332.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 01:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3885 | Harman Becker MGU21 Bluetooth Improper Input Validation Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3885</link><description>Harman Becker MGU21 Bluetooth Improper Input Validation Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Harman Becker MGU21 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Bluetooth stack of the BCM89359 chipset. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of Bluetooth frames. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-23942.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 01:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3887 | GStreamer H265 Codec Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3887</link><description>GStreamer H265 Codec Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of GStreamer. Interaction with this library is required to exploit this vulnerability but attack vectors may vary depending on the implementation.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of H265 slice headers. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26596.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 01:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5059 | Campcodes Online Shopping Portal edit-subcategory.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5059</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Online Shopping Portal 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit-subcategory.php. The manipulation of the argument productimage1/productimage2/productimage3 leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 22:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34025 | Versa Concerto Actuator Insecure Docker Mount Container Escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34025</link><description>The Versa Concerto SD-WAN orchestration platform is vulnerable to an privileges escalation and container escape vulnerability caused by unsafe default mounting of host binary paths that allow the container to modify host paths. The escape can be used to trigger remote code execution or direct host access depending on the host operating system configuration.This issue is known to affect Concerto from 12.1.2 through 12.2.0. Additional versions may be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 22:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34026 | Versa Concerto Actuator Authentication Bypass Information Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34026</link><description>The Versa Concerto SD-WAN orchestration platform is vulnerable to an authentication bypass in the Traefik reverse proxy configuration, allowing at attacker to access administrative endpoints. The internal Actuator endpoint can be leveraged for access to heap dumps and trace logs.This issue is known to affect Concerto from 12.1.2 through 12.2.0. Additional versions may be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 22:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47947 | ModSecurity Has Possible DoS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47947</link><description>ModSecurity is an open source, cross platform web application firewall (WAF) engine for Apache, IIS and Nginx. Versions up to and including 2.9.8 are vulnerable to denial of service in one special case (in stable released versions): when the payload's content type is `application/json`, and there is at least one rule which does a `sanitiseMatchedBytes` action. A patch is available at pull request 3389 and expected to be part of version 2.9.9. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 22:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48070 | Plane has insecure permissions in UserSerializer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48070</link><description>Plane is open-source project management software. Versions prior to 0.23 have insecure permissions in UserSerializer that allows users to change fields that are meant to be read-only, such as email. This can lead to account takeover when chained with another vulnerability such as cross-site scripting (XSS). Version 0.23 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 22:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34027 | Versa Concerto Authentication Bypass File Write Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34027</link><description>The Versa Concerto SD-WAN orchestration platform is vulnerable to an authentication bypass in the Traefik reverse proxy configuration, allowing at attacker to access administrative endpoints. The Spack upload endpoint can be leveraged for a Time-of-Check to Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) write in combination with a race condition to achieve remote code execution via path loading manipulation, allowing an unauthenticated actor to achieve remote code execution (RCE).This issue is known to affect Concerto from 12.1.2 through 12.2.0. Additional versions may be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 22:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5056 | Campcodes Online Shopping Portal edit-products.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5056</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Shopping Portal 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-products.php. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 22:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5057 | Campcodes Online Shopping Portal insert-product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5057</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Shopping Portal 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/insert-product.php. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 22:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47942 | Learners on edX Platform can download python_lib.zip</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47942</link><description>The Open edX Platform is a learning management platform. Prior to commit 6740e75c0fdc7ba095baf88e9f5e4f3e15cfd8ba, edxapp has no built-in protection against downloading the python_lib.zip asset from courses, which is a concern since it often contains custom grading code or answers to course problems. This potentially affects any course using custom Python-graded problem blocks. The openedx/configuration repo has had a patch since 2016 in the form of an nginx rule, but this was only intended as a temporary mitigation. As the configuration repo has been deprecated and we have not been able to locate any similar protection in Tutor, it is likely that most deployments have no protection against python_lib.zip being downloaded. The recommended mitigation, implemented in commit 6740e75c0fdc7ba095baf88e9f5e4f3e15cfd8ba, restricts python_lib.zip downloads to just the course team and site staff/superusers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 21:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5052 | FreeFloat FTP Server LS Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5052</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component LS Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 21:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5053 | FreeFloat FTP Server MDIR Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5053</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component MDIR Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 21:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44040 | An issue in OrangeHRM v.5.7 allows an attacker to escalate privileges via the UserService.php and the checkFOrOldHash function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44040</link><description>An issue in OrangeHRM v.5.7 allows an attacker to escalate privileges via the UserService.php and the checkFOrOldHash function</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 20:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45753 | A vulnerability in Vtiger CRM Open Source Edition v8.3.0 allows an attacker with admin privileges to execute arbitrary PHP code by exploitin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45753</link><description>A vulnerability in Vtiger CRM Open Source Edition v8.3.0 allows an attacker with admin privileges to execute arbitrary PHP code by exploiting the ZIP import functionality in the Module Import feature.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 20:49:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5051 | FreeFloat FTP Server BINARY Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5051</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component BINARY Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 20:25:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36535 | AutomationDirect MB-Gateway Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36535</link><description>The embedded web server lacks authentication and access controls, allowing unrestricted remote access. This could lead to configuration changes, operational disruption, or arbitrary code execution depending on the environment and exposed functionality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 20:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45755 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Vtiger CRM Open Source Edition v8.3.0, exploitable via the Services Import featu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45755</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Vtiger CRM Open Source Edition v8.3.0, exploitable via the Services Import feature. An attacker can craft a malicious CSV file containing an XSS payload, mapped to the Service Name field. When the file is uploaded, the application improperly sanitizes user input, leading to persistent script execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 19:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41426 | Vertiv Liebert RDU101 and UNITY Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41426</link><description>Affected Vertiv products contain a stack based buffer overflow vulnerability. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to gain code execution on the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 19:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46412 | Vertiv Liebert RDU101 and UNITY Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46412</link><description>Affected Vertiv products do not properly protect webserver functions that could allow an attacker to bypass authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 19:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44083 | An issue in D-Link DI-8100 16.07.26A1 allows a remote attacker to bypass administrator login authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44083</link><description>An issue in D-Link DI-8100 16.07.26A1 allows a remote attacker to bypass administrator login authentication</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 19:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27558 | IEEE P802.11-REVme D1.1 through D7.0 allows FragAttacks against mesh networks. In mesh networks using Wi-Fi Protected Access (WPA, WPA2, or ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27558</link><description>IEEE P802.11-REVme D1.1 through D7.0 allows FragAttacks against mesh networks. In mesh networks using Wi-Fi Protected Access (WPA, WPA2, or WPA3) or Wired Equivalent Privacy (WEP), an adversary can exploit this vulnerability to inject arbitrary frames towards devices that support receiving non-SSP A-MSDU frames. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incorrect fix for CVE-2020-24588. P802.11-REVme, as of early 2025, is a planned release of the 802.11 standard.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57529 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Jeppesen JetPlanner Pro v.1.6.2.20 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57529</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Jeppesen JetPlanner Pro v.1.6.2.20 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2261 | TIBCO BPM Enterprise XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2261</link><description>Stored XSS in TIBCO ActiveMatrix Administrator allows malicious data to appear to be part of the website and run within user's browser under the privileges of the web application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45752 | A vulnerability in SeedDMS 6.0.32 allows an attacker with admin privileges to execute arbitrary PHP code by exploiting the zip import functi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45752</link><description>A vulnerability in SeedDMS 6.0.32 allows an attacker with admin privileges to execute arbitrary PHP code by exploiting the zip import functionality in the Extension Manager.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5049 | FreeFloat FTP Server APPEND Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5049</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component APPEND Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5050 | FreeFloat FTP Server BELL Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5050</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component BELL Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3751 | TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3751</link><description>The component listed above contains a vulnerability that can be exploited by an attacker to perform a SQL Injection attack. This could lead to unauthorised access to the database and exposure of sensitive information</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48069 | ejson2env has insufficient input sanitization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48069</link><description>ejson2env allows users to decrypt EJSON secrets and export them as environment variables. Prior to version 2.0.8, the `ejson2env` tool has a vulnerability related to how it writes to `stdout`. Specifically, the tool is intended to write an export statement for environment variables and their values. However, due to inadequate output sanitization, there is a potential risk where variable names or values may include malicious content, resulting in additional unintended commands being output to `stdout`. If this output is improperly utilized in further command execution, it could lead to command injection, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the host system. Version 2.0.8 sanitizes output during decryption. Other mitigations involve avoiding use of `ejson2env` to decrypt untrusted user secrets and/or avoiding evaluating or executing the direct output from `ejson2env` without removing nonprintable characters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48063 | XWiki Platform Security Authorization Bridge allows users with just edit right can enforce required rights with programming right</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48063</link><description>XWiki is a generic wiki platform. In XWiki 16.10.0, required rights were introduced as a way to limit which rights a document can have. Part of the security model of required rights is that a user who doesn't have a right also cannot define that right as required right. That way, users who are editing documents on which required rights are enforced can be sure that they're not giving a right to a script or object that it didn't have before. A bug in the implementation of the enforcement of this rule means that in fact, it was possible for any user with edit right on a document to set programming right as required right. If then a user with programming right edited that document, the content of that document would gain programming right, allowing remote code execution. This thereby defeats most of the security benefits of required rights. As XWiki still performs the required rights analysis when a user edits a page even when required rights are enforced, the user with programming right would still be warned about the dangerous content unless the attacker managed to bypass this check. Note also that none of the affected versions include a UI for enabling the enforcing of required rights so it seems unlikely that anybody relied on them for security in the affected versions. As this vulnerability provides no additional attack surface unless all documents in the wiki enforce required rights, we consider the impact of this attack to be low even though gaining programming right could have a high impact. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 16.10.4 and 17.1.0RC1. No known workarounds are available except for upgrading.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48064 | GitHub Desktop vulnerable to maliciously crafted file renames leading to information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48064</link><description>GitHub Desktop is an open-source, Electron-based GitHub app designed for git development. Prior to version 3.4.20-beta3, an attacker convincing a user to view a file in a commit of their making in the history view can cause information disclosure by means of Git attempting to access a network share. This affects GitHub Desktop users on Windows that view malicious commits in the history view. macOS users are not affected. When viewing a file diff in the history view GitHub Desktop will call `git log` or `git diff` with the object id (SHA) of the commit, the name of the file, and the old name of the file if the file has been renamed. As a security precaution Git will attempt to fully resolve the old and new path via `realpath`, traversing symlinks, to ensure that the resolved paths reside within the repository working directory. This can lead to Git attempting to access a path that resides on a network share (UNC path) and in doing so Windows will attempt to perform NTLM authentication which passes information such as the computer name, the currently signed in (Windows) user name, and an NTLM hash. GitHub Desktop 3.4.20 and later fix this vulnerability. The beta channel includes the fix in 3.4.20-beta3. As a workaround to use until upgrading is possible, only browse commits in the history view that comes from trusted sources.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46822 | Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read via Absolute Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46822</link><description>OsamaTaher/Java-springboot-codebase is a collection of Java and Spring Boot code snippets, applications, and projects. Prior to commit c835c6f7799eacada4c0fc77e0816f250af01ad2, insufficient path traversal mechanisms make absolute path traversal possible. This vulnerability allows unauthorized access to sensitive internal files. Commit c835c6f7799eacada4c0fc77e0816f250af01ad2 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47291 | containerd CRI plugin: Incorrect cgroup hierarchy assignment for containers running in usernamespaced Kubernetes pods.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47291</link><description>containerd is an open-source container runtime. A bug was found in the containerd's CRI implementation where containerd, starting in version 2.0.1 and prior to version 2.0.5, doesn't put usernamespaced containers under the Kubernetes' cgroup hierarchy, therefore some Kubernetes limits are not honored. This may cause a denial of service of the Kubernetes node. This bug has been fixed in containerd 2.0.5+ and 2.1.0+. Users should update to these versions to resolve the issue. As a workaround, disable usernamespaced pods in Kubernetes temporarily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48060 | AddressSanitizer: stack-buffer-overflow in jq_fuzz_execute (jv_string_vfmt)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48060</link><description>jq is a command-line JSON processor. In versions up to and including 1.7.1, a heap-buffer-overflow is present in function `jv_string_vfmt` in the jq_fuzz_execute harness from oss-fuzz. This crash happens on file jv.c, line 1456 `void* p = malloc(sz);`. As of time of publication, no patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5033 | XiaoBingby TeaCMS addUser cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5033</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in XiaoBingby TeaCMS 2.0.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file src/main/java/me/teacms/controller/admin/UserManageController/addUser. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2102 | Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following') vulnerability in HYPR Passwordless on Windows allows Privilege Escalation.Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2102</link><description>Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following') vulnerability in HYPR Passwordless on Windows allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects HYPR Passwordless: before 10.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5020 | Opening maliciously-crafted URLs in Firefox from other apps such as Safari could have allowed attackers to spoof website addresses if the UR...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5020</link><description>Opening maliciously-crafted URLs in Firefox from other apps such as Safari could have allowed attackers to spoof website addresses if the URLs utilized non-HTTP schemes used internally by the Firefox iOS client This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 139.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0372 | Concurrent Execution using Shared Resource with Improper Synchronization ('Race Condition') vulnerability in HYPR Passwordless on Windows al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0372</link><description>Concurrent Execution using Shared Resource with Improper Synchronization ('Race Condition') vulnerability in HYPR Passwordless on Windows allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects HYPR Passwordless: before 10.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45754 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in SeedDMS 6.0.32. This vulnerability allows an attacker to inject malicious JavaSc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45754</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in SeedDMS 6.0.32. This vulnerability allows an attacker to inject malicious JavaScript payloads by creating a document with an XSS payload as the document name.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56428 | The local iLabClient database in itech iLabClient 3.7.1 allows local attackers to read cleartext credentials (from the CONFIGS table) for th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56428</link><description>The local iLabClient database in itech iLabClient 3.7.1 allows local attackers to read cleartext credentials (from the CONFIGS table) for their servers configured in the client.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25539 | Local File Inclusion vulnerability in Vasco v3.14and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via help menu.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25539</link><description>Local File Inclusion vulnerability in Vasco v3.14and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via help menu.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5031 | Ackites KillWxapkg wxapkg File Decompression resource consumption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5031</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Ackites KillWxapkg up to 2.4.1. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component wxapkg File Decompression Handler. The manipulation leads to resource consumption. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5032 | Campcodes Online Shopping Portal edit-category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5032</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Online Shopping Portal 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit-category.php. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20246 | A vulnerability in Cisco Webex could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack.&#13;
&#13; A vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20246</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack.
&#13; A vulnerability is due to improper filtering of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting attack against the targeted user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:56:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20247 | A vulnerability in Cisco Webex could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack.&#13;
&#13; A vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20247</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack.
&#13; A vulnerability is due to improper filtering of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting attack against the targeted user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:56:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20250 | A vulnerability in Cisco Webex could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack.&#13;
&#13; A vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20250</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack.
&#13; A vulnerability is due to improper filtering of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting attack against the targeted user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:56:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20255 | A vulnerability in client join services of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to manipulate cached HTTP re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20255</link><description>A vulnerability in client join services of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to manipulate cached HTTP responses within the meeting join service.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of malicious HTTP requests to the affected service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating stored HTTP responses within the service, also known as HTTP cache poisoning. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Webex Meetings service to return incorrect HTTP responses to clients.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20258 | A vulnerability in the self-service portal of Cisco Duo could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary commands into em...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20258</link><description>A vulnerability in the self-service portal of Cisco Duo could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary commands into emails that are sent by the service.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting arbitrary commands into a portion of an email that is sent by the service. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send emails that contain malicious content to unsuspecting users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20242 | A vulnerability in the Cloud Connect component of Cisco Unified Contact Center Enterprise (CCE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20242</link><description>A vulnerability in the Cloud Connect component of Cisco Unified Contact Center Enterprise (CCE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to read and modify data on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper authentication controls. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted TCP data to a specific port on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read or modify data on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5030 | Ackites KillWxapkg wxapkg File Parser unpack.go processFile os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5030</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Ackites KillWxapkg up to 2.4.1. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function processFile of the file internal/unpack/unpack.go of the component wxapkg File Parser. The manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20112 | Cisco Unified Communications Products Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20112</link><description>A vulnerability in multiple Cisco Unified Communications and Contact Center Solutions products could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to excessive permissions that have been assigned to system commands.&amp;nbsp;An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by executing crafted commands on the underlying operating system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to escape the restricted shell and gain root privileges on the underlying operating system of an affected device. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need administrative access to the ESXi hypervisor.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20113 | Cisco Unified Intelligence Center Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20113</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Unified Intelligence Center could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to Administrator for a limited set of functions on an affected system.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient server-side validation of user-supplied parameters in API or HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted API or HTTP request to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access, modify, or delete data beyond the sphere of their intended access level, including obtaining potentially sensitive information stored in the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20114 | Cisco Unified Intelligence Center Insecure Direct Object Reference Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20114</link><description>A vulnerability in the API of Cisco Unified Intelligence Center could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a horizontal privilege escalation attack on an affected system.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied parameters in API requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting crafted API requests to an affected system to execute an insecure direct object reference attack. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access specific data that is associated with different users on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20152 | ISE restart</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20152</link><description>A vulnerability in the RADIUS message processing feature of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain RADIUS requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specific authentication request to a network access device (NAD) that uses Cisco ISE for authentication, authorization, and accounting (AAA). A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause Cisco ISE to reload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20256 | Cisco Secure Network Analytics Manager Server-Side Template Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20256</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Network Analytics Manager and Cisco Secure Network Analytics Virtual Manager could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with valid administrative credentials to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation in specific fields of the web-based management interface. An attacker with valid administrative credentials could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root privileges.&amp;nbsp;</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20257 | Cisco Secure Network Analytics API Authorization Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20257</link><description>A vulnerability in an API subsystem of Cisco Secure Network Analytics Manager and Cisco Secure Network Analytics Virtual Manager could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with low privileges to generate fraudulent findings that are used to generate alarms and alerts on an affected product.

Thi vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization enforcement on a specific API. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating as a low-privileged user and performing API calls with crafted input. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obfuscate legitimate findings in analytics reports or create false indications with alarms and alerts on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20267 | Cisco Identity Services Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20267</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48009 | Single Content Sync - Moderately critical - Access bypass - SA-CONTRIB-2025-060</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48009</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Drupal Single Content Sync allows Functionality Misuse.This issue affects Single Content Sync: from 0.0.0 before 1.4.12.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48010 | One Time Password - Moderately critical - Access bypass - SA-CONTRIB-2025-061</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48010</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Drupal One Time Password allows Functionality Bypass.This issue affects One Time Password: from 0.0.0 before 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48011 | One Time Password - Moderately critical - Access bypass - SA-CONTRIB-2025-062</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48011</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Drupal One Time Password allows Functionality Bypass.This issue affects One Time Password: from 0.0.0 before 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48012 | One Time Password - Moderately critical - Access bypass - SA-CONTRIB-2025-063</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48012</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Capture-replay vulnerability in Drupal One Time Password allows Remote Services with Stolen Credentials.This issue affects One Time Password: from 0.0.0 before 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4415 | Piwik PRO - Moderately critical - Cross Site Scripting - SA-CONTRIB-2025-058</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4415</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Drupal Piwik PRO allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Piwik PRO: from 0.0.0 before 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4416 | Events Log Track - Moderately critical - Denial of Service - SA-CONTRIB-2025-059</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4416</link><description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in Drupal Events Log Track allows Excessive Allocation.This issue affects Events Log Track: from 0.0.0 before 3.1.11, from 4.0.0 before 4.0.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27997 | An issue in Blizzard Battle.net v2.40.0.15267 allows attackers to escalate privileges via placing a crafted shell script or executable into ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27997</link><description>An issue in Blizzard Battle.net v2.40.0.15267 allows attackers to escalate privileges via placing a crafted shell script or executable into the C:\ProgramData directory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:19:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27998 | An issue in Valvesoftware Steam Client Steam Client 1738026274 allows attackers to escalate privileges via a crafted executable or DLL.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27998</link><description>An issue in Valvesoftware Steam Client Steam Client 1738026274 allows attackers to escalate privileges via a crafted executable or DLL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48207 | The reint_downloadmanager extension through 5.0.0 for TYPO3 allows Insecure Direct Object Reference.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48207</link><description>The reint_downloadmanager extension through 5.0.0 for TYPO3 allows Insecure Direct Object Reference.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48203 | The cs_seo extension through 9.2.0 for TYPO3 allows XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48203</link><description>The cs_seo extension through 9.2.0 for TYPO3 allows XSS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48202 | The femanager extension through 8.2.1 for TYPO3 allows Insecure Direct Object Reference.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48202</link><description>The femanager extension through 8.2.1 for TYPO3 allows Insecure Direct Object Reference.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:50:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48204 | The ns_backup extension through 13.0.0 for TYPO3 allows command injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48204</link><description>The ns_backup extension through 13.0.0 for TYPO3 allows command injection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:50:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48206 | The ns_backup extension through 13.0.0 for TYPO3 allows XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48206</link><description>The ns_backup extension through 13.0.0 for TYPO3 allows XSS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48201 | The ns_backup extension through 13.0.0 for TYPO3 has a Predictable Resource Location.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48201</link><description>The ns_backup extension through 13.0.0 for TYPO3 has a Predictable Resource Location.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48205 | The sr_feuser_register extension through 12.4.8 for TYPO3 allows Insecure Direct Object Reference.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48205</link><description>The sr_feuser_register extension through 12.4.8 for TYPO3 allows Insecure Direct Object Reference.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4008 | Arbitrary Command Injection in Smartbedded MeteoBridge</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4008</link><description>The Meteobridge web interface let meteobridge administrator manage their weather station data collection and administer their meteobridge system through a web application written in CGI shell scripts and C.

This web interface exposes an endpoint that is vulnerable to command injection.

Remote unauthenticated attackers can gain arbitrary command execution with elevated privileges ( root ) on affected devices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48200 | The sr_feuser_register extension through 12.4.8 for TYPO3 allows Remote Code Execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48200</link><description>The sr_feuser_register extension through 12.4.8 for TYPO3 allows Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23337 | jq has signed integer overflow in jv.c:jvp_array_write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23337</link><description>jq is a command-line JSON processor. In versions up to and including 1.7.1, an integer overflow arises when assigning value using an index of 2147483647, the signed integer limit. This causes a denial of service. Commit de21386681c0df0104a99d9d09db23a9b2a78b1e contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 14:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5029 | Kingdee Cloud Galaxy Private Cloud BBC System File deleteFileAction.jhtml path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5029</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Kingdee Cloud Galaxy Private Cloud BBC System up to 9.0 Patch April 2025 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function BaseServiceFactory.getFileUploadService.deleteFileAction of the file fileUpload/deleteFileAction.jhtml of the component File Handler. The manipulation of the argument filePath leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 14:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44892 | FW-WGS-804HPT v1.305b241111 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ownekey parameter in the web_rmon_alarm_post_rmon_alarm funct...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44892</link><description>FW-WGS-804HPT v1.305b241111 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ownekey parameter in the web_rmon_alarm_post_rmon_alarm function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 14:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44895 | FW-WGS-804HPT v1.305b241111 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ipv4Aclkey parameter in the web_acl_ipv4BasedAceAdd function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44895</link><description>FW-WGS-804HPT v1.305b241111 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ipv4Aclkey parameter in the web_acl_ipv4BasedAceAdd function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 14:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42922 | AAPanel v7.0.7 was discovered to contain an OS command injection vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42922</link><description>AAPanel v7.0.7 was discovered to contain an OS command injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 14:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56429 | itech iLabClient 3.7.1 relies on the hard-coded YngAYdgAE/kKZYu2F2wm6w== key (found in iLabClient.jar) for local users to read or write to t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56429</link><description>itech iLabClient 3.7.1 relies on the hard-coded YngAYdgAE/kKZYu2F2wm6w== key (found in iLabClient.jar) for local users to read or write to the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1416 | Password disclosure in Proget MDM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1416</link><description>In Proget MDM, a low-privileged user can retrieve passwords for managed devices and subsequently use functionalities restricted by the MDM (Mobile Device Management). For it to happen, they must know the UUIDs of targetted devices, which might be obtained by exploiting CVE-2025-1415 or CVE-2025-1417.

This issue has been fixed in 2.17.5 version of Konsola Proget (server part of the MDM suite).</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1417 | Information disclosure in Proget MDM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1417</link><description>In Proget MDM, a low-privileged user can access information about changes contained in backups of all devices managed by the MDM (Mobile Device Management). This information include user ids, email addresses, first names, last names and device UUIDs. The last one can be used for exploitation of CVE-2025-1416.

Successful exploitation requires UUID of a targeted backup, which cannot be brute forced. 

This issue has been fixed in 2.17.5 version of Konsola Proget (server part of the MDM suite).</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1418 | Information disclosure in Proget MDM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1418</link><description>A low-privileged user can access information about profiles created in Proget MDM (Mobile Device Management), which contain details about allowed/prohibited functions. The profiles do not reveal any sensitive information (including their usage in connected devices).   


This issue has been fixed in 2.17.5 version of Konsola Proget (server part of the MDM suite).</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1419 | XSS in Proget MDM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1419</link><description>Input provided in comment section of Konsola Proget is not sanitized correctly, allowing a high-privileged user to perform a Stored Cross-Site Scripting attack.


This issue has been fixed in 2.17.5 version of Konsola Proget (server part of the MDM suite).</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1420 | XSS in Proget MDM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1420</link><description>Input provided in a field containing "activationMessage" in Konsola Proget is not sanitized correctly, allowing a high-privileged user to perform a Stored Cross-Site Scripting attack.


This issue has been fixed in 2.17.5 version of Konsola Proget (server part of the MDM suite).</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1421 | Formula injection in a CSV file in Proget MDM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1421</link><description>Data provided in a request performed to the server while activating a new device are put in a database. Other high privileged users might download this data as a CSV file and corrupt their PC by opening it in a tool such as Microsoft Excel. The attacker could gain remote access to the user's PC.


This issue has been fixed in 2.17.5 version of Konsola Proget (server part of the MDM suite).</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40775 | DNS message with invalid TSIG causes an assertion failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40775</link><description>When an incoming DNS protocol message includes a Transaction Signature (TSIG), BIND always checks it.  If the TSIG contains an invalid value in the algorithm field, BIND immediately aborts with an assertion failure.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.20.0 through 9.20.8 and 9.21.0 through 9.21.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48417 | Hard-Coded Certificate and Private Key for HTTPS Web Interface in eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 / cPP2 charging stations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48417</link><description>The certificate and private key used for providing transport layer security for connections to the web interface (TCP port 443) is hard-coded in the firmware and are shipped with the update files. An attacker can use the private key to perform man-in-the-middle attacks against users of the admin interface. The files are located in /etc/ssl (e.g. salia.local.crt, salia.local.key and salia.local.pem). There is no option to upload/configure custom TLS certificates.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48415 | Backdoor Functionality via USB Drive in eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 / cPP2 charging stations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48415</link><description>A USB backdoor feature can be triggered by attaching a USB drive that contains specially crafted "salia.ini" files. The .ini file can contain several "commands" that could be exploited by an attacker to export or modify the device configuration, enable an SSH backdoor  or perform other administrative actions. Ultimately, this backdoor also allows arbitrary execution of OS commands.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48416 | Backdoor Functionality via SSH in eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 / cPP2 charging stations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48416</link><description>An OpenSSH daemon listens on TCP port 22. There is a hard-coded entry in the "/etc/shadow" file in the firmware image for the "root" user. However, in the default SSH configuration the "PermitRootLogin" is disabled, preventing the root user from logging in via SSH. This configuration can be bypassed/changed by an attacker through multiple paths though.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48413 | Hard-coded OS root credentials in eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 / cPP2 charging stations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48413</link><description>The `/etc/passwd` and `/etc/shadow` files reveal hard-coded password hashes for the operating system "root" user. The credentials are shipped with the update files. There is no option for deleting or changing their passwords for an enduser. An attacker can use the credentials to log into the device. Authentication can be performed via SSH backdoor or likely via physical access (UART shell).</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48414 | Hard-coded web interface credentials in eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 / cPP2 charging stations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48414</link><description>There are several scripts in the web interface that are accessible via undocumented hard-coded credentials. The scripts provide access to additional administrative/debug functionality and are likely intended for debugging during development and provides an additional attack surface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27804 | OS Command Injection Vulnerability in eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 / cPP2 charging stations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27804</link><description>Several OS command injection vulnerabilities exist in the device firmware in the /var/salia/mqtt.php script. By publishing a specially crafted message to a certain MQTT topic arbitrary OS commands can be executed with root permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27803 | Missing Authentication in eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 / cPP2 charging stations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27803</link><description>The devices do not implement any authentication for the web interface or the MQTT server. An attacker who has network access to the device immediately gets administrative access to the devices and can perform arbitrary administrative actions and reconfigure the devices or potentially gain access to sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1415 | Information disclosure in Proget MDM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1415</link><description>A low-privileged user is able to obtain information about tasks executed on devices controlled by Proget MDM (Mobile Device Management), as well as details of the devices like their UUIDs needed for exploitation of CVE-2025-1416.

In order to perform the attack, one has to know a task_id, but since it's a low integer and there is no limit of requests an attacker can perform to a vulnerable endpoint, the task_id might be simply brute forced.

This issue has been fixed in 2.17.5 version of Konsola Proget (server part of the MDM suite).</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:52:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41232 | CVE-2025-41232: Spring Security authorization bypass for method security annotations on private methods</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41232</link><description>Spring Security Aspects may not correctly locate method security annotations on private methods. This can cause an authorization bypass.

Your application may be affected by this if the following are true:

  *  You are using @EnableMethodSecurity(mode=ASPECTJ) and spring-security-aspects, and
  *  You have Spring Security method annotations on a private method
In that case, the target method may be able to be invoked without proper authorization.

You are not affected if:

  *  You are not using @EnableMethodSecurity(mode=ASPECTJ) or spring-security-aspects, or
  *  You have no Spring Security-annotated private methods</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12561 | Affiliate Sales in Google Analytics and other tools &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12561</link><description>The Affiliate Sales in Google Analytics and other tools plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Open Redirect in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.9. This is due to insufficient validation on the redirect url supplied via the 'afflink' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users to potentially malicious sites if they can successfully trick them into performing an action.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3750 | Network Posts Extended &amp;lt;= 7.7.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via post_height Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3750</link><description>The Network Posts Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘post_height’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 7.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3781 | Raisely Donation Form &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via raisely_donation_form Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3781</link><description>The Raisely Donation Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's raisely_donation_form shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4105 | Splitit &amp;lt;= 4.2.8 - Missing Authorization to Multiple Administrative Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4105</link><description>The Splitit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to missing capability checks on several functions in the 'splitIt-flexfields-payment-gateway.php' file in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change plugin settings, including changing the environment from sandbox to production and vice versa.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4217 | WP YouTube Video Optimizer &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4217</link><description>The WP YouTube Video Optimizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ib_youtube' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4219 | DPEPress &amp;lt;= 0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4219</link><description>The DPEPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'dpe' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4221 | Animated Buttons &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4221</link><description>The Animated Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'auto-downloader' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4611 | Slim SEO &amp;lt;= 4.5.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via slim_seo_breadcrumbs Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4611</link><description>The Slim SEO – Fast &amp; Automated WordPress SEO Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's slim_seo_breadcrumbs shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4803 | Glossary by WPPedia &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4803</link><description>The Glossary by WPPedia – Best Glossary plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'posttypes' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1712 | Arbitrary file write with vcrtrace</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1712</link><description>Argument injection in special agent configuration in Checkmk &lt;2.4.0p1, &lt;2.3.0p32, &lt;2.2.0p42 and 2.1.0 allows authenticated attackers to write arbitrary files</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-16536 | Stack overflow leading to DoS can be triggered by a malicious authenticated client.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16536</link><description>Stack overflow leading to DoS can be triggered by a malicious authenticated client in Clickhouse before 19.14.3.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 07:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-25255 | Yandex Browser Lite for Android prior to version 21.1.0 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25255</link><description>Yandex Browser Lite for Android prior to version 21.1.0 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 07:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-25262 | Yandex Browser for Android prior to version 21.3.0 allows remote attackers to perform IDN homograph attack.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25262</link><description>Yandex Browser for Android prior to version 21.3.0 allows remote attackers to perform IDN homograph attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 07:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-25254 | Yandex Browser Lite for Android before 21.1.0 allows remote attackers to spoof the address bar.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25254</link><description>Yandex Browser Lite for Android before 21.1.0 allows remote attackers to spoof the address bar.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 07:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4949 | XXE vulnerability in Eclipse JGit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4949</link><description>In Eclipse JGit versions 7.2.0.202503040940-r and older, the ManifestParser class used by the repo command and the AmazonS3 class used to implement the experimental amazons3 git transport protocol allowing to store git pack files in an Amazon S3 bucket, are vulnerable to XML External Entity (XXE) attacks when parsing XML files. This vulnerability can lead to information disclosure, denial of service, and other security issues.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 06:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4524 | Madara – Responsive and modern WordPress theme for manga sites &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4524</link><description>The Madara – Responsive and modern WordPress theme for manga sites theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.2 via the 'template' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 06:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4094 | Digits &amp;lt; 8.4.6.1 - Auth Bypass via OTP Bruteforcing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4094</link><description>The DIGITS: WordPress Mobile Number Signup and Login WordPress plugin before 8.4.6.1 does not rate limit OTP validation attempts, making it straightforward for attackers to bruteforce them.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 06:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4969 | Libsoup: off-by-one out-of-bounds read in find_boundary() in soup-multipart.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4969</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the libsoup package. This flaw stems from its failure to correctly verify the termination of multipart HTTP messages. This can allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted multipart HTTP body, causing the libsoup-consuming server to read beyond its allocated memory boundaries (out-of-bounds read).</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 02:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5013 | HkCms Search index.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5013</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in HkCms up to 2.3.2.240702. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php/search/index.html of the component Search. The manipulation of the argument keyword leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5011 | moonlightL hexo-boot Dynamic List Page index.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5011</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in moonlightL hexo-boot 4.3.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/home/index.html of the component Dynamic List Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>