<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:06:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-13918 | Elevation of Privileges in Symantec Endpoint Protection Windows Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13918</link><description>Symantec Endpoint Protection, prior to 14.3 RU10 Patch 1, RU9 Patch 2, and RU8 Patch 3, may be susceptible to a Elevation of Privilege vulnerability, which is a type of issue whereby an attacker may attempt to compromise the software application to gain elevated access to resources that are normally protected from an application or user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:06:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13919 | Component Object Model (COM) Hijacking in Symantec Endpoint Protection Windows Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13919</link><description>Symantec Endpoint Protection, prior to 14.3 RU10 Patch 1, RU9 Patch 2, and RU8 Patch 3, may be susceptible to a COM Hijacking vulnerability, which is a type of issue whereby an attacker attempts to establish persistence and evade detection by hijacking COM references in the Windows Registry.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:06:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24685 | OpenProject has Argument Injection on Repository module that allows Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24685</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. Versions prior to 16.6.6 and 17.0.2 have an arbitrary file write vulnerability in OpenProject’s repository diff download endpoint (`/projects/:project_id/repository/diff.diff`) when rendering a single revision via git show. By supplying a specially crafted rev value (for example, `rev=--output=/tmp/poc.txt)`, an attacker can inject git show command-line options. When OpenProject executes the SCM command, Git interprets the attacker-controlled rev as an option and writes the output to an attacker-chosen path. As a result, any user with the `:browse_repository` permission on the project can create or overwrite arbitrary files that the OpenProject process user is permitted to write. The written contents consist of git show output (commit metadata and patch), but overwriting application or configuration files still leads to data loss and denial of service, impacting integrity and availability. The issue has been fixed in OpenProject 17.0.2 and 16.6.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:06:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13917 | Elevation of Privileges in Web Security Services (WSS) Agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13917</link><description>WSS Agent, prior to 9.8.5, may be susceptible to a Elevation of Privilege vulnerability, which is a type of issue whereby an attacker may attempt to compromise the software application to gain elevated access to resources that are normally protected from an application or user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:06:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65887 | A division-by-zero vulnerability in the flow.floor_divide() component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65887</link><description>A division-by-zero vulnerability in the flow.floor_divide() component of OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input tensor with zero.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:06:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65888 | A dimension validation flaw in the flow.empty() component of OneFlow 0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a negativ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65888</link><description>A dimension validation flaw in the flow.empty() component of OneFlow 0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a negative or excessively large dimension value.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:06:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1522 | Open5GS SGWC s5c-handler.c sgwc_s5c_handle_modify_bearer_response denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1522</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. This vulnerability affects the function sgwc_s5c_handle_modify_bearer_response of the file src/sgwc/s5c-handler.c of the component SGWC. Executing a manipulation can lead to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. This patch is called b19cf6a. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue. The issue report is flagged as already-fixed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:06:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65886 | A shape mismatch vulnerability in OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying crafted tensor shapes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65886</link><description>A shape mismatch vulnerability in OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying crafted tensor shapes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22243 | EGroupware has SQL Injection in Nextmatch Filter Processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22243</link><description>EGroupware is a Web based groupware server written in PHP. A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the core components of EGroupware prior to versions 23.1.20260113 and 26.0.20260113, specifically in the `Nextmatch` filter processing. The flaw allows authenticated attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands into the `WHERE` clause of database queries. This is achieved by exploiting a PHP type juggling issue where JSON decoding converts numeric strings into integers, bypassing the `is_int()` security check used by the application. Versions 23.1.20260113 and 26.0.20260113 patch the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61140 | The value function in jsonpath 1.1.1 lib/index.js is vulnerable to Prototype Pollution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61140</link><description>The value function in jsonpath 1.1.1 lib/index.js is vulnerable to Prototype Pollution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57283 | The Node.js package browserstack-local 1.5.8 contains a command injection vulnerability. This occurs because the logfile variable is not pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57283</link><description>The Node.js package browserstack-local 1.5.8 contains a command injection vulnerability. This occurs because the logfile variable is not properly sanitized in lib/Local.js.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:55:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58150 | x86: buffer overrun with shadow paging + tracing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58150</link><description>Shadow mode tracing code uses a set of per-CPU variables to avoid
cumbersome parameter passing.  Some of these variables are written to
with guest controlled data, of guest controllable size.  That size can
be larger than the variable, and bounding of the writes was missing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69517 | An issue in Amidaware Inc Tactical RMM v1.3.1 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /api/tacticalrmm/apiv3/v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69517</link><description>An issue in Amidaware Inc Tactical RMM v1.3.1 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /api/tacticalrmm/apiv3/views.py component</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23553 | x86: incomplete IBPB for vCPU isolation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23553</link><description>In the context switch logic Xen attempts to skip an IBPB in the case of
a vCPU returning to a CPU on which it was the previous vCPU to run.
While safe for Xen's isolation between vCPUs, this prevents the guest
kernel correctly isolating between tasks.  Consider:

 1) vCPU runs on CPU A, running task 1.
 2) vCPU moves to CPU B, idle gets scheduled on A.  Xen skips IBPB.
 3) On CPU B, guest kernel switches from task 1 to 2, issuing IBPB.
 4) vCPU moves back to CPU A.  Xen skips IBPB again.

Now, task 2 is running on CPU A with task 1's training still in the BTB.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70336 | A Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in 'Create New Live Item' in PodcastGenerator 3.2.9 allows remote attackers to inject arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70336</link><description>A Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in 'Create New Live Item' in PodcastGenerator 3.2.9 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary script or HTML via the 'TITLE', 'SHORT DESCRIPTION' and 'LONG DESCRIPTION' parameters. The saved payload gets executed on 'View All Live Items' and 'Live Stream' pages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1536 | Libsoup: libsoup: http header injection or response splitting via crlf injection in content-disposition header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1536</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup. An attacker who can control the input for the Content-Disposition header can inject CRLF (Carriage Return Line Feed) sequences into the header value. These sequences are then interpreted verbatim when the HTTP request or response is constructed, allowing arbitrary HTTP headers to be injected. This vulnerability can lead to HTTP header injection or HTTP response splitting without requiring authentication or user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1539 | Libsoup: libsoup: credential leakage via http redirects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1539</link><description>A flaw was found in the libsoup HTTP library that can cause proxy authentication credentials to be sent to unintended destinations. When handling HTTP redirects, libsoup removes the Authorization header but does not remove the Proxy-Authorization header if the request is redirected to a different host. As a result, sensitive proxy credentials may be leaked to third-party servers. Applications using libsoup for HTTP communication may unintentionally expose proxy authentication data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1237 | Vulnerable cross-model authorization in juju. If a charm's cross-model permissions are revoked or expire, a malicious user who is able to up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1237</link><description>Vulnerable cross-model authorization in juju. If a charm's cross-model permissions are revoked or expire, a malicious user who is able to update database records can mint an invalid macaroon that is incorrectly validated by the juju controller, enabling a charm to maintain otherwise revoked or expired permissions. This allows a charm to continue relating to another charm in a cross-model relation, and use their workload without their permission. No fix is available as of the time of writing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:21:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1520 | rethinkdb Secondary Index cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1520</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in rethinkdb up to 2.4.3. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Secondary Index Handler. Such manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1521 | Open5GS SGWC s5c-handler.c denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1521</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. This affects the function sgwc_s5c_handle_bearer_resource_failure_indication of the file src/sgwc/s5c-handler.c of the component SGWC. Performing a manipulation results in denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The patch is named 69b53add90a9479d7960b822fc60601d659c328b. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1060 | WP Adminify &amp;lt;= 4.0.7.7 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via &amp;#x27;get-addons-list&amp;#x27; REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1060</link><description>The WP Adminify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.7.7 via the /wp-json/adminify/v1/get-addons-list REST API endpoint. The endpoint is registered with permission_callback set to __return_true, allowing unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the complete list of available addons, their installation status, version numbers, and download URLs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23014 | perf: Ensure swevent hrtimer is properly destroyed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23014</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

perf: Ensure swevent hrtimer is properly destroyed

With the change to hrtimer_try_to_cancel() in
perf_swevent_cancel_hrtimer() it appears possible for the hrtimer to
still be active by the time the event gets freed.

Make sure the event does a full hrtimer_cancel() on the free path by
installing a perf_event::destroy handler.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14795 | Stop Spammers Classic &amp;lt;= 2026.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via Email Allowlist</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14795</link><description>The Stop Spammers Classic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2026.1. This is due to missing nonce validation in the ss_addtoallowlist class. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add arbitrary email addresses to the spam allowlist via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 2026.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 13:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36984 | EPSON 1.124 - &amp;#x27;seksmdb.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36984</link><description>EPSON 1.124 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the SENADB service that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in C:\Program Files (x86)\EPSON_P2B\Printer Software\Status Monitor\ to inject malicious executables that will run with LocalSystem permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36985 | IP Watcher v3.0.0.30 - &amp;#x27;PACService.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36985</link><description>IP Watcher 3.0.0.30 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configuration that allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted binary path to inject malicious executables that will be launched with elevated LocalSystem privileges during service startup.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36986 | Prey 1.9.6 - &amp;quot;CronService&amp;quot; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36986</link><description>Prey 1.9.6 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in the CronService to insert malicious code that would execute during application startup or system reboot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36987 | Program Access Controller v1.2.0.0 - &amp;#x27;PACService.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36987</link><description>Program Access Controller 1.2.0.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in PACService.exe that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path during system startup or reboot to inject and run malicious executables with LocalSystem permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36988 | PDW File Browser &amp;lt;= v1.3 - Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36988</link><description>PDW File Browser version 1.3 contains stored and reflected cross-site scripting vulnerabilities that allow authenticated attackers to inject malicious scripts through file rename and path parameters. Attackers can craft malicious URLs or rename files with XSS payloads to execute arbitrary JavaScript in victims' browsers when they access the file browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36989 | ForensiTAppxService 2.2.0.4 - &amp;#x27;ForensiTAppxService.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36989</link><description>ForensiT AppX Management Service 2.2.0.4 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in the service configuration to inject malicious code that would execute with LocalSystem account permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36990 | Input Director 1.4.3 - &amp;#x27;Input Director&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36990</link><description>Input Director 1.4.3 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configuration that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path during system startup or reboot to inject and run malicious executables with LocalSystem permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36991 | ShareMouse 5.0.43 - &amp;#x27;ShareMouse Service&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36991</link><description>ShareMouse 5.0.43 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the insecure service path configuration by placing malicious executables in specific system directories to gain elevated access during service startup.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36992 | Nord VPN-6.31.13.0 - &amp;#x27;nordvpn-service&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36992</link><description>Nord VPN 6.31.13.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its nordvpn-service that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted binary path during system startup or reboot to potentially run malicious code with LocalSystem permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36993 | LimeSurvey &amp;lt;= 4.3.10 - &amp;#x27;Survey Menu&amp;#x27; Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36993</link><description>LimeSurvey 4.3.10 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Survey Menu functionality of the administration panel. Attackers can inject malicious SVG scripts through the Surveymenu[title] and Surveymenu[parent_id] parameters to execute arbitrary JavaScript in administrative contexts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14865 | Passster – Password Protect Pages and Content &amp;lt;= 4.2.24 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14865</link><description>The Passster – Password Protect Pages and Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'content_protector' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.24. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 4.2.21.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1056 | Snow Monkey Forms &amp;lt;= 12.0.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion via Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1056</link><description>The Snow Monkey Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the 'generate_user_dirpath' function in all versions up to, and including, 12.0.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59896 | Authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59896</link><description>Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18 contain a persistent authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An attacker could send malicious content to an authenticated user and steal information from their session due to insufficient validation of user input in '/add_command?sid=', affecting the 'command_name' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59897 | Authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59897</link><description>Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18 contain a persistent authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An attacker could send malicious content to an authenticated user and steal information from their session due to insufficient validation of user input in '/edit_command?sid=', affecting the 'source_dir' and ‘dest_dir’ parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59898 | Authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59898</link><description>Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18 contain a persistent authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An attacker could send malicious content to an authenticated user and steal information from their session due to insufficient validation of user input in '/add_exclude_dir?sid=', affecting the 'exclude_dir' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59899 | Authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59899</link><description>Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18 contain a persistent authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An attacker could send malicious content to an authenticated user and steal information from their session due to insufficient validation of user input in  '/server_options?sid=', affecting the 'tasks_logs_dir', 'errors_logs_dir', 'error_notifications_address', 'status_notifications_address', and 'status_reports_address' parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59900 | Authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59900</link><description>Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18 contain a persistent authenticated Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An attacker could send malicious content to an authenticated user and steal information from their session due to insufficient validation of user input in  '/server_options?sid=', affecting the 'tasks_logs_dir', 'errors_logs_dir', 'error_notifications_address', 'status_notifications_address', and 'status_reports_address' parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59901 | authenticated reflected XSS vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59901</link><description>Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18 has an authenticated reflected XSS vulnerability in the '/monitor_directory?sid=' endpoint, caused by insufficient validation of the 'monitor_directory' parameter sent by POST. An attacker could exploit this weakness to send malicious content to an authenticated user and steal information from their session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59891 | Cross-Site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59891</link><description>Cross-Site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18. An authenticated user could cause another user to perform unwanted actions within the application they are logged into. This vulnerability is possible due to the lack of proper CSRF token implementation. Among other things, it is possible, using a POST request to change a user's password or create users via '/setup_login?sid=', affecting the 'username', 'password', and 'cpassword' parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59892 | Cross-Site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59892</link><description>Cross-Site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18. An authenticated user could cause another user to perform unwanted actions within the application they are logged into. This vulnerability is possible due to the lack of proper CSRF token implementation. Among other things, it is possible, using a POST request to delete commands individually via '/delete_command?sid=', using the 'cid' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59893 | Cross-Site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59893</link><description>Cross-Site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18. An authenticated user could cause another user to perform unwanted actions within the application they are logged into. This vulnerability is possible due to the lack of proper CSRF token implementation. Among other things, it is possible, using a POST request to rename commands via '/rename_command?sid=', affecting the 'command_name' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59894 | Cross-Site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59894</link><description>Cross-Site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18. An authenticated user could cause another user to perform unwanted actions within the application they are logged into. This vulnerability is possible due to the lack of proper CSRF token implementation. Among other things, it is possible, using a POST request to delete all commands via '/delete_all_commands?sid='.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59895 | remote denial-of-service (DoS) vulnerability in Sync Breeze Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59895</link><description>Sync Breeze Enterprise Server v10.4.18 and Disk Pulse Enterprise v10.4.18 contain a remote denial-of-service (DoS) vulnerability in the configuration restore functionality. The issue is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied data during this process. An attacker could send malicious requests to alter the configuration file, causing the application to become unresponsive. In a successful scenario, the service may not recover on its own and require a complete reinstallation, as the configuration becomes corrupted and prevents the service from restarting, even manually.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0483 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in LiveHelperChat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0483</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the PDF file upload functionality of Live Helper Chat, versions prior to 4.72. An attacker can upload a malicious PDF file containing an XSS payload, which will be executed in the user's context when they download and open the file via the link generated by the application. The vulnerability allows arbitrary JavaScript code to be executed in the user's local context.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14063 | SEO Links Interlinking &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;google_error&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14063</link><description>The SEO Links Interlinking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'google_error' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14283 | BlockArt Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder Blocks ,WordPress Block Plugin, Sections &amp;amp; Template Library &amp;lt;= 2.2.14 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14283</link><description>The BlockArt Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder Blocks ,WordPress Block Plugin, Sections &amp; Template Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the BlockArt Counter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14386 | Search Atlas SEO – Premier SEO Plugin for One-Click WP Publishing &amp;amp; Integrated AI Optimization 2.4.4 - 2.5.12 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Authentication Bypass via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14386</link><description>The Search Atlas SEO – Premier SEO Plugin for One-Click WP Publishing &amp; Integrated AI Optimization plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass due to a missing capability check on the 'generate_sso_url' and 'validate_sso_token' functions in versions 2.4.4 to 2.5.12. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to extract the 'nonce_token' authentication value to log in to the first Administrator's account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14616 | Recooty &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14616</link><description>The Recooty – Job Widget (Old Dashboard) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6. This is due to missing nonce validation on the recooty_save_maybe() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the recooty_key option and inject malicious content into iframe src attributes via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15511 | Rupantorpay &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Order Status Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15511</link><description>The Rupantorpay plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the handle_webhook() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify WooCommerce order statuses by sending crafted requests to the WooCommerce API endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26386 | Johnson Controls iSTAR Configuration Utility (ICU) tool has Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26386</link><description>Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Johnson Controls iSTAR Configuration Utility (ICU) allows Overflow Buffers.This issue affects iSTAR Configuration Utility (ICU): iSTAR Configuration Utility (ICU) tool version 6.9.7 and prior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0844 | Simple User Registration &amp;lt;= 6.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via profile_save_field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0844</link><description>The Simple User Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions up to, and including, 6.7 due to insufficient restriction on the 'profile_save_field' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with minimal permissions such as a subscriber, to modify their user role by supplying the 'wp_capabilities' parameter during a profile update.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1280 | Frontend File Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 23.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Sharing via &amp;#x27;file_id&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1280</link><description>The Frontend File Manager Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized file sharing due to a missing capability check on the 'wpfm_send_file_in_email' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 23.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to share arbitrary uploaded files via email by supplying a file ID. Since file IDs are sequential integers, attackers can enumerate all uploaded files on the site and exfiltrate sensitive data that was intended to be restricted to administrators only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1377 | imwptip &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1377</link><description>The imwptip plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to missing nonce validation on the settings update functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1380 | Bitcoin Donate Button &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1380</link><description>The Bitcoin Donate Button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the settings page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's settings, including donation addresses and display configurations, via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1391 | Vzaar Media Management &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1391</link><description>The Vzaar Media Management plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the $_SERVER['PHP_SELF'] variable. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1398 | Change WP URL &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1398</link><description>The Change WP URL plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'change-wp-url' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the WP Login URL via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1399 | WP Google Ad Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Admin Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1399</link><description>The WP Google Ad Manager Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41351 | Weak encryption on Funambol&amp;#x27;s cloud server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41351</link><description>Vulnerability that allows a Padding Oracle Attack to be performed on the Funambol v30.0.0.20 cloud server. The thumbnail display URL allows an attacker to decrypt and encrypt the parameters used by the application to generate ‘self-signed’ access URLs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7740 | Use of default credentials vulnerability in Hitachi Energy SuprOS product</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7740</link><description>Default credentials vulnerability exists in SuprOS
product. If exploited, this could allow an authenticated
local attacker to use an admin account created during
product deployment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0702 | VidShop – Shoppable Videos for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Unauthenticated Time-Based SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;fields&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0702</link><description>The VidShop – Shoppable Videos for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the 'fields' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:02:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1053 | Ivory Search &amp;lt;= 5.5.13 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;menu_gcse&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;nothing_found_text&amp;#x27; Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1053</link><description>The Ivory Search – WordPress Search Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:02:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1381 | Order Minimum/Maximum Amount Limits for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.6.8 - Authenticated (Shop Manager+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Hide Add to Cart Content Fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1381</link><description>The Order Minimum/Maximum Amount Limits for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via settings in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:02:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1400 | AI Engine &amp;lt;= 3.3.2 - Authenticated (Editor+) Arbitrary File Upload via &amp;#x27;filename&amp;#x27; Parameter in update_media_metadata Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1400</link><description>The AI Engine – The Chatbot and AI Framework for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the `rest_helpers_update_media_metadata` function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. The attacker can upload a benign image file, then use the `update_media_metadata` endpoint to rename it to a PHP file, creating an executable PHP file in the uploads directory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:02:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40537 | SolarWinds Web Help Desk Hardcoded Credentials Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40537</link><description>SolarWinds Web Help Desk was found to be susceptible to a hardcoded credentials vulnerability that, under certain situations, could allow access to administrative functions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40551 | SolarWinds Web Help Desk Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40551</link><description>SolarWinds Web Help Desk was found to be susceptible to an untrusted data deserialization vulnerability that could lead to remote code execution, which would allow an attacker to run commands on the host machine. This could be exploited without authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40552 | SolarWinds Web Help Desk Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40552</link><description>SolarWinds Web Help Desk was found to be susceptible to an authentication bypass vulnerability that if exploited, would allow a malicious actor to execute actions and methods that should be protected by authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40553 | SolarWinds Web Help Desk Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40553</link><description>SolarWinds Web Help Desk was found to be susceptible to an untrusted data deserialization vulnerability that could lead to remote code execution, which would allow an attacker to run commands on the host machine. This could be exploited without authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40554 | SolarWinds Web Help Desk Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40554</link><description>SolarWinds Web Help Desk was found to be susceptible to an authentication bypass vulnerability that, if exploited, could allow an attacker to invoke specific actions within Web Help Desk.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0818 | CSS-based exfiltration of the content from partially encrypted emails when allowing remote content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0818</link><description>CSS-based exfiltration of the content from partially encrypted emails when allowing remote content. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 147.0.1 and Thunderbird &lt; 140.7.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40536 | SolarWinds Web Help Desk Security Control Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40536</link><description>SolarWinds Web Help Desk was found to be susceptible to a security control bypass vulnerability that if exploited, could allow an unauthenticated attacker to gain access to certain restricted functionality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1054 | RegistrationMagic &amp;lt;= 6.0.7.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Settings Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1054</link><description>The RegistrationMagic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in versions up to, and including, 6.0.7.4. This is due to missing nonce verification and capability checks on the rm_set_otp AJAX action handler. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify arbitrary plugin settings, including reCAPTCHA keys, security settings, and frontend menu titles.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1389 | Document Embedder &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary Document Library Entry Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1389</link><description>The Document Embedder – Embed PDFs, Word, Excel, and Other Files plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.4. This is due to the plugin not verifying that a user has permission to access the requested resource in the 'bplde_save_document_library', 'bplde_get_single', and 'bplde_delete_document_library' AJAX actions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to read, modify, and delete Document Library entries created by other users, including administrators, via the 'id' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12709 | Interactions – Create Interactive Experiences in the Block Editor &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12709</link><description>The Interactions – Create Interactive Experiences in the Block Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via event selectors in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14039 | Simple Folio &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;Client name&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;Link&amp;#x27; Meta Fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14039</link><description>The Simple Folio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the '_simple_folio_item_client_name' and '_simple_folio_item_link' meta fields in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9082 | WPBITS Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9082</link><description>The WPBITS Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple widget parameters in versions up to, and including, 1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping when dynamic content is enabled. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level permissions and above to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0825 | Database for Contact Form 7, WPforms, Elementor forms &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Form Data Exfiltration via CSV Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0825</link><description>The Database for Contact Form 7, WPforms, Elementor forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to missing capability checks on the CSV export functionality in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download sensitive form submission data containing personally identifiable information (PII) by accessing the CSV export endpoint with an export key that is exposed in publicly accessible page source code. The vulnerability is created because while the shortcode properly filters displayed entries by user, the CSV export handler completely bypasses this filtering and exports all entries regardless of user permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0832 | New User Approve &amp;lt;= 3.2.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Approval, Denial, and Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0832</link><description>The New User Approve plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data and modification of data due to a missing capability check on multiple REST API endpoints in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to approve or deny user accounts, retrieve sensitive user information including emails and roles, and force logout of privileged users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1244 | Forms Bridge &amp;lt;= 4.2.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;id&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1244</link><description>The Forms Bridge – Infinite integrations plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' shortcode attribute in the 'financoop_campaign' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.5. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the user-supplied 'id' parameter in the forms_bridge_financoop_shortcode_error function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1295 | Buy Now Plus &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1295</link><description>The Buy Now Plus – Buy Now buttons for Stripe plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'buynowplus' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on shortcode attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1310 | Simple calendar for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.6.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Calendar Entry Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1310</link><description>The Simple calendar for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.6. This is due to missing capability checks on the `miga_ajax_editor_cal_delete` function that is hooked to the `miga_editor_cal_delete` AJAX action with both authenticated and unauthenticated access enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary calendar entries by sending a request with a valid nonce and the calendar entry ID.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1466 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in Jirafeau</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1466</link><description>Jirafeau normally prevents browser preview for text files due to the possibility that for example SVG and HTML documents could be exploited for cross site scripting. This was done by storing the MIME type of a file and allowing only browser preview for MIME types beginning with image (except for image/svg+xml, see CVE-2022-30110, CVE-2024-12326 and CVE-2025-7066), video and audio. However, it was possible to bypass this check by sending a manipulated HTTP request with an invalid MIME type like image. When doing the preview, the browser tries to automatically detect the MIME type resulting in detecting SVG and possibly executing JavaScript code. To prevent this, MIME sniffing is disabled by sending the HTTP header X-Content-Type-Options: nosniff.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13471 | User Activity Log &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Unauthenticated Limited Arbitrary Option Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13471</link><description>The User Activity Log WordPress plugin through 2.2 does not properly handle failed login attempts in some cases, allowing unauthenticated users to set arbitrary options to 1 (for example to enable User Registration when it has been turned off)</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14610 | TableMaster for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Authenticated (Author+) Server-Side Request Forgery via &amp;#x27;csv_url&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14610</link><description>The TableMaster for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.6. This is due to the plugin not restricting which URLs can be fetched when importing CSV data from a URL in the Data Table widget. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations, including localhost and internal network services, and read sensitive files such as wp-config.php via the 'csv_url' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 05:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8072 | Target Video Easy Publish &amp;lt;= 3.8.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via placeholder_img Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8072</link><description>The Target Video Easy Publish plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘placeholder_img’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 05:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1083 | Appointment Hour Booking – Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.5.60 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;Min/Max Length&amp;#x27; Field Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1083</link><description>The Appointment Hour Booking – Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via form field configuration parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.60 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'Min length/characters' and 'Max length/characters' field configuration values. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the form builder interface. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 05:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1298 | Easy Replace Image &amp;lt;= 3.5.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Attachment Replacement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1298</link><description>The Easy Replace Image plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.2. This is due to missing capability checks on the `image_replacement_from_url` function that is hooked to the `eri_from_url` AJAX action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to replace arbitrary image attachments on the site with images from external URLs, potentially enabling site defacement, phishing attacks, or content manipulation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 05:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1514 | 2100 Technology｜Official Document Management System - Incorrect Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1514</link><description>Official Document Management System developed by 2100 Technology has a Incorrect Authorization vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to modify front-end code to read all official documents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 04:16:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1506 | D-Link DIR-615 MAC Filter Configuration adv_mac_filter.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1506</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DIR-615 4.10. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /adv_mac_filter.php of the component MAC Filter Configuration. This manipulation of the argument mac causes os command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1505 | D-Link DIR-615 URL Filter set_temp_nodes.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1505</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-615 4.10. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /set_temp_nodes.php of the component URL Filter. The manipulation results in os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1513 | billboard.js before 3.18.0 allows an attacker to execute malicious JavaScript due to improper sanitization during chart option binding.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1513</link><description>billboard.js before 3.18.0 allows an attacker to execute malicious JavaScript due to improper sanitization during chart option binding.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21569 | This High severity XXE (XML External Entity Injection) vulnerability was introduced in version 7.1.0 of Crowd Data Center and Server. 
	
	Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21569</link><description>This High severity XXE (XML External Entity Injection) vulnerability was introduced in version 7.1.0 of Crowd Data Center and Server. 
	
	This XXE (XML External Entity Injection) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.9, allows an authenticated attacker to access local and remote content which has high impact to confidentiality, low impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Crowd Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		* Crowd Data Center and Server 7.1: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 7.1.3
		
		
	
	See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/crowd/crowd-release-notes-199094.html). You can download the latest version of Crowd Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/crowd/download-archive). 
	
	This vulnerability was reported via our Atlassian (Internal) program.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24850 | ML-DSA Signature Verification Accepts Signatures with Repeated Hint Indices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24850</link><description>The ML-DSA crate is a Rust implementation of the Module-Lattice-Based Digital Signature Standard (ML-DSA). Starting in version 0.0.4 and prior to version 0.1.0-rc.4, the ML-DSA signature verification implementation in the RustCrypto `ml-dsa` crate incorrectly accepts signatures with repeated (duplicate) hint indices. According to the ML-DSA specification (FIPS 204 / RFC 9881), hint indices within each polynomial must be **strictly increasing**. The current implementation uses a non-strict monotonic check (`&lt;=` instead of `&lt;`), allowing duplicate indices. This is a regression bug. The original implementation was correct, but a commit in version 0.0.4 inadvertently changed the strict `&lt;` comparison to `&lt;=`, introducing the vulnerability. Version 0.1.0-rc.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24852 | iccDEV has a heap-buffer-overflow in icXmlParseTextString()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24852</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Prior to version 2.3.1.2, a heap buffer over-read when the strlen() function attempts to read a non-null-terminated buffer potentially leaking heap memory contents and causing application termination. This vulnerability affects users of the iccDEV library who process ICC color profiles. ICC Profile Injection vulnerabilities arise when user-controllable input is incorporated into ICC profile data or other structured binary blobs in an unsafe manner. Version 2.3.1.2 contains a fix for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24838 | DotNetNuke.Core Vulnerable to Stored XSS via Module Title</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24838</link><description>DNN (formerly DotNetNuke) is an open-source web content management platform (CMS) in the Microsoft ecosystem. Prior to versions 9.13.10 and 10.2.0,  module title supports richtext which could include scripts that would execute in certain scenarios. Versions 9.13.10 and 10.2.0 contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24839 | Dokploy has a clickjacking vulnerability - Missing X-Frame-Options and CSP frame-ancestors headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24839</link><description>Dokploy is a free, self-hostable Platform as a Service (PaaS). In versions prior to 0.26.6, the Dokploy web interface is vulnerable to Clickjacking attacks due to missing frame-busting headers. This allows attackers to embed Dokploy pages in malicious iframes and trick authenticated users into performing unintended actions. Version 0.26.6 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24840 | Dokploy uses hardcoded credentials in installation script, which could result in database access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24840</link><description>Dokploy is a free, self-hostable Platform as a Service (PaaS). In versions prior to 0.26.6, a hardcoded credential in the provided installation script (located at https://dokploy.com/install.sh, line 154) uses a hardcoded password when creating the database container. This means that nearly all Dokploy installations use the same database credentials and could be compromised. Version 0.26.6 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24841 | Dokploy Vulnerable to Authenticated Remote Code Execution via Command Injection in Docker Container Terminal WebSocket Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24841</link><description>Dokploy is a free, self-hostable Platform as a Service (PaaS). In versions prior to 0.26.6, a critical command injection vulnerability exists in Dokploy's WebSocket endpoint `/docker-container-terminal`. The `containerId` and `activeWay` parameters are directly interpolated into shell commands without sanitization, allowing authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the host server. Version 0.26.6 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24842 | node-tar Vulnerable to Arbitrary File Creation/Overwrite via Hardlink Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24842</link><description>node-tar,a Tar for Node.js, contains a vulnerability in versions prior to 7.5.7 where the security check for hardlink entries uses different path resolution semantics than the actual hardlink creation logic. This mismatch allows an attacker to craft a malicious TAR archive that bypasses path traversal protections and creates hardlinks to arbitrary files outside the extraction directory. Version 7.5.7 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24837 | DotNetNuke.Core Vulnerable to Stored XSS in Module Deletion Confirmation Modal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24837</link><description>DNN (formerly DotNetNuke) is an open-source web content management platform (CMS) in the Microsoft ecosystem. Starting in version 9.0.0 and prior to versions 9.13.10 and 10.2.0, a module friendly name could include scripts that will run during some module operations in the Persona Bar. Versions 9.13.10 and 10.2.0 contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24784 | DotNetNuke.Core has a potential XSS vulnerability in modules&amp;#x27; header and footer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24784</link><description>DNN (formerly DotNetNuke) is an open-source web content management platform (CMS) in the Microsoft ecosystem. Starting in version 9.0.0 and prior to versions 9.13.10 and 10.2.0, a content editor could inject scripts in module headers/footers that would run for other users. Versions 9.13.10 and 10.2.0 contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24833 | DotNetNuke.Core Vulnerable to Stored XSS in Module Description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24833</link><description>DNN (formerly DotNetNuke) is an open-source web content management platform (CMS) in the Microsoft ecosystem. Prior to versions 9.13.10 and 10.2.0, a module could install with richtext in its description field which could contain scripts that will run for user in the Persona Bar. Versions 9.13.10 and 10.2.0 contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24836 | DotNetNuke.Core Vulnerable to Stored XSS in Scheduler LogNotes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24836</link><description>DNN (formerly DotNetNuke) is an open-source web content management platform (CMS) in the Microsoft ecosystem. Starting in version 9.0.0 and prior to versions 9.13.10 and 10.2.0, extensions could write richtext in log notes which can include scripts that would run in the PersonaBar when displayed. Versions 9.13.10 and 10.2.0 contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24134 | StudioCMS has an Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24134</link><description>StudioCMS is a server-side-rendered, Astro native, headless content management system. Versions prior to 0.2.0 contain a Broken Object Level Authorization (BOLA) vulnerability in the Content Management feature that allows users with the "Visitor" role to access draft content created by Editor/Admin/Owner users. Version 0.2.0 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24785 | Clatter has a PSK Validity Rule Violation issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24785</link><description>Clatter is a no_std compatible, pure Rust implementation of the Noise protocol framework with post-quantum support. Versiosn prior to2.2.0 have a protocol compliance vulnerability. The library allowed post-quantum handshake patterns that violated the PSK validity rule (Noise Protocol Framework Section 9.3). This could allow PSK-derived keys to be used for encryption without proper randomization by self-chosen ephemeral randomness, weakening security guarantees and potentially allowing catastrophic key reuse. Affected default patterns include `noise_pqkk_psk0`, `noise_pqkn_psk0`, `noise_pqnk_psk0`, `noise_pqnn_psk0``, and some hybrid variants. Users of these patterns may have been using handshakes that do not meet the intended security properties. The issue is fully patched and released in Clatter v2.2.0. The fixed version includes runtime checks to detect offending handshake patterns. As a workaround, avoid using offending `*_psk0` variants of post-quantum patterns. Review custom handshake patterns carefully.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55292 | In Meshtastic, an attacker can spoof licensed amateur flag for a node</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55292</link><description>Meshtastic is an open source mesh networking solution. In the current Meshtastic architecture, a Node is identified by their NodeID, generated from the MAC address, rather than their public key. This aspect downgrades the security, specifically by abusing the HAM mode which doesn't use encryption. An attacker can, as such, forge a NodeInfo on behalf of a victim node advertising that the HAM mode is enabled. This, in turn, will allow the other nodes on the mesh to accept the new information and overwriting the NodeDB. The other nodes will then only be able to send direct messages to the victim by using the shared channel key instead of the PKC. Additionally, because HAM mode by design doesn't provide any confidentiality or authentication of information, the attacker could potentially also be able to change the Node details, like the full name, short code, etc. To keep the attack persistent, it is enough to regularly resend the forged NodeInfo, in particular right after the victim sends their own. A patch is available in version 2.7.6.834c3c5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23830 | SandboxJS has Sandbox Escape via Unprotected AsyncFunction Constructor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23830</link><description>SandboxJS is a JavaScript sandboxing library. Versions prior to 0.8.26 have a sandbox escape vulnerability due to `AsyncFunction` not being isolated in `SandboxFunction`. The library attempts to sandbox code execution by replacing the global `Function` constructor with a safe, sandboxed version (`SandboxFunction`). This is handled in `utils.ts` by mapping `Function` to `sandboxFunction` within a map used for lookups. However, before version 0.8.26, the library did not include mappings for `AsyncFunction`, `GeneratorFunction`, and `AsyncGeneratorFunction`. These constructors are not global properties but can be accessed via the `.constructor` property of an instance (e.g., `(async () =&gt; {}).constructor`). In `executor.ts`, property access is handled. When code running inside the sandbox accesses `.constructor` on an async function (which the sandbox allows creating), the `executor` retrieves the property value. Since `AsyncFunction` was not in the safe-replacement map, the `executor` returns the actual native host `AsyncFunction` constructor. Constructors for functions in JavaScript (like `Function`, `AsyncFunction`) create functions that execute in the global scope. By obtaining the host `AsyncFunction` constructor, an attacker can create a new async function that executes entirely outside the sandbox context, bypassing all restrictions and gaining full access to the host environment (Remote Code Execution). Version 0.8.26 patches this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54373 | OpenEMR may expose Contents of Clinical Notes and Care Planto users who do not have Sensitivities=high privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54373</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Versions prior to 7.0.4 have a vulnerability where sensitive data is unintentionally revealed to unauthorized parties. Contents of Clinical Notes and Care Plan, where an encounter has Sensitivity=high, can be viewed and changed by users who do not have Sensitivities=high privilege. Version 7.0.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:26:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67645 | OpenEMR Vulnerable to Broken Access Control in Profile Edit Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67645</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Versions prior to 7.0.4 have a broken access control in the Profile Edit endpoint. An authenticated normal user can modify the request parameters (pubpid / pid) to reference another user’s record; the server accepts the modified IDs and applies the changes to that other user’s profile. This allows one user to alter another user’s profile data (name, contact info, etc.), and could enable account takeover. Version 7.0.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24910 | In Bun before 1.3.5, the default trusted dependencies list (aka trust allow list) can be spoofed by a non-npm package in the case of a match...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24910</link><description>In Bun before 1.3.5, the default trusted dependencies list (aka trust allow list) can be spoofed by a non-npm package in the case of a matching name (for file, link, git, or github).</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24909 | vlt before 1.0.0-rc.10 mishandles path sanitization for tar, leading to path traversal during extraction.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24909</link><description>vlt before 1.0.0-rc.10 mishandles path sanitization for tar, leading to path traversal during extraction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24783 | soroban-fixed-point-math has Incorrect Rounding and Overflow Handling in Signed Fixed-Point Math with Negatives</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24783</link><description>soroban-fixed-point-math is a fixed-point math library for Soroban smart contacts. In versions 1.3.0 and 1.4.0, the `mulDiv(x, y, z)` function incorrectly handled cases where both the intermediate product $x * y$ and the divisor $z$ were negative. The logic assumed that if the intermediate product was negative, the final result must also be negative, neglecting the sign of $z$. This resulted in rounding being applied in the wrong direction for cases where both $x * y$ and $z$ were negative. The functions most at risk are `fixed_div_floor` and `fixed_div_ceil`, as they often use non-constant numbers as the divisor $z$ in `mulDiv`.  This error is present in all signed `FixedPoint` and `SorobanFixedPoint` implementations, including `i64`, `i128`, and `I256`. Versions 1.3.1 and 1.4.1 contain a patch. No known workarounds for this issue are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24778 | Ghost vulnerable to XSS via malicious Portal preview links</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24778</link><description>Ghost is an open source content management system. In Ghost versions 5.43.0 through 5.12.04 and 6.0.0 through 6.14.0, an attacker was able to craft a malicious link that, when accessed by an authenticated staff user or member, would execute JavaScript with the victim's permissions, potentially leading to account takeover. Ghost Portal versions 2.29.1 through 2.51.4 and 2.52.0 through 2.57.0 were vulnerable to this issue. Ghost automatically loads the latest patch of the members Portal component via CDN. For Ghost 5.x users, upgrading to v5.121.0 or later fixes the vulnerability. v5.121.0 loads Portal v2.51.5, which contains the patch. For Ghost 6.x users, upgrading to v6.15.0 or later fixes the vulnerability. v6.15.0 loads Portal v2.57.1, which contains the patch. For Ghost installations using a customized or self-hosted version of Portal, it will be necessary to manually rebuild from or update to the latest patch version.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24779 | vLLM vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in `MediaConnector`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24779</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). Prior to version 0.14.1, a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in the `MediaConnector` class within the vLLM project's multimodal feature set. The load_from_url and load_from_url_async methods obtain and process media from URLs provided by users, using different Python parsing libraries when restricting the target host. These two parsing libraries have different interpretations of backslashes, which allows the host name restriction to be bypassed. This allows an attacker to coerce the vLLM server into making arbitrary requests to internal network resources. This vulnerability is particularly critical in containerized environments like `llm-d`, where a compromised vLLM pod could be used to scan the internal network, interact with other pods, and potentially cause denial of service or access sensitive data. For example, an attacker could make the vLLM pod send malicious requests to an internal `llm-d` management endpoint, leading to system instability by falsely reporting metrics like the KV cache state. Version 0.14.1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24770 | RAGFlow Affected by Zip Slip Remote Code Execution (RCE) in MinerUParser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24770</link><description>RAGFlow is an open-source RAG (Retrieval-Augmented Generation) engine. In version 0.23.1 and possibly earlier versions, the MinerU parser contains a "Zip Slip" vulnerability, allowing an attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on the server (leading to Remote Code Execution) via a malicious ZIP archive. The MinerUParser class retrieves and extracts ZIP files from an external source (mineru_server_url). The extraction logic in `_extract_zip_no_root` fails to sanitize filenames within the ZIP archive. Commit 64c75d558e4a17a4a48953b4c201526431d8338f contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24765 | PHPUnit Vulnerable to Unsafe Deserialization in PHPT Code Coverage Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24765</link><description>PHPUnit is a testing framework for PHP. A vulnerability has been discovered in versions prior to 12.5.8, 11.5.50, 10.5.62, 9.6.33, and 8.5.52 involving unsafe deserialization of code coverage data in PHPT test execution. The vulnerability exists in the `cleanupForCoverage()` method, which deserializes code coverage files without validation, potentially allowing remote code execution if malicious `.coverage` files are present prior to the execution of the PHPT test. The vulnerability occurs when a `.coverage` file, which should not exist before test execution, is deserialized without the `allowed_classes` parameter restriction. An attacker with local file write access can place a malicious serialized object with a `__wakeup()` method into the file system, leading to arbitrary code execution during test runs with code coverage instrumentation enabled. This vulnerability requires local file write access to the location where PHPUnit stores or expects code coverage files for PHPT tests. This can occur through CI/CD pipeline attacks, the local development environment, and/or compromised dependencies. Rather than just silently sanitizing the input via `['allowed_classes' =&gt; false]`, the maintainer has chosen to make the anomalous state explicit by treating pre-existing `.coverage` files for PHPT tests as an error condition. Starting in versions  in versions 12.5.8, 11.5.50, 10.5.62, 9.6.33, when a `.coverage` file is detected for a PHPT test prior to execution, PHPUnit will emit a clear error message identifying the anomalous state. Organizations can reduce the effective risk of this vulnerability through proper CI/CD configuration, including ephemeral runners, code review enforcement, branch protection, artifact isolation, and access control.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:51:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24748 | Kargo&amp;#x27;s `GetConfig()` and `RefreshResource()` API endpoints allow unauthenticated access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24748</link><description>Kargo manages and automates the promotion of software artifacts. Prior to versions 1.8.7, 1.7.7, and 1.6.3, a bug was found with authentication checks on the `GetConfig()` API endpoint. This allowed unauthenticated users to access this endpoint by specifying an `Authorization` header with any non-empty `Bearer` token value, regardless of validity.  This vulnerability did allow for exfiltration of configuration data such as endpoints for connected Argo CD clusters. This data could allow an attacker to enumerate cluster URLs and namespaces for use in subsequent attacks. Additionally, the same bug affected the `RefreshResource` endpoint. This endpoint does not lead to any information disclosure, but could be used by an unauthenticated attacker to perform a denial-of-service style attack against the Kargo API. `RefreshResource` sets an annotation on specific Kubernetes resources to trigger reconciliations. If run on a constant loop, this could also slow down legitimate requests to the Kubernetes API server. This problem has been patched in Kargo versiosn 1.8.7, 1.7.7, and 1.6.3. There are no workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24741 | ConvertX Vulnerable to Arbitrary File Deletion via Path Traversal in `POST /delete`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24741</link><description>ConvertXis a self-hosted online file converter. In versions prior to 0.17.0, the `POST /delete` endpoint uses a user-controlled `filename` value to construct a filesystem path and deletes it via `unlink` without sufficient validation. By supplying path traversal sequences (e.g., `../`), an attacker can delete arbitrary files outside the intended uploads directory, limited only by the permissions of the server process. Version 0.17.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24747 | PyTorch Vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via Untrusted Checkpoint Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24747</link><description>PyTorch is a Python package that provides tensor computation. Prior to version 2.10.0, a vulnerability in PyTorch's `weights_only` unpickler allows an attacker to craft a malicious checkpoint file (`.pth`) that, when loaded with `torch.load(..., weights_only=True)`, can corrupt memory and potentially lead to arbitrary code execution. Version 2.10.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24738 | gmrtd ReadFile Vulnerable to Denial of Service via Excessive TLV Length Values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24738</link><description>gmrtd is a Go library for reading Machine Readable Travel Documents (MRTDs). Prior to version 0.17.2, ReadFile accepts TLVs with lengths that can range up to 4GB, which can cause unconstrained resource consumption in both memory and cpu cycles. ReadFile can consume an extended TLV with lengths well outside what would be available in ICs. It can accept something all the way up to 4GB which would take too many iterations in 256 byte chunks, and would also try to allocate memory that might not be available in constrained environments like phones. Or if an API sends data  to ReadFile, the same problem applies. The very small chunked read also locks the goroutine in  accepting data for a very large number of iterations.  projects using the gmrtd library to read files from NFCs can experience extreme slowdowns or memory consumption. A malicious NFC can just behave like the mock transceiver described above and by just sending dummy bytes as each chunk to be read, can make the receiving thread unresponsive and fill up memory on the host system. Version 0.17.2 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:20:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24740 | Dozzle Agent Label-Based Access Control Bypass Allows Unauthorized Container Shell Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24740</link><description>Dozzle is a realtime log viewer for docker containers. Prior to version 9.0.3, a flaw in Dozzle’s agent-backed shell endpoints allows a user restricted by label filters (for example, `label=env=dev`) to obtain an interactive root shell in out‑of‑scope containers (for example, `env=prod`) on the same agent host by directly targeting their container IDs. Version 9.0.3 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1504 | Inappropriate implementation in Background Fetch API in Google Chrome prior to 144.0.7559.110 allowed a remote attacker to leak cross-origin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1504</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Background Fetch API in Google Chrome prior to 144.0.7559.110 allowed a remote attacker to leak cross-origin data via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24736 | Squidex has Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Issue in Webhook Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24736</link><description>Squidex is an open source headless content management system and content management hub. Versions of the application up to and including 7.21.0 allow users to define "Webhooks" as actions within the Rules engine. The url parameter in the webhook configuration does not appear to validate or restrict destination IP addresses. It accepts local addresses such as 127.0.0.1 or localhost. When a rule is triggered (Either manual trigger by manually calling the trigger endpoint or by a content update or any other triggers), the backend server executes an HTTP request to the user-supplied URL. Crucially, the server logs the full HTTP response in the rule execution log (lastDump field), which is accessible via the API. Which turns a "Blind" SSRF into a "Full Read" SSRF. As of time of publication, no patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21589 | Session Smart Router, Session Smart Conductor, WAN Assurance Router: API Authentication Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21589</link><description>An Authentication Bypass Using an
Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Juniper Networks Session Smart
Router may allows a network-based attacker to bypass authentication
and take administrative control of the device.

This issue affects Session Smart Router: 



  *  from 5.6.7 before 5.6.17, 
  *  from 6.0 before 6.0.8 (affected from 6.0.8),

  *  from 6.1 before 6.1.12-lts, 
  *  from 6.2 before 6.2.8-lts, 
  *  from 6.3 before 6.3.3-r2; 




This issue affects Session Smart Conductor: 



  *  from 5.6.7 before 5.6.17, 
  *  from 6.0 before 6.0.8 (affected from 6.0.8),

  *  from 6.1 before 6.1.12-lts, 
  *  from 6.2 before 6.2.8-lts, 
  *  from 6.3 before 6.3.3-r2; 




This issue affects WAN Assurance Managed Routers: 



  *  from 5.6.7 before 5.6.17, 
  *  from 6.0 before 6.0.8 (affected from 6.0.8),

  *  from 6.1 before 6.1.12-lts, 
  *  from 6.2 before 6.2.8-lts, 
  *  from 6.3 before 6.3.3-r2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14988 | Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in iba Systems ibaPDA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14988</link><description>A security issue has been identified in ibaPDA that could allow unauthorized actions on the file system under certain conditions. This may impact the confidentiality, integrity, or availability of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12810 | Failure in Password Rotation and Check-in Mechanism in Secret Server Allows Reuse of Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12810</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Delinea Inc. Secret Server On-Prem (RPC Password Rotation modules).This issue affects Secret Server On-Prem: 11.8.1, 11.9.6, 11.9.25.

A secret with "change password on check in" enabled automatically checks in even when the password change fails after reaching its retry limit.  This leaves the secret in an inconsistent state with the wrong password.

Remediation: Upgrade to 11.9.47 or later. The secret will remain checked out when the password change fails.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24472 | Hono cache middleware ignores &amp;quot;Cache-Control: private&amp;quot; leading to Web Cache Deception</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24472</link><description>Hono is a Web application framework that provides support for any JavaScript runtime. Prior to version 4.11.7, Cache Middleware contains an information disclosure vulnerability caused by improper handling of HTTP cache control directives. The middleware does not respect standard cache control headers such as `Cache-Control: private` or `Cache-Control: no-store`, which may result in private or authenticated responses being cached and subsequently exposed to unauthorized users. Version 4.11.7 has a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24473 | Hono has an Arbitrary Key Read in Serve static Middleware (Cloudflare Workers Adapter)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24473</link><description>Hono is a Web application framework that provides support for any JavaScript runtime. Prior to version 4.11.7, Serve static Middleware for the Cloudflare Workers adapter contains an information disclosure vulnerability that may allow attackers to read arbitrary keys from the Workers environment. Improper validation of user-controlled paths can result in unintended access to internal asset keys. Version 4.11.7 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24688 | pypdf has possible Infinite Loop when processing outlines/bookmarks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24688</link><description>pypdf is a free and open-source pure-python PDF library. An attacker who uses an infinite loop vulnerability that is present in versions prior to 6.6.2 can craft a PDF which leads to an infinite loop. This requires accessing the outlines/bookmarks. This has been fixed in pypdf 6.6.2. If projects cannot upgrade yet, consider applying the changes from PR #3610 manually.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24771 | Hono has a Cross-site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24771</link><description>Hono is a Web application framework that provides support for any JavaScript runtime. Prior to version 4.11.7, a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the `ErrorBoundary` component of the hono/jsx library. Under certain usage patterns, untrusted user-controlled strings may be rendered as raw HTML, allowing arbitrary script execution in the victim's browser. Version 4.11.7 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24858 | An Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability [CWE-288] vulnerability in Fortinet FortiAnalyzer 7.6.0 through 7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24858</link><description>An Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability [CWE-288] vulnerability in Fortinet FortiAnalyzer 7.6.0 through 7.6.5, FortiAnalyzer 7.4.0 through 7.4.9, FortiAnalyzer 7.2.0 through 7.2.11, FortiAnalyzer 7.0.0 through 7.0.15, FortiManager 7.6.0 through 7.6.5, FortiManager 7.4.0 through 7.4.9, FortiManager 7.2.0 through 7.2.11, FortiManager 7.0.0 through 7.0.15, FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.5, FortiOS 7.4.0 through 7.4.10, FortiOS 7.2.0 through 7.2.12, FortiOS 7.0.0 through 7.0.18 may allow an attacker with a FortiCloud account and a registered device to log into other devices registered to other accounts, if FortiCloud SSO authentication is enabled on those devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24116 | Wasmtime segfault or unused out-of-sandbox load with f64.copysign operator on x86-64</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24116</link><description>Wasmtime is a runtime for WebAssembly. Starting in version 29.0.0 and prior to version 36.0.5, 40.0.3, and 41.0.1, on x86-64 platforms with AVX, Wasmtime's compilation of the `f64.copysign` WebAssembly instruction with Cranelift may load 8 more bytes than is necessary. When signals-based-traps are disabled this can result in a uncaught segfault due to loading from unmapped guard pages. With guard pages disabled it's possible for out-of-sandbox data to be loaded, but unless there is another bug in Cranelift this data is not visible to WebAssembly guests. Wasmtime 36.0.5, 40.0.3, and 41.0.1 have been released to fix this issue. Users are recommended to upgrade to the patched versions of Wasmtime. Other affected versions are not patched and users should updated to supported major version instead. This bug can be worked around by enabling signals-based-traps. While disabling guard pages can be a quick fix in some situations, it's not recommended to disabled guard pages as it is a key defense-in-depth measure of Wasmtime.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24398 | Hono&amp;#x27;s IPv4 address validation bypass in IP Restriction Middleware allows IP spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24398</link><description>Hono is a Web application framework that provides support for any JavaScript runtime. Prior to version 4.11.7, IP Restriction Middleware in Hono is vulnerable to an IP address validation bypass. The `IPV4_REGEX` pattern and `convertIPv4ToBinary` function in `src/utils/ipaddr.ts` do not properly validate that IPv4 octet values are within the valid range of 0-255, allowing attackers to craft malformed IP addresses that bypass IP-based access controls. Version 4.11.7 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36974 | Realtek Andrea RT Filters 1.0.64.7 - &amp;#x27;AERTSr64.EXE&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36974</link><description>Realtek Andrea RT Filters 1.0.64.7 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in 'C:\Program Files\IDT\WDM\AESTSr64.exe' to inject malicious code that would execute during service startup or system reboot.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36975 | EPSON Status Monitor 3 &amp;#x27;EPSON_PM_RPCV4_06&amp;#x27; - Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36975</link><description>EPSON Status Monitor 3 version 8.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code by exploiting the service binary path. Attackers can leverage the unquoted path in 'C:\Program Files\Common Files\EPSON\EPW!3SSRP\E_S60RPB.EXE' to inject malicious executables and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36976 | Global Registration Service 1.0.0.3 - &amp;#x27;GREGsvc.exe&amp;#x27;  Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36976</link><description>Acer Global Registration Service 1.0.0.3 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its service configuration that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in C:\Program Files (x86)\Acer\Registration\ to inject malicious executables that would run with elevated LocalSystem privileges during service startup.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36977 | Wondershare Driver Install Service help 10.7.1.321 - &amp;#x27;ElevationService&amp;#x27; Unquote Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36977</link><description>Wondershare Driver Install Service contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the ElevationService executable that allows local attackers to potentially inject malicious code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path to replace the service binary with a malicious executable, enabling privilege escalation to LocalSystem account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36978 | Froxlor Froxlor Server Management Panel 0.10.16 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36978</link><description>Froxlor Server Management Panel 0.10.16 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability in customer registration input fields. Attackers can inject malicious scripts through username, name, and firstname parameters to execute code when administrators view customer traffic modules.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36979 | Atheros Coex Service Application 8.0.0.255 -&amp;#x27;ZAtheros Bt&amp;amp;Wlan Coex Agent&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36979</link><description>Atheros Coex Service Application 8.0.0.255 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configuration. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path by placing malicious executables in the service path to gain elevated system privileges during service startup.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36980 | SAntivirus IC 10.0.21.61 - &amp;#x27;SAntivirusIC&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36980</link><description>SAntivirus IC 10.0.21.61 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configuration that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted executable path to inject malicious files in the service binary path, enabling privilege escalation to system-level permissions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36981 | Motorola Device Manager 2.4.5 - &amp;#x27;ForwardDaemon.exe &amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36981</link><description>Motorola Device Manager 2.4.5 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the PST Service that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in ForwardDaemon.exe to inject malicious code that will execute with elevated system privileges during service startup.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36982 | Motorola Device Manager 2.5.4 - &amp;#x27;MotoHelperService.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36982</link><description>Motorola Device Manager 2.5.4 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the MotoHelperService.exe service that allows local users to potentially inject malicious code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in the service configuration to execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges during service startup.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36983 | Quick &amp;#x27;n Easy FTP Service 3.2 -  Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36983</link><description>Quick 'n Easy FTP Service 3.2 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code during service startup. Attackers can exploit the misconfigured service binary path to inject malicious executables with elevated LocalSystem privileges during system boot or service restart.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23892 | OctoPrint has Timing Side-Channel Vulnerability in API Key Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23892</link><description>OctoPrint provides a web interface for controlling consumer 3D printers. OctoPrint versions up to and including 1.11.5 are affected by a (theoretical) timing attack vulnerability that allows API key extraction over the network. Due to using character based comparison that short-circuits on the first mismatched character during API key validation, rather than a cryptographical method with static runtime regardless of the point of mismatch, an attacker with network based access to an affected OctoPrint could extract API keys valid on the instance by measuring the response times of the denied access responses and guess an API key character by character. The vulnerability is patched in version 1.11.6. The likelihood of this attack actually working is highly dependent on the network's latency, noise and similar parameters. An actual proof of concept was not achieved so far. Still, as always administrators are advised to not expose their OctoPrint instance on hostile networks, especially not on the public Internet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24881 | In GnuPG before 2.5.17, a crafted CMS (S/MIME) EnvelopedData message carrying an oversized wrapped session key can cause a stack-based buffe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24881</link><description>In GnuPG before 2.5.17, a crafted CMS (S/MIME) EnvelopedData message carrying an oversized wrapped session key can cause a stack-based buffer overflow in gpg-agent during PKDECRYPT--kem=CMS handling. This can easily be leveraged for denial of service; however, there is also memory corruption that could lead to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24882 | In GnuPG before 2.5.17, a stack-based buffer overflow exists in tpm2daemon during handling of the PKDECRYPT command for TPM-backed RSA and E...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24882</link><description>In GnuPG before 2.5.17, a stack-based buffer overflow exists in tpm2daemon during handling of the PKDECRYPT command for TPM-backed RSA and ECC keys.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24883 | In GnuPG before 2.5.17, a long signature packet length causes parse_signature to return success with sig-&gt;data[] set to a NULL value, leadin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24883</link><description>In GnuPG before 2.5.17, a long signature packet length causes parse_signature to return success with sig-&gt;data[] set to a NULL value, leading to a denial of service (application crash).</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0746 | AI Engine &amp;lt;= 3.3.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0746</link><description>The AI Engine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.2 via the 'get_audio' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services, if "Public API" is enabled in the plugin settings, and 'allow_url_fopen' is set to 'On' on the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22262 | Suricata datasets: stack overflow when saving a set</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22262</link><description>Suricata is a network IDS, IPS and NSM engine. While saving a dataset a stack buffer is used to prepare the data. Prior to versions 8.0.3 and 7.0.14, if the data in the dataset is too large, this can result in a stack overflow. Versions 8.0.3 and 7.0.14 contain a patch. As a workaround, do not use rules with datasets `save` nor `state` options.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22263 | Suricata http1: quadratic complexity in headers parsing over multiple packets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22263</link><description>Suricata is a network IDS, IPS and NSM engine. Starting in version 8.0.0 and prior to version 8.0.3, inefficiency in http1 headers parsing can lead to slowdown over multiple packets. Version 8.0.3 patches the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22264 | Suricata detect/alert: heap-use-after-free on alert queue expansion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22264</link><description>Suricata is a network IDS, IPS and NSM engine. Prior to version 8.0.3 and 7.0.14, an unsigned integer overflow can lead to a heap use-after-free condition when generating excessive amounts of alerts for a single packet. Versions 8.0.3 and 7.0.14 contain a patch. As a workaround, do not run untrusted rulesets or run with less than 65536 signatures that can match on the same packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22261 | Suricata eve/alert: http1 xff handling can lead to denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22261</link><description>Suricata is a network IDS, IPS and NSM engine. Prior to versions 8.0.3 and 7.0.14, various inefficiencies in xff handling, especially for alerts not triggered in a tx, can lead to severe slowdowns. Versions 8.0.3 and 7.0.14 contain a patch. As a workaround, disable XFF support in the eve configuration. The setting is disabled by default.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33234 | NVIDIA runx contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause a code injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33234</link><description>NVIDIA runx contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause a code injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23592 | Insecure File Handling allows Remote Code Execution in Backup Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23592</link><description>Insecure file operations in HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composerâ€™s backup functionality could allow authenticated attackers to achieve remote code execution. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23593 | Unauthenticated Limited File Read allows Data Exposure in Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23593</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composer could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to view some system files. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to read files within the affected directory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0918 | Null Pointer Dereference in Tapo SmartCam HTTP Service on TP-Link Tapo C220 &amp;amp; C520WS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0918</link><description>The Tapo C220 v1 and C520WS v2 cameras’ HTTP service does not safely handle POST requests containing an excessively large Content-Length header. The resulting failed memory allocation triggers a NULL pointer dereference, causing the main service process to crash. An unauthenticated attacker can repeatedly crash the service, causing temporary denial of service. The device restarts automatically, and repeated requests can keep it unavailable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:02:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0919 | Unauthenticated Denial of Service via Oversized URL in HTTP Parser on TP-Link Tapo C220 &amp;amp; C520WS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0919</link><description>The HTTP parser of Tapo C220 v1 and C520WS v2 cameras improperly handles requests containing an excessively long URL path. An invalid‑URL error path continues into cleanup code that assumes allocated buffers exist, leading to a crash and service restart. An unauthenticated attacker can force repeated service crashes or device reboots, causing denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:02:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1315 | Unauthenticated Denial of Service via Firmware Update Endpoint on TP-Link Tapo C220 &amp;amp; C520WS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1315</link><description>By sending crafted files to the firmware update endpoint of Tapo C220 v1 and C520WS v2, the device terminates core system services before verifying authentication or firmware integrity. An unauthenticated attacker can trigger a persistent denial of service, requiring a manual reboot or application initiated restart to restore normal device operation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:02:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14911 | Integer Overflow in GridFS chunkSize Leading to Heap Allocation Failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14911</link><description>User-controlled chunkSize metadata from MongoDB lacks appropriate validation allowing malformed GridFS metadata to overflow the bounding container.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:48:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22260 | Suricata http1: infinite recursion in decompression</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22260</link><description>Suricata is a network IDS, IPS and NSM engine. Starting in version 8.0.0 and prior to version 8.0.3, Suricata can crash with a stack overflow. Version 8.0.3 patches the issue. As a workaround, use default values for `request-body-limit` and `response-body-limit`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:48:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22259 | Suricata dnp3: unbounded transaction growth</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22259</link><description>Suricata is a network IDS, IPS and NSM engine. Prior to versions 8.0.3 and 7.0.14, specially crafted traffic can cause Suricata to consume large amounts of memory while parsing DNP3 traffic. This can lead to the process slowing down and running out of memory, potentially leading to it getting killed by the OOM killer. Versions 8.0.3 or 7.0.14 contain a patch. As a workaround, disable the DNP3 parser in the suricata yaml (disabled by default).</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65264 | The kernel driver of CPUID CPU-Z v2.17 and earlier does not validate user-supplied values passed via its IOCTL interface, allowing an attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65264</link><description>The kernel driver of CPUID CPU-Z v2.17 and earlier does not validate user-supplied values passed via its IOCTL interface, allowing an attacker to access sensitive information via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0705 | Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cloud Manager (Windows) before b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0705</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cloud Manager (Windows) before build 6.4.25342.354.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1477 | Out-of-band SQL injection in Quatuor Performance Evaluation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1477</link><description>An out-of-band SQL injection vulnerability (OOB SQLi) has been detected in the Performance Evaluation (EDD) application developed by Gabinete Técnico de Programación. Exploiting this vulnerability in the parameter 'Id_usuario' and 'Id_evaluacion’ in ‘/evaluacion_competencias_evalua_old.aspx’, could allow an attacker to extract sensitive information from the database through external channels, without the affected application returning the data directly, compromising the confidentiality of the stored information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1478 | Out-of-band SQL injection in Quatuor Performance Evaluation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1478</link><description>An out-of-band SQL injection vulnerability (OOB SQLi) has been detected in the Performance Evaluation (EDD) application developed by Gabinete Técnico de Programación. Exploiting this vulnerability in the parameter 'Id_usuario' and 'Id_evaluacion’ in ‘/evaluacion_hca_evalua.aspx’, could allow an attacker to extract sensitive information from the database through external channels, without the affected application returning the data directly, compromising the confidentiality of the stored information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1479 | Out-of-band SQL injection in Quatuor Performance Evaluation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1479</link><description>An out-of-band SQL injection vulnerability (OOB SQLi) has been detected in the Performance Evaluation (EDD) application developed by Gabinete Técnico de Programación. Exploiting this vulnerability in the parameters 'Id_usuario' and 'Id_evaluacion’ in ‘/evaluacion_hca_ver_auto.asp', could allow an attacker to extract sensitive information from the database through external channels, without the affected application returning the data directly, compromising the confidentiality of the stored information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1480 | Out-of-band SQL injection in Quatuor Performance Evaluation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1480</link><description>An out-of-band SQL injection vulnerability (OOB SQLi) has been detected in the Performance Evaluation (EDD) application developed by Gabinete Técnico de Programación. Exploiting this vulnerability in the parameter 'Id_usuario' in '/evaluacion_objetivos_anyo_sig_evalua.aspx', could allow an attacker to extract sensitive information from the database through external channels, without the affected application returning the data directly, compromising the confidentiality of the stored information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1481 | Out-of-band SQL injection in Quatuor Performance Evaluation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1481</link><description>An out-of-band SQL injection vulnerability (OOB SQLi) has been detected in the Performance Evaluation (EDD) application developed by Gabinete Técnico de Programación. Exploiting this vulnerability in the parameter 'Id_usuario' in '/evaluacion_objetivos_anyo_sig_ver_auto.aspx', could allow an attacker to extract sensitive information from the database through external channels, without the affected application returning the data directly, compromising the confidentiality of the stored information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1482 | Out-of-band SQL injection in Quatuor Performance Evaluation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1482</link><description>An out-of-band SQL injection vulnerability (OOB SQLi) has been detected in the Performance Evaluation (EDD) application developed by Gabinete Técnico de Programación. Exploiting this vulnerability in the parameter 'Id_evaluacion' in '/evaluacion_objetivos_evalua_definido.aspx', could allow an attacker to extract sensitive information from the database through external channels, without the affected application returning the data directly, compromising the confidentiality of the stored information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1483 | Out-of-band SQL injection in Quatuor Performance Evaluation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1483</link><description>An out-of-band SQL injection vulnerability (OOB SQLi) has been detected in the Performance Evaluation (EDD) application developed by Gabinete Técnico de Programación. Exploiting this vulnerability in the parameter 'Id_usuario' in '/evaluacion_objetivos_ver_auto.aspx', could allow an attacker to extract sensitive information from the database through external channels, without the affected application returning the data directly, compromising the confidentiality of the stored information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69559 | code-projects Computer Book Store 1.0 is vulnerable to File Upload in admin_add.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69559</link><description>code-projects Computer Book Store 1.0 is vulnerable to File Upload in admin_add.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69562 | code-projects Mobile Shop Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /insertmessage.php via the userid parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69562</link><description>code-projects Mobile Shop Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /insertmessage.php via the userid parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69564 | code-projects Mobile Shop Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /ExAddNewUser.php via the Name, Address, email, UserName, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69564</link><description>code-projects Mobile Shop Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /ExAddNewUser.php via the Name, Address, email, UserName, Password, confirm_password, Role, Branch, and Activate parameters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1472 | Out-of-band SQL injection in Quatuor Performance Evaluation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1472</link><description>An out-of-band SQL injection vulnerability (OOB SQLi) has been detected in the Performance Evaluation (EDD) application developed by Gabinete Técnico de Programación. Exploiting this vulnerability in the parameter 'txAny' in '/evaluacion_competencias_autoeval_list.aspx', could allow an attacker to extract sensitive information from the database through external channels, without the affected application returning the data directly, compromising the confidentiality of the stored information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1473 | Out-of-band SQL injection in Quatuor Performance Evaluation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1473</link><description>An out-of-band SQL injection vulnerability (OOB SQLi) has been detected in the Performance Evaluation (EDD) application developed by Gabinete Técnico de Programación. Exploiting this vulnerability in the parameter 'Id_usuario’ in '/evaluacion_competencias_evalua.aspx', could allow an attacker to extract sensitive information from the database through external channels, without the affected application returning the data directly, compromising the confidentiality of the stored information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1474 | Out-of-band SQL injection in Quatuor Performance Evaluation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1474</link><description>An out-of-band SQL injection vulnerability (OOB SQLi) has been detected in the Performance Evaluation (EDD) application developed by Gabinete Técnico de Programación. Exploiting this vulnerability in the parameter 'Id_usuario' and 'Id_evaluacion' en ‘/evaluacion_inicio.aspx’, could allow an attacker to extract sensitive information from the database through external channels, without the affected application returning the data directly, compromising the confidentiality of the stored information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1475 | Out-of-band SQL injection in Quatuor Performance Evaluation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1475</link><description>An out-of-band SQL injection vulnerability (OOB SQLi) has been detected in the Performance Evaluation (EDD) application developed by Gabinete Técnico de Programación. Exploiting this vulnerability in the parameter ‘Id_usuario' in ‘/evaluacion_acciones_evalua.aspx’, could allow an attacker to extract sensitive information from the database through external channels, without the affected application returning the data directly, compromising the confidentiality of the stored information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1476 | Out-of-band SQL injection in Quatuor Performance Evaluation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1476</link><description>An out-of-band SQL injection vulnerability (OOB SQLi) has been detected in the Performance Evaluation (EDD) application developed by Gabinete Técnico de Programación. Exploiting this vulnerability in the parameter 'Id_usuario' in ‘/evaluacion_acciones_ver_auto.aspx’, could allow an attacker to extract sensitive information from the database through external channels, without the affected application returning the data directly, compromising the confidentiality of the stored information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22258 | Suricata DCERPC: unbounded fragment buffering leads to memory exhaustion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22258</link><description>Suricata is a network IDS, IPS and NSM engine. Prior to versions 8.0.3 and 7.0.14, crafted DCERPC traffic can cause Suricata to expand a buffer w/o limits, leading to memory exhaustion and the process getting killed. While reported for DCERPC over UDP, it is believed that DCERPC over TCP and SMB are also vulnerable. DCERPC/TCP in the default configuration should not be vulnerable as the default stream depth is limited to 1MiB. Versions 8.0.3 and 7.0.14 contain a patch. Some workarounds are available. For DCERPC/UDP, disable the parser. For DCERPC/TCP, the `stream.reassembly.depth` setting will limit the amount of data that can be buffered. For DCERPC/SMB, the `stream.reassembly.depth` can be used as well, but is set to unlimited by default. Imposing a limit here may lead to loss of visibility in SMB.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69563 | code-projects Mobile Shop Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /ExLogin.php via the Password parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69563</link><description>code-projects Mobile Shop Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /ExLogin.php via the Password parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22039 | Kyverno Cross-Namespace Privilege Escalation via Policy apiCall</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22039</link><description>Kyverno is a policy engine designed for cloud native platform engineering teams. Versions prior to 1.16.3 and 1.15.3 have a critical authorization boundary bypass in namespaced Kyverno Policy apiCall. The resolved `urlPath` is executed using the Kyverno admission controller ServiceAccount, with no enforcement that the request is limited to the policy’s namespace. As a result, any authenticated user with permission to create a namespaced Policy can cause Kyverno to perform Kubernetes API requests using Kyverno’s admission controller identity, targeting any API path allowed by that ServiceAccount’s RBAC. This breaks namespace isolation by enabling cross-namespace reads (for example, ConfigMaps and, where permitted, Secrets) and allows cluster-scoped or cross-namespace writes (for example, creating ClusterPolicies) by controlling the urlPath through context variable substitution. Versions 1.16.3 and 1.15.3 contain a patch for the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23881 | Kyverno Denial of Service via Context Variable Amplification in Policy Engine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23881</link><description>Kyverno is a policy engine designed for cloud native platform engineering teams. Versions prior to 1.16.3 and 1.15.3 have unbounded memory consumption in Kyverno's policy engine that allows users with policy creation privileges to cause denial of service by crafting policies that exponentially amplify string data through context variables. Versions 1.16.3 and 1.15.3 contain a patch for the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11187 | Improper validation of PBMAC1 parameters in PKCS#12 MAC verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11187</link><description>Issue summary: PBMAC1 parameters in PKCS#12 files are missing validation
which can trigger a stack-based buffer overflow, invalid pointer or NULL
pointer dereference during MAC verification.

Impact summary: The stack buffer overflow or NULL pointer dereference may
cause a crash leading to Denial of Service for an application that parses
untrusted PKCS#12 files. The buffer overflow may also potentially enable
code execution depending on platform mitigations.

When verifying a PKCS#12 file that uses PBMAC1 for the MAC, the PBKDF2
salt and keylength parameters from the file are used without validation.
If the value of keylength exceeds the size of the fixed stack buffer used
for the derived key (64 bytes), the key derivation will overflow the buffer.
The overflow length is attacker-controlled. Also, if the salt parameter is
not an OCTET STRING type this can lead to invalid or NULL pointer
dereference.

Exploiting this issue requires a user or application to process
a maliciously crafted PKCS#12 file. It is uncommon to accept untrusted
PKCS#12 files in applications as they are usually used to store private
keys which are trusted by definition. For this reason the issue was assessed
as Moderate severity.

The FIPS modules in 3.6, 3.5 and 3.4 are not affected by this issue, as
PKCS#12 processing is outside the OpenSSL FIPS module boundary.

OpenSSL 3.6, 3.5 and 3.4 are vulnerable to this issue.

OpenSSL 3.3, 3.0, 1.1.1 and 1.0.2 are not affected by this issue as they do
not support PBMAC1 in PKCS#12.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15467 | Stack buffer overflow in CMS AuthEnvelopedData parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15467</link><description>Issue summary: Parsing CMS AuthEnvelopedData message with maliciously
crafted AEAD parameters can trigger a stack buffer overflow.

Impact summary: A stack buffer overflow may lead to a crash, causing Denial
of Service, or potentially remote code execution.

When parsing CMS AuthEnvelopedData structures that use AEAD ciphers such as
AES-GCM, the IV (Initialization Vector) encoded in the ASN.1 parameters is
copied into a fixed-size stack buffer without verifying that its length fits
the destination. An attacker can supply a crafted CMS message with an
oversized IV, causing a stack-based out-of-bounds write before any
authentication or tag verification occurs.

Applications and services that parse untrusted CMS or PKCS#7 content using
AEAD ciphers (e.g., S/MIME AuthEnvelopedData with AES-GCM) are vulnerable.
Because the overflow occurs prior to authentication, no valid key material
is required to trigger it. While exploitability to remote code execution
depends on platform and toolchain mitigations, the stack-based write
primitive represents a severe risk.

The FIPS modules in 3.6, 3.5, 3.4, 3.3 and 3.0 are not affected by this
issue, as the CMS implementation is outside the OpenSSL FIPS module
boundary.

OpenSSL 3.6, 3.5, 3.4, 3.3 and 3.0 are vulnerable to this issue.

OpenSSL 1.1.1 and 1.0.2 are not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15468 | NULL dereference in SSL_CIPHER_find() function on unknown cipher ID</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15468</link><description>Issue summary: If an application using the SSL_CIPHER_find() function in
a QUIC protocol client or server receives an unknown cipher suite from
the peer, a NULL dereference occurs.

Impact summary: A NULL pointer dereference leads to abnormal termination of
the running process causing Denial of Service.

Some applications call SSL_CIPHER_find() from the client_hello_cb callback
on the cipher ID received from the peer. If this is done with an SSL object
implementing the QUIC protocol, NULL pointer dereference will happen if
the examined cipher ID is unknown or unsupported.

As it is not very common to call this function in applications using the QUIC 
protocol and the worst outcome is Denial of Service, the issue was assessed
as Low severity.

The vulnerable code was introduced in the 3.2 version with the addition
of the QUIC protocol support.

The FIPS modules in 3.6, 3.5, 3.4 and 3.3 are not affected by this issue,
as the QUIC implementation is outside the OpenSSL FIPS module boundary.

OpenSSL 3.6, 3.5, 3.4 and 3.3 are vulnerable to this issue.

OpenSSL 3.0, 1.1.1 and 1.0.2 are not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15469 | &amp;#x27;openssl dgst&amp;#x27; one-shot codepath silently truncates inputs &amp;gt;16MB</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15469</link><description>Issue summary: The 'openssl dgst' command-line tool silently truncates input
data to 16MB when using one-shot signing algorithms and reports success instead
of an error.

Impact summary: A user signing or verifying files larger than 16MB with
one-shot algorithms (such as Ed25519, Ed448, or ML-DSA) may believe the entire
file is authenticated while trailing data beyond 16MB remains unauthenticated.

When the 'openssl dgst' command is used with algorithms that only support
one-shot signing (Ed25519, Ed448, ML-DSA-44, ML-DSA-65, ML-DSA-87), the input
is buffered with a 16MB limit. If the input exceeds this limit, the tool
silently truncates to the first 16MB and continues without signaling an error,
contrary to what the documentation states. This creates an integrity gap where
trailing bytes can be modified without detection if both signing and
verification are performed using the same affected codepath.

The issue affects only the command-line tool behavior. Verifiers that process
the full message using library APIs will reject the signature, so the risk
primarily affects workflows that both sign and verify with the affected
'openssl dgst' command. Streaming digest algorithms for 'openssl dgst' and
library users are unaffected.

The FIPS modules in 3.5 and 3.6 are not affected by this issue, as the
command-line tools are outside the OpenSSL FIPS module boundary.

OpenSSL 3.5 and 3.6 are vulnerable to this issue.

OpenSSL 3.4, 3.3, 3.0, 1.1.1 and 1.0.2 are not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66199 | TLS 1.3 CompressedCertificate excessive memory allocation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66199</link><description>Issue summary: A TLS 1.3 connection using certificate compression can be
forced to allocate a large buffer before decompression without checking
against the configured certificate size limit.

Impact summary: An attacker can cause per-connection memory allocations of
up to approximately 22 MiB and extra CPU work, potentially leading to
service degradation or resource exhaustion (Denial of Service).

In affected configurations, the peer-supplied uncompressed certificate
length from a CompressedCertificate message is used to grow a heap buffer
prior to decompression. This length is not bounded by the max_cert_list
setting, which otherwise constrains certificate message sizes. An attacker
can exploit this to cause large per-connection allocations followed by
handshake failure. No memory corruption or information disclosure occurs.

This issue only affects builds where TLS 1.3 certificate compression is
compiled in (i.e., not OPENSSL_NO_COMP_ALG) and at least one compression
algorithm (brotli, zlib, or zstd) is available, and where the compression
extension is negotiated. Both clients receiving a server CompressedCertificate
and servers in mutual TLS scenarios receiving a client CompressedCertificate
are affected. Servers that do not request client certificates are not
vulnerable to client-initiated attacks.

Users can mitigate this issue by setting SSL_OP_NO_RX_CERTIFICATE_COMPRESSION
to disable receiving compressed certificates.

The FIPS modules in 3.6, 3.5, 3.4 and 3.3 are not affected by this issue,
as the TLS implementation is outside the OpenSSL FIPS module boundary.

OpenSSL 3.6, 3.5, 3.4 and 3.3 are vulnerable to this issue.

OpenSSL 3.0, 1.1.1 and 1.0.2 are not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68160 | Heap out-of-bounds write in BIO_f_linebuffer on short writes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68160</link><description>Issue summary: Writing large, newline-free data into a BIO chain using the
line-buffering filter where the next BIO performs short writes can trigger
a heap-based out-of-bounds write.

Impact summary: This out-of-bounds write can cause memory corruption which
typically results in a crash, leading to Denial of Service for an application.

The line-buffering BIO filter (BIO_f_linebuffer) is not used by default in
TLS/SSL data paths. In OpenSSL command-line applications, it is typically
only pushed onto stdout/stderr on VMS systems. Third-party applications that
explicitly use this filter with a BIO chain that can short-write and that
write large, newline-free data influenced by an attacker would be affected.
However, the circumstances where this could happen are unlikely to be under
attacker control, and BIO_f_linebuffer is unlikely to be handling non-curated
data controlled by an attacker. For that reason the issue was assessed as
Low severity.

The FIPS modules in 3.6, 3.5, 3.4, 3.3 and 3.0 are not affected by this issue,
as the BIO implementation is outside the OpenSSL FIPS module boundary.

OpenSSL 3.6, 3.5, 3.4, 3.3, 3.0, 1.1.1 and 1.0.2 are vulnerable to this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69418 | Unauthenticated/unencrypted trailing bytes with low-level OCB function calls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69418</link><description>Issue summary: When using the low-level OCB API directly with AES-NI or&lt;br /&gt;other hardware-accelerated code paths, inputs whose length is not a multiple&lt;br /&gt;of 16 bytes can leave the final partial block unencrypted and unauthenticated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Impact summary: The trailing 1-15 bytes of a message may be exposed in&lt;br /&gt;cleartext on encryption and are not covered by the authentication tag,&lt;br /&gt;allowing an attacker to read or tamper with those bytes without detection.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The low-level OCB encrypt and decrypt routines in the hardware-accelerated&lt;br /&gt;stream path process full 16-byte blocks but do not advance the input/output&lt;br /&gt;pointers. The subsequent tail-handling code then operates on the original&lt;br /&gt;base pointers, effectively reprocessing the beginning of the buffer while&lt;br /&gt;leaving the actual trailing bytes unprocessed. The authentication checksum&lt;br /&gt;also excludes the true tail bytes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However, typical OpenSSL consumers using EVP are not affected because the&lt;br /&gt;higher-level EVP and provider OCB implementations split inputs so that full&lt;br /&gt;blocks and trailing partial blocks are processed in separate calls, avoiding&lt;br /&gt;the problematic code path. Additionally, TLS does not use OCB ciphersuites.&lt;br /&gt;The vulnerability only affects applications that call the low-level&lt;br /&gt;CRYPTO_ocb128_encrypt() or CRYPTO_ocb128_decrypt() functions directly with&lt;br /&gt;non-block-aligned lengths in a single call on hardware-accelerated builds.&lt;br /&gt;For these reasons the issue was assessed as Low severity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The FIPS modules in 3.6, 3.5, 3.4, 3.3, 3.2, 3.1 and 3.0 are not affected&lt;br /&gt;by this issue, as OCB mode is not a FIPS-approved algorithm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OpenSSL 3.6, 3.5, 3.4, 3.3, 3.0 and 1.1.1 are vulnerable to this issue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OpenSSL 1.0.2 is not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69419 | Out of bounds write in PKCS12_get_friendlyname() UTF-8 conversion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69419</link><description>Issue summary: Calling PKCS12_get_friendlyname() function on a maliciously
crafted PKCS#12 file with a BMPString (UTF-16BE) friendly name containing
non-ASCII BMP code point can trigger a one byte write before the allocated
buffer.

Impact summary: The out-of-bounds write can cause a memory corruption
which can have various consequences including a Denial of Service.

The OPENSSL_uni2utf8() function performs a two-pass conversion of a PKCS#12
BMPString (UTF-16BE) to UTF-8. In the second pass, when emitting UTF-8 bytes,
the helper function bmp_to_utf8() incorrectly forwards the remaining UTF-16
source byte count as the destination buffer capacity to UTF8_putc(). For BMP
code points above U+07FF, UTF-8 requires three bytes, but the forwarded
capacity can be just two bytes. UTF8_putc() then returns -1, and this negative
value is added to the output length without validation, causing the
length to become negative. The subsequent trailing NUL byte is then written
at a negative offset, causing write outside of heap allocated buffer.

The vulnerability is reachable via the public PKCS12_get_friendlyname() API
when parsing attacker-controlled PKCS#12 files. While PKCS12_parse() uses a
different code path that avoids this issue, PKCS12_get_friendlyname() directly
invokes the vulnerable function. Exploitation requires an attacker to provide
a malicious PKCS#12 file to be parsed by the application and the attacker
can just trigger a one zero byte write before the allocated buffer.
For that reason the issue was assessed as Low severity according to our
Security Policy.

The FIPS modules in 3.6, 3.5, 3.4, 3.3 and 3.0 are not affected by this issue,
as the PKCS#12 implementation is outside the OpenSSL FIPS module boundary.

OpenSSL 3.6, 3.5, 3.4, 3.3, 3.0 and 1.1.1 are vulnerable to this issue.

OpenSSL 1.0.2 is not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69420 | Missing ASN1_TYPE validation in TS_RESP_verify_response() function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69420</link><description>Issue summary: A type confusion vulnerability exists in the TimeStamp Response
verification code where an ASN1_TYPE union member is accessed without first
validating the type, causing an invalid or NULL pointer dereference when
processing a malformed TimeStamp Response file.

Impact summary: An application calling TS_RESP_verify_response() with a
malformed TimeStamp Response can be caused to dereference an invalid or
NULL pointer when reading, resulting in a Denial of Service.

The functions ossl_ess_get_signing_cert() and ossl_ess_get_signing_cert_v2()
access the signing cert attribute value without validating its type.
When the type is not V_ASN1_SEQUENCE, this results in accessing invalid memory
through the ASN1_TYPE union, causing a crash.

Exploiting this vulnerability requires an attacker to provide a malformed
TimeStamp Response to an application that verifies timestamp responses. The
TimeStamp protocol (RFC 3161) is not widely used and the impact of the
exploit is just a Denial of Service. For these reasons the issue was
assessed as Low severity.

The FIPS modules in 3.5, 3.4, 3.3 and 3.0 are not affected by this issue,
as the TimeStamp Response implementation is outside the OpenSSL FIPS module
boundary.

OpenSSL 3.6, 3.5, 3.4, 3.3, 3.0 and 1.1.1 are vulnerable to this issue.

OpenSSL 1.0.2 is not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69421 | NULL Pointer Dereference in PKCS12_item_decrypt_d2i_ex function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69421</link><description>Issue summary: Processing a malformed PKCS#12 file can trigger a NULL pointer
dereference in the PKCS12_item_decrypt_d2i_ex() function.

Impact summary: A NULL pointer dereference can trigger a crash which leads to
Denial of Service for an application processing PKCS#12 files.

The PKCS12_item_decrypt_d2i_ex() function does not check whether the oct
parameter is NULL before dereferencing it. When called from
PKCS12_unpack_p7encdata() with a malformed PKCS#12 file, this parameter can
be NULL, causing a crash. The vulnerability is limited to Denial of Service
and cannot be escalated to achieve code execution or memory disclosure.

Exploiting this issue requires an attacker to provide a malformed PKCS#12 file
to an application that processes it. For that reason the issue was assessed as
Low severity according to our Security Policy.

The FIPS modules in 3.6, 3.5, 3.4, 3.3 and 3.0 are not affected by this issue,
as the PKCS#12 implementation is outside the OpenSSL FIPS module boundary.

OpenSSL 3.6, 3.5, 3.4, 3.3, 3.0, 1.1.1 and 1.0.2 are vulnerable to this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69565 | code-projects Mobile Shop Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to File Upload in /ExAddProduct.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69565</link><description>code-projects Mobile Shop Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to File Upload in /ExAddProduct.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22795 | Missing ASN1_TYPE validation in PKCS#12 parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22795</link><description>Issue summary: An invalid or NULL pointer dereference can happen in
an application processing a malformed PKCS#12 file.

Impact summary: An application processing a malformed PKCS#12 file can be
caused to dereference an invalid or NULL pointer on memory read, resulting
in a Denial of Service.

A type confusion vulnerability exists in PKCS#12 parsing code where
an ASN1_TYPE union member is accessed without first validating the type,
causing an invalid pointer read.

The location is constrained to a 1-byte address space, meaning any
attempted pointer manipulation can only target addresses between 0x00 and 0xFF.
This range corresponds to the zero page, which is unmapped on most modern
operating systems and will reliably result in a crash, leading only to a
Denial of Service. Exploiting this issue also requires a user or application
to process a maliciously crafted PKCS#12 file. It is uncommon to accept
untrusted PKCS#12 files in applications as they are usually used to store
private keys which are trusted by definition. For these reasons, the issue
was assessed as Low severity.

The FIPS modules in 3.5, 3.4, 3.3 and 3.0 are not affected by this issue,
as the PKCS12 implementation is outside the OpenSSL FIPS module boundary.

OpenSSL 3.6, 3.5, 3.4, 3.3, 3.0 and 1.1.1 are vulnerable to this issue.

OpenSSL 1.0.2 is not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22796 | ASN1_TYPE Type Confusion in the PKCS7_digest_from_attributes() function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22796</link><description>Issue summary: A type confusion vulnerability exists in the signature
verification of signed PKCS#7 data where an ASN1_TYPE union member is
accessed without first validating the type, causing an invalid or NULL
pointer dereference when processing malformed PKCS#7 data.

Impact summary: An application performing signature verification of PKCS#7
data or calling directly the PKCS7_digest_from_attributes() function can be
caused to dereference an invalid or NULL pointer when reading, resulting in
a Denial of Service.

The function PKCS7_digest_from_attributes() accesses the message digest attribute
value without validating its type. When the type is not V_ASN1_OCTET_STRING,
this results in accessing invalid memory through the ASN1_TYPE union, causing
a crash.

Exploiting this vulnerability requires an attacker to provide a malformed
signed PKCS#7 to an application that verifies it. The impact of the
exploit is just a Denial of Service, the PKCS7 API is legacy and applications
should be using the CMS API instead. For these reasons the issue was
assessed as Low severity.

The FIPS modules in 3.5, 3.4, 3.3 and 3.0 are not affected by this issue,
as the PKCS#7 parsing implementation is outside the OpenSSL FIPS module
boundary.

OpenSSL 3.6, 3.5, 3.4, 3.3, 3.0, 1.1.1 and 1.0.2 are vulnerable to this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24868 | Mitigation bypass in the Privacy: Anti-Tracking component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24868</link><description>Mitigation bypass in the Privacy: Anti-Tracking component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24869 | Use-after-free in the Layout: Scrolling and Overflow component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24869</link><description>Use-after-free in the Layout: Scrolling and Overflow component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28162 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in libpng 1.6.43-1.6.46 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the pngimage with AddressSani...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28162</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in libpng 1.6.43-1.6.46 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the pngimage with AddressSanitizer (ASan), the program leaks memory in various locations, eventually leading to high memory usage and causing the program to become unresponsive</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68670 | xrdp improperly checks bounds of domain string length, which leads to Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68670</link><description>xrdp is an open source RDP server. xrdp before v0.10.5 contains an unauthenticated stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability. The issue stems from improper bounds checking when processing user domain information during the connection sequence. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on the target system. The vulnerability allows an attacker to overwrite the stack buffer and the return address, which could theoretically be used to redirect the execution flow. The impact of this vulnerability is lessened if a compiler flag has been used to build the xrdp executable with stack canary protection. If this is the case, a second vulnerability would need to be used to leak the stack canary value. Upgrade to version 0.10.5 to receive a patch. Additionally, do not rely on stack canary protection on production systems.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24870 | Information disclosure in ixray-1.6-stcop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24870</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in ixray-team ixray-1.6-stcop.This issue affects ixray-1.6-stcop: before 1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24871 | Code injection in Minecraft-Rcon-Manage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24871</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in pilgrimage233 Minecraft-Rcon-Manage.This issue affects Minecraft-Rcon-Manage: before 3.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24872 | Pointer arithmetic error in SkyFire_548</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24872</link><description>improper pointer arithmetic

 vulnerability in ProjectSkyfire SkyFire_548.This issue affects SkyFire_548: before 5.4.8-stable5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24873 | Out-of-bounds read in lpp-vita</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24873</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in Rinnegatamante lpp-vita.This issue affects lpp-vita: before lpp-vita r6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24874 | Type confusion in xray-monolith</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24874</link><description>Access of Resource Using Incompatible Type ('Type Confusion') vulnerability in themrdemonized xray-monolith.This issue affects xray-monolith: before 2025.12.30.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24875 | Integer overflow in modizer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24875</link><description>Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in yoyofr modizer.This issue affects modizer: before 4.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55095 | The function _ux_host_class_storage_media_mount() is responsible for mounting partitions on a USB mass storage device. When it encounters an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55095</link><description>The function _ux_host_class_storage_media_mount() is responsible for mounting partitions on a USB mass storage device. When it encounters an extended partition entry in the partition table, it recursively calls itself to mount the next logical partition.

This recursion occurs in _ux_host_class_storage_partition_read(), which parses up to four partition entries. If an extended partition is found (with type UX_HOST_CLASS_STORAGE_PARTITION_EXTENDED or EXTENDED_LBA_MAPPED), the code invokes:
            _ux_host_class_storage_media_mount(storage, sector + _ux_utility_long_get(...));


There is no limit on the recursion depth or tracking of visited sectors. As a result, a malicious or malformed disk image can include cyclic or excessively deep chains of extended partitions, causing the function to recurse until stack overflow occurs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0648 | The vulnerability stems from an incorrect error-checking logic in the CreateCounter() function (in threadx/utility/rtos_compatibility_layers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0648</link><description>The vulnerability stems from an incorrect error-checking logic in the CreateCounter() function (in threadx/utility/rtos_compatibility_layers/OSEK/tx_osek.c) when handling the return value of osek_get_counter(). Specifically, the current code checks if cntr_id equals 0u to determine failure, but @osek_get_counter() actually returns E_OS_SYS_STACK (defined as 12U) when it fails. This mismatch causes the error branch to never execute even when the counter pool is exhausted.

As a result, when the counter pool is depleted, the code proceeds to cast the error code (12U) to a pointer (OSEK_COUNTER *), creating a wild pointer. Subsequent writes to members of this pointer lead to writes to illegal memory addresses (e.g., 0x0000000C), which can trigger immediate HardFaults or silent memory corruption.

This vulnerability poses significant risks, including potential denial-of-service attacks (via repeated calls to exhaust the counter pool) and unauthorized memory access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24831 | Infinite loop (DoS) in ixray-1.6-stcop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24831</link><description>Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in ixray-team ixray-1.6-stcop.This issue affects ixray-1.6-stcop: before 1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24832 | Out-of-bounds write in ixray-1.6-stcop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24832</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in ixray-team ixray-1.6-stcop.This issue affects ixray-1.6-stcop: before 1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36938 | WinAVR Version 20100110 - Insecure Folder Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36938</link><description>WinAVR version 20100110 contains an insecure permissions vulnerability that allows authenticated users to modify system files and executables. Attackers can leverage the overly permissive access controls to potentially modify critical DLLs and executable files in the WinAVR installation directory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36939 | Cassandra Web 0.5.0 - Remote File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36939</link><description>Cassandra Web 0.5.0 contains a directory traversal vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files by manipulating path traversal parameters. Attackers can exploit the disabled Rack::Protection module to read sensitive system files like /etc/passwd and retrieve Apache Cassandra database credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36940 | Easy CD &amp;amp; DVD Cover Creator 4.13 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36940</link><description>Easy CD &amp; DVD Cover Creator 4.13 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the serial number input field that allows attackers to crash the application. Attackers can generate a 6000-byte payload and paste it into the serial number field to trigger an application crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36941 | Knockpy 4.1.1 - CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36941</link><description>Knockpy 4.1.1 contains a CSV injection vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious formulas into CSV reports through unfiltered server headers. Attackers can manipulate server response headers to include spreadsheet formulas that will execute when the CSV is opened in spreadsheet applications.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36942 | Victor CMS 1.0 - File Upload To RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36942</link><description>Victor CMS 1.0 contains a file upload vulnerability that allows authenticated users to upload malicious PHP files through the profile image upload feature. Attackers can upload a PHP shell to the /img directory and execute system commands by accessing the uploaded file via web browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36946 | SyncBreeze 10.0.28 - &amp;#x27;login&amp;#x27; Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36946</link><description>SyncBreeze 10.0.28 contains a denial of service vulnerability in the login endpoint that allows remote attackers to crash the service. Attackers can send an oversized payload in the login request to overwhelm the application and potentially disrupt service availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36947 | LibreNMS 1.46 - MAC Accounting Graph Authenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36947</link><description>LibreNMS 1.46 contains an authenticated SQL injection vulnerability in the MAC accounting graph endpoint that allows remote attackers to extract database information. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability by manipulating the 'sort' parameter with crafted SQL injection techniques to retrieve sensitive database contents through time-based blind SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36948 | VestaCP 0.9.8-26 - &amp;#x27;LoginAs&amp;#x27; Insufficient Session Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36948</link><description>VestaCP 0.9.8-26 contains a session token vulnerability in the LoginAs module that allows remote attackers to manipulate authentication tokens. Attackers can exploit insufficient token validation to access user accounts and perform unauthorized login requests without proper administrative permissions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36949 | TapinRadio 2.13.7 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36949</link><description>TapinRadio 2.13.7 contains a denial of service vulnerability in the application proxy settings that allows attackers to crash the program by overflowing input fields. Attackers can paste a large buffer of 20,000 characters into the username and address fields to cause the application to become unresponsive and require reinstallation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36950 | Laravel Nova 3.7.0 - &amp;#x27;range&amp;#x27; DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36950</link><description>Laravel Nova 3.7.0 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows authenticated users to crash the application by manipulating the 'range' parameter. Attackers can send simultaneous requests with an extremely high range value to overwhelm and crash the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36951 | Phpscript-sgh 0.1.0 - Time Based Blind SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36951</link><description>Phpscript-sgh 0.1.0 contains a time-based blind SQL injection vulnerability in the admin interface that allows attackers to manipulate database queries through the 'id' parameter. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by crafting malicious payloads that trigger time delays, enabling them to extract sensitive database information through conditional sleep techniques.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47900 | Gila CMS &amp;lt; 2.0.0 - Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47900</link><description>Gila CMS versions prior to 2.0.0 contain a remote code execution vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary system commands through manipulated HTTP headers. Attackers can inject PHP code in the User-Agent header with shell_exec() to run system commands by sending crafted requests to the admin endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47901 | dirsearch 0.4.1 - CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47901</link><description>Dirsearch 0.4.1 contains a CSV injection vulnerability when using the --csv-report flag that allows attackers to inject formulas through redirected endpoints. Attackers can craft malicious server redirects with comma-separated paths containing Excel formulas to manipulate the generated CSV report.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47902 | Testa Online Test Management System 3.4.7 - &amp;#x27;q&amp;#x27; SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47902</link><description>Testa Online Test Management System 3.4.7 contains a SQL injection vulnerability that allows attackers to manipulate database queries through the 'q' search parameter. Attackers can inject malicious SQL code in the search field to extract database information, potentially accessing sensitive user or system data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28164 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in libpng 1.6.43-1.6.46 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via png_create_read_struct() func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28164</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in libpng 1.6.43-1.6.46 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via png_create_read_struct() function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55102 | A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the NetX IPv6 component functionality of Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo. A specially crafted network p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55102</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the NetX IPv6 component functionality of Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo. A specially crafted network packet of "Packet Too Big" with more than 15 different source address can lead to denial of service. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1489 | Glib: glib: memory corruption via integer overflow in unicode case conversion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1489</link><description>A flaw was found in GLib. An integer overflow vulnerability in its Unicode case conversion implementation can lead to memory corruption. By processing specially crafted and extremely large Unicode strings, an attacker could trigger an undersized memory allocation, resulting in out-of-bounds writes. This could cause applications utilizing GLib for string conversion to crash or become unstable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1470 | Authenticated users can bypass the Expression sandbox mechanism to achieve full remote code execution on n8n’s main node.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1470</link><description>n8n contains a critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in its workflow Expression evaluation system. Expressions supplied by authenticated users during workflow configuration may be evaluated in an execution context that is not sufficiently isolated from the underlying runtime.

An authenticated attacker could abuse this behavior to execute arbitrary code with the privileges of the n8n process. Successful exploitation may lead to full compromise of the affected instance, including unauthorized access to sensitive data, modification of workflows, and execution of system-level operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:55:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1213 | Askbot 0.12.2 - Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1213</link><description>All versions of askbot before and including 0.12.2 allow an attacker authenticated with normal user permissions to modify the profile picture of other application users.This issue affects askbot: 0.12.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1484 | Glib: integer overflow leading to buffer underflow and out-of-bounds write in glib g_base64_encode()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1484</link><description>A flaw was found in the GLib Base64 encoding routine when processing very large input data. Due to incorrect use of integer types during length calculation, the library may miscalculate buffer boundaries. This can cause memory writes outside the allocated buffer. Applications that process untrusted or extremely large Base64 input using GLib may crash or behave unpredictably.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1485 | Glib: glib: local denial of service via buffer underflow in content type parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1485</link><description>A flaw was found in Glib's content type parsing logic. This buffer underflow vulnerability occurs because the length of a header line is stored in a signed integer, which can lead to integer wraparound for very large inputs. This results in pointer underflow and out-of-bounds memory access. Exploitation requires a local user to install or process a specially crafted treemagic file, which can lead to local denial of service or application instability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12386 | Missing Authentication for Critical Endpoint in Pix-Link LV-WR21Q</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12386</link><description>Pix-Link LV-WR21Q does not enforce any form of authentication for endpoint /goform/getHomePageInfo. Remote unauthenticated attacker is able to use this endpoint to e.g: retrieve cleartext password to the access point.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version V108_108 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12387 | Denial of Service in Pix-Link LV-WR21Q</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12387</link><description>A vulnerability in the Pix-Link LV-WR21Q router's language module allows remote attackers to trigger a denial of service (DoS) by sending a specially crafted HTTP POST request containing non-existing language parameter. This renders the server unable to serve correct lang.js file, which causes administrator panel to not work, resulting in DoS until the language settings is reverted to a correct value. The Denial of Service affects only the administrator panel and does not affect other router functionalities.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version V108_108 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41728 | Beckhoff: Information leak via Beckhoff Device Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41728</link><description>A low privileged remote attacker may be able to disclose confidential information from the memory of a privileged process by sending specially crafted calls to the Device Manager web service that cause an out-of-bounds read operation under certain circumstances due to ASLR and thereby potentially copy confidential information into a response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41726 | Beckhoff: Arbitrary code execution within privileged processes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41726</link><description>A low privileged remote attacker can execute arbitrary code by sending specially crafted calls to the web service of the Device Manager or locally via an API and can cause integer overflows which then may lead to arbitrary code execution within privileged processes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41727 | Beckhoff:  Performing privileged operations and gaining administrator access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41727</link><description>A local low privileged attacker can bypass the authentication of the Device Manager user interface, allowing them to perform privileged operations and gain administrator access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21417 | Dell CloudBoost Virtual Appliance, versions prior to 19.14.0.0, contains a Plaintext Storage of Password vulnerability. A high privileged at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21417</link><description>Dell CloudBoost Virtual Appliance, versions prior to 19.14.0.0, contains a Plaintext Storage of Password vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24347 | Arbitrary file write to /tmp directory in EZCast Pro II Dongle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24347</link><description>Improper input validation in Admin UI of EZCast Pro II version 1.17478.146 allows attackers to manipulate files in the /tmp directory</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24348 | Multiple cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in EZCast Pro II Dongle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24348</link><description>Multiple cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in Admin UI of EZCast Pro II version 1.17478.146 allow attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the browser of other Admin UI users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24830 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in IronOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24830</link><description>Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Ralim IronOS.This issue affects IronOS: before v2.23-rc2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1467 | Libsoup: libsoup: http header injection via specially crafted urls when an http proxy is configured</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1467</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup, an HTTP client library. This vulnerability, known as CRLF (Carriage Return Line Feed) Injection, occurs when an HTTP proxy is configured and the library improperly handles URL-decoded input used to create the Host header. A remote attacker can exploit this by providing a specially crafted URL containing CRLF sequences, allowing them to inject additional HTTP headers or complete HTTP request bodies. This can lead to unintended or unauthorized HTTP requests being forwarded by the proxy, potentially impacting downstream services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24345 | Cross-Site Request Forgery in EZCast Pro II Dongle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24345</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery in Admin UI of EZCast Pro II version 1.17478.146 allows attackers to bypass authorization checks and gain full access to the admin UI</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24346 | Use of well-known default credentials in EZCast Pro II Dongle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24346</link><description>Use of well-known default credentials in Admin UI of EZCast Pro II version 1.17478.146 allows attackers to access protected areas in the web application</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24826 | Out-of-bounds write in turso3d</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24826</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write, Divide By Zero, NULL Pointer Dereference, Use of Uninitialized Resource, Out-of-bounds Read, Reachable Assertion vulnerability in cadaver turso3d.This issue affects .</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24827 | Out-of-bounds write in Commander-Genius</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24827</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in gerstrong Commander-Genius.This issue affects Commander-Genius: before Release refs/pull/358/merge.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24828 | Memory leak in is-Engine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24828</link><description>Missing Release of Memory after Effective Lifetime vulnerability in Is-Daouda is-Engine.This issue affects is-Engine: before 3.3.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24829 | Out-of-bounds write in is-Engine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24829</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write, Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Is-Daouda is-Engine.This issue affects is-Engine: before 3.3.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21720 | Unauthenticated DoS: avatar cache leaks goroutines when /avatar/:hash requests time out</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21720</link><description>Every uncached /avatar/:hash request spawns a goroutine that refreshes the Gravatar image. If the refresh sits in the 10-slot worker queue longer than three seconds, the handler times out and stops listening for the result, so that goroutine blocks forever trying to send on an unbuffered channel. Sustained traffic with random hashes keeps tripping this timeout, so goroutine count grows linearly, eventually exhausting memory and causing Grafana to crash on some systems.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21721 | Dashboard Permissions Scope Bypass Enables Cross‑Dashboard Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21721</link><description>The dashboard permissions API does not verify the target dashboard scope and only checks the dashboards.permissions:* action. As a result, a user who has permission management rights on one dashboard can read and modify permissions on other dashboards. This is an organization‑internal privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24344 | Multiple Buffer Overflows in EZCast Pro II Dongle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24344</link><description>Multiple Buffer Overflows in Admin UI of EZCast Pro II version 1.17478.146 allow attackers to cause a program crash and potential remote code execution</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24821 | A heap-based buffer over-read that might affect a system that compiles untrusted Lua code in turanszkij/WickedEngine.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24821</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in turanszkij WickedEngine (WickedEngine/LUA modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files lparser.C.

This issue affects WickedEngine: through 0.71.727.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24822 | a heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in ttttupup/wxhelper via src/mongoose.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24822</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write, Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in ttttupup wxhelper (src modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files mongoose.C.

This issue affects wxhelper: through 3.9.10.19-v1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24823 | A heap-based buffer over-read or buffer overflow vulnerability in FASTSHIFT/X-TRACK</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24823</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write, Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in FASTSHIFT X-TRACK (Software/X-Track/USER/App/Utils/lv_img_png/PNGdec/src modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files inflate.C.

This issue affects X-TRACK: through v2.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24824 | A XSS in yacy/yacy_search_server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24824</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in yacy yacy_search_server (source/net/yacy/http/servlets modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files YaCyDefaultServlet.Java.

This issue affects yacy_search_server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24825 | a memory leak in ydb-platform/ydb with use of yajl_tree_parse function from src/yail module, which will cause out-of-memory in server and cause crash.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24825</link><description>Missing Release of Memory after Effective Lifetime vulnerability in ydb-platform ydb (contrib/libs/yajl modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files yail_tree.C.

This issue affects ydb: through 24.4.4.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24807 | Buffer Overflow Vulnerability in liuyueyi/quick-media</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24807</link><description>Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature vulnerability in liuyueyi quick-media (plugins/svg-plugin/batik-codec-fix/src/main/java/org/apache/batik/ext/awt/image/codec/util modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files SeekableOutputStream.Java.

This issue affects quick-media: before v1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24808 | A  possible integer overflow vulnerability in RawTherapee/RawTherapee</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24808</link><description>Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in RawTherapee (rtengine modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files dcraw.Cc.

This issue affects RawTherapee: through 5.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24809 | Save stack space while handling errors in praydog/REFramework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24809</link><description>An issue from the component luaG_runerror in dependencies/lua/src/ldebug.c in praydog/REFramework version before 1.5.5 leads to a heap-buffer overflow when a recursive error occurs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24810 | A buffer overflow in rethinkdb/rethinkdb</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24810</link><description>Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in rethinkdb (src/cjson modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files cJSON.Cc.

This issue affects rethinkdb: through v2.4.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24811 | An improper pointer arithmetic in root-project/root at builtins/zlib/inffast.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24811</link><description>Vulnerability in root-project root (builtins/zlib modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files inffast.C.

This issue affects root.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24812 | An improper pointer arithmetic in root-project/root at builtins/zlib/inftrees.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24812</link><description>Vulnerability in root-project root (builtins/zlib modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files inftrees.C.

This issue affects root: through 6.36.00-rc1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24813 | A null pointer dereference in abcz316/SKRoot-linuxKernelRoot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24813</link><description>NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in abcz316 SKRoot-linuxKernelRoot (testRoot/jni/utils modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files cJSON.Cpp.

This issue affects SKRoot-linuxKernelRoot.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24814 | A integer overflow in swoole/swoole-src</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24814</link><description>Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in swoole swoole-src (thirdparty/hiredis modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files sds.C.

This issue affects swoole-src: before 6.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24815 | A XStream Security Vulnerability in XML Deserialization in datavane/tis</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24815</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type, Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in datavane tis (tis-plugin/src/main/java/com/qlangtech/tis/extension/impl modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files XmlFile.Java.

This issue affects tis: before v4.3.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24816 | Cookie Security Vulnerabilities in datavane/tis</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24816</link><description>Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in datavane tis (tis-console/src/main/java/com/qlangtech/tis/runtime/module/action modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files ChangeDomainAction.Java.

This issue affects tis: before v4.3.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24817 | A potential heap-buffer overflow in praydog/UEVR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24817</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in praydog UEVR (dependencies/lua/src modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files ldebug.C, lvm.C.

This issue affects UEVR: before 1.05.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24818 | A heap-based buffer over-read that might affect a system that compiles untrusted Lua code in praydog/UEVR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24818</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in praydog UEVR (dependencies/lua/src modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files lparser.C.

This issue affects UEVR: before 1.05.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24819 | An out-of-memory (OOM) issue in foxinmy/weixin4j</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24819</link><description>Improperly Controlled Sequential Memory Allocation vulnerability in foxinmy weixin4j (weixin4j-base/src/main/java/com/foxinmy/weixin4j/util modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files CharArrayBuffer.Java, ClassUtil.Java.

This issue affects weixin4j.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24820 | A stack overflow vulnerability in turanszkij/WickedEngine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24820</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in turanszkij WickedEngine (WickedEngine/LUA modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files ldebug.C.

This issue affects WickedEngine: before 0.71.705.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24798 | An Uninitialized stack variable vulnerability in GaijinEntertainment/DagorEngine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24798</link><description>Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer vulnerability in GaijinEntertainment DagorEngine (prog/3rdPartyLibs/miniupnpc modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files upnpreplyparse.C.

This issue affects DagorEngine: through dagor_2025_01_15.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24799 | A heap-based buffer over-read or buffer overflow in davisking/dlib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24799</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write, Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in davisking dlib (dlib/external/zlib modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files inflate.C.

This issue affects dlib: before v19.24.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24800 | A heap-based buffer over-read or buffer overflow in tildearrow/furnace</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24800</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write, Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in tildearrow furnace (extern/zlib modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files inflate.C.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24801 | A Potential SPA-vulnerability in Ralim/IronOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24801</link><description>Vulnerability in Ralim IronOS (source/Core/BSP/Pinecilv2/bl_mcu_sdk/components/ble/ble_stack/common/tinycrypt/source modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files ecc_dsa.C.

This issue affects IronOS: before v2.23-rc3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24802 | Buffer Overflow Vulnerability in briandilley/jsonrpc4j</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24802</link><description>Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in briandilley jsonrpc4j (src/main/java/com/googlecode/jsonrpc4j modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files NoCloseOutputStream.Java.

This issue affects jsonrpc4j: through 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24803 | A possible infinite loop vulnerability in coolsnowwolf/lede</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24803</link><description>Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in coolsnowwolf lede (package/lean/mt/drivers/mt7615d/src/mt_wifi/embedded/security modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files bn_lib.C.

This issue affects lede: through r25.10.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24804 | A infinite loop vulnerability in coolsnowwolf/lede</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24804</link><description>Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in coolsnowwolf lede (package/lean/mt/drivers/mt7603e/src/mt7603_wifi/common modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files bn_lib.C.

This issue affects lede: through r25.10.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24805 | Mishandles certain out-of-memory conditions in visualfc/liteide via liteidex/src/3rdparty/libvterm/src module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24805</link><description>NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in visualfc liteide (liteidex/src/3rdparty/libvterm/src modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files screen.C, state.C, vterm.C.

This issue affects liteide: before x38.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24806 | Buffer Write Security Vulnerability in liuyueyi/quick-media</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24806</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in liuyueyi quick-media (plugins/svg-plugin/batik-codec-fix/src/main/java/org/apache/batik/ext/awt/image/codec/png modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files PNGImageEncoder.Java.

This issue affects quick-media: before v1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:05:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1464 | A  possible integer overflow vulnerability in RawTherapee/RawTherapee</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1464</link><description>Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in MuntashirAkon AppManager (app/src/main/java/org/apache/commons/compress/archivers/tar modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files TarUtils.Java.

This issue affects AppManager: before 4.0.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:43:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1465 | A heap-based buffer over-read or buffer overflow in tildearrow/furnace</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1465</link><description>Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer vulnerability in anyrtcIO-Community anyRTC-RTMP-OpenSource (third_party/faad2-2.7/libfaad modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files bits.C, syntax.C.

This issue affects anyRTC-RTMP-OpenSource: before 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24793 | A heap-based buffer over-read or buffer overflow vulnerability in azerothcore/azerothcore-wotlk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24793</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write, Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in azerothcore azerothcore-wotlk (deps/zlib modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files inflate.C.

This issue affects azerothcore-wotlk: through v4.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24794 | Chunk Unloading Security Vulnerability in CardboardPowered/cardboard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24794</link><description>Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer vulnerability in CardboardPowered cardboard (src/main/java/org/cardboardpowered/impl/world modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files WorldImpl.Java.

This issue affects cardboard: before 1.21.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24795 | An Out-of-bounds Write in CloverHackyColor/CloverBootloader</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24795</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in CloverHackyColor CloverBootloader (MdeModulePkg/Universal/RegularExpressionDxe/Oniguruma modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files regcomp.C.

This issue affects CloverBootloader: before 5162.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:43:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24796 | A Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in CloverHackyColor/CloverBootloader</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24796</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in CloverHackyColor CloverBootloader (MdeModulePkg/Universal/RegularExpressionDxe/Oniguruma modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files regparse.C.

This issue affects CloverBootloader: before 5162.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:43:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24797 | An out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check in neka-nat/cupoch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24797</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in neka-nat cupoch (third_party/libjpeg-turbo/libjpeg-turbo modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files tjbench.C.

This issue affects cupoch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:43:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14971 | Link Invoice Payment for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.8.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Partial Payment Creation/Cancellation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14971</link><description>The Link Invoice Payment for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the createPartialPayment and cancelPartialPayment functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create partial payments on any order or cancel any existing partial payment via ID enumeration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21408 | beat-access for Windows version 3.0.3 and prior contains an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to insecurely loading Dynamic Lin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21408</link><description>beat-access for Windows version 3.0.3 and prior contains an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to insecurely loading Dynamic Link Libraries. As a result, arbitrary code may be executed with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 05:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1361 | ASDA-Soft Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1361</link><description>ASDA-Soft Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24479 | HUSTOJ has Arbitrary File Write (Zip Slip) in Problem Import Modules that leads to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24479</link><description>HUSTOF is an open source online judge based on PHP/C++/MySQL/Linux for ACM/ICPC and NOIP training. Prior to version 26.01.24, the problem_import_qduoj.php and problem_import_hoj.php modules fail to properly sanitize filenames within uploaded ZIP archives. Attackers can craft a malicious ZIP file containing files with path traversal sequences (e.g., ../../shell.php). When extracted by the server, this allows writing files to arbitrary locations in the web root, leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE). Version 26.01.24 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:10:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24480 | QGIS had validated RCE and Repository Takeover via GitHub Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24480</link><description>QGIS is a free, open source, cross platform geographical information system (GIS) The repository contains a GitHub Actions workflow called "pre-commit checks" that, before commit 76a693cd91650f9b4e83edac525e5e4f90d954e9, was vulnerable to remote code execution and repository compromise because it used the `pull_request_target` trigger and then checked out and executed untrusted pull request code in a privileged context. Workflows triggered by `pull_request_target` ran with the base repository's credentials and access to secrets. If these workflows then checked out and executed code from the head of an external pull request (which could have been attacker controlled), the attacker could have executed arbitrary commands with elevated privileges. This insecure pattern has been documented as a security risk by GitHub and security researchers. Commit 76a693cd91650f9b4e83edac525e5e4f90d954e9 removed the vulnerable code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24486 | Python-Multipart has Arbitrary File Write via Non-Default Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24486</link><description>Python-Multipart is a streaming multipart parser for Python. Prior to version 0.0.22, a Path Traversal vulnerability exists when using non-default configuration options `UPLOAD_DIR` and `UPLOAD_KEEP_FILENAME=True`. An attacker can write uploaded files to arbitrary locations on the filesystem by crafting a malicious filename. Users should upgrade to version 0.0.22 to receive a patch or, as a workaround, avoid using `UPLOAD_KEEP_FILENAME=True` in project configurations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24489 | Gakido vulnerable to HTTP Header Injection (CRLF Injection)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24489</link><description>Gakido is a Python HTTP client focused on browser impersonation and anti-bot evasion. A vulnerability was discovered in Gakido prior to version 0.1.1 that allowed HTTP header injection through CRLF (Carriage Return Line Feed) sequences in user-supplied header values and names. When making HTTP requests with user-controlled header values containing `\r\n` (CRLF), `\n` (LF), or `\x00` (null byte) characters, an attacker could inject arbitrary HTTP headers into the request. The fix in version 0.1.1 adds a `_sanitize_header()` function that strips `\r`, `\n`, and `\x00` characters from both header names and values before they are included in HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24490 | MobSF has Stored XSS via Manifest Analysis - Dialer Code Host Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24490</link><description>MobSF is a mobile application security testing tool used. Prior to version 4.4.5, a Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MobSF's Android manifest analysis allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of a victim's browser session by uploading a malicious APK. The `android:host` attribute from `` elements is rendered in HTML reports without sanitization, enabling session hijacking and account takeover. Version 4.4.5 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:10:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24686 | go-tuf Path Traversal in TAP 4 Multirepo Client Allows Arbitrary File Write via Malicious Repository Names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24686</link><description>go-tuf is a Go implementation of The Update Framework (TUF). go-tuf's TAP 4 Multirepo Client uses the map file repository name string (`repoName`) as a filesystem path component when selecting the local metadata cache directory. Starting in version 2.0.0 and prior to version 2.4.1, if an application accepts a map file from an untrusted source, an attacker can supply a `repoName` containing traversal (e.g., `../escaped-repo`) and cause go-tuf to create directories and write the root metadata file outside the intended `LocalMetadataDir` cache base, within the running process's filesystem permissions. Version 2.4.1 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:10:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23683 | Missing Authorization check in SAP Fiori App (Intercompany Balance Reconciliation)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23683</link><description>SAP Fiori App Intercompany Balance Reconciliation does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. This has low impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:10:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1448 | D-Link DIR-615 Web Management wiz_policy_3_machine.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1448</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DIR-615 up to 4.10. This impacts an unknown function of the file /wiz_policy_3_machine.php of the component Web Management Interface. Performing a manipulation of the argument ipaddr results in os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1449 | Hisense TransTech Smart Bus Management System TireMng.aspx Page_Load sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1449</link><description>A flaw has been found in Hisense TransTech Smart Bus Management System up to 20260113. Affected is the function Page_Load of the file YZSoft/Forms/XForm/BM/BusComManagement/TireMng.aspx. Executing a manipulation of the argument key can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24478 | AnythingLLM vulnerable to Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24478</link><description>AnythingLLM is an application that turns pieces of content into context that any LLM can use as references during chatting. Prior to version 1.10.0, a critical Path Traversal vulnerability in the DrupalWiki integration allows a malicious admin (or an attacker who can convince an admin to configure a malicious DrupalWiki URL) to write arbitrary files to the server. This can lead to Remote Code Execution (RCE) by overwriting configuration files or writing executable scripts. Version 1.10.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24477 | AnythingLLM has key leak in `systemSettings.js`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24477</link><description>AnythingLLM is an application that turns pieces of content into context that any LLM can use as references during chatting. If AnythingLLM prior to version 1.10.0 is configured to use Qdrant as the vector database with an API key, this QdrantApiKey could be exposed in plain text to unauthenticated users via the `/api/setup-complete` endpoint. Leakage of QdrantApiKey allows an unauthenticated attacker full read/write access to the Qdrant vector database instance used by AnythingLLM. Since Qdrant often stores the core knowledge base for RAG in AnythingLLM, this can lead to complete compromise of the semantic search / retrieval functionality and indirect leakage of confidential uploaded documents. Version 1.10.0 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30248 | DLL hijacking in the WD Discovery Installer in Western Digital WD Discovery 5.2.730 on Windows allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30248</link><description>DLL hijacking in the WD Discovery Installer in Western Digital WD Discovery 5.2.730 on Windows allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via placement of a crafted dll in the installer's search path.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24470 | Skipper Ingress Controller Allows Unauthorized Access to Internal Services via ExternalName</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24470</link><description>Skipper is an HTTP router and reverse proxy for service composition. Prior to version 0.24.0, when running Skipper as an Ingress controller, users with permissions to create an Ingress and a Service of type ExternalName can create routes that enable them to use Skipper's network access to reach internal services. Version 0.24.0 disables Kubernetes ExternalName by default. As a workaround, developers can allow list targets of an ExternalName and allow list via regular expressions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24476 | Shaarli vulnerable to stored XSS via Suggested Tags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24476</link><description>Shaarli is a personal bookmarking service. Prior to version 0.16.0, crafting a malicious tag which starting with `"` prematurely ends the `&lt;input /&gt;` tag on the start page and allows an attacker to add arbitrary html leading to a possible XSS attack. Version 0.16.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24123 | BentoML has a Path Traversal via Bentofile Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24123</link><description>BentoML is a Python library for building online serving systems optimized for AI apps and model inference. Prior to version 1.4.34, BentoML's `bentofile.yaml` configuration allows path traversal attacks through multiple file path fields (`description`, `docker.setup_script`, `docker.dockerfile_template`, `conda.environment_yml`). An attacker can craft a malicious bentofile that, when built by a victim, exfiltrates arbitrary files from the filesystem into the bento archive. This enables supply chain attacks where sensitive files (SSH keys, credentials, environment variables) are silently embedded in bentos and exposed when pushed to registries or deployed. Version 1.4.34 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24400 | AssertJ has XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability when parsing untrusted XML via isXmlEqualTo assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24400</link><description>AssertJ provides Fluent testing assertions for Java and the Java Virtual Machine (JVM). Starting in version 1.4.0 and prior to version 3.27.7, an XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability exists in `org.assertj.core.util.xml.XmlStringPrettyFormatter`: the `toXmlDocument(String)` method initializes `DocumentBuilderFactory` with default settings, without disabling DTDs or external entities. This formatter is used by the `isXmlEqualTo(CharSequence)` assertion for `CharSequence` values. An application is vulnerable only when it uses untrusted XML input with either `isXmlEqualTo(CharSequence)` from `org.assertj.core.api.AbstractCharSequenceAssert` or `xmlPrettyFormat(String)` from `org.assertj.core.util.xml.XmlStringPrettyFormatter`. If untrusted XML input is processed by tone of these methods, an attacker couldnread arbitrary local files via `file://` URIs (e.g., `/etc/passwd`, application configuration files); perform Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via HTTP/HTTPS URIs, and/or cause Denial of Service via "Billion Laughs" entity expansion attacks. `isXmlEqualTo(CharSequence)` has been deprecated in favor of XMLUnit in version 3.18.0 and will be removed in version 4.0. Users of affected versions should, in order of preference: replace `isXmlEqualTo(CharSequence)` with XMLUnit, upgrade to version 3.27.7, or avoid using `isXmlEqualTo(CharSequence)` or `XmlStringPrettyFormatter` with untrusted input. `XmlStringPrettyFormatter` has historically been considered a utility for `isXmlEqualTo(CharSequence)` rather than a feature for AssertJ users, so it is deprecated in version 3.27.7 and removed in version 4.0, with no replacement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24408 | sigstore has CSRF possibility in OIDC authentication during signing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24408</link><description>sigstore-python is a Python tool for generating and verifying Sigstore signatures. Prior to version 4.2.0, the sigstore-python OAuth authentication flow is susceptible to Cross-Site Request Forgery. `_OAuthSession` creates a unique "state" and sends it as a parameter in the authentication request but the "state" in the server response seems not not be cross-checked with this value. Version 4.2.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1445 | iJason-Liu Books_Manager upload_bookCover.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1445</link><description>A vulnerability was found in iJason-Liu Books_Manager up to 298ba736387ca37810466349af13a0fdf828e99c. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file controllers/books_center/upload_bookCover.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument book_cover results in unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24003 | EvseV2G has sequence state validation bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24003</link><description>EVerest is an EV charging software stack. In versions up to and including 2025.12.1, it is possible to bypass the sequence state verification including authentication, and send requests that transition to forbidden states relative to the current one, thereby updating the current context with illegitimate data.cThanks to the modular design of EVerest, authorization is handled in a separate module and EVSEManager Charger internal state machine cannot transition out of the `WaitingForAuthentication` state through ISO 15118-2 communication. From this state, it was however possible through ISO 15118-2 messages which are published to the MQTT server to trick it into preparing to charge, and even to prepare to send current. The final requirement to actually send current to the EV was the closure of the contactors, which does not appear to be possible without leaving the `WaitingForAuthentication` state and leveraging ISO 15118-2 messages. As of time of publication, no fixed versions are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24131 | pnpm has Path Traversal via arbitrary file permission modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24131</link><description>pnpm is a package manager. Prior to version 10.28.2, when pnpm processes a package's `directories.bin` field, it uses `path.join()` without validating the result stays within the package root. A malicious npm package can specify `"directories": {"bin": "../../../../tmp"}` to escape the package directory, causing pnpm to chmod 755 files at arbitrary locations. This issue only affects Unix/Linux/macOS. Windows is not affected (`fixBin` gated by `EXECUTABLE_SHEBANG_SUPPORTED`). Version 10.28.2 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24056 | pnpm has symlink traversal in file:/git dependencies</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24056</link><description>pnpm is a package manager. Prior to version 10.28.2, when pnpm installs a `file:` (directory) or `git:` dependency, it follows symlinks and reads their target contents without constraining them to the package root. A malicious package containing a symlink to an absolute path (e.g., `/etc/passwd`, `~/.ssh/id_rsa`) causes pnpm to copy that file's contents into `node_modules`, leaking local data. The vulnerability only affects `file:` and `git:` dependencies. Registry packages (npm) have symlinks stripped during publish and are NOT affected. The issue impacts developers installing local/file dependencies andCI/CD pipelines installing git dependencies. It can lead to credential theft via symlinks to `~/.aws/credentials`, `~/.npmrc`, `~/.ssh/id_rsa`. Version 10.28.2 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:19:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23889 | pnpm has Windows-specific tarball Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23889</link><description>pnpm is a package manager. Prior to version 10.28.1, a path traversal vulnerability in pnpm's tarball extraction allows malicious packages to write files outside the package directory on Windows. The path normalization only checks for `./` but not `.\`. On Windows, backslashes are directory separators, enabling path traversal. This vulnerability is Windows-only. This issue impacts Windows pnpm users, Windows CI/CD pipelines (GitHub Actions Windows runners, Azure DevOps), and those who can overwrite `.npmrc`, build configs, or other files. Version 10.28.1 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23890 | pnpm scoped bin name Path Traversal allows arbitrary file creation outside node_modules/.bin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23890</link><description>pnpm is a package manager. Prior to version 10.28.1, a path traversal vulnerability in pnpm's bin linking allows malicious npm packages to create executable shims or symlinks outside of `node_modules/.bin`. Bin names starting with `@` bypass validation, and after scope normalization, path traversal sequences like `../../` remain intact. This issue affects all pnpm users who install npm packages, CI/CD pipelines using pnpm, and those who can overwrite config files, scripts, or other sensitive files. Version 10.28.1 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59471 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in self-hosted Next.js applications that have `remotePatterns` configured for the Image Optimizer. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59471</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in self-hosted Next.js applications that have `remotePatterns` configured for the Image Optimizer. The image optimization endpoint (`/_next/image`) loads external images entirely into memory without enforcing a maximum size limit, allowing an attacker to cause out-of-memory conditions by requesting optimization of arbitrarily large images. This vulnerability requires that `remotePatterns` is configured to allow image optimization from external domains and that the attacker can serve or control a large image on an allowed domain.

Strongly consider upgrading to 15.5.10 or 16.1.5 to reduce risk and prevent availability issues in Next applications.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59472 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in Next.js versions with Partial Prerendering (PPR) enabled when running in minimal mode. The PPR r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59472</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in Next.js versions with Partial Prerendering (PPR) enabled when running in minimal mode. The PPR resume endpoint accepts unauthenticated POST requests with the `Next-Resume: 1` header and processes attacker-controlled postponed state data. Two closely related vulnerabilities allow an attacker to crash the server process through memory exhaustion:

1. **Unbounded request body buffering**: The server buffers the entire POST request body into memory using `Buffer.concat()` without enforcing any size limit, allowing arbitrarily large payloads to exhaust available memory.

2. **Unbounded decompression (zipbomb)**: The resume data cache is decompressed using `inflateSync()` without limiting the decompressed output size. A small compressed payload can expand to hundreds of megabytes or gigabytes, causing memory exhaustion.

Both attack vectors result in a fatal V8 out-of-memory error (`FATAL ERROR: Reached heap limit Allocation failed - JavaScript heap out of memory`) causing the Node.js process to terminate. The zipbomb variant is particularly dangerous as it can bypass reverse proxy request size limits while still causing large memory allocation on the server.

To be affected you must have an application running with `experimental.ppr: true` or `cacheComponents: true` configured along with the NEXT_PRIVATE_MINIMAL_MODE=1 environment variable.

Strongly consider upgrading to 15.6.0-canary.61 or 16.1.5 to reduce risk and prevent availability issues in Next applications.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59473 | SQL Injection vulnerability in the Structure for Admin authenticated user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59473</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in the Structure for Admin authenticated user</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23888 | pnpm: Binary ZIP extraction allows arbitrary file write via path traversal (Zip Slip)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23888</link><description>pnpm is a package manager. Prior to version 10.28.1, a path traversal vulnerability in pnpm's binary fetcher allows malicious packages to write files outside the intended extraction directory. The vulnerability has two attack vectors: (1) Malicious ZIP entries containing `../` or absolute paths that escape the extraction root via AdmZip's `extractAllTo`, and (2) The `BinaryResolution.prefix` field is concatenated into the extraction path without validation, allowing a crafted prefix like `../../evil` to redirect extracted files outside `targetDir`. The issue impacts all pnpm users who install packages with binary assets, users who configure custom Node.js binary locations, CI/CD pipelines that auto-install binary dependencies, and those who can overwrite config files, scripts, or other sensitive files leading to RCE. Version 10.28.1 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1444 | iJason-Liu Books_Manager add_book_check.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1444</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in iJason-Liu Books_Manager up to 298ba736387ca37810466349af13a0fdf828e99c. This affects an unknown part of the file controllers/books_center/add_book_check.php. Such manipulation of the argument mark leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22696 | dcap-qvl has Missing Verification for QE Identity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22696</link><description>dcap-qvl implements the quote verification logic for DCAP (Data Center Attestation Primitives). A vulnerability present in versions prior to 0.3.9 involves a critical gap in the cryptographic verification process within the dcap-qvl. The library fetches QE Identity collateral (including qe_identity, qe_identity_signature, and qe_identity_issuer_chain) from the PCCS. However, it skips to verify the QE Identity signature against its certificate chain and does not enforce policy constraints on the QE Report. An attacker can forge the QE Identity data to whitelist a malicious or non-Intel Quoting Enclave. This allows the attacker to forge the QE and sign untrusted quotes that the verifier will accept as valid. Effectively, this bypasses the entire remote attestation security model, as the verifier can no longer trust the entity responsible for signing the quotes. All deployments utilizing the dcap-qvl library for SGX or TDX quote verification are affected. The vulnerability has been patched in dcap-qvl version 0.3.9. The fix implements the missing cryptographic verification for the QE Identity signature and enforces the required checks for MRSIGNER, ISVPRODID, and ISVSVN against the QE Report. Users of the `@phala/dcap-qvl-node` and `@phala/dcap-qvl-web` packages should switch to the pure JavaScript implementation, `@phala/dcap-qvl`. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability. Users must upgrade to the patched version to ensure that QE Identity collateral is properly verified.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22709 | vm2 has a Sandbox Escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22709</link><description>vm2 is an open source vm/sandbox for Node.js. In vm2 prior to version 3.10.2, `Promise.prototype.then` `Promise.prototype.catch` callback sanitization can be bypassed. This allows attackers to escape the sandbox and run arbitrary code. In lib/setup-sandbox.js, the callback function of `localPromise.prototype.then` is sanitized, but `globalPromise.prototype.then` is not sanitized. The return value of async functions is `globalPromise` object. Version 3.10.2 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1443 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminDeleteUser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1443</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminDeleteUser.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9615 | Networkmanager: networkmanager file access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9615</link><description>A flaw was found in NetworkManager. The NetworkManager package allows access to files that may belong to other users. NetworkManager allows non-root users to configure the system's network. The daemon runs with root privileges and can access files owned by users different from the one who added the connection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9820 | Gnutls: stack-based buffer overflow in gnutls_pkcs11_token_init() function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9820</link><description>A flaw was found in the GnuTLS library, specifically in the gnutls_pkcs11_token_init() function that handles PKCS#11 token initialization. When a token label longer than expected is processed, the function writes past the end of a fixed-size stack buffer. This programming error can cause the application using GnuTLS to crash or, in certain conditions, be exploited for code execution. As a result, systems or applications relying on GnuTLS may be vulnerable to a denial of service or local privilege escalation attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11065 | Github.com/go-viper/mapstructure/v2: go-viper&amp;#x27;s mapstructure may leak sensitive information in logs in github.com/go-viper/mapstructure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11065</link><description>A flaw was found in github.com/go-viper/mapstructure/v2, in the field processing component using mapstructure.WeakDecode. This vulnerability allows information disclosure through detailed error messages that may leak sensitive input values via malformed user-supplied data processed in security-critical contexts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11687 | Gi-docgen: reflected dom xss in gi-docgen</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11687</link><description>A flaw was found in the gi-docgen. This vulnerability allows arbitrary JavaScript execution in the context of the page — enabling DOM access, session cookie theft and other client-side attacks — via a crafted URL that supplies a malicious value to the q GET parameter (reflected DOM XSS).</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14459 | Virt-cdi-controller: unauthorized pvc cloning via dataimportcron</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14459</link><description>A flaw was found in KubeVirt Containerized Data Importer (CDI). This vulnerability allows a user to clone PersistentVolumeClaims (PVCs) from unauthorized namespaces, resulting in unauthorized access to data via the DataImportCron PVC source mechanism.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14525 | Kubevirt: kubevirt: vm administration denial of service via guest agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14525</link><description>A flaw was found in kubevirt. A user within a virtual machine (VM), if the guest agent is active, can exploit this by causing the agent to report an excessive number of network interfaces. This action can overwhelm the system's ability to store VM configuration updates, effectively blocking changes to the Virtual Machine Instance (VMI). This allows the VM user to restrict the VM administrator's ability to manage the VM, leading to a denial of service for administrative operations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14969 | Hibernate-reactive-core: hibernate reactive: denial of service due to connection leak on http client disconnect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14969</link><description>A flaw was found in Hibernate Reactive. When an HTTP endpoint is exposed to perform database operations, a remote client can prematurely close the HTTP connection. This action may lead to leaking connections from the database connection pool, potentially causing a Denial of Service (DoS) by exhausting available database connections.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9520 | IDOR Leading to Owner Account Hijacking in Omada Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9520</link><description>An IDOR vulnerability exists in Omada Controllers that allows an attacker with Administrator permissions to manipulate requests and potentially hijack the Owner account.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9521 | Password Confirmation Bypass in Omada Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9521</link><description>Password Confirmation Bypass vulnerability in Omada Controllers, allowing an attacker with a valid session token to bypass secondary verification, and change the user’s password without proper confirmation, leading to weakened account security.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9522 | Blind Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in Omada Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9522</link><description>Blind Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in Omada Controllers through webhook functionality, enabling crafted requests to internal services, which may lead to enumeration of information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0810 | Gix-date: gix-date: undefined behavior due to invalid string generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0810</link><description>A flaw was found in gix-date. The `gix_date::parse::TimeBuf::as_str` function can generate strings containing invalid non-UTF8 characters. This issue violates the internal safety invariants of the `TimeBuf` component, leading to undefined behavior when these malformed strings are subsequently processed. This could potentially result in application instability or other unforeseen consequences.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1190 | Org.keycloak/keycloak-services: keycloak saml brokering: response delay due to unchecked notonorafter in subjectconfirmationdata</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1190</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak's SAML brokering functionality. When Keycloak is configured as a client in a Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) setup, it fails to validate the `NotOnOrAfter` timestamp within the `SubjectConfirmationData`. This allows an attacker to delay the expiration of SAML responses, potentially extending the time a response is considered valid and leading to unexpected session durations or resource consumption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23864 | Multiple denial of service vulnerabilities exist in React Server Components, affecting the following packages: react-server-dom-parcel, reac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23864</link><description>Multiple denial of service vulnerabilities exist in React Server Components, affecting the following packages: react-server-dom-parcel, react-server-dom-turbopack, react-server-dom-webpack.

The vulnerabilities are triggered by sending specially crafted HTTP requests to Server Function endpoints, and could lead to server crashes, out-of-memory exceptions or excessive CPU usage; depending on the vulnerable code path being exercised, the application configuration and application code.

Strongly consider upgrading to the latest package versions to reduce risk and prevent availability issues in applications using React Server Components.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70368 | Worklenz version 2.1.5 contains a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Project Updates feature. An attacker can submit a m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70368</link><description>Worklenz version 2.1.5 contains a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Project Updates feature. An attacker can submit a malicious payload in the Updates text field which is then rendered in the reporting view without proper sanitization. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim's browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14756 | Authenticated Command Injection Vulnerability in Archer MR600</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14756</link><description>Command injection vulnerability was found in the admin interface component of TP-Link Archer MR600 v5 firmware, allowing authenticated attackers to execute system commands with a limited character length via crafted input in the browser developer console, possibly leading to service disruption or full compromise.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57784 | Tomahawk authentication timing attack due to usage of &amp;#x27;strcmp&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57784</link><description>Tomahawk auth timing attack due to usage of `strcmp` has been identified in Hiawatha webserver version 11.7 which allows a local attacker to access the management client.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57785 | Double free in XSLT in &amp;#x27;show_index&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57785</link><description>A Double Free in XSLT `show_index` has been identified in Hiawatha webserver version 11.7 which allows an unauthenticated attacker to corrupt data which may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71178 | Crucial Storage Executive &amp;lt; 11.08.082025.00 Installer DLL Preloading LPE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71178</link><description>Crucial Storage Executive installer versions prior to 11.08.082025.00 contain a DLL preloading vulnerability. During installation, the installer runs with elevated privileges and loads Windows DLLs using an uncontrolled search path, which can cause a malicious DLL placed alongside the installer to be loaded instead of the intended system library. A local attacker who can convince a victim to run the installer from a directory containing the attacker-supplied DLL can achieve arbitrary code execution with administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0925 | Tanium addressed an improper input validation vulnerability in Discover.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0925</link><description>Tanium addressed an improper input validation vulnerability in Discover.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24432 | Tenda W30E V2 Missing CSRF Protections for Administrative Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24432</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) lack cross-site request forgery (CSRF) protections on administrative endpoints, including those used to change administrator account credentials. As a result, an attacker can craft malicious requests that, when triggered by an authenticated user’s browser, modify administrative passwords and other configuration settings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24435 | Tenda W30E V2 Permissive CORS Allows Cross-origin Data Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24435</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) implement an insecure Cross-Origin Resource Sharing (CORS) policy on authenticated administrative endpoints. The device sets Access-Control-Allow-Origin: * in combination with Access-Control-Allow-Credentials: true, allowing attacker-controlled origins to issue credentialed cross-origin requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24439 | Tenda W30E V2 Lacks X-Content-Type-Options Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24439</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) fail to include the X-Content-Type-Options: nosniff response header on web management interfaces. As a result, browsers that perform MIME sniffing may incorrectly interpret attacker-influenced responses as executable script.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36953 | MiniTool ShadowMaker 3.2 - &amp;#x27;MTAgentService&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36953</link><description>MiniTool ShadowMaker 3.2 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the MTAgentService that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in 'C:\Program Files\MiniTool ShadowMaker\AgentService.exe' to inject malicious executables and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36954 | Xeroneit Library Management System 3.1 - &amp;quot;Add Book Category &amp;quot; Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36954</link><description>Xeroneit Library Management System 3.1 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Book Category feature that allows administrators to inject malicious scripts. Attackers can insert a payload in the Category Name field to execute arbitrary JavaScript code when the page is loaded.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36955 | Grav CMS 1.6.30 Admin Plugin 1.9.18 - &amp;#x27;Page Title&amp;#x27; Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36955</link><description>Grav CMS 1.6.30 with Admin Plugin 1.9.18 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows authenticated attackers to inject malicious scripts through the page title field. Attackers can create a new page with a malicious script in the title, which will be executed when the page is viewed in the admin panel or on the site.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36956 | Openfire 4.6.0 - &amp;#x27;path&amp;#x27; Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36956</link><description>Openfire 4.6.0 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the nodejs plugin that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts through the 'path' parameter. Attackers can craft a payload with script tags to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of administrative users viewing the nodejs configuration page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36957 | PDF Complete 3.5.310.2002 - &amp;#x27;pdfsvc.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36957</link><description>PDF Complete 3.5.310.2002 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its pdfsvc.exe service configuration. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path to inject and execute malicious code with elevated LocalSystem privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36958 | Kite 1.2020.1119.0 - &amp;#x27;KiteService&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36958</link><description>Kite 1.2020.1119.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the KiteService Windows service that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in 'C:\Program Files\Kite\KiteService.exe' to inject malicious executables and escalate privileges on the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36959 | IDT PC Audio 1.0.6499.0 - &amp;#x27;STacSV&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36959</link><description>IDT PC Audio 1.0.6499.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in the STacSV service to inject malicious code that would execute with LocalSystem account permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36960 | Forma LMS 2.3 - &amp;#x27;First &amp;amp; Last Name&amp;#x27; Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36960</link><description>Forma LMS 2.3 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into user profile first and last name fields. Attackers can craft scripts like '' to execute arbitrary JavaScript when the profile is viewed by other users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57783 | Improper header parsing may lead to request smuggling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57783</link><description>Improper header parsing may lead to request smuggling has been identified in Hiawatha webserver version 11.7 which allows an unauthenticated attacker to access restricted resources managed by Hiawatha webserver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1224 | Tanium addressed an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in Discover.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1224</link><description>Tanium addressed an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in Discover.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24428 | Tenda W30E V2 Incorrect Authorization Allows Administrator Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24428</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) contain an authorization flaw in the user management API that allows a low-privileged authenticated user to change the administrator account password. By sending a crafted request directly to the backend endpoint, an attacker can bypass role-based restrictions enforced by the web interface and obtain full administrative privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24429 | Tenda W30E V2 Hardcoded Default Password for Built-in Account</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24429</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) ship with a predefined default password for a built-in authentication account that is not required to be changed during initial configuration. An attacker can leverage these default credentials to gain authenticated access to the management interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24430 | Tenda W30E V2 HTTP Responses Expose Plaintext Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24430</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) disclose sensitive account credentials in cleartext within HTTP responses generated by the maintenance interface. Because the management interface is accessible over unencrypted HTTP by default, credentials may be exposed to network-based interception.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24431 | Tenda W30E V2 Web UI Reveals Passwords in Cleartext</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24431</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) display stored user account passwords in plaintext within the administrative web interface. Any user with access to the affected management pages can directly view credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24433 | Tenda W30E V2 Stored XSS via Username Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24433</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) contain a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the user creation functionality. Insufficient input validation allows attacker-controlled script content to be stored and later executed when administrative users access the affected management pages.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24436 | Tenda W30E V2 Lacks Rate Limiting on Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24436</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) do not enforce rate limiting or account lockout mechanisms on authentication endpoints. This allows attackers to perform unrestricted brute-force attempts against administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24437 | Tenda W30E V2 Missing Cache Controls for Credential-bearing Pages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24437</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) serve sensitive administrative content without appropriate cache-control directives. As a result, browsers may store credential-bearing responses locally, exposing them to subsequent unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24440 | Tenda W30E V2 Allows Password Changes Without Verifying Current Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24440</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) allow account passwords to be changed through the maintenance interface without requiring verification of the existing password. This enables unauthorized password changes when access to the affected endpoint is obtained.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1446 | There is a Cross Site Scripting issue in Esri ArcGIS Pro versions 3.6.0 and earlier. A local attacker could supply malicious strings into Ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1446</link><description>There is a Cross Site Scripting issue in Esri ArcGIS Pro versions 3.6.0 and earlier. A local attacker could supply malicious strings into ArcGIS Pro which may execute when a specific dialog is opened.  This issue is fixed in ArcGIS Pro 3.6.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21509 | Microsoft Office Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21509</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70982 | Incorrect access control in the importUser function of SpringBlade v4.5.0 allows attackers with low-level privileges to arbitrarily import s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70982</link><description>Incorrect access control in the importUser function of SpringBlade v4.5.0 allows attackers with low-level privileges to arbitrarily import sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:18:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67274 | An issue in continuous.software aangine v.2025.2 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the excel-integration-service ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67274</link><description>An issue in continuous.software aangine v.2025.2 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the excel-integration-service template download module, integration-persistence-service job listing module, portfolio-item-service data retrieval module endpoints</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:18:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36952 | IObit Uninstaller 10 Pro - Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36952</link><description>IObit Uninstaller 10 Pro contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted service path in the IObit Uninstaller Service to insert malicious code that would execute with SYSTEM-level permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50537 | Stack overflow vulnerability in eslint before 9.26.0 when serializing objects with circular references in eslint/lib/shared/serialization.js...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50537</link><description>Stack overflow vulnerability in eslint before 9.26.0 when serializing objects with circular references in eslint/lib/shared/serialization.js. The exploit is triggered via the RuleTester.run() method, which validates test cases and checks for duplicates. During validation, the internal function checkDuplicateTestCase() is called, which in turn uses the isSerializable() function for serialization checks. When a circular reference object is passed in, isSerializable() enters infinite recursion, ultimately causing a stack overflow.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1283 | Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability affecting the EPRT file reading procedure in SOLIDWORKS eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS 2025 through Release SOLIDWORKS 2026</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1283</link><description>A Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability affecting the EPRT file reading procedure in SOLIDWORKS eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS 2025 through Release SOLIDWORKS 2026 could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code while opening a specially crafted EPRT file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1284 | Out-Of-Bounds Write vulnerability affecting the EPRT file reading procedure in SOLIDWORKS eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS 2025 through Release SOLIDWORKS 2026</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1284</link><description>An Out-Of-Bounds Write vulnerability affecting the EPRT file reading procedure in SOLIDWORKS eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS 2025 through Release SOLIDWORKS 2026 could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code while opening a specially crafted EPRT file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15057 | Apache Continuum: Command injection leading to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15057</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability in Apache Continuum.

This issue affects Apache Continuum: all versions.

Attackers with access to the installations REST API can use this to invoke arbitrary commands on the server.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59090 | Unauthenticated SOAP API in dormakaba Kaba exos 9300</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59090</link><description>On the exos 9300 server, a SOAP API is reachable on port 8002. This API does not require any authentication prior to sending requests. Therefore, network access to the exos server allows e.g. the creation of arbitrary access log events as well as querying the 2FA PINs associated with the enrolled chip cards.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59091 | Hardcoded Legacy Accounts Allowing Control Over Access Managers in dormakaba Kaba exos 9300</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59091</link><description>Multiple hardcoded credentials have been identified, which are allowed to sign-in to the exos 9300 datapoint server running on port 1004 and 1005. This server is used for relaying status information from and to the Access Managers. This information, among other things, is used to graphically visualize open doors and alerts. However, controlling the Access Managers via this interface is also possible.

To send and receive status information, authentication is necessary. The Kaba exos 9300 application contains hard-coded credentials for four different users, which are allowed to login to the datapoint server and receive as well as send information, including commands to open arbitrary doors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59092 | Unauthenticated RPC Service in dormakaba Kaba exos 9300</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59092</link><description>An RPC service, which is part of exos 9300, is reachable on port 4000, run by the process FSMobilePhoneInterface.exe. This service is used for interprocess communication between services and the Kaba exos 9300 GUI, containing status information about the Access Managers. Interacting with the service does not require any authentication. Therefore, it is possible to send arbitrary status information about door contacts etc. without prior authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59093 | Insecure Password Derivation Function for Database Administrator in dormakaba Kaba exos 9300</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59093</link><description>Exos 9300 instances are using a randomly generated database password to connect to the configured MSSQL server. The password is derived from static random values, which are concatenated to the hostname and a random string that can be read by every user from the registry. This allows an attacker to derive the database password and get authenticated access to the central exos 9300 database as the user Exos9300Common. The user has the roles ExosDialog and ExosDialogDotNet assigned, which are able to read most tables of the database as well as update and insert into many tables.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59094 | Local Privilege Escalation in dormakaba Kaba exos 9300 System management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59094</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability has been identified in the Kaba exos 9300 System management application (d9sysdef.exe). Within this application it is possible to specify an arbitrary executable as well as the weekday and start time, when the specified executable should be run with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59095 | Hard-coded Key for PIN Encryption in dormakaba Kaba exos 9300</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59095</link><description>The program libraries (DLL) and binaries used by exos 9300 contain multiple hard-coded secrets. One notable example is the function "EncryptAndDecrypt" in the library Kaba.EXOS.common.dll. This algorithm uses a simple XOR encryption technique combined with a cryptographic key (cryptoKey) to transform each character of the input string. However, it's important to note that this implementation does not provide strong encryption and should not be considered secure for sensitive data. It's more of a custom encryption approach rather than a common algorithm used in cryptographic applications. The key itself is static and based on the founder's name of the company. The functionality is for example used to encrypt the user PINs before storing them in the MSSQL database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59096 | Weak Default Password in dormakaba Kaba exos 9300</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59096</link><description>The default password for the extended admin user mode in the application U9ExosAdmin.exe ("Kaba 9300 Administration") is hard-coded in multiple locations as well as documented in the locally stored user documentation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59097 | Unauthenticated SOAP API in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59097</link><description>The exos 9300 application can be used to configure Access Managers (e.g. 92xx, 9230 and 9290). The configuration is done in a graphical user interface on the dormakaba exos server. As soon as the save button is clicked in exos 9300, the whole configuration is sent to the selected Access Manager via SOAP. The SOAP request is sent without any prior authentication or authorization by default. Though authentication and authorization can be configured using IPsec for 92xx-K5 devices and mTLS for 92xx-K7 devices, it is not enabled by default and must therefore be activated with additional steps.

This insecure default allows an attacker with network level access to completely control the whole environment. An attacker is for example easily able to conduct the following tasks without prior authentication:
- Re-configure Access Managers (e.g. remove alarming system requirements)
- Freely re-configure the inputs and outputs
- Open all connected doors permanently
- Open all doors for a defined time interval
- Change the admin password
- and many more

Network level access can be gained due to an insufficient network segmentation as well as missing LAN firewalls. Devices with an insecure configuration have been identified to be directly exposed to the internet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59098 | Trace Functionality Leaking Sensitive Data in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59098</link><description>The Access Manager is offering a trace functionality to debug errors and issues with the device. The trace functionality is implemented as a simple TCP socket. A tool called TraceClient.exe, provided by dormakaba via the Access Manager web interface, is used to connect to the socket and receive debug information. The data is permanently broadcasted on the TCP socket. The socket can be accessed without any authentication or encryption. 

The transmitted data is based on the set verbosity level. The verbosity level can be set using the http(s) endpoint with the service interface password or with the guessable identifier of the device via the SOAP interface.

The transmitted data contains sensitive data like the Card ID as well as all button presses on Registration units. This allows an attacker with network level access to retrieve all entered PINs on a registration unit.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59099 | Unauthenticated Path Traversal in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59099</link><description>The Access Manager is using the open source web server CompactWebServer written in C#. This web server is affected by a path traversal vulnerability, which allows an attacker to directly access files via simple GET requests without prior authentication. 

Hence, it is possible to retrieve all files stored on the file system, including the SQLite database Database.sq3, containing badge information and the corresponding PIN codes. Additionally, when trying to access certain files, the web server crashes and becomes unreachable for about 60 seconds. This can be abused to continuously send the request and cause denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59100 | Unauthenticated Access to the SQLite Database in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59100</link><description>The web interface offers a functionality to export the internal SQLite database. After executing the database export, an automatic download is started and the device reboots. After rebooting, the exported database is deleted and cannot be accessed anymore. However, it was noticed that sometimes the device does not reboot and therefore the exported database is not deleted, or the device reboots and the export is not deleted for unknown reasons. The path where the database export is located can be accessed without prior authentication. This leads to the fact that an attacker might be able to get access to the exported database without prior authentication. 
The database includes sensitive data like passwords, card pins, encrypted Mifare sitekeys and much more.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59101 | Insufficient Session Management in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59101</link><description>Instead of typical session tokens or cookies, it is verified on a per-request basis if the originating IP address has once successfully logged in. As soon as an authentication request from a certain source IP is successful, the IP address is handled as authenticated. No other session information is stored. Therefore, it is possible to spoof the IP address of a logged-in user to gain access to the Access Manager web interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59102 | Secrets Stored in Plaintext in Database in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59102</link><description>The web server of the Access Manager offers a functionality to download a backup of the local database stored on the device. This database contains the whole configuration. This includes encrypted MIFARE keys, card data, user PINs and much more. The PINs are even stored unencrypted. Combined with the fact that an attacker can easily get access to the backup functionality by abusing the session management issue (CVE-2025-59101), or by exploiting the weak default password (CVE-2025-59108), or by simply setting a new password without prior authentication via the SOAP API (CVE-2025-59097), it is easily possible to access the sensitive data on the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59103 | Weak Default Passwords for SSH Access in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59103</link><description>The Access Manager 92xx in hardware revision K7 is based on Linux instead of Windows CE embedded in older hardware revisions. In this new hardware revision it was noticed that an SSH service is exposed on port 22. By analyzing the firmware of the devices, it was noticed that there are two users with hardcoded and weak passwords that can be used to access the devices via SSH. The passwords can be also guessed very easily. The password of at least one user is set to a random value after the first deployment, with the restriction that the password is only randomized if the configured date is prior to 2022. Therefore, under certain circumstances, the passwords are not randomized. For example, if the clock is never set on the device, the battery of the clock module has been changed, the Access Manager has been factory reset and has not received a time yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59104 | Unlocked Bootloader in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59104</link><description>With physical access to the device and enough time an attacker is able to solder test leads to the debug footprint (or use the 6-Pin tag-connect cable). Thus, the attacker gains access to the bootloader, where the kernel command line can be changed. An attacker is able to gain a root shell through this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59105 | Unencrypted Flash Storage in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59105</link><description>With physical access to the device and enough time an attacker can desolder the flash memory, modify it and then reinstall it because of missing encryption. Thus, essential files, such as "/etc/passwd", as well as stored certificates, cryptographic keys, stored PINs and so on can be modified and read, in order to gain SSH root access on the Linux-based K7 model. On the Windows CE based K5 model, the password for the Access Manager can additionally be read in plain text from the stored SQLite database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59106 | Web Server Running with Root Privileges in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59106</link><description>The binary serving the web server and executing basically all actions launched from the Web UI is running with root privileges. This is against the least privilege principle. If an attacker is able to execute code on the system via other vulnerabilities it is possible to directly execute commands with highest privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59107 | Static Firmware Encryption Password in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59107</link><description>Dormakaba provides the software FWServiceTool to update the firmware version of the Access Managers via the network. The firmware in some instances is provided in an encrypted ZIP file. Within this tool, the password used to decrypt the ZIP and extract the firmware is set statically and can be extracted. This password was valid for multiple observed firmware versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59108 | Weak Default Passwords in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59108</link><description>By default, the password for the Access Manager's web interface, is set to 'admin'. In the tested version changing the password was not enforced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59109 | UART Leaking Sensitive Data in dormakaba registration unit 9002</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59109</link><description>The dormakaba registration units 9002 (PIN Pad Units) have an exposed UART header on the backside. The PIN pad is sending every button press to the UART interface. An attacker can use the interface to exfiltrate PINs. As the devices are explicitly built as Plug-and-Play to be easily replaced, an attacker is easily able to remove the device, install a hardware implant which connects to the UART and exfiltrates the data exposed via UART to another system (e.g. via WiFi).</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27821 | HDFS native client: Out of bounds write in URI parser of native HDFS client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27821</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in Apache Hadoop HDFS native client.

This issue affects Apache Hadoop: from 3.2.0 before 3.4.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.4.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41083 | Improper Neutralization in Altitude Communication Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41083</link><description>Vulnerability in Altitude Authentication Service and Altitude Communication Server v8.5.3290.0 by Altitude, where manipulation of Host header in HTTP requests allows redirection to an arbitrary URL or modification of the base URL to trick the victim into sending login credentials to a malicious website. This behavior can be used to redirect clients to endpoints controlled by the attacker.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24656 | Apache Karaf: Decanter log-socket collector has deserialization vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24656</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache Karaf Decanter.


The Decanter log socket collector exposes the port 4560, without authentication. If the collector exposes allowed classes property, this configuration can be bypassed.
It means that the log socket collector is vulnerable to deserialization of untrusted data, eventually causing DoS.


NB: Decanter log socket collector is not installed by default. Users who have not installed Decanter log socket are not impacted by this issue.

This issue affects Apache Karaf Decanter before 2.12.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.12.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41082 | HTTP Request/Response Smuggling in Altitude Communication Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41082</link><description>Illegal HTTP request traffic vulnerability (CL.0) in Altitude Communication Server, caused by inconsistent analysis of multiple HTTP requests over a single Keep-Alive connection using  Content-Length headers. This can cause a desynchronization of requests between frontend and backend servers, which could allow request hiding, cache poisoning or security bypass.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 09:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1428 | WellChoose｜Single Sign-On Portal System - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1428</link><description>Single Sign-On Portal System developed by WellChoose has a OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary OS commands and execute them on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1429 | WellChoose｜Single Sign-On Portal System - Reflected Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1429</link><description>Single Sign-On Portal System developed by WellChoose has a Reflected Cross-site Scripting vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript codes in user's browser through phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1427 | WellChoose｜Single Sign-On Portal System -  OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1427</link><description>Single Sign-On Portal System developed by WellChoose has a OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary OS commands and execute them on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1425 | pymumu SmartDNS SVBC Record dns.c _dns_decode_SVCB_HTTPS stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1425</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in pymumu SmartDNS up to 47.1. This vulnerability affects the function _dns_decode_rr_head/_dns_decode_SVCB_HTTPS of the file src/dns.c of the component SVBC Record Parser. The manipulation results in stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. A high complexity level is associated with this attack. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The patch is identified as 2d57c4b4e1add9b4537aeb403f794a084727e1c8. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 07:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1424 | PHPGurukul News Portal Profile Pic unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1424</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in PHPGurukul News Portal 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Profile Pic Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 07:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1423 | code-projects Online Examination System admin_pic.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1423</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Online Examination System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin_pic.php. Executing a manipulation can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14316 | AhaChat Messenger Marketing &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14316</link><description>The AhaChat Messenger Marketing WordPress plugin through 1.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14973 | Recipe Card Blocks &amp;lt; 3.4.13 - Contributor+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14973</link><description>The Recipe Card Blocks Lite WordPress plugin before 3.4.13 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing contributors and above to perform SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1422 | code-projects Online Examination System Login Page index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1422</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Examination System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php of the component Login Page. Performing a manipulation of the argument User results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1421 | code-projects Online Examination System Add Pages cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1421</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Online Examination System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component Add Pages. Such manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1420 | Tenda AC23 WifiExtraSet buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1420</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda AC23 16.03.07.52. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/WifiExtraSet. This manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto causes buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1419 | D-Link DCS700l Web Form setDayNightMode command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1419</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DCS700l 1.03.09. Affected is an unknown function of the file /setDayNightMode of the component Web Form Handler. Executing a manipulation of the argument LightSensorControl can lead to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1418 | GPAC SRT Subtitle Import text_to_bifs.c gf_text_import_srt_bifs out-of-bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1418</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in GPAC up to 2.4.0. This affects the function gf_text_import_srt_bifs of the file src/scene_manager/text_to_bifs.c of the component SRT Subtitle Import. Such manipulation leads to out-of-bounds write. The attack needs to be performed locally. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The name of the patch is 10c73b82cf0e367383d091db38566a0e4fe71772. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1416 | GPAC filedump.c DumpMovieInfo null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1416</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in GPAC up to 2.4.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function DumpMovieInfo of the file applications/mp4box/filedump.c. The manipulation results in null pointer dereference. The attack must be initiated from a local position. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The patch is identified as d45c264c20addf0c1cc05124ede33f8ffa800e68. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1417 | GPAC filedump.c dump_isom_rtp null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1417</link><description>A weakness has been identified in GPAC up to 2.4.0. Affected by this issue is the function dump_isom_rtp of the file applications/mp4box/filedump.c. This manipulation causes null pointer dereference. The attack needs to be launched locally. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. Patch name: f96bd57c3ccdcde4335a0be28cd3e8fe296993de. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1414 | Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Security Management System HTTP POST Request get_Information getInformation command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1414</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Security Management System up to 3.0.12. This impacts the function getInformation of the file /equipment/get_Information of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. Executing a manipulation of the argument fortEquipmentIp can lead to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 03:06:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1415 | GPAC media_export.c gf_media_export_webvtt_metadata null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1415</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in GPAC up to 2.4.0. Affected is the function gf_media_export_webvtt_metadata of the file src/media_tools/media_export.c. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to null pointer dereference. The attack must be carried out locally. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The identifier of the patch is af951b892dfbaaa38336ba2eba6d6a42c25810fd. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 03:06:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1413 | Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Security Management System HTTP POST Request port_validate portValidate command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1413</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Security Management System up to 3.0.12. This affects the function portValidate of the file /fort/ip_and_port/port_validate of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. Performing a manipulation of the argument port results in command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 03:06:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1412 | Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Security Management System HTTP POST Request get_clip_img command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1412</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Security Management System up to 3.0.12. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /fort/audit/get_clip_img of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. Such manipulation of the argument frame/dirno leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 03:06:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1410 | Beetel 777VR1 UART missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1410</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Beetel 777VR1 up to 01.00.09/01.00.09_55. Impacted is an unknown function of the component UART Interface. The manipulation results in missing authentication. An attack on the physical device is feasible. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1411 | Beetel 777VR1 UART access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1411</link><description>A flaw has been found in Beetel 777VR1 up to 01.00.09/01.00.09_55. The affected element is an unknown function of the component UART Interface. This manipulation causes improper access controls. It is feasible to perform the attack on the physical device. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>