<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 07:37:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-5435 | Marwal Infotech CMS page.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5435</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Marwal Infotech CMS 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /page.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 07:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5113 | Authenticated Remote Command Injection in Diviotec NBR IP Cameras</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5113</link><description>The Diviotec professional series exposes a web interface. One endpoint is vulnerable to arbitrary command injection and hardcoded passwords are used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 07:24:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4010 | Arbitrary Command Injection in Netcom NTC-6200 &amp;amp; NWL-222</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4010</link><description>The Netcom NTC 6200 and NWL 222 series expose a web interface to be configured and set up by operators. Multiple endpoints of the web interface are vulnerable to arbitrary command injection and use insecure hardcoded passwords. Remote authenticated attackers can gain arbitrary code execution with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 07:24:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5434 | Aem Solutions CMS page.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5434</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Aem Solutions CMS up to 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /page.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 07:24:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5433 | Fengoffice Feng Office index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5433</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Fengoffice Feng Office 3.5.1.5 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php?c=account&amp;amp;a=set_timezone. The manipulation of the argument tz_offset leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:51:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1235 | WAGO: Switches affected by year 2k38 problem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1235</link><description>A low privileged attacker can set the date of the devices to the 19th of January 2038 an therefore exceed the 32-Bit time limit. This causes the date of the switch to be set back to January 1st, 1970.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1485 | Real Cookie Banner &amp;lt; 5.1.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1485</link><description>The Real Cookie Banner: GDPR &amp; ePrivacy Cookie Consent WordPress plugin before 5.1.6, real-cookie-banner-pro WordPress plugin before 5.1.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3951 | WP-Optimize &amp;lt; 4.2.0 - Admin+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3951</link><description>The WP-Optimize  WordPress plugin before 4.2.0 does not properly escape user input when checking image compression statuses, which could allow users with the administrator role to conduct SQL Injection attacks in the context of Multi-Site WordPress configurations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5432 | AssamLook CMS view_tender.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5432</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in AssamLook CMS 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /view_tender.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5431 | AssamLook CMS department-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5431</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in AssamLook CMS 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /department-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 05:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5430 | AssamLook CMS product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5430</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in AssamLook CMS 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /product.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 05:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49113 | Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.10 and 1.6.x before 1.6.11 allows remote code execution by authenticated users because the _from parameter in a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49113</link><description>Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.10 and 1.6.x before 1.6.11 allows remote code execution by authenticated users because the _from parameter in a URL is not validated in program/actions/settings/upload.php, leading to PHP Object Deserialization.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5429 | juzaweb CMS Plugins Page install access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5429</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin-cp/plugin/install of the component Plugins Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25179 | GPU DDK - Freelist GPU VA can be remapped to another reservation/PMR to trigger GPU arbitrary write to physical memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25179</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to subvert GPU HW to write to arbitrary physical memory pages.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49112 | setDeferredReply in networking.c in Valkey through 8.1.1 has an integer underflow for prev-&gt;size - prev-&gt;used.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49112</link><description>setDeferredReply in networking.c in Valkey through 8.1.1 has an integer underflow for prev-&gt;size - prev-&gt;used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5428 | juzaweb CMS Error Logs Page log-viewer access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5428</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin-cp/log-viewer of the component Error Logs Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 04:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11857 | Realtek Bluetooth HCI Adaptor - Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11857</link><description>Bluetooth HCI Adaptor from Realtek has a Link Following vulnerability. Local attackers with regular privileges can create a symbolic link with the same name as a specific file, causing the product to delete arbitrary files pointed to by the link. Subsequently, attackers can leverage arbitrary file deletion to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5427 | juzaweb CMS Permalinks Page permalinks access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5427</link><description>A vulnerability was found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin-cp/permalinks of the component Permalinks Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20672 | In Bluetooth driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20672</link><description>In Bluetooth driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00412257; Issue ID: MSV-3292.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20673 | In wlan STA driver, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with User exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20673</link><description>In wlan STA driver, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00413200; Issue ID: MSV-3304.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20674 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible way to inject arbitrary packet due to a missing permission check. This could lead to remote escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20674</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible way to inject arbitrary packet due to a missing permission check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00413202; Issue ID: MSV-3303.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20675 | In wlan STA driver, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with User exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20675</link><description>In wlan STA driver, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00413201; Issue ID: MSV-3302.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20676 | In wlan STA driver, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with User exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20676</link><description>In wlan STA driver, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00412240; Issue ID: MSV-3293.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20677 | In Bluetooth driver, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with User exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20677</link><description>In Bluetooth driver, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00412256; Issue ID: MSV-3284.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20678 | In ims service, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20678</link><description>In ims service, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01394606; Issue ID: MSV-2739.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5425 | juzaweb CMS Theme Editor Page default access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5425</link><description>A vulnerability was found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin-cp/theme/editor/default of the component Theme Editor Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5426 | juzaweb CMS Menu Page menus access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5426</link><description>A vulnerability was found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin-cp/menus of the component Menu Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5424 | juzaweb CMS Media Page media access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5424</link><description>A vulnerability was found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin-cp/media of the component Media Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 02:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5423 | juzaweb CMS General Setting Page general access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5423</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin-cp/setting/system/general of the component General Setting Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 02:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5422 | juzaweb CMS Email Logs Page email access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5422</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin-cp/logs/email of the component Email Logs Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 01:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5421 | juzaweb CMS Plugin Editor Page editor access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5421</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin-cp/plugin/editor of the component Plugin Editor Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 01:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5420 | juzaweb CMS Profile Page upload cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5420</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin-cp/file-manager/upload of the component Profile Page. The manipulation of the argument Upload leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 01:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5412 | Mist Community Edition Authentication Endpoint views.py login cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5412</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Mist Community Edition up to 4.7.1. Affected is the function Login of the file src/mist/api/views.py of the component Authentication Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument return_to leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.7.2 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is db10ecb62ac832c1ed4924556d167efb9bc07fad. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 23:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5411 | Mist Community Edition views.py tag_resources cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5411</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Mist Community Edition up to 4.7.1. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function tag_resources of the file src/mist/api/tag/views.py. The manipulation of the argument tag leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.7.2 is able to address this issue. The patch is named db10ecb62ac832c1ed4924556d167efb9bc07fad. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 23:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5410 | Mist Community Edition middleware.py session_start_response cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5410</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Mist Community Edition up to 4.7.1. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function session_start_response of the file src/mist/api/auth/middleware.py. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.7.2 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as db10ecb62ac832c1ed4924556d167efb9bc07fad. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 22:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5409 | Mist Community Edition API Token views.py create_token access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5409</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Mist Community Edition up to 4.7.1. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function create_token of the file src/mist/api/auth/views.py of the component API Token Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.7.2 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is db10ecb62ac832c1ed4924556d167efb9bc07fad. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 22:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5408 | WAVLINK WL-WN576K1 HTTP POST Request login.cgi sys_login buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5408</link><description>A vulnerability was found in WAVLINK QUANTUM D2G, QUANTUM D3G, WL-WN530G3A, WL-WN530HG3, WL-WN532A3 and WL-WN576K1 up to V1410_240222 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function sys_login of the file /cgi-bin/login.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument login_page leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 21:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5407 | chaitak-gorai Blogbook register_script.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5407</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in chaitak-gorai Blogbook up to 92f5cf90f8a7e6566b576fe0952e14e1c6736513 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /register_script.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 21:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5406 | chaitak-gorai Blogbook posts.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5406</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in chaitak-gorai Blogbook up to 92f5cf90f8a7e6566b576fe0952e14e1c6736513. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/posts.php?source=add_post. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 18:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5405 | chaitak-gorai Blogbook post.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5405</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in chaitak-gorai Blogbook up to 92f5cf90f8a7e6566b576fe0952e14e1c6736513. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /post.php. The manipulation of the argument comment_author/comment_email/comment_content leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 18:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5404 | chaitak-gorai Blogbook GET Parameter search.php denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5404</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in chaitak-gorai Blogbook up to 92f5cf90f8a7e6566b576fe0952e14e1c6736513. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /search.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument Search leads to denial of service. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 16:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5403 | chaitak-gorai Blogbook GET Parameter view_all_posts.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5403</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in chaitak-gorai Blogbook up to 92f5cf90f8a7e6566b576fe0952e14e1c6736513. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/view_all_posts.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument post_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 16:17:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5402 | chaitak-gorai Blogbook GET Parameter edit_post.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5402</link><description>A vulnerability was found in chaitak-gorai Blogbook up to 92f5cf90f8a7e6566b576fe0952e14e1c6736513. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/includes/edit_post.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument edit_post_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 14:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40908 | YAML-LibYAML prior to 0.903.0 for Perl uses 2-args open, allowing existing files to be modified</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40908</link><description>YAML-LibYAML prior to 0.903.0 for Perl uses 2-args open, allowing existing files to be modified</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 13:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5401 | chaitak-gorai Blogbook GET Parameter post.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5401</link><description>A vulnerability was found in chaitak-gorai Blogbook up to 92f5cf90f8a7e6566b576fe0952e14e1c6736513. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /post.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument p_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 13:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25044 | IBM Planning Analytics Local cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25044</link><description>IBM Planning Analytics Local 2.0 and 2.1 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 11:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2896 | IBM Planning Analytics Local cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2896</link><description>IBM Planning Analytics Local 2.0 and 2.1 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 11:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33004 | IBM Planning Analytics Local path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33004</link><description>IBM Planning Analytics Local 2.0 and 2.1 could allow a privileged user to delete files from directories due to improper pathname restriction.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 11:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33005 | IBM Planning Analytics Local session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33005</link><description>IBM Planning Analytics Local 2.0 and 2.1 does not invalidate session after a logout which could allow an authenticated user to impersonate another user on the system.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 11:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1499 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1499</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 stores credential information for database authentication in a cleartext parameter file that could be viewed by an authenticated user.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 11:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5400 | chaitak-gorai Blogbook GET Parameter user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5400</link><description>A vulnerability was found in chaitak-gorai Blogbook up to 92f5cf90f8a7e6566b576fe0952e14e1c6736513. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /user.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument u_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 08:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5390 | JeeWMS File filedeal.do filedeal access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5390</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in JeeWMS up to 20250504. This affects the function filedeal of the file /systemController/filedeal.do of the component File Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5389 | JeeWMS File generateController.do dogenerateOne2Many access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5389</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in JeeWMS up to 20250504. Affected by this issue is the function dogenerateOne2Many of the file /generateController.do?dogenerateOne2Many of the component File Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be launched remotely. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 18:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5388 | JeeWMS generateController.do dogenerate sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5388</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in JeeWMS up to 20250504. Affected by this vulnerability is the function dogenerate of the file /generateController.do?dogenerate. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 18:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5387 | JeeWMS File generateController.do dogenerate access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5387</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in JeeWMS up to 20250504. Affected is the function dogenerate of the file /generateController.do?dogenerate of the component File Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 17:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5386 | JeeWMS cgformTransController.do transEditor sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5386</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JeeWMS up to 20250504. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function transEditor of the file /cgformTransController.do?transEditor. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 17:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5385 | JeeWMS cgformTemplateController.do doAdd path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5385</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JeeWMS up to 20250504. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function doAdd of the file /cgformTemplateController.do?doAdd. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 16:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5384 | JeeWMS cgAutoListController.do CgAutoListController sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5384</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JeeWMS up to 20250504. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function CgAutoListController of the file /cgAutoListController.do?datagrid. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 16:14:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5383 | Yifang CMS Article Management Module cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5383</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Yifang CMS up to 2.0.2 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Article Management Module. The manipulation of the argument Default Value leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 15:17:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5381 | Yifang CMS Admin Panel downloadFile path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5381</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Yifang CMS up to 2.0.2. Affected is the function downloadFile of the file /api/File/downloadFile of the component Admin Panel. The manipulation of the argument File leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 14:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5380 | ashinigit 天青一白 XueShengZhuSu 学生住宿管理系统 Image File Upload upload path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5380</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ashinigit 天青一白 XueShengZhuSu 学生住宿管理系统 up to 4d3f0ada0e71482c1e51fd5f5615e5a3d8bcbfbb. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /upload/ of the component Image File Upload. The manipulation of the argument File leads to path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 14:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5379 | NuCom NC-WR744G Console Application hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5379</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in NuCom NC-WR744G 8.5.5 Build 20200530.307. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Console Application. The manipulation of the argument CMCCAdmin/useradmin/CUAdmin leads to hard-coded credentials. The attack can be initiated remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 13:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5378 | Astun Technology iShare Maps mycouncil2.aspx cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5378</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Astun Technology iShare Maps 5.4.0. This affects an unknown part of the file mycouncil2.aspx. The manipulation of the argument atTxtStreet leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 13:34:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5377 | Astun Technology iShare Maps historic1.asp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5377</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Astun Technology iShare Maps 5.4.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file historic1.asp. The manipulation of the argument Zoom leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 13:05:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5376 | SourceCodester Health Center Patient Record Management System patient.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5376</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Health Center Patient Record Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /patient.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 11:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4691 | Free Booking Plugin for Hotels, Restaurants and Car Rentals – eaSYNC Booking &amp;lt;= 1.3.21 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4691</link><description>The Free Booking Plugin for Hotels, Restaurants and Car Rentals – eaSYNC Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.21 via the 'view_request_details' due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view the details of any booking request. The vulnerability was partially patched in versions 1.3.18 and 1.3.21.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 11:22:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4857 | Newsletters &amp;lt;= 4.9.9.9 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4857</link><description>The Newsletters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.9.9 via the 'file' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 11:22:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5375 | PHPGurukul HPGurukul Online Birth Certificate System registered-users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5375</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul HPGurukul Online Birth Certificate System 2.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/registered-users.php. The manipulation of the argument del leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 10:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5374 | PHPGurukul Online Birth Certificate System all-applications.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5374</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Birth Certificate System 2.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/all-applications.php. The manipulation of the argument del leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 10:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5373 | PHPGurukul Online Birth Certificate System users-applications.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5373</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Online Birth Certificate System 2.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/users-applications.php. The manipulation of the argument userid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 08:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5371 | SourceCodester Health Center Patient Record Management System admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5371</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Health Center Patient Record Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 08:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3813 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.7.1020 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3813</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘_elementor_data’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1020 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 07:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5290 | Borderless – Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5290</link><description>The Borderless – Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘title’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 07:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4103 | WP-GeoMeta 0.3.4 - 0.3.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via wp_ajax_wpgm_start_geojson_import Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4103</link><description>The WP-GeoMeta plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check on the wp_ajax_wpgm_start_geojson_import() function in versions 0.3.4 to 0.3.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to elevate their privileges to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 06:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4590 | Daisycon prijsvergelijkers &amp;lt;= 4.8.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4590</link><description>The Daisycon prijsvergelijkers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'daisycon_uitvaart' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 06:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4595 | FastSpring &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4595</link><description>The FastSpring plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'fastspring/block-fastspringblocks-complete-product-catalog' block in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'color' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 06:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4607 | PSW Front-end Login &amp;amp; Registration &amp;lt;= 1.12 - Insufficiently Random Values to Unauthenticated Account Takeover/Privilege Escalation via customer_registration Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4607</link><description>The PSW Front-end Login &amp; Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.12 via the customer_registration() function. This is due to the use of a weak, low-entropy OTP mechanism in the forget() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to initiate a password reset for any user, including administrators, and elevate their privileges for full site takeover.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 06:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4631 | Profitori 2.0.6.0 - 2.1.1.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via stocktend_object Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4631</link><description>The Profitori plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check on the stocktend_object endpoint in versions 2.0.6.0 to 2.1.1.3. This makes it possible to trigger the save_object_as_user() function for objects whose '_datatype' is set to 'users',. This allows unauthenticated attackers to write arbitrary strings straight into the user’s wp_capabilities meta field, potentially elevating the privileges of an existing user account or a newly created one to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 06:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4672 | Offsprout Page Builder 2.2.1 - 2.15.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Privilege Escalation via permission_callback Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4672</link><description>The Offsprout Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to improper authorization placed on the permission_callback() function in versions 2.2.1 to 2.15.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read, create, update or delete any user meta, including flipping their own wp_capabilities to administrator and fully escalate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 06:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5285 | Product Subtitle for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.3.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via htmlTag Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5285</link><description>The Product Subtitle for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘htmlTag’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 06:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5292 | Element Pack Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor addons with Ready Templates, Blocks, Widgets and WooCommerce Builder &amp;lt;= 5.11.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5292</link><description>The Element Pack Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor addons with Ready Templates, Blocks, Widgets and WooCommerce Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'marker_content’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.11.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 06:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5370 | PHPGurukul News Portal forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5370</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul News Portal 4.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 05:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5369 | SourceCodester PHP Display Username After Login login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5369</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester PHP Display Username After Login 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 05:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5368 | PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker System expense-yearwise-reports-detailed.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5368</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker System 1.1. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /expense-yearwise-reports-detailed.php. The manipulation of the argument todate leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 04:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5016 | Relevanssi &amp;lt;= 4.24.5 (Free) and &amp;lt;= 2.27.6 (Premium) - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Excerpt Highlights</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5016</link><description>The Relevanssi – A Better Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Excerpt Highlights in all versions up to, and including, 4.24.5 (Free) and 2.27.6 (Premium) due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 03:55:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5367 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal Project category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5367</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal Project 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /category.php. The manipulation of the argument Product leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 02:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25111 | django-helpdesk before 1.0.0 allows Sensitive Data Exposure because of os.umask(0) in models.py.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25111</link><description>django-helpdesk before 1.0.0 allows Sensitive Data Exposure because of os.umask(0) in models.py.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 01:02:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5365 | Campcodes Online Hospital Management System patient-search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5365</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Hospital Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/patient-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 01:02:45 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>