<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:43:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-62674 | Missing Authentication for RTSP in iCam Cameras</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62674</link><description>The affected product allows unauthenticated access to Real Time Streaming Protocol (RTSP) services, which may allow an attacker unauthorized access to camera configuration information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63807 | An issue was discovered in weijiang1994 university-bbs (aka Blogin) in commit 9e06bab430bfc729f27b4284ba7570db3b11ce84 (2025-01-13). A weak ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63807</link><description>An issue was discovered in weijiang1994 university-bbs (aka Blogin) in commit 9e06bab430bfc729f27b4284ba7570db3b11ce84 (2025-01-13). A weak verification code generation mechanism combined with missing rate limiting allows attackers to perform brute-force attacks on verification codes without authentication. Successful exploitation may result in account takeover via password reset or other authentication bypass methods.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64770 | Missing Authentication for ONVIF in iCam Cameras</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64770</link><description>The affected products allow unauthenticated access to Open Network Video Interface Forum (ONVIF) services, which may allow an attacker unauthorized access to camera configuration information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35029 | Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health stored cross site scripting via Demographic Information page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35029</link><description>Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health has a stored cross site scripting vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker to add arbitrary content in the 'Demographic Information' page. This content will be rendered and executed when a victim accesses it. This issue is fixed as of 2025-03-14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48986 | Authorization bypass in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes an logged in attacker to change other users' email addre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48986</link><description>Authorization bypass in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes an logged in attacker to change other users' email address and potentialy take over their accounts using the forgot password functionality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48987 | Improper Neutralization of Input in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes a potential reflected XSS attack.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48987</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes a potential reflected XSS attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52666 | Improper neutralisation of format characters in the settings of Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes an administrator...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52666</link><description>Improper neutralisation of format characters in the settings of Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes an administrator user to disable the admin user console due to a fatal PHP error.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52667 | Missing JSON Content-Type header in a script in Revive Adserver 6.0.1 and 5.5.2 and earlier versions causes a stored XSS attack to be possib...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52667</link><description>Missing JSON Content-Type header in a script in Revive Adserver 6.0.1 and 5.5.2 and earlier versions causes a stored XSS attack to be possible for a logged in manager user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52668 | Improper input neutralization in the stats-conversions.php script in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes potential i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52668</link><description>Improper input neutralization in the stats-conversions.php script in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes potential information disclosure and session hijacking via a stored XSS attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52669 | Insecure design policies in the user management system of Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes non-admin users to hav...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52669</link><description>Insecure design policies in the user management system of Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes non-admin users to have access to the contact name and email address of other users on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52670 | Missing authorization check in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes users on the system to delete banners owned by ot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52670</link><description>Missing authorization check in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes users on the system to delete banners owned by other accounts</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52671 | Debug information disclosure in the SQL error message to in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes non-admin users to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52671</link><description>Debug information disclosure in the SQL error message to in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes non-admin users to acquire information about the software, PHP and database versions currently in use.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55123 | Improper neutralization of input in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes manager accounts to be able to craft XSS att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55123</link><description>Improper neutralization of input in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes manager accounts to be able to craft XSS attacks to their own advertiser users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55124 | Improper neutralisation of input in Revive Adserver 6.0.0+ causes a reflected XSS attack in the banner-zone.php script.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55124</link><description>Improper neutralisation of input in Revive Adserver 6.0.0+ causes a reflected XSS attack in the banner-zone.php script.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55126 | HackerOne community member Dang Hung Vi (vidang04) has reported a stored XSS vulnerability involving the navigation box at the top of advert...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55126</link><description>HackerOne community member Dang Hung Vi (vidang04) has reported a stored XSS vulnerability involving the navigation box at the top of advertiser-related pages, with campaign names being the vector for the stored XSS</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55127 | HackerOne community member Dao Hoang Anh (yoyomiski) has reported an improper neutralization of whitespace in the username when adding new u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55127</link><description>HackerOne community member Dao Hoang Anh (yoyomiski) has reported an improper neutralization of whitespace in the username when adding new users. A username with leading or trailing whitespace could be virtually indistinguishable from its legitimate counterpart when the username is displayed in the UI, potentially leading to confusion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55128 | HackerOne community member Dao Hoang Anh (yoyomiski) has reported an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in the “userlog-index.p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55128</link><description>HackerOne community member Dao Hoang Anh (yoyomiski) has reported an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in the “userlog-index.php”. An attacker with access to the admin interface could request an arbitrarily large number of items per page, potentially leading to a denial of service</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63700 | An issue was discovered in Clerk-js 5.88.0 allowing attackers to bypass the OAuth authentication flow by manipulating the request at the OTP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63700</link><description>An issue was discovered in Clerk-js 5.88.0 allowing attackers to bypass the OAuth authentication flow by manipulating the request at the OTP verification stage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 18:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10571 | ABB Ability Edgenius Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10571</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in ABB ABB Ability Edgenius.This issue affects ABB Ability Edgenius: 3.2.0.0, 3.2.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 18:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64524 | CUPS rastertopclx Filter Vulnerable to Heap Buffer Overflow Leading to Potential Arbitrary Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64524</link><description>cups-filters contains backends, filters, and other software required to get the cups printing service working on operating systems other than macos. In versions 2.0.1 and prior, a heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability in the rastertopclx filter causes the program to crash with a segmentation fault when processing maliciously crafted input data. This issue can be exploited to trigger memory corruption, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution. This issue has been patched via commit 956283c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 18:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63888 | The read function in file thinkphp\library\think\template\driver\File.php in ThinkPHP 5.0.24 contains a remote code execution vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63888</link><description>The read function in file thinkphp\library\think\template\driver\File.php in ThinkPHP 5.0.24 contains a remote code execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 18:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63889 | The fetch function in file thinkphp\library\think\Template.php in ThinkPHP 5.0.24 allows attackers to read arbitrary files via crafted file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63889</link><description>The fetch function in file thinkphp\library\think\Template.php in ThinkPHP 5.0.24 allows attackers to read arbitrary files via crafted file path in a template value.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64428 | DataEase DB2 JNDI Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64428</link><description>Dataease is an open source data visualization analysis tool. Versions prior to 2.10.17 are vulnerable to JNDI injection. A blacklist was added in the patch for version 2.10.14. However, JNDI injection remains possible via the iiop, corbaname, and iiopname schemes. The vulnerability has been fixed in version 2.10.17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63848 | Stored cross site scripting (xss) vulnerability in SWISH prolog thru 2.2.0 allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted web IDE ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63848</link><description>Stored cross site scripting (xss) vulnerability in SWISH prolog thru 2.2.0 allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted web IDE notebook.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64185 | Open OnDemand RPM packages create world writable locations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64185</link><description>Open OnDemand is an open-source HPC portal. Prior to versions 4.0.8 and 3.1.16, Open OnDemand packages create world writable locations in the GEM_PATH. Open OnDemand versions 4.0.8 and 3.1.16 have been patched for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62709 | ClipBucket v5 is vulnerable to password reset link manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62709</link><description>ClipBucket v5 is an open source video sharing platform. In ClipBucket version 5.5.2, a change to network.class.php causes the application to dynamically build the server URL from the incoming HTTP Host header when the configuration base_url is not set. Because Host is a client-controlled header, an attacker can supply an arbitrary Host value. This allows an attacker to cause password-reset links (sent by forget.php) to be generated with the attacker’s domain. If a victim follows that link and enters their activation code on the attacker-controlled domain, the attacker can capture the code and use it to reset the victim’s password and take over the account. This issue has been patched in version 5.5.2#162.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62724 | Open OnDemand allowlist bypass using symlinks in directory downloads (TOCTOU)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62724</link><description>Open OnDemand is an open-source HPC portal. Prior to versions 4.0.8 and 3.1.16, users can craft a "Time of Check to Time of Use" (TOCTOU) attack when downloading zip files to access files outside of the OOD_ALLOWLIST. This vulnerability impacts sites that use the file browser allowlists in all current versions of OOD. However, files accessed are still protected by the UNIX permissions. Open OnDemand versions 4.0.8 and 3.1.16 have been patched for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12120 | CVE-2025-12120</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12120</link><description>Lite XL versions 2.1.8 and prior automatically execute the .lite_project.lua file when opening a project directory, without prompting the user for confirmation. The .lite_project.lua file is intended for project-specific configuration but can contain executable Lua logic. This behavior could allow execution of untrusted Lua code if a user opens a malicious project, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution with the privileges of the Lite XL process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12121 | CVE-2025-12121</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12121</link><description>Lite XL versions 2.1.8 and prior contain a vulnerability in the system.exec function, which allowed arbitrary command execution through unsanitized shell command construction. This function was used in project directory launching (core.lua), drag-and-drop file handling (rootview.lua), and the “open in system” command in the treeview plugin (treeview.lua). If an attacker could influence input to system.exec, they might execute arbitrary commands with the privileges of the Lite XL process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64027 | Snipe-IT v8.3.4 (build 20218) contains a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CSV Import workflow. When an invalid CSV ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64027</link><description>Snipe-IT v8.3.4 (build 20218) contains a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CSV Import workflow. When an invalid CSV file is uploaded, the application returns a progress_message value that is rendered as raw HTML in the admin interface. An attacker can intercept and modify the POST /livewire/update request to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript into the progress_message. Because the server accepts the modified input without sanitization and reflects it back to the user, arbitrary JavaScript executes in the browser of any authenticated admin who views the import page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13437 | Arbitrary node_modules Directory Deletion in Google zx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13437</link><description>When zx is invoked with --prefer-local=, the CLI creates a symlink named ./node_modules pointing to /node_modules. Due to a logic error in src/cli.ts (linkNodeModules / cleanup), the function returns the target path instead of the alias (symlink path). The later cleanup routine removes what it received, which deletes the target directory itself. Result: zx can delete an external /node_modules outside the current working directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52410 | Institute-of-Current-Students v1.0 contains a time-based blind SQL injection vulnerability in the mydetailsstudent.php endpoint. The `myds` ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52410</link><description>Institute-of-Current-Students v1.0 contains a time-based blind SQL injection vulnerability in the mydetailsstudent.php endpoint. The `myds` GET parameter is not adequately sanitized before being used in SQL queries.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62875 | Local DoS in OpenSMTPD via UNIX domain socket smtpd.sock</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62875</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in OpenSMTPD allows local users to crash OpenSMTPD.




This issue affects openSUSE Tumbleweed: from ? before 7.8.0p0-1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62294 | Predictable Generation of Password Recovery Token</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62294</link><description>SOPlanning is vulnerable to Predictable Generation of Password Recovery Token. Due to weak mechanism of generating recovery tokens, a malicious attacker is able to brute-force all possible values and takeover any account in reasonable amount of time.

This issue was fixed in version 1.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62295 | Stored XSS in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62295</link><description>SOPlanning is vulnerable to Stored XSS in /groupe_form endpoint. Malicious attacker with medium privileges can inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed when opening editor.

This issue was fixed in version 1.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62296 | Stored XSS in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62296</link><description>SOPlanning is vulnerable to Stored XSS in /taches endpoint. Malicious attacker with medium privileges can inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed when opening editor.

This issue was fixed in version 1.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62297 | Stored XSS in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62297</link><description>SOPlanning is vulnerable to Stored XSS in /projets endpoint. Malicious attacker with medium privileges can inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed when opening edited page.

This issue was fixed in version 1.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62729 | Stored XSS in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62729</link><description>SOPlanning is vulnerable to Stored XSS in /status endpoint. Malicious attacker with an account can inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed when opening multiple pages.

This issue was fixed in version 1.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62730 | Privilege Escalation via Incorrect Authorization in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62730</link><description>SOPlanning is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in user management tab. Users with user_manage_team role are allowed to modify permissions of users. However, they are able to assign administrative permissions to any user including themselves. This allow a malicious authenticated attacker with this role to escalate to admin privileges. This issue affects both Bulk Update functionality and regular edition of user's right and privileges.

This issue was fixed in version 1.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62731 | Stored XSS in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62731</link><description>SOPlanning is vulnerable to Stored XSS in /feries endpoint. Malicious attacker with access to public holidays feature is able to inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed when opening multiple pages. By default only administrators and users with special privileges are able to access this endpoint.

This issue was fixed in version 1.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62293 | Broken Access Control in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62293</link><description>SOPlanning is vulnerable to Broken Access Control in /status endpoint. Due to lack of permission checks in Project Status functionality an authenticated attacker is able to add, edit and delete any status.


This issue was fixed in version 1.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13425 | Denial of Service in OSV-SCALIBR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13425</link><description>A bug in the filesystem traversal fallback path causes fs/diriterate/diriterate.go:Next() to overindex an empty slice when ReadDir returns nil for an empty directory, resulting in a panic (index out of range) and an application crash (denial of service) in OSV-SCALIBR.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34320 | BASIS BBj &amp;lt; 25.00 Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34320</link><description>BASIS BBj versions prior to 25.00 contain a Jetty-served web endpoint that fails to properly validate or canonicalize input path segments. This allows unauthenticated directory traversal sequences to cause the server to read arbitrary system files accessible to the account running the service. Retrieved configuration artifacts may contain account credentials used for BBj Enterprise Manager; possession of these credentials enables administrative access and use of legitimate management functionality that can result in execution of system commands under the service account. Depending on the operating system and the privileges of the BBj service account, this issue may also allow access to other sensitive files on the host, including operating system or application data, potentially exposing additional confidential information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36161 | IBM Concert Software Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36161</link><description>IBM Concert 1.0.0 through 2.0.0 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by the failure to properly enable HTTP Strict-Transport-Security. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information using man in the middle techniques.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60737 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Ilevia EVE X1 Server Firmware Version&lt;= 4.7.18.0.eden:Logic Version&lt;=6.00 - 2025_07_21 allows a remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60737</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Ilevia EVE X1 Server Firmware Version&lt;= 4.7.18.0.eden:Logic Version&lt;=6.00 - 2025_07_21 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /index.php component</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60738 | An issue in Ilevia EVE X1 Server Firmware Version v4.7.18.0.eden and before Logic Version v6.00 - 2025_07_21 and before allows a remote atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60738</link><description>An issue in Ilevia EVE X1 Server Firmware Version v4.7.18.0.eden and before Logic Version v6.00 - 2025_07_21 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ping.php component does not perform secure filtering on IP parameters</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60798 | phpPgAdmin 7.13.0 and earlier contains a SQL injection vulnerability in display.php at line 396. The application passes user-controlled inpu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60798</link><description>phpPgAdmin 7.13.0 and earlier contains a SQL injection vulnerability in display.php at line 396. The application passes user-controlled input from $_REQUEST['query'] directly to the browseQuery function without proper sanitization. An authenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary SQL commands through malicious query manipulation, potentially leading to complete database compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60799 | phpPgAdmin 7.13.0 and earlier contains an incorrect access control vulnerability in sql.php at lines 68-76. The application allows unauthori...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60799</link><description>phpPgAdmin 7.13.0 and earlier contains an incorrect access control vulnerability in sql.php at lines 68-76. The application allows unauthorized manipulation of session variables by accepting user-controlled parameters ('subject', 'server', 'database', 'queryid') without proper validation or access control checks. Attackers can exploit this to store arbitrary SQL queries in $_SESSION['sqlquery'] by manipulating these parameters, potentially leading to session poisoning, stored cross-site scripting, or unauthorized access to sensitive session data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65220 | Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in: /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg via the list parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65220</link><description>Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in: /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg via the list parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60796 | phpPgAdmin 7.13.0 and earlier contains multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities across various components. User-supplied input fr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60796</link><description>phpPgAdmin 7.13.0 and earlier contains multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities across various components. User-supplied input from $_REQUEST parameters is reflected in HTML output without proper encoding or sanitization in multiple locations including sequences.php, indexes.php, admin.php, and other unspecified files. An attacker can exploit these vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary JavaScript in victims' browsers, potentially leading to session hijacking, credential theft, or other malicious actions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:21:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60797 | phpPgAdmin 7.13.0 and earlier contains a SQL injection vulnerability in dataexport.php at line 118. The application directly executes user-s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60797</link><description>phpPgAdmin 7.13.0 and earlier contains a SQL injection vulnerability in dataexport.php at line 118. The application directly executes user-supplied SQL queries from the $_REQUEST['query'] parameter without any sanitization or parameterization via $data-&gt;conn-&gt;Execute($_REQUEST['query']). An authenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary SQL commands, potentially leading to complete database compromise, data theft, or privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65221 | Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the list parameter of /goform/setPptpUserList.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65221</link><description>Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the list parameter of /goform/setPptpUserList.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65222 | Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the rebootTime parameter of /goform/SetSysAutoRebbotCfg.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65222</link><description>Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the rebootTime parameter of /goform/SetSysAutoRebbotCfg.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65223 | Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the urls parameter of /goform/saveParentControlInfo.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65223</link><description>Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the urls parameter of /goform/saveParentControlInfo.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 14:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60794 | Session tokens and passwords in couch-auth 0.21.2 are stored in JavaScript objects and remain in memory without explicit clearing in src/use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60794</link><description>Session tokens and passwords in couch-auth 0.21.2 are stored in JavaScript objects and remain in memory without explicit clearing in src/user.ts lines 700-707. This creates a window of opportunity for sensitive data extraction through memory dumps, debugging tools, or other memory access techniques, potentially leading to session hijacking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 14:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65226 | Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the deviceId parameter in /goform/saveParentControlInfo.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65226</link><description>Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the deviceId parameter in /goform/saveParentControlInfo.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 14:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0645 | Arbitrary File Upload in Narkom Communication Technologies&amp;#x27; Pyxis Signage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0645</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Narkom Communication and Software Technologies Trade Ltd. Co. Pyxis Signage allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Pyxis Signage: through 31012025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13469 | Public Knowledge Project omp/ojs Payment Instructions Setting paymentForm.tpl cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13469</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Public Knowledge Project omp and ojs 3.3.0/3.4.0/3.5.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file plugins/paymethod/manual/templates/paymentForm.tpl of the component Payment Instructions Setting Handler. The manipulation of the argument manualInstructions leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. You should upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0643 | XSS in Narkom Communication Technologies&amp;#x27; Pyxis Signage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0643</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Narkom Communication and Software Technologies Trade Ltd. Co. Pyxis Signage allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Pyxis Signage: through 31012025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13468 | SourceCodester Alumni Management System Delete admin_class.php delete_event authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13468</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Alumni Management System 1.0. This issue affects the function delete_forum/delete_career/delete_comment/delete_gallery/delete_event of the file admin/admin_class.php of the component Delete Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to missing authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41074 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Limesurvey</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41074</link><description>Vulnerability in LimeSurvey 6.13.0  in the endpoint /optout that causes infinite HTTP redirects when accessed directly. This behavior can be exploited to generate a Denegation of Service (DoS  attack), by exhausting server or client resources. The system is unable to break the redirect loop, which can cause service degradation or browser instability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41075 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Limesurvey</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41075</link><description>Vulnerability in LimeSurvey 6.13.0 in the endpoint /optin that causes infinite HTTP redirects when accessed directly. This behavior can be exploited to generate a Denegation of Service (DoS  attack), by exhausting server or client resources. The system is unable to break the redirect loop, which can cause service degradation or browser instability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41076 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Limesurvey</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41076</link><description>In version 6.13.0 of LimeSurvey, any external user can cause a 500 error in the survey system by sending a malformed session cookie. Instead of displaying a generic error message, the system exposes internal backend information, including the use of the Yii framework, the MySQL/MariaDB database engine, the table name 'lime_sessions', primary keys, and fragments of the content that caused the conflict. This information can simplify the collection of data about the internal architecture of the application by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40601 | A Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SonicOS SSLVPN service allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause Denial of Servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40601</link><description>A Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SonicOS SSLVPN service allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS), which could cause an impacted firewall to crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 12:56:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40604 | Download of Code Without Integrity Check Vulnerability in the SonicWall Email Security appliance loads root filesystem images without verify...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40604</link><description>Download of Code Without Integrity Check Vulnerability in the SonicWall Email Security appliance loads root filesystem images without verifying signatures, allowing attackers with VMDK or datastore access to modify system files and gain persistent arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 12:56:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40605 | A Path Traversal vulnerability has been identified in the Email Security appliance allows an attacker to manipulate file system paths by inj...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40605</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability has been identified in the Email Security appliance allows an attacker to manipulate file system paths by injecting crafted directory-traversal sequences (such as ../) and may access files and directories outside the intended restricted path.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 12:56:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12414 | Looker account compromise via punycode homograph attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12414</link><description>An attacker could take over a Looker account in a Looker instance configured with OIDC authentication, due to email address string normalization.Looker-hosted and Self-hosted were found to be vulnerable.

This issue has already been mitigated for Looker-hosted.


Self-hosted instances must be upgraded as soon as possible. This vulnerability has been patched in all supported versions of Self-hosted.
The versions below have all been updated to protect from this vulnerability. You can download these versions at the Looker download page   https://download.looker.com/ :
  *  24.12.100+
  *  24.18.193+
  *  25.0.69+
  *  25.6.57+
  *  25.8.39+
  *  25.10.22+
  *  25.12.0+</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 10:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11676 | UPnP DOS in TL-WR940N V6</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11676</link><description>Improper input validation vulnerability in TP-Link System Inc. TL-WR940N V6 (UPnP modules), which allows unauthenticated adjacent attackers to perform DoS attack. This issue affects TL-WR940N V6 &lt;= Build 220801.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 08:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62346 | HCL Glovius Cloud is susceptible to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62346</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability was identified in HCL Glovius Cloud. An attacker can force a user's web browser to execute an unwanted, malicious action on a trusted site where the user is authenticated, specifically on one endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 08:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64984 | Kaspersky has fixed a security issue in Kaspersky Endpoint Security for Linux (any version with anti-virus databases prior to 18.11.2025), K...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64984</link><description>Kaspersky has fixed a security issue in Kaspersky Endpoint Security for Linux (any version with anti-virus databases prior to 18.11.2025), Kaspersky Industrial CyberSecurity for Linux Nodes (any version with anti-virus databases prior to 18.11.2025), and Kaspersky Endpoint Security for Mac (12.0.0.325, 12.1.0.553, and 12.2.0.694 with anti-virus databases prior to 18.11.2025) that could have allowed a reflected XSS attack to be carried out by an attacker using phishing techniques.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 07:00:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5092 | Multiple Plugins and Themes &amp;lt;= (Various Versions) - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via lightGallery JavaScript Library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5092</link><description>Multiple plugins and/or themes for WordPress are vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's bundled lightGallery library (&lt;= 2.8.3) in various versions due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 06:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12502 | Attention Bar &amp;lt;= 0.7.2.1 - Admin+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12502</link><description>The attention-bar WordPress plugin through 0.7.2.1 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing high privilege users such as administrator to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 06:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12778 | Ultimate Member Widgets for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12778</link><description>The Ultimate Member Widgets for Elementor – WordPress User Directory plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the handle_filter_users function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract partial metadata of all WordPress users, including their first name, last name and email addresses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 04:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13450 | SourceCodester Online Shop Project register.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13450</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Online Shop Project 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /shop/register.php. This manipulation of the argument f_name causes cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13451 | SourceCodester Online Shop Project action.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13451</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SourceCodester Online Shop Project 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /action.php. Such manipulation of the argument Search leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13446 | Tenda AC21 SetSysTimeCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13446</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC21 16.03.08.16. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/SetSysTimeCfg. The manipulation of the argument timeZone/time leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:09:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13449 | code-projects Online Shop Project login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13449</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Shop Project 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument Password results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:09:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13443 | macrozheng mall delete access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13443</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in macrozheng mall up to 1.0.3. Affected by this issue is the function delete of the file /member/readHistory/delete. Performing manipulation of the argument ids results in improper access controls. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:09:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13445 | Tenda AC21 SetIpMacBind stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13445</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda AC21 16.03.08.16. This affects an unknown part of the file /goform/SetIpMacBind. Executing manipulation of the argument list can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:09:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13435 | Dreampie Resty HttpClient HttpClient.java request path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13435</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Dreampie Resty up to 1.3.1.SNAPSHOT. This affects the function Request of the file /resty-httpclient/src/main/java/cn/dreampie/client/HttpClient.java of the component HttpClient Module. Such manipulation of the argument filename leads to path traversal. The attack may be performed from remote. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is reported as difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:57:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13442 | UTT 进取 750W formPdbUpConfig system command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13442</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in UTT 进取 750W up to 3.2.2-191225. Affected by this vulnerability is the function system of the file /goform/formPdbUpConfig. Such manipulation of the argument policyNames leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:57:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13434 | jameschz Hush Framework HTTP Host Header Util.php http headers for scripting syntax</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13434</link><description>A weakness has been identified in jameschz Hush Framework 2.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file Hush\hush-lib\hush\Util.php of the component HTTP Host Header Handler. This manipulation of the argument $_SERVER['HOST'] causes improper neutralization of http headers for scripting syntax. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:57:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13433 | Muse Group MuseHub Windows Service Muse.Updater.exe unquoted search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13433</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Muse Group MuseHub 2.1.0.1567. The affected element is an unknown function of the file C:\Program Files\WindowsApps\Muse.MuseHub_2.1.0.1567_x64__rb9pth70m6nz6\Muse.Updater.exe of the component Windows Service. The manipulation results in unquoted search path. The attack is only possible with local access. A high complexity level is associated with this attack. The exploitability is described as difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:57:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13424 | Campcodes Supplier Management System add_product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13424</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Supplier Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/add_product.php. The manipulation of the argument txtProductName leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:57:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13422 | freeprojectscodes Sports Club Management System change_s_pwd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13422</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in freeprojectscodes Sports Club Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /dashboard/admin/change_s_pwd.php. Performing manipulation of the argument login_id results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13423 | Campcodes Retro Basketball Shoes Online Store admin_product.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13423</link><description>A flaw has been found in Campcodes Retro Basketball Shoes Online Store 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/admin_product.php. Executing manipulation of the argument product_image can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13421 | itsourcecode Human Resource Management System NoticeStore.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13421</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Human Resource Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /src/store/NoticeStore.php. Such manipulation of the argument noticeDesc leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:14:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13420 | itsourcecode Human Resource Management System EventStore.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13420</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Human Resource Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /src/store/EventStore.php. This manipulation of the argument eventSubject causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13415 | icret EasyImages SVG Image upload.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13415</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in icret EasyImages up to 2.8.6. This affects an unknown part of the file /app/upload.php of the component SVG Image Handler. The manipulation of the argument File leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11001 | 7-Zip ZIP File Parsing Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11001</link><description>7-Zip ZIP File Parsing Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of 7-Zip. Interaction with this product is required to exploit this vulnerability but attack vectors may vary depending on the implementation.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of symbolic links in ZIP files. Crafted data in a ZIP file can cause the process to traverse to unintended directories. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of a service account. Was ZDI-CAN-26753.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 21:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11884 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability discovered in OpenText™ Universal Discovery and CMDB</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11884</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in opentext uCMDB allows Stored XSS. The vulnerability could allow an attacker has high level access to UCMDB to create or update data with malicious scripts

This issue affects uCMDB: 24.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 21:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13412 | Campcodes Retro Basketball Shoes Online Store admin_running.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13412</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Campcodes Retro Basketball Shoes Online Store 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin_running.php. Executing manipulation of the argument product_name can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 21:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63719 | Campcodes Online Hospital Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /admin/index.php via the parameter username.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63719</link><description>Campcodes Online Hospital Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /admin/index.php via the parameter username.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 21:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63371 | Milos Paripovic OneCommander 3.102.0.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The vulnerability resides in the ZIP file processing component,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63371</link><description>Milos Paripovic OneCommander 3.102.0.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The vulnerability resides in the ZIP file processing component, specifically in the functionality responsible for extracting and handling ZIP archive contents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 20:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13147 | External Service Interaction (DNS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13147</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Progress MOVEit Transfer.This issue affects MOVEit Transfer: before 2024.1.8, from 2025.0.0 before 2025.0.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 20:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47914 | CVE-2025-47914 in golang.org/x/crypto/ssh/agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47914</link><description>SSH Agent servers do not validate the size of messages when processing new identity requests, which may cause the program to panic if the message is malformed due to an out of bounds read.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 20:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58181 | CVE-2025-58181 in golang.org/x/crypto/ssh</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58181</link><description>SSH servers parsing GSSAPI authentication requests do not validate the number of mechanisms specified in the request, allowing an attacker to cause unbounded memory consumption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 20:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13410 | Campcodes Retro Basketball Shoes Online Store receipt.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13410</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Retro Basketball Shoes Online Store 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/receipt.php. Such manipulation of the argument tid leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 20:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13411 | Campcodes Retro Basketball Shoes Online Store admin_football.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13411</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Retro Basketball Shoes Online Store 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin_football.php. Performing manipulation of the argument product_image results in unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 20:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63932 | D-Link Router DIR-868L A1 FW106KRb01.bin has an unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability in the cgibin binary. The HNAP service p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63932</link><description>D-Link Router DIR-868L A1 FW106KRb01.bin has an unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability in the cgibin binary. The HNAP service provided by cgibin does not filter the HTTP SOAPAction header field. The unauthenticated remote attacker can execute the shell command.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 20:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36371 | IBM i Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36371</link><description>IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, 7.5, and 7.6 are impacted by obtaining an information vulnerability in the database plan cache implementation.  A user with access to the database plan cache could see information they do not have authority to view.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51661 | A path Traversal vulnerability found in FileCodeBox v2.2 and earlier allows arbitrary file writes when application is configured to use loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51661</link><description>A path Traversal vulnerability found in FileCodeBox v2.2 and earlier allows arbitrary file writes when application is configured to use local filesystem storage. SystemFileStorage.save_file method in core/storage.py uses filenames from user input without validation to construct save_path and save files. This allows remote attackers to perform arbitrary file writes outside the intended directory by sending crafted POST requests with malicious traversal sequences to /share/file/ upload endpoint, which does not require any authorization.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51662 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability is found in the text sharing feature of FileCodeBox version 2.2 and earlier. Insufficient ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51662</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability is found in the text sharing feature of FileCodeBox version 2.2 and earlier. Insufficient input validation allows attackers to inject arbitrary JavaScript code into shared text "codeboxes". The xss payload is automatically executed in the browsers of any users who try to access the infected codebox by clicking link or entering share code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51663 | A vulnerability found in IPRateLimit implementation of FileCodeBox up to 2.2 allows remote attackers to bypass ip-based rate limit protectio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51663</link><description>A vulnerability found in IPRateLimit implementation of FileCodeBox up to 2.2 allows remote attackers to bypass ip-based rate limit protection and failed attempt restrictions by faking X-Real-IP and X-Forwarded-For HTTP headers. This can enable attackers to perform DoS attacks or brute force share codes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63214 | An issue was discovered in bridgetech VBC Server &amp; Element Manager, firmware version 6.5.0-10 , 6.5.0-9, allowing unauthorized attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63214</link><description>An issue was discovered in bridgetech VBC Server &amp; Element Manager, firmware version 6.5.0-10 , 6.5.0-9, allowing unauthorized attackers to delete and create arbitrary accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63212 | GatesAir Flexiva-LX devices on firmware 1.0.13 and 2.0, including models LX100, LX300, LX600, and LX1000, expose sensitive session identifie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63212</link><description>GatesAir Flexiva-LX devices on firmware 1.0.13 and 2.0, including models LX100, LX300, LX600, and LX1000, expose sensitive session identifiers (sid) in the publicly accessible log file located at /log/Flexiva%20LX.log. An unauthenticated attacker can retrieve valid session IDs and hijack sessions without providing any credentials. This attack requires the legitimate user (admin) to have previously closed the browser window without logging out.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:48:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63213 | The QVidium Opera11 device (firmware version 2.9.0-Ax4x-opera11) is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) due to improper input validati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63213</link><description>The QVidium Opera11 device (firmware version 2.9.0-Ax4x-opera11) is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) due to improper input validation on the /cgi-bin/net_ping.cgi endpoint. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted GET request with a malicious parameter to inject arbitrary commands. These commands are executed with root privileges, allowing attackers to gain full control over the device. This poses a significant security risk to any device running this software.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65103 | OpenSTAManager has an authenticated SQL Injection vulnerability in API via &amp;#x27;display&amp;#x27; parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65103</link><description>OpenSTAManager is an open source management software for technical assistance and invoicing. Prior to version 2.9.5, an authenticated SQL Injection vulnerability in the API allows any user, regardless of permission level, to execute arbitrary SQL queries. By manipulating the display parameter in an API request, an attacker can exfiltrate, modify, or delete any data in the database, leading to a full system compromise. This issue has been patched in version 2.9.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65094 | WBCE CMS is Vulnerable to Privilege Escalation via Group ID Manipulation (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65094</link><description>WBCE CMS is a content management system. Prior to version 1.6.4, a low-privileged user in WBCE CMS can escalate their privileges to the Administrators group by manipulating the groups[] parameter in the /admin/users/save.php request. The UI restricts users to assigning only their existing group, but server-side validation is missing, allowing attackers to overwrite their group membership and obtain full administrative access. This results in a complete compromise of the CMS. This issue has been patched in version 1.6.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65100 | Security Snapshot May Use Unintended Timestamp When Only ISAR_APT_SNAPSHOT_DATE Is Set</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65100</link><description>Isar is an integration system for automated root filesystem generation. In versions 0.11-rc1 and 0.11, defining ISAR_APT_SNAPSHOT_DATE alone does not set the correct timestamp value for security distribution, leading to missed security updates. This issue has been patched via commit 738bcbb.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:56:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64759 | Homarr is Vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) and Possible Privilege Escalation via Malicious SVG Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64759</link><description>Homarr is an open-source dashboard. Prior to version 1.43.3, stored XSS vulnerability exists, allowing the execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user's browser, with minimal or no user interaction required, due to the rendering of a malicious uploaded SVG file. This could be abused to add an attacker's account to the "credentials-admin" group, giving them full administrative access, if a user logged in as an administrator was to view the page which renders or redirects to the SVG. This issue has been patched in version 1.43.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63211 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in bridgetech VBC Server &amp; Element Manager, firmware versions 6.5.0-9 thru 6.5.0-10, allows attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63211</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in bridgetech VBC Server &amp; Element Manager, firmware versions 6.5.0-9 thru 6.5.0-10, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the addName parameter to the /vbc/core/userSetupDoc/userSetupDoc endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13316 | Hard-coded encryption keys in Twonky Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13316</link><description>Twonky Server 8.5.2 on Linux and Windows is vulnerable to a cryptographic flaw, use of hard-coded cryptographic keys. An attacker with knowledge of the encrypted administrator password can decrypt the value with static keys to view the plain text password and gain administrator-level access to Twonky Server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13315 | Unauthenticated log access in Twonky Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13315</link><description>Twonky Server 8.5.2 on Linux and Windows is vulnerable to an access control flaw. An unauthenticated attacker can bypass web service API authentication controls to leak a log file and read the administrator's username and encrypted password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65089 | XWiki view file macro: User can view content of office file without view rights on the attachment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65089</link><description>XWiki Remote Macros provides XWiki rendering macros that are useful when migrating content from Confluence. Prior to version 1.27.0, a user with no view rights on a page may see the content of an office attachment displayed with the view file macro. This issue has been patched in version 1.27.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65095 | Lookyloo is vulnerable due to improper user input sanitization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65095</link><description>Lookyloo is a web interface that allows users to capture a website page and then display a tree of domains that call each other. Prior to version 1.35.1, there is potential cross-site scripting on index and tree page. This issue has been patched in version 1.35.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63210 | The Newtec Celox UHD (models: CELOXA504, CELOXA820) running firmware version celox-21.6.13 is vulnerable to an authentication bypass. An att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63210</link><description>The Newtec Celox UHD (models: CELOXA504, CELOXA820) running firmware version celox-21.6.13 is vulnerable to an authentication bypass. An attacker can exploit this issue by modifying intercepted responses from the /celoxservice endpoint. By injecting a forged response body during the loginWithUserName flow, the attacker can gain Superuser or Operator access without providing valid credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65025 | esm.sh CDN service has arbitrary file write via tarslip</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65025</link><description>esm.sh is a nobuild content delivery network(CDN) for modern web development. Prior to version 136, the esm.sh CDN service is vulnerable to path traversal during NPM package tarball extraction. An attacker can craft a malicious NPM package containing specially crafted file paths (e.g., package/../../tmp/evil.js). When esm.sh downloads and extracts this package, files may be written to arbitrary locations on the server, escaping the intended extraction directory. This issue has been patched in version 136.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65026 | esm.sh CDN service has JS Template Literal Injection in CSS-to-JavaScript</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65026</link><description>esm.sh is a nobuild content delivery network(CDN) for modern web development. Prior to version 136, The esm.sh CDN service contains a Template Literal Injection vulnerability (CWE-94) in its CSS-to-JavaScript module conversion feature. When a CSS file is requested with the ?module query parameter, esm.sh converts it to a JavaScript module by embedding the CSS content directly into a template literal without proper sanitization. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript code using ${...} expressions within CSS files, which will execute when the module is imported by victim applications. This enables Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in browsers and Remote Code Execution (RCE) in Electron applications. This issue has been patched in version 136.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65099 | Claude Code vulnerable to command execution prior to startup trust dialog</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65099</link><description>Claude Code is an agentic coding tool. Prior to version 1.0.39, when running on a machine with Yarn 3.0 or above, Claude Code could have been tricked to execute code contained in a project via yarn plugins before the user accepted the startup trust dialog. Exploiting this would have required a user to start Claude Code in an untrusted directory and to be using Yarn 3.0 or above. This issue has been patched in version 1.0.39.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63207 | The R.V.R Elettronica TEX product (firmware TEXL-000400, Web GUI TLAN-000400) is vulnerable to broken access control due to improper authent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63207</link><description>The R.V.R Elettronica TEX product (firmware TEXL-000400, Web GUI TLAN-000400) is vulnerable to broken access control due to improper authentication checks on the /_Passwd.html endpoint. An attacker can send an unauthenticated POST request to change the Admin, Operator, and User passwords, resulting in complete system compromise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63208 | An issue was discovered in bridgetech VB288 Objective QoE Content Extractor, firmware version 5.6.0-8, allowing attackers to gain sensitive ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63208</link><description>An issue was discovered in bridgetech VB288 Objective QoE Content Extractor, firmware version 5.6.0-8, allowing attackers to gain sensitive information such as administrator passwords via the /probe/core/setup/passwd endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63209 | The ELCA Star Transmitter Remote Control firmware 1.25 for STAR150, BP1000, STAR300, STAR2000, STAR1000, STAR500, and possibly other models,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63209</link><description>The ELCA Star Transmitter Remote Control firmware 1.25 for STAR150, BP1000, STAR300, STAR2000, STAR1000, STAR500, and possibly other models, contains an information disclosure vulnerability allowing unauthenticated attackers to retrieve admin credentials and system settings via an unprotected /setup.xml endpoint. The admin password is stored in plaintext under the  XML tag, potentially leading to remote compromise of the transmitter system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65020 | Rallly Has Unauthorized Poll Duplication via Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65020</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in the poll duplication endpoint (/api/trpc/polls.duplicate) allows any authenticated user to duplicate polls they do not own by modifying the pollId parameter. This effectively bypasses access control and lets unauthorized users clone private or administrative polls. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65021 | Rallly Has Unauthorized Poll Finalization via Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65021</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability exists in the poll finalization feature of the application. Any authenticated user can finalize a poll they do not own by manipulating the pollId parameter in the request. This allows unauthorized users to finalize other users’ polls and convert them into events without proper authorization checks, potentially disrupting user workflows and causing data integrity and availability issues. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65028 | Rallly Has an IDOR Vulnerability in Vote Update Endpoint Allows Unauthorized Manipulation of Participant Votes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65028</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability allows any authenticated user to modify other participants’ votes in polls without authorization. The backend relies solely on the participantId parameter to identify which votes to update, without verifying ownership or poll permissions. This allows an attacker to alter poll results in their favor, directly compromising data integrity. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65029 | Rallly Has an IDOR Vulnerability in Participant Deletion Endpoint Allows Unauthorized Removal of Poll Participants</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65029</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability allows any authenticated user to delete arbitrary participants from polls without ownership verification. The endpoint relies solely on a participant ID to authorize deletions, enabling attackers to remove other users (including poll owners) from polls. This impacts the integrity and availability of poll participation data. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65030 | Rallly Improper Authorization in Comment Deletion Endpoint Allows Unauthorized Comment Removal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65030</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an authorization flaw in the comment deletion API allows any authenticated user to delete comments belonging to other users, including poll owners and administrators. The endpoint relies solely on the comment ID for deletion and does not validate whether the requesting user owns the comment or has permission to remove it. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65031 | Rallly Improper Authorization in Comment Endpoint Allows User Impersonation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65031</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an improper authorization flaw in the comment creation endpoint allows authenticated users to impersonate any other user by altering the authorName field in the API request. This enables attackers to post comments under arbitrary usernames, including privileged ones such as administrators, potentially misleading other users and enabling phishing or social engineering attacks. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65032 | Rallly Has an IDOR Vulnerability in Participant Rename Function Allows Unauthorized Modification of Other Users’ Names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65032</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability allows any authenticated user to change the display names of other participants in polls without being an admin or the poll owner. By manipulating the participantId parameter in a rename request, an attacker can modify another user’s name, violating data integrity and potentially causing confusion or impersonation attacks. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65033 | Rallly Broken Authorization: Any User Can Pause or Resume Any Poll via Poll ID Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65033</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an authorization flaw in the poll management feature allows any authenticated user to pause or resume any poll, regardless of ownership. The system only uses the public pollId to identify polls, and it does not verify whether the user performing the action is the poll owner. As a result, any user can disrupt polls created by others, leading to a loss of integrity and availability across the application. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65034 | Rallly Improper Authorization Allows Reopening of Any Finalized Poll via Public pollId</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65034</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an improper authorization vulnerability allows any authenticated user to reopen finalized polls belonging to other users by manipulating the pollId parameter. This can disrupt events managed by other users and compromise both availability and integrity of poll data. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63205 | An issue was discovered in bridgetech probes VB220 IP Network Probe,VB120 Embedded IP + RF Probe, VB330 High-Capacity Probe, VB440 ST 2110 P...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63205</link><description>An issue was discovered in bridgetech probes VB220 IP Network Probe,VB120 Embedded IP + RF Probe, VB330 High-Capacity Probe, VB440 ST 2110 Production Analytics Probe, and NOMAD, firmware versions 6.5.0-9, allowing attackers to gain sensitive information such as administrator passwords via the /probe/core/setup/passwd endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63206 | An authentication bypass issue was discovered in Dasan Switch DS2924 web based interface, firmware versions 1.01.18 and 1.02.00, allowing at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63206</link><description>An authentication bypass issue was discovered in Dasan Switch DS2924 web based interface, firmware versions 1.01.18 and 1.02.00, allowing attackers to gain escalated privileges via storing crafted cookies in the web browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13400 | Tenda CH22 WrlExtraGet formWrlExtraGet buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13400</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda CH22 1.0.0.1. Affected is the function formWrlExtraGet of the file /goform/WrlExtraGet. Performing manipulation of the argument chkHz results in buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64521 | authentik deactivated service accounts can authenticate to OAuth</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64521</link><description>authentik is an open-source Identity Provider. Prior to versions 2025.8.5 and 2025.10.2, when authenticating with client_id and client_secret to an OAuth provider, authentik creates a service account for the provider. In previous authentik versions, authentication for this account was possible even when the account was deactivated. Other permissions are correctly applied and federation with other providers still take assigned policies correctly into account. authentik versions 2025.8.5 and 2025.10.2 fix this issue. A workaround involves adding a policy to the application that explicitly checks if the service account is still valid, and deny access if not.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64708 | authentik invitation expiry is delayed by at least 5 minutes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64708</link><description>authentik is an open-source Identity Provider. Prior to versions 2025.8.5 and 2025.10.2, in previous authentik versions, invitations were considered valid regardless if they are expired or not, thus relying on background tasks to clean up expired ones. In a normal scenario this can take up to 5 minutes because the cleanup of expired objects is scheduled to run every 5 minutes. However, with a large amount of tasks in the backlog, this might take longer. authentik versions 2025.8.5 and 2025.10.2 fix this issue. A workaround involves creating a policy that explicitly checks whether the invitation is still valid, and then bind it to the invitation stage on the invitation flow, and denying access if the invitation is not valid.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12743 | SQL Injection in Looker Project Generation Endpoint Allows Access to Internal MySQL Database</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12743</link><description>The Looker endpoint for generating new projects from database connections allows users to specify "looker" as a connection name, which is a reserved internal name for Looker's internal MySQL database. The schemas parameter is vulnerable to SQL injection, enabling attackers to manipulate SELECT queries that are constructed and executed against the internal MySQL database. This vulnerability allows users with developer permissions to extract data from Looker's internal MySQL database.

Looker-hosted and Self-hosted were found to be vulnerable.
This issue has already been mitigated for Looker-hosted instances. No user action is required for these.


Self-hosted instances must be upgraded as soon as possible. This vulnerability has been patched in all supported versions of Self-hosted.
The versions below have all been updated to protect against this vulnerability. You can download these versions at the Looker download page  https://download.looker.com/ :
  *  24.12.106
  *  24.18.198+
  *  25.0.75
  *  25.6.63+
  *  25.8.45+
  *  25.10.33+
  *  25.12.1+
  *  25.14+</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64757 | Astro Development Server is Vulnerable to Arbitrary Local File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64757</link><description>Astro is a web framework. Prior to version 5.14.3, a vulnerability has been identified in the Astro framework's development server that allows arbitrary local file read access through the image optimization endpoint. The vulnerability affects Astro development environments and allows remote attackers to read any image file accessible to the Node.js process on the host system. This issue has been patched in version 5.14.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64764 | Astro is vulnerable to Reflected XSS via the server islands feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64764</link><description>Astro is a web framework. Prior to version 5.15.8, a reflected XSS vulnerability is present when the server islands feature is used in the targeted application, regardless of what was intended by the component template(s). This issue has been patched in version 5.15.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64765 | Astro middleware authentication checks based on url.pathname can be bypassed via url encoded values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64765</link><description>Astro is a web framework. Prior to version 5.15.8, a mismatch exists between how Astro normalizes request paths for routing/rendering and how the application’s middleware reads the path for validation checks. Astro internally applies decodeURI() to determine which route to render, while the middleware uses context.url.pathname without applying the same normalization (decodeURI). This discrepancy may allow attackers to reach protected routes using encoded path variants that pass routing but bypass validation checks. This issue has been patched in version 5.15.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65019 | Astro Cloudflare adapter has a Stored Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in /_image endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65019</link><description>Astro is a web framework. Prior to version 5.15.9, when using Astro's Cloudflare adapter (@astrojs/cloudflare) with output: 'server', the image optimization endpoint (/_image) contains a critical vulnerability in the isRemoteAllowed() function that unconditionally allows data: protocol URLs. This enables Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks through malicious SVG payloads, bypassing domain restrictions and Content Security Policy protections. This issue has been patched in version 5.15.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34328 | AudioCodes Fax/IVR Appliance &amp;lt;= 2.6.23 Unauthenticated File Upload RCE via ajaxScript.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34328</link><description>AudioCodes Fax Server and Auto-Attendant IVR appliances versions up to and including 2.6.23 include a web administration component (F2MAdmin) that exposes an unauthenticated script-management endpoint at AudioCodes_files/utils/IVR/diagram/ajaxScript.php. The saveScript action writes attacker-supplied data directly to a server-side file path under the privileges of the web service account, which runs as NT AUTHORITY\\SYSTEM on Windows deployments. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can write arbitrary files into the product’s web-accessible directory structure and subsequently execute them.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34329 | AudioCodes Fax/IVR Appliance &amp;lt;= 2.6.23 Unauthenticated Backup Upload RCE via ajaxBackupUploadFile.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34329</link><description>AudioCodes Fax Server and Auto-Attendant IVR appliances versions up to and including 2.6.23 expose an unauthenticated backup upload endpoint at AudioCodes_files/ajaxBackupUploadFile.php in the F2MAdmin web interface. The script derives a backup folder path from application configuration, creates the directory if it does not exist, and then moves an uploaded file to that location using the attacker-controlled filename, without any authentication, authorization, or file-type validation. On default Windows deployments where the backup directory resolves to the system drive, a remote attacker can upload web server or interpreter configuration files that cause a log file or other server-controlled resource to be treated as executable code. This allows subsequent HTTP requests to trigger arbitrary command execution under the web server account, which runs as NT AUTHORITY\\SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34330 | AudioCodes Fax/IVR Appliance &amp;lt;= 2.6.23 Unauthenticated Prompt File Upload via ajaxPromptUploadFile.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34330</link><description>AudioCodes Fax Server and Auto-Attendant IVR appliances versions up to and including 2.6.23 include a web administration component (F2MAdmin) that exposes an unauthenticated prompt upload endpoint at AudioCodes_files/utils/IVR/diagram/ajaxPromptUploadFile.php. The script accepts an uploaded file and writes it into the C:\\F2MAdmin\\tmp directory using a filename derived from application constants, without any authentication, authorization, or file-type validation. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can upload or overwrite prompt- or music-on-hold–related files in this directory, potentially leading to tampering with IVR audio content or preparing files for use in further attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34331 | AudioCodes Fax/IVR Appliance &amp;lt;= 2.6.23 Unauthenticated File Read via download.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34331</link><description>AudioCodes Fax Server and Auto-Attendant IVR appliances versions up to and including 2.6.23 contain an unauthenticated file read vulnerability via the download.php script. The endpoint exposes a file download mechanism that lacks access control, allowing remote, unauthenticated users to request files stored on the appliance based solely on attacker-supplied path and filename parameters. While limited to specific file extensions permitted by the application logic, sensitive backup archives can be retrieved, exposing internal databases and credential hashes. Successful exploitation may lead to disclosure of administrative password hashes and other sensitive configuration data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34332 | AudioCodes Fax/IVR Appliance &amp;lt;= 2.6.23 Insecure Service Control Scripts LPE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34332</link><description>AudioCodes Fax Server and Auto-Attendant IVR appliances versions up to and including 2.6.23 include a web administration component that controls back-end Windows services using helper batch scripts located under C:\\F2MAdmin\\F2E\\AudioCodes_files\\utils\\Services. When certain service actions are requested through ajaxPost.php, these scripts are invoked by PHP using system() under the NT AUTHORITY\\SYSTEM account. The batch files in this directory are writable by any authenticated local user due to overly permissive ACLs, allowing them to replace script contents with arbitrary commands. On the next service start/stop operation, the modified script is executed as SYSTEM, enabling elevation of local privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34333 | AudioCodes Fax/IVR Appliance &amp;lt;= 2.6.23 World-Writable Webroot LPE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34333</link><description>AudioCodes Fax Server and Auto-Attendant IVR appliances versions up to and including 2.6.23 configure the web document root at C:\\F2MAdmin\\F2E with overly permissive file system permissions. Authenticated local users have modify rights on this directory, while the associated web server process runs as NT AUTHORITY\\SYSTEM. As a result, any local user can create or alter server-side scripts within the webroot and then trigger them via HTTP requests, causing arbitrary code to execute with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34334 | AudioCodes Fax/IVR Appliance &amp;lt;= 2.6.23 Authenticated Command Injection via TestFax.php &amp;amp; LPE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34334</link><description>AudioCodes Fax Server and Auto-Attendant IVR appliances versions up to and including 2.6.23 are vulnerable to an authenticated command injection in the fax test functionality implemented by AudioCodes_files/TestFax.php. When a fax "send" test is requested, the application builds a faxsender command line using attacker-supplied parameters and passes it to GlobalUtils::RunBatchFile without proper validation or shell-argument sanitization. The resulting batch file is written into a temporary run directory and then executed via a backend service that runs as NT AUTHORITY\\SYSTEM. An authenticated attacker with access to the fax test interface can craft parameter values that inject additional shell commands into the generated batch file, leading to arbitrary command execution with SYSTEM privileges. In addition, because the generated batch files reside in a location with overly permissive file system permissions, a local low-privilege user on the server can modify pending batch files to achieve the same elevation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34335 | AudioCodes Fax/IVR Appliance &amp;lt;= 2.6.23 Authenticated Command Injection via ActivateLicense.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34335</link><description>AudioCodes Fax Server and Auto-Attendant IVR appliances versions up to and including 2.6.23 expose an authenticated command injection vulnerability in the license activation workflow handled by AudioCodes_files/ActivateLicense.php. When a license file is uploaded, the application derives a new filename by combining a generated base name with the attacker-controlled extension portion of the original upload name, then constructs a command line for fax_server_lic_cmdline.exe that includes this path. The extension value is incorporated into the command string without input validation, escaping, or proper argument quotation before being passed to exec(). An authenticated user with access to the license upload interface can supply a specially crafted filename whose extension injects additional shell metacharacters, causing arbitrary commands to be executed as NT AUTHORITY\\SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34336 | eGovFramework &amp;lt;= 4.3.1 Unauthenticated File Upload via Web Editor Image Upload Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34336</link><description>eGovFramework/egovframe-common-components versions up to and including 4.3.1 contain an unauthenticated file upload vulnerability via the /utl/wed/insertImage.do and /utl/wed/insertImageCk.do image upload endpoints. These controllers accept multipart requests without authentication, pass the uploaded content to a shared upload helper, and store the file on the server under a framework-controlled path. The framework then returns a download URL that can be used to retrieve the uploaded content, including an attacker-controlled Content-Type within the limits of the image upload functionality. While a filename extension whitelist is enforced, the attacker fully controls the file contents. The response MIME type used is also attacker-controlled when the file is served up to version &lt; 4.1.2. Since version 4.1.2, it is possible to download any image uploaded with any whitelisted content type. But any file uploaded other than an image will be served with the `application/octet-stream` content type (the content type is no longer controlled by the attacker since version 4.1.2). This enables an unauthenticated attacker to use any affected application as a persistent file hosting service for arbitrary content under the application's origin. KISA/KrCERT has identified this unpatched vulnerability as "KVE-2023-5280."</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34337 | eGovFramework &amp;lt;= 4.3.1 Unauthenticated Encryption Oracle via Web Editor Image Upload Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34337</link><description>eGovFramework/egovframe-common-components versions up to and including 4.3.1 includes Web Editor image upload and related file delivery functionality that uses symmetric encryption to protect URL parameters, but exposes an encryption oracle that allows attackers to generate valid ciphertext for chosen values. The image upload endpoints /utl/wed/insertImage.do and /utl/wed/insertImageCk.do encrypt server-side paths, filenames, and MIME types and embed them directly into a download URL that is returned to the client. Because these same encrypted parameters are trusted by other endpoints, such as /utl/web/imageSrc.do and /cmm/fms/getImage.do, an unauthenticated attacker can abuse the upload functionality to obtain encrypted representations of attacker-chosen identifiers and then replay those ciphertext values to file-serving APIs. This design failure allows an attacker to bypass access controls that rely solely on the secrecy of encrypted parameters and retrieve arbitrary stored files that are otherwise expected to require an existing session or specific authorization context. KISA/KrCERT has identified this unpatched vulnerability as "KVE-2023-5281."</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12766 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in the Management Console of affected versions of BlackBerry AtHoc.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12766</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in the Management Console of BlackBerry® AtHoc® (OnPrem) version 7.21 could allow an attacker to potentially gain unauthorized knowledge about other organizations hosted on the same Interactive Warning System (IWS).</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63223 | The Axel Technology StreamerMAX MK II devices (firmware versions 0.8.5 to 1.0.3) are vulnerable to Broken Access Control due to missing auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63223</link><description>The Axel Technology StreamerMAX MK II devices (firmware versions 0.8.5 to 1.0.3) are vulnerable to Broken Access Control due to missing authentication on the /cgi-bin/gstFcgi.fcgi endpoint. Unauthenticated remote attackers can list user accounts, create new administrative users, delete users, and modify system settings, leading to full compromise of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63224 | The Itel DAB Encoder (IDEnc build 25aec8d) is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to improper JWT validation across devices. Attackers c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63224</link><description>The Itel DAB Encoder (IDEnc build 25aec8d) is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to improper JWT validation across devices. Attackers can reuse a valid JWT token obtained from one device to authenticate and gain administrative access to any other device running the same firmware, even if the passwords and networks are different. This allows full compromise of affected devices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65022 | i-Educar Authenticated Time-based SQL Injection in `agenda.php`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65022</link><description>i-Educar is free, fully online school management software. In versions 2.10.0 and prior, an authenticated time-based SQL injection vulnerability exists in the ieducar/intranet/agenda.php script. An attacker with access to an authenticated session can execute arbitrary SQL commands against the application's database. This vulnerability is caused by the improper handling of the cod_agenda request parameter, which is directly concatenated into multiple SQL queries without proper sanitization. This issue has been patched in commit b473f92.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65023 | i-Educar Authenticated Time-based SQL Injection in `funcionario_vinculo_cad.php`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65023</link><description>i-Educar is free, fully online school management software. In versions 2.10.0 and prior, an authenticated time-based SQL injection vulnerability exists in the ieducar/intranet/funcionario_vinculo_cad.php script. An attacker with access to an authenticated session can execute arbitrary SQL commands against the application's database. This vulnerability is caused by the improper handling of the cod_funcionario_vinculo GET parameter, which is directly concatenated into an SQL query without proper sanitization. This issue has been patched in commit a00dfa3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65024 | i-Educar Authenticated Time-based SQL Injection in `agenda_admin_cad.php`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65024</link><description>i-Educar is free, fully online school management software. In versions 2.10.0 and prior, an authenticated time-based SQL injection vulnerability exists in the ieducar/intranet/agenda_admin_cad.php script. An attacker with access to an authenticated session can execute arbitrary SQL commands against the application's database. This vulnerability is caused by the improper handling of the cod_agenda GET parameter, which is directly concatenated into an SQL query without proper sanitization. This issue has been patched in commit 3e9763a.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63879 | A reflected cross-site scripted (XSS) vulnerability in the /ecommerce/products.php component of E-commerce Project v1.0 and earlier allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63879</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripted (XSS) vulnerability in the /ecommerce/products.php component of E-commerce Project v1.0 and earlier allows attackers to execute arbitrary Javascript in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload into the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10702 | Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Progress DataDirect Connect for JDBC drivers, Progress DataDirect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10702</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Progress DataDirect Connect for JDBC drivers, Progress DataDirect Open Access JDBC driver and Hybrid Data Pipeline allows Remote Code Inclusion.


The SpyAttribute connection option implemented by the DataDirect Connect for JDBC drivers, DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline JDBC driver and the DataDirect OpenAccess JDBC driver supports an undocumented syntax construct for the option value that if discovered can be used by an attacker.  If an application allows an end user to specify a value for the SpyAttributes connection option then an attacker can use the undocumented syntax to cause the driver to load an arbitrary class on the class path and execute a constructor on that class.  


This issue affects:

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Amazon Redshift: through 6.0.0.001392, fixed in 6.0.0.001541

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Apache Cassandra: through 6.0.0.000805, fixed in 6.0.0.000833

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Hive: through 6.0.1.001499, fixed in 6.0.1.001628

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Apache Impala: through 6.0.0.001155, fixed in 6.0.0.001279

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Apache SparkSQL: through 6.0.1.001222, fixed in 6.0.1.001344

DataDirect Connect for JDBC Autonomous REST Connector: through 6.0.1.006961, fixed in 6.0.1.007063

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for DB2: through 6.0.0.000717, fixed in 6.0.0.000964

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Google Analytics 4: through 6.0.0.000454, fixed in 6.0.0.000525

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Google BigQuery: through 6.0.0.002279, fixed in 6.0.0.002410
DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Greenplum: through 6.0.0.001712, fixed in 6.0.0.001727
DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Informix: through 6.0.0.000690, fixed in 6.0.0.0851


DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Microsoft Dynamics 365: through 6.0.0.003161, fixed in 6.0.0.3198

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Microsoft SQLServer: through 6.0.0.001936, fixed in 6.0.0.001957

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Microsoft Sharepoint: through 6.0.0.001559, fixed in 6.0.0.001587

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for MongoDB: through 6.1.0.001654, fixed in 6.1.0.001669

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for MySQL: through 5.1.4.000330, fixed in 5.1.4.000364

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Oracle Database: through 6.0.0.001747, fixed in 6.0.0.001776

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Oracle Eloqua: through 6.0.0.001438, fixed in 6.0.0.001458

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Oracle Sales Cloud: through 6.0.0.001225, fixed in 6.0.0.001316

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Oracle Service Cloud: through 5.1.4.000298, fixed in 5.1.4.000309
DataDirect Connect for JDBC for PostgreSQL: through 6.0.0.001843, fixed in 6.0.0.001856

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Progress OpenEdge: through 5.1.4.000187, fixed in 5.1.4.000189

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Salesforce: through 6.0.0.003020, fixed in 6.0.0.003125
DataDirect Connect for JDBC for SAP HANA: through 6.0.0.000879, product retired

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for SAP S/4 HANA: through 6.0.1.001818, fixed in 6.0.1.001858

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Sybase ASE: through 5.1.4.000161, fixed in 5.1.4.000162

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Snowflake: through 6.0.1.001821, fixed in 6.0.1.001856

DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline Server: through 4.6.2.3309, fixed in 4.6.2.3430

DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline JDBC Driver: through 4.6.2.0607, fixed in 4.6.2.1023

DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline On Premises Connector: through 4.6.2.1223, fixed in 4.6.2.1339
DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline Docker: through 4.6.2.3316, fixed in 4.6.2.3430

DataDirect OpenAccess JDBC Driver: through 8.1.0.0177, fixed in 8.1.0.0183

DataDirect OpenAccess JDBC Driver: through 9.0.0.0019, fixed in 9.0.0.0022</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:57:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10703 | Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Progress DataDirect Connect for JDBC drivers, Progress DataDirect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10703</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Progress DataDirect Connect for JDBC drivers, Progress DataDirect Open Access JDBC driver and Hybrid Data Pipeline allows Remote Code Inclusion.

The SpyAttribute connection option implemented by the DataDirect Connect for JDBC drivers, DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline JDBC driver and the DataDirect OpenAccess JDBC driver log=(file) construct allows the user to specify an arbitrary file for the JDBC driver to write its log information to.  If an application allows an end user to specify a value for the SpyAttributes connection option then an attacker could cause java script to be written to a log file.  If the log file was in the correct location with the correct extension, an application server could see that log file as a resource to be served.  The attacker could fetch the resource from the server causing the java script to be executed.





This issue affects:



DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Amazon Redshift: through 6.0.0.001392, fixed in 6.0.0.001541

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Apache Cassandra: through 6.0.0.000805, fixed in 6.0.0.000833

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Hive: through 6.0.1.001499, fixed in 6.0.1.001628

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Apache Impala: through 6.0.0.001155, fixed in 6.0.0.001279

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Apache SparkSQL: through 6.0.1.001222, fixed in 6.0.1.001344

DataDirect Connect for JDBC Autonomous REST Connector: through 6.0.1.006961, fixed in 6.0.1.007063

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for DB2: through 6.0.0.000717, fixed in 6.0.0.000964

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Google Analytics 4: through 6.0.0.000454, fixed in 6.0.0.000525

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Google BigQuery: through 6.0.0.002279, fixed in 6.0.0.002410
DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Greenplum: through 6.0.0.001712, fixed in 6.0.0.001727
DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Informix: through 6.0.0.000690, fixed in 6.0.0.0851


DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Microsoft Dynamics 365: through 6.0.0.003161, fixed in 6.0.0.3198

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Microsoft SQLServer: through 6.0.0.001936, fixed in 6.0.0.001957

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Microsoft Sharepoint: through 6.0.0.001559, fixed in 6.0.0.001587

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for MongoDB: through 6.1.0.001654, fixed in 6.1.0.001669

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for MySQL: through 5.1.4.000330, fixed in 5.1.4.000364

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Oracle Database: through 6.0.0.001747, fixed in 6.0.0.001776

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Oracle Eloqua: through 6.0.0.001438, fixed in 6.0.0.001458

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Oracle Sales Cloud: through 6.0.0.001225, fixed in 6.0.0.001316

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Oracle Service Cloud: through 5.1.4.000298, fixed in 5.1.4.000309
DataDirect Connect for JDBC for PostgreSQL: through 6.0.0.001843, fixed in 6.0.0.001856


DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Progress OpenEdge: through 5.1.4.000187, fixed in 5.1.4.000189

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Salesforce: through 6.0.0.003020, fixed in 6.0.0.003125
DataDirect Connect for JDBC for SAP HANA: through 6.0.0.000879, product retired

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for SAP S/4 HANA: through 6.0.1.001818, fixed in 6.0.1.001858

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Sybase ASE: through 5.1.4.000161, fixed in 5.1.4.000162

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Snowflake: through 6.0.1.001821, fixed in 6.0.1.001856

DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline Server: through 4.6.2.3309, fixed in 4.6.2.3430

DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline JDBC Driver: through 4.6.2.0607, fixed in 4.6.2.1023

DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline On Premises Connector: through 4.6.2.1223, fixed in 4.6.2.1339
DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline Docker: through 4.6.2.3316, fixed in 4.6.2.3430

DataDirect OpenAccess JDBC Driver: through 8.1.0.0177, fixed in 8.1.0.0183

DataDirect OpenAccess JDBC Driver: through 9.0.0.0019, fixed in 9.0.0.0022</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:57:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63221 | The Axel Technology puma devices (firmware versions 0.8.5 to 1.0.3) are vulnerable to Broken Access Control due to missing authentication on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63221</link><description>The Axel Technology puma devices (firmware versions 0.8.5 to 1.0.3) are vulnerable to Broken Access Control due to missing authentication on the /cgi-bin/gstFcgi.fcgi endpoint. Unauthenticated remote attackers can list user accounts, create new administrative users, delete users, and modify system settings, leading to full compromise of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:57:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63220 | The Sound4 FIRST web-based management interface is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) via a malicious firmware update package. The up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63220</link><description>The Sound4 FIRST web-based management interface is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) via a malicious firmware update package. The update mechanism fails to validate the integrity of manual.sh, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary commands by modifying this script and repackaging the firmware.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13396 | code-projects Courier Management System add-office.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13396</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Courier Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /add-office.php. This manipulation of the argument OfficeName causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13397 | mrubyc alloc.c mrbc_raw_realloc null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13397</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in mrubyc up to 3.4. This impacts the function mrbc_raw_realloc of the file src/alloc.c. Such manipulation of the argument ptr leads to null pointer dereference. An attack has to be approached locally. The name of the patch is 009111904807b8567262036bf45297c3da8f1c87. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63878 | Github Restaurant Website Restoran v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the Contact Form page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63878</link><description>Github Restaurant Website Restoran v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the Contact Form page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63219 | The ITEL ISO FM SFN Adapter (firmware ISO2 2.0.0.0, WebServer 2.0) is vulnerable to session hijacking due to improper session management on ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63219</link><description>The ITEL ISO FM SFN Adapter (firmware ISO2 2.0.0.0, WebServer 2.0) is vulnerable to session hijacking due to improper session management on the /home.html endpoint. An attacker can access an active session without authentication, allowing them to control the device, modify configurations, and compromise system integrity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63218 | The Axel Technology WOLF1MS and WOLF2MS devices (firmware versions 0.8.5 to 1.0.3) are vulnerable to Broken Access Control due to missing au...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63218</link><description>The Axel Technology WOLF1MS and WOLF2MS devices (firmware versions 0.8.5 to 1.0.3) are vulnerable to Broken Access Control due to missing authentication on the /cgi-bin/gstFcgi.fcgi endpoint. Unauthenticated remote attackers can list user accounts, create new administrative users, delete users, and modify system settings, leading to full compromise of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63243 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the password change functionality of Pixeon WebLaudos 25.1 (01). The sle_sSen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63243</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the password change functionality of Pixeon WebLaudos 25.1 (01). The sle_sSenha parameter to the loginAlterarSenha.asp file. An attacker can craft a malicious URL that, when visited by a victim, causes arbitrary JavaScript code to be executed in the victim's browser within the security context of the vulnerable application. This issue could allow attackers to steal session cookies, disclose sensitive information, perform unauthorized actions on behalf of the user, or conduct phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 14:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11963 | Reflected XSS in Saysis&amp;#x27;s StarCities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11963</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Saysis Computer Systems Trade Ltd. Co. StarCities allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects StarCities: before 1.1.61.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 14:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0421 | iFrame Injection in Mikrogrup&amp;#x27;s Shopside</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0421</link><description>Improper Restriction of Rendered UI Layers or Frames vulnerability in Shopside Software Technologies Inc. Shopside allows iFrame Overlay.This issue affects Shopside: through 05022025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 13:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8527 | ALC WebCTRL Carrier i-Vu Open Redirect via URL parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8527</link><description>Open Redirect in URL parameter in Automated Logic WebCTRL and Carrier i-Vu versions 6.0, 6.5, 7.0, 8.0, 8.5, 9.0 may allow attackers to exploit user sessions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 13:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8528 | ALC WebCTRL Carrier i-Vu Reflected XSS due to unsanitized parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8528</link><description>Reflected XSS using a specific URL in Automated Logic WebCTRL and Carrier i-VU can allow delivery of malicious payload due to a specific GET parameter not being sanitized.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 13:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12592 | Use of default login credentials in Legacy Vivotek Devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12592</link><description>Legacy Vivotek Device firmware uses default credetials for the root and user login accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 12:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10437 | SQLi in Exagate&amp;#x27;s Webpack Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10437</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Eksagate Electronic Engineering and Computer Industry Trade Inc. Webpack Management System allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Webpack Management System: through 20251119.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13395 | codehub666 94list function.php login sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13395</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in codehub666 94list up to 5831c8240e99a72b7d3508c79ef46ae4b96befe8. The impacted element is the function Login of the file /function.php. The manipulation results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12472 | Remote Code Execution in Looker due to Improperly Validated Directory Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12472</link><description>An attacker with a Looker Developer role could manipulate a LookML project to exploit a race condition during Git directory deletion, leading to arbitrary command execution on the Looker instance.



Looker-hosted and Self-hosted were found to be vulnerable.
This issue has already been mitigated for Looker-hosted instances. No user action is required for these.


Self-hosted instances must be upgraded as soon as possible. This vulnerability has been patched in all supported versions of Self-hosted.
The versions below have all been updated to protect from this vulnerability. You can download these versions at the Looker download page  https://download.looker.com/ :
  *  24.12.103+
  *  24.18.195+
  *  25.0.72+
  *  25.6.60+
  *  25.8.42+
  *  25.10.22+</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 10:47:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64408 | Apache Causeway: Java deserialization vulnerability to authenticated attackers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64408</link><description>Apache Causeway faces Java deserialization vulnerabilities that allow remote code execution (RCE) through user-controllable URL parameters. These vulnerabilities affect all applications using Causeway's ViewModel functionality and can be exploited by authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code with application privileges. 

This issue affects all current versions.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.5.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 10:47:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58412 | A improper neutralization of script-related html tags in a web page (basic xss) vulnerability in Fortinet FortiADC 8.0.0, FortiADC 7.6.0 thr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58412</link><description>A improper neutralization of script-related html tags in a web page (basic xss) vulnerability in Fortinet FortiADC 8.0.0, FortiADC 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, FortiADC 7.4 all versions, FortiADC 7.2 all versions may allow attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 09:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11230 | Denial of service vulnerability in HAProxy mjson library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11230</link><description>Inefficient algorithm complexity in mjson in HAProxy allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via specially crafted JSON requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 09:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11446 | Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in upKeeper Solutions upKeeper Manager allows Use of Known Domain Credentials...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11446</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in upKeeper Solutions upKeeper Manager allows Use of Known Domain Credentials.This issue affects upKeeper Manager: from 5.2.0 before 5.2.12.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 08:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12484 | Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress – Get More Website Traffic, Email Subscribers, and Social Followers &amp;lt;= 1.12.19 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12484</link><description>The Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress – Get More Website Traffic, Email Subscribers, and Social Followers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple social media username parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 07:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13035 | Code Snippets &amp;lt;= 3.9.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Code Injection via extract() and PHP Filter Chains</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13035</link><description>The Code Snippets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Code Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.1. This is due to the plugin's use of extract() on attacker-controlled shortcode attributes within the `evaluate_shortcode_from_flat_file` method, which can be used to overwrite the `$filepath` variable and subsequently passed to require_once. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to execute arbitrary PHP code on the server via the `[code_snippet]` shortcode using PHP filter chains granted they can trick an administrator into enabling the "Enable file-based execution" setting and creating at least one active Content snippet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 07:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13206 | GiveWP - Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform &amp;lt;= 4.13.0 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;name&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13206</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘name’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.13.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Avatars must be enabled in the WordPress install in order to exploit the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 07:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11243 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in Shelly Pro 4PM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11243</link><description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in Shelly Pro 4PM (before v1.6) allows Excessive Allocation via network.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 06:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12056 | Out-of-bounds Read in Shelly Pro 3EM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12056</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read in Shelly Pro 3EM (before v1.4.4) allows Overread Buffers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 06:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12535 | SureForms &amp;lt;= 1.13.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery Protection Bypass via Improper Nonce Distribution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12535</link><description>The SureForms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.1. This is due to the plugin distributing generic WordPress REST API nonces (wp_rest) to unauthenticated users via the 'wp_ajax_nopriv_rest-nonce' action. While the plugin legitimately needs to support unauthenticated form submissions, it incorrectly uses generic REST nonces instead of form-specific nonces. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass CSRF protection on REST API endpoints that rely solely on nonce verification without additional authentication checks, allowing them to trigger unauthorized actions such as the plugin's own post-submission hooks and potentially other plugins' REST endpoints.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 06:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13085 | SiteSEO – SEO Simplified &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Sensitive Post Meta Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13085</link><description>The SiteSEO – SEO Simplified plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Improper Authorization leading to Sensitive Post Meta Disclosure in versions up to and including 1.3.2. This is due to missing object-level authorization checks in the resolve_variables() AJAX handler. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with the siteseo_manage capability (e.g., Author-level users who have been granted SiteSEO access by an administrator) to read arbitrary post metadata from any post, page, attachment, or WooCommerce order they cannot edit, via the custom field variable resolution feature granted they have been given access to SiteSEO by an administrator and legacy storage is enabled. In affected WooCommerce installations, this exposes sensitive customer billing information including names, email addresses, phone numbers, physical addresses, and payment methods.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 06:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12057 | WavePlayer &amp;lt; 3.8.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12057</link><description>The WavePlayer WordPress plugin before 3.8.0 does not have authorization in an AJAX action as well as does not validate the file to be copied locally, allowing unauthenticated users to upload arbitrary file on the server and lead to RCE</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 06:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12174 | Directorist: AI-Powered Business Directory Plugin with Classified Ads Listings &amp;lt;= 8.5.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Data Export and Slug Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12174</link><description>The Directorist: AI-Powered Business Directory Plugin with Classified Ads Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the 'directorist_prepare_listings_export_file' and 'directorist_type_slug_change' AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 8.5.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to export listing details and change the directorist slug.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12359 | Responsive Lightbox &amp;amp; Gallery &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Authenticated (Author+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12359</link><description>The Responsive Lightbox &amp; Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.3 via the 'get_image_size_by_url' function. This is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied URLs when determining image dimensions for gallery items. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application which can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12646 | Community Events &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12646</link><description>The Community Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'dayofyear' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12710 | Pet-Manager – Petfinder &amp;lt;= 3.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via kwm-petfinder Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12710</link><description>The Pet-Manager – Petfinder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the kwm-petfinder shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12751 | WSChat – WordPress Live Chat &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12751</link><description>The WSChat – WordPress Live Chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'reset_settings' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to reset the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12814 | SiteSEO – SEO Simplified &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Improper Authorization to Authenticated Settings Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12814</link><description>The SiteSEO – SEO Simplified plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to n incorrect capability check on the siteseo_reset_settings function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, who have been granted access to at least on SiteSEO setting capability, to reset the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12822 | WP Login and Register using JWT &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) API Key Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12822</link><description>The WP Login and Register using JWT plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'mo_jwt_generate_new_api_key' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to generate a new API key on site's that do not have an API key configured and subsequently use that to access restricted endpoints.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12842 | Booking Plugin for WordPress Appointments – Time Slot &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Email Sending</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12842</link><description>The Booking Plugin for WordPress Appointments – Time Slot plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized email sending in versions up to, and including, 1.4.7 due to missing validation on the tslot_appt_email AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send appointment notification emails to arbitrary recipients with attacker-controlled text content in certain email fields, potentially enabling the site to be abused for phishing campaigns or spam distribution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12878 | FunnelKit – Funnel Builder for WooCommerce Checkout &amp;lt;= 3.13.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wfop_phone Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12878</link><description>The FunnelKit – Funnel Builder for WooCommerce Checkout plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `wfop_phone` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.13.1.2. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the user-supplied `default` attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13054 | User Profile Builder – Beautiful User Registration Forms, User Profiles &amp;amp; User Role Editor &amp;lt;= 3.14.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13054</link><description>The User Profile Builder – Beautiful User Registration Forms, User Profiles &amp; User Role Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wppb-embed shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.14.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13145 | WP Import – Ultimate CSV XML Importer for WordPress &amp;lt;= 7.33.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) PHP Object Injection via CSV Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13145</link><description>The WP Import – Ultimate CSV XML Importer for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 7.33.1. This is due to deserialization of untrusted data supplied via CSV file imports in the import_single_post_as_csv function within SingleImportExport.php. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access or higher, to inject a PHP object. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12349 | Email Subscribers &amp;amp; Newsletters &amp;lt;= 5.9.10 - Missing Authentication to Unauthenticated Mailing Queue Trigger</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12349</link><description>The Icegram Express - Email Subscribers, Newsletters and Marketing Automation Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authorization in versions up to, and including, 5.9.10. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action in the `trigger_mailing_queue_sending` function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to force immediate email sending, bypass the schedule, increase server load, and change plugin state (e.g., last-cron-hit), enabling abuse or DoS-like effects.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 04:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12426 | Quiz Maker &amp;lt;= 6.7.0.80 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12426</link><description>The Quiz Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 6.7.0.80. This is due to the plugin exposing quiz answers through the ays_quiz_check_answer AJAX action without proper authorization checks. The endpoint only validates a nonce, but that same nonce is publicly available to all site visitors via the quiz_maker_ajax_public localized script data. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including quiz answers for any quiz question.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 04:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12427 | YITH WooCommerce Wishlist &amp;lt;= 4.10.0 - Unauthenticated Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Wishlist Rename</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12427</link><description>The YITH WooCommerce Wishlist plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.0 via the REST API endpoint and AJAX handler due to missing validation on user-controlled keys. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to discover any user's wishlist token ID, and subsequently rename the victim's wishlist without authorization (integrity impact). This can be exploited to target multi-user stores for defacement, social engineering attacks, mass tampering, and profiling at scale.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 03:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12770 | New User Approve &amp;lt;= 3.0.9 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Disclosure via Type Juggling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12770</link><description>The New User Approve plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized data disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.9 due to insufficient API key validation using loose equality comparison. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve personally identifiable information (PII), including usernames and email addresses of users with various approval statuses via the Zapier REST API endpoints, by exploiting PHP type juggling with the api_key parameter set to "0" on sites where the Zapier API key has not been configured.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 03:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12777 | YITH WooCommerce Wishlist &amp;lt;= 4.10.0 - Unauthenticated Wishlist Token Disclosure to Wishlist Item Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12777</link><description>The YITH WooCommerce Wishlist plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.0. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform actions on the REST API /wp-json/yith/wishlist/v1/lists endpoint (which uses permission_callback =&gt; '__return_true') and the AJAX delete_item handler (which only checks nonce validity without verifying object-level authorization). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to disclose wishlist tokens for any user and subsequently delete wishlist items by chaining the REST API authorization bypass with the exposed delete_item nonce on shared wishlist pages and the AJAX handler's missing object-level authorization check.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 03:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6251 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.7.1036 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6251</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via $item['field_id'] in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1036 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 03:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13051 | Windows service used an uncontrolled search path element will cause unauthorized code execution with localsystem privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13051</link><description>When the service of ABP and AES is installed in a directory writable by non-administrative users, an attacker can replace or plant a DLL with the same name as one loaded by the service. Upon service restart, the malicious DLL is loaded and executed under the LocalSystem account, resulting in unauthorized code execution with elevated privileges.
This issue affects ABP and AES: from ABP 2.0 through 2.0.7.9050, from AES 1.0 through 1.0.6.8290.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 03:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13225 | Tanium addressed an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in TanOS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13225</link><description>Tanium addressed an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in TanOS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 03:04:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12852 | DLL Loading vulnerability in NEC Corporation RakurakuMusen Start EX All Verisons allows a attacker to manipulate the PC environment to cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12852</link><description>DLL Loading vulnerability in NEC Corporation RakurakuMusen Start EX All Verisons allows a attacker to manipulate the PC environment to cause unintended operations on the user's device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65013 | LibreNMS vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in endpoint `/maps/nodeimage` parameter `Image Name`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65013</link><description>LibreNMS is an auto-discovering PHP/MySQL/SNMP based network monitoring tool. Prior to version 25.11.0, a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the LibreNMS application at the /maps/nodeimage endpoint. The Image Name parameter is reflected in the HTTP response without proper output encoding or sanitization, allowing an attacker to craft a URL that, when visited by a victim, causes arbitrary JavaScript execution in the victim’s browser. This issue has been patched in version 25.11.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 23:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65014 | LibreNMS has Weak Password Policy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65014</link><description>LibreNMS is an auto-discovering PHP/MySQL/SNMP based network monitoring tool. Prior to version 25.11.0, a weak password policy vulnerability was identified in the user management functionality of the LibreNMS application. This vulnerability allows administrators to create accounts with extremely weak and predictable passwords, such as 12345678. This exposes the platform to brute-force and credential stuffing attacks. This issue has been patched in version 25.11.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 23:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65015 | joserfc has Possible Uncontrolled Resource Consumption Vulnerability Triggered by Logging Arbitrarily Large JWT Token Payloads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65015</link><description>joserfc is a Python library that provides an implementation of several JSON Object Signing and Encryption (JOSE) standards. In versions from 1.3.3 to before 1.3.5 and from 1.4.0 to before 1.4.2, the ExceededSizeError exception messages are embedded with non-decoded JWT token parts and may cause Python logging to record an arbitrarily large, forged JWT payload. In situations where a misconfigured — or entirely absent — production-grade web server sits in front of a Python web application, an attacker may be able to send arbitrarily large bearer tokens in the HTTP request headers. When this occurs, Python logging or diagnostic tools (e.g., Sentry) may end up processing extremely large log messages containing the full JWT header during the joserfc.jwt.decode() operation. The same behavior also appears when validating claims and signature payload sizes, as the library raises joserfc.errors.ExceededSizeError() with the full payload embedded in the exception message. Since the payload is already fully loaded into memory at this stage, the library cannot prevent or reject it. This issue has been patched in versions 1.3.5 and 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 23:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65093 | LibreNMS is vulnerable to SQL Injection (Boolean-Based Blind) in hostname parameter in ajax_output.php endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65093</link><description>LibreNMS is an auto-discovering PHP/MySQL/SNMP based network monitoring tool. Prior to version 25.11.0, a boolean-based blind SQL injection vulnerability was identified in the LibreNMS application at the /ajax_output.php endpoint. The hostname parameter is interpolated directly into an SQL query without proper sanitization or parameter binding, allowing an attacker to manipulate the query logic and infer data from the database through conditional responses. This issue has been patched in version 25.11.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 23:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65012 | Kirby CMS has cross-site scripting (XSS) in the changes dialog</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65012</link><description>Kirby is an open-source content management system. From versions 5.0.0 to 5.1.3, attackers could change the title of any page or the name of any user to a malicious string. Then they could modify any content field of the same model without saving, making the model a candidate for display in the "Changes" dialog. If another authenticated user subsequently opened the dialog in their Panel, the malicious code would be executed. This vulnerability affects all Kirby 5 sites that might have potential attackers in the group of authenticated Panel users or that allow external visitors to update page titles or usernames. The attack requires user interaction by another Panel user and cannot be automated. This issue has been patched in version 5.1.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 22:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64515 | Open Forms prefill data in read-only components can be tampered</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64515</link><description>Open Forms allows users create and publish smart forms. Prior to versions 3.2.7 and 3.3.3, forms where the prefill data fields are dynamically set to readonly/disabled can be modified by malicious users deliberately trying to modify data they're not supposed to. For regular users, the form fields are marked as readonly and cannot be modified through the user interface. This issue has been patched in versions 3.2.7 and 3.3.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 22:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64325 | Emby Server is Vulnerable to Remote Code Execution Through XSS in Admin Dashboard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64325</link><description>Emby Server is a personal media server. Prior to version 4.8.1.0 and prior to Beta version 4.9.0.0-beta, a malicious user can send an authentication request with a manipulated X-Emby-Client value, which gets added to the devices section of the admin dashboard without sanitization. This issue has been patched in version 4.8.1.0 and Beta version 4.9.0.0-beta.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 22:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54990 | XWiki AdminTools application doesn&amp;#x27;t set permissions on the AdminTools space</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54990</link><description>XWiki AdminTools integrates administrative tools for managing a running XWiki instance. Prior to version 1.1, users without admin rights have access to AdminTools.SpammedPages. View rights are not restricted only to admin users for AdminTools.SpammedPages. While no data is visible to non admin users, the page is still accessible. This issue has been patched in version 1.1. A workaround involves setting the view rights for the AdminTools space to be only available for the XWikiAdminGroup.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 22:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62406 | Piwigo is vulnerable to one-click account takeover by modifying the password-reset link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62406</link><description>Piwigo is a full featured open source photo gallery application for the web. In Piwigo 15.6.0, using the password reset function allows sending a password-reset URL by entering an existing username or email address. However, the hostname used to construct this URL is taken from the HTTP request's Host header and is not validated at all. Therefore, an attacker can send a password-reset URL with a modified hostname to an existing user whose username or email the attacker knows or guesses. This issue has been patched in version 15.7.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 22:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64324 | KubeVirt Vulnerable to Arbitrary Host File Read and Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64324</link><description>KubeVirt is a virtual machine management add-on for Kubernetes. The `hostDisk` feature in KubeVirt allows mounting a host file or directory owned by the user with UID 107 into a VM. However, prior to version 1.6.1 and 1.7.0, the implementation of this feature and more specifically the `DiskOrCreate` option (which creates a file if it doesn't exist) has a logic bug that allows an attacker to read and write arbitrary files owned by more privileged users on the host system. Versions 1.6.1 and 1.7.0 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 22:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12119 | Bulk write with options may read invalid memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12119</link><description>A mongoc_bulk_operation_t may read invalid memory if large options are passed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 21:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63215 | The Sound4 IMPACT web-based management interface is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) via a malicious firmware update package. The u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63215</link><description>The Sound4 IMPACT web-based management interface is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) via a malicious firmware update package. The update mechanism fails to validate the integrity of manual.sh, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary commands by modifying this script and repackaging the firmware.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 21:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63216 | The Itel DAB Gateway (IDGat build c041640a) is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to improper JWT validation across devices. Attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63216</link><description>The Itel DAB Gateway (IDGat build c041640a) is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to improper JWT validation across devices. Attackers can reuse a valid JWT token obtained from one device to authenticate and gain administrative access to any other device running the same firmware, even if the passwords and networks are different. This allows full compromise of affected devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 21:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63217 | The Itel DAB MUX (IDMUX build c041640a) is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to improper JWT validation across devices. Attackers can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63217</link><description>The Itel DAB MUX (IDMUX build c041640a) is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to improper JWT validation across devices. Attackers can reuse a valid JWT token obtained from one device to authenticate and gain administrative access to any other device running the same firmware, even if the passwords and networks are different. This allows full compromise of affected devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 21:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63229 | The Mozart FM Transmitter web management interface on version WEBMOZZI-00287, contains a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63229</link><description>The Mozart FM Transmitter web management interface on version WEBMOZZI-00287, contains a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /main0.php endpoint. By injecting a malicious JavaScript payload into the ?m= query parameter, an attacker can execute arbitrary code in the victim's browser, potentially stealing sensitive information, hijacking sessions, or performing unauthorized actions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 21:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63228 | The Mozart FM Transmitter web management interface on version WEBMOZZI-00287, contains an unauthenticated file upload vulnerability in the /...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63228</link><description>The Mozart FM Transmitter web management interface on version WEBMOZZI-00287, contains an unauthenticated file upload vulnerability in the /upload_file.php endpoint. An attacker can exploit this by sending a crafted POST request with a malicious file (e.g., a PHP webshell) to the server. The uploaded file is stored in the /upload/ directory, enabling remote code execution and full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 20:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63227 | The Mozart FM Transmitter web management interface on version WEBMOZZI-00287, contains an unrestricted file upload vulnerability in the /pat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63227</link><description>The Mozart FM Transmitter web management interface on version WEBMOZZI-00287, contains an unrestricted file upload vulnerability in the /patch.php endpoint. An attacker with administrative credentials can upload arbitrary files (e.g., PHP webshells), which are stored in the /patch/ directory. This allows the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the server, potentially leading to full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37161 | Unauthenticated Remote Denial-of-Service (DoS) Vulnerability in Web Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37161</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of affected products could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a denial of service.  Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to crash the system, preventing it from rebooting without manual intervention and disrupting network operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37162 | Authenticated Command Injection Vulnerability Leading to Arbitrary Remote Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37162</link><description>A vulnerability in the command line interface of affected devices could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct a command injection attack. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63226 | The Sencore SMP100 SMP Media Platform (firmware versions V4.2.160, V60.1.4, V60.1.29) is vulnerable to session hijacking due to improper ses...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63226</link><description>The Sencore SMP100 SMP Media Platform (firmware versions V4.2.160, V60.1.4, V60.1.29) is vulnerable to session hijacking due to improper session management on the /UserManagement.html endpoint. Attackers who are on the same network as the victim and have access to the target's logged-in session can access the endpoint and add new users without any authentication. This allows attackers to gain unauthorized access to the system and perform malicious activities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37163 | Authenticated Command Injection Vulnerability in HPE Aruba Networking Management Software (AirWave) CLI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37163</link><description>A command injection vulnerability has been identified in the command line interface of the HPE Aruba Networking Airwave Platform. An authenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary operating system commands with elevated privileges on the underlying  operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63225 | The Eurolab ELTS100_UBX device (firmware version ELTS100v1.UBX) is vulnerable to Broken Access Control due to missing authentication on crit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63225</link><description>The Eurolab ELTS100_UBX device (firmware version ELTS100v1.UBX) is vulnerable to Broken Access Control due to missing authentication on critical administrative endpoints. Attackers can directly access and modify sensitive system and network configurations, upload firmware, and execute unauthorized actions without any form of authentication. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to fully compromise the device, control its functionality, and disrupt its operation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37160 | Authenticated Broken Access Control (BAC) in REST API Configuration Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37160</link><description>A broken access control (BAC) vulnerability in the web-based management interface could allow an authenticated remote attacker with low privileges to view sensitive information. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could enable the attacker to disclose sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52639 | HCL Connections is vulnerable to sensitive information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52639</link><description>HCL Connections is vulnerable to a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability which could allow a user to obtain sensitive information they are not entitled to, caused by improper rendering of application data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37156 | ArubaOS-CX Platform-Level Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37156</link><description>A platform-level denial-of-service (DoS) vulnerability exists in ArubaOS-CX software. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker with administrative access to execute specific code that renders the switch non-bootable and effectively non-functional.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37157 | Authenticated Command Injection allows Unauthorized Command Execution in AOS-CX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37157</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in the AOS-CX Operating System. Successful exploitation could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct a Remote Code Execution (RCE) on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37158 | Authenticated Command Injection allows Unauthorized Command Execution in AOS-CX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37158</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in the AOS-CX Operating System. Successful exploitation could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct a Remote Code Execution (RCE) on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37159 | Authenticated Session Hijacking Allows Unauthorized Access in Network Switching Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37159</link><description>A vulnerability in the web management interface of the AOS-CX OS user authentication service could allow an authenticated remote attacker to hijack an active user session. Successful exploitation may enable the attacker to maintain unauthorized access to the session, potentially leading to the view or modification of sensitive configuration data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54320 | In Ascertia SigningHub through 8.6.8, there is a lack of rate limiting on the invite user function, leading to an email bombing vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54320</link><description>In Ascertia SigningHub through 8.6.8, there is a lack of rate limiting on the invite user function, leading to an email bombing vulnerability. An authenticated attacker can exploit this by automating invite requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56499 | Incorrect access control in mihomo v1.19.11 allows authenticated attackers with low-level privileges to read arbitrary files with elevated p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56499</link><description>Incorrect access control in mihomo v1.19.11 allows authenticated attackers with low-level privileges to read arbitrary files with elevated privileges via obtaining the external control key from the config file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37155 | Authenticated Privilege Escalation Allows Unauthorized Access in Network Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37155</link><description>A vulnerability in the SSH restricted shell interface of the network management services allows improper access control for authenticated read-only users. If successfully exploited, this vulnerability could allow an attacker with read-only privileges to gain administrator access on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54321 | In Ascertia SigningHub through 8.6.8, there is a lack of rate limiting on the reset password function, leading to an email bombing vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54321</link><description>In Ascertia SigningHub through 8.6.8, there is a lack of rate limiting on the reset password function, leading to an email bombing vulnerability. An authenticated attacker can exploit this by automating reset password requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54770 | Grub2: use-after-free in net_set_vlan</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54770</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the GRUB2 bootloader's network module that poses an immediate Denial of Service (DoS) risk. This flaw is a Use-after-Free issue, caused because the net_set_vlan command is not properly unregistered when the network module is unloaded from memory. An attacker who can execute this command can force the system to access memory locations that are no longer valid. Successful exploitation leads directly to system instability, which can result in a complete crash and halt system availability</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60455 | Unsafe Deserialization vulnerability in Modular Max Serve before 25.6, specifically when the "--experimental-enable-kvcache-agent" feature i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60455</link><description>Unsafe Deserialization vulnerability in Modular Max Serve before 25.6, specifically when the "--experimental-enable-kvcache-agent" feature is used allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63749 | pnetlab 5.3.11 is vulnerable to Command Injection via the qemu_options parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63749</link><description>pnetlab 5.3.11 is vulnerable to Command Injection via the qemu_options parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63955 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the manage-students.php component of PHPGurukul Student Record System v3.2 allows an at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63955</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the manage-students.php component of PHPGurukul Student Record System v3.2 allows an attacker to trick an authenticated administrator into submitting a forged request. This leads to the unauthorized deletion of user accounts, causing a Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54771 | Grub2: use-after-free in grub_file_close()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54771</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability has been identified in the GNU GRUB (Grand Unified Bootloader). The flaw occurs because the file-closing process incorrectly retains a memory pointer, leaving an invalid reference to a file system structure. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to cause grub to crash, leading to a Denial of Service. Possible data integrity or confidentiality compromise is not discarded.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61661 | Grub2: out-of-bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61661</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the GRUB (Grand Unified Bootloader) component. This flaw occurs because the bootloader mishandles string conversion when reading information from a USB device, allowing an attacker to exploit inconsistent length values. A local attacker can connect a maliciously configured USB device during the boot sequence to trigger this issue. A successful exploitation may lead GRUB to crash, leading to a Denial of Service. Data corruption may be also possible, although given the complexity of the exploit the impact is most likely limited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61662 | Grub2: missing unregister call for gettext command may lead to use-after-free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61662</link><description>A Use-After-Free vulnerability has been discovered in GRUB's gettext module. This flaw stems from a programming error where the gettext command remains registered in memory after its module is unloaded. An attacker can exploit this condition by invoking the orphaned command, causing the application to access a memory location that is no longer valid. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to cause grub to crash, leading to a Denial of Service. Possible data integrity or confidentiality compromise is not discarded.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61663 | Grub2: missing unregister call for normal commands may lead to use-after-free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61663</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the GRUB2 bootloader's normal command that poses an immediate Denial of Service (DoS) risk. This flaw is a Use-after-Free issue, caused because the normal command is not properly unregistered when the module is unloaded. An attacker who can execute this command can force the system to access memory locations that are no longer valid. Successful exploitation leads directly to system instability, which can result in a complete crash and halt system availability. Impact on the data integrity and confidentiality is also not discarded.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61664 | Grub2: missing unregister call for normal_exit command may lead to use-after-free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61664</link><description>A vulnerability in the GRUB2 bootloader has been identified in the normal module. This flaw, a memory Use After Free issue, occurs because the normal_exit command is not properly unregistered when its related module is unloaded. An attacker can exploit this condition by invoking the command after the module has been removed, causing the system to improperly access a previously freed memory location. This leads to a system crash or possible impacts in data confidentiality and integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63693 | The comment editing template (dzz/comment/template/edit_form.htm) in DzzOffice 2.3.x lacks adequate security escaping for user-controllable ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63693</link><description>The comment editing template (dzz/comment/template/edit_form.htm) in DzzOffice 2.3.x lacks adequate security escaping for user-controllable data in multiple contexts, including HTML and JavaScript strings. This allows low-privilege attackers to construct comment content or request parameters and execute arbitrary JavaScript code when the victim opens the editing pop-up.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63695 | DzzOffice v2.3.7 and before is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload in /dzz/system/ueditor/php/controller.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63695</link><description>DzzOffice v2.3.7 and before is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload in /dzz/system/ueditor/php/controller.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:23:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63994 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the /php/UploadHandler.php component of RichFilemanager v2.7.6 allows attackers to execute arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63994</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the /php/UploadHandler.php component of RichFilemanager v2.7.6 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63694 | DzzOffice v2.3.7 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection in explorer/groupmanage.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63694</link><description>DzzOffice v2.3.7 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection in explorer/groupmanage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64076 | Multiple vulnerabilities exist in cbor2 through version 5.7.0 in the decode_definite_long_string() function of the C extension decoder (sour...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64076</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities exist in cbor2 through version 5.7.0 in the decode_definite_long_string() function of the C extension decoder (source/decoder.c): (1) Integer Underflow Leading to Out-of-Bounds Read (CWE-191, CWE-125): An incorrect variable reference and missing state reset in the chunk processing loop causes buffer_length to not be reset to zero after UTF-8 character consumption. This results in subsequent chunk_length calculations producing negative values (e.g., chunk_length = 65536 - buffer_length), which are passed as signed integers to the read() method, potentially triggering unlimited read operations and resource exhaustion. (2) Memory Leak via Missing Reference Count Release (CWE-401): The main processing loop fails to release Python object references (Py_DECREF) for chunk objects allocated in each iteration. For CBOR strings longer than 65536 bytes, this causes cumulative memory leaks proportional to the payload size, enabling memory exhaustion attacks through repeated processing of large CBOR payloads. Both vulnerabilities can be exploited remotely without authentication by sending specially-crafted CBOR data containing definite-length text strings with multi-byte UTF-8 characters positioned at 65536-byte chunk boundaries. Successful exploitation results in denial of service through process crashes (CBORDecodeEOF exceptions) or memory exhaustion. The vulnerabilities affect all applications using cbor2's C extension to process untrusted CBOR data, including web APIs, IoT data collectors, and message queue processors. Fixed in commit 851473490281f82d82560b2368284ef33cf6e8f9 pushed with released version 5.7.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56643 | Requarks Wiki.js 2.5.307 does not properly revoke or invalidate active JWT tokens when a user logs out. As a result, previously issued token...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56643</link><description>Requarks Wiki.js 2.5.307 does not properly revoke or invalidate active JWT tokens when a user logs out. As a result, previously issued tokens remain valid and can be reused to access the system, even after logout. This behavior affects session integrity and may allow unauthorized access if a token is compromised. The issue is present in the authentication resolver logic and affects both the GraphQL endpoint and the logout mechanism.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:55:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63514 | kishan0725 Hospital Management System has a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in appsearch.php via the email parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63514</link><description>kishan0725 Hospital Management System has a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in appsearch.php via the email parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:46:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63828 | Host Header Injection vulnerability in Backdrop CMS 1.32.1 allows attackers to manipulate the Host header in password reset requests, leadin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63828</link><description>Host Header Injection vulnerability in Backdrop CMS 1.32.1 allows attackers to manipulate the Host header in password reset requests, leading to redirects to malicious domains and potential session hijacking via cookie injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12760 | Email TFA - Moderately critical - Access bypass - SA-CONTRIB-2025-115</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12760</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Drupal Email TFA allows Functionality Bypass.This issue affects Email TFA: from 0.0.0 before 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12761 | Simple multi step form - Moderately critical - Cross-site Scripting - SA-CONTRIB-2025-116</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12761</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ("Cross-site Scripting") vulnerability in Drupal Simple multi step form allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Simple multi step form: from 0.0.0 before 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13082 | Drupal core - Moderately critical - Defacement - SA-CORE-2025-007</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13082</link><description>User Interface (UI) Misrepresentation of Critical Information vulnerability in Drupal Drupal core allows Content Spoofing.This issue affects Drupal core: from 8.0.0 before 10.4.9, from 10.5.0 before 10.5.6, from 11.0.0 before 11.1.9, from 11.2.0 before 11.2.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13083 | Drupal core - Moderately critical - Information disclosure - SA-CORE-2025-008</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13083</link><description>Use of Web Browser Cache Containing Sensitive Information vulnerability in Drupal Drupal core allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Drupal core: from 8.0.0 before 10.4.9, from 10.5.0 before 10.5.6, from 11.0.0 before 11.1.9, from 11.2.0 before 11.2.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33183 | NVIDIA Isaac-GR00T for all platforms contains a vulnerability in a Python component, where an attacker could cause a code injection issue. A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33183</link><description>NVIDIA Isaac-GR00T for all platforms contains a vulnerability in a Python component, where an attacker could cause a code injection issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33184 | NVIDIA Isaac-GR00T for all platforms contains a vulnerability in a Python component, where an attacker could cause a code injection issue. A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33184</link><description>NVIDIA Isaac-GR00T for all platforms contains a vulnerability in a Python component, where an attacker could cause a code injection issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46215 | An Improper Isolation or Compartmentalization vulnerability [CWE-653] in Fortinet FortiSandbox 5.0.0 through 5.0.1, FortiSandbox 4.4.0 throu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46215</link><description>An Improper Isolation or Compartmentalization vulnerability [CWE-653] in Fortinet FortiSandbox 5.0.0 through 5.0.1, FortiSandbox 4.4.0 through 4.4.7, FortiSandbox 4.2 all versions, FortiSandbox 4.0 all versions may allow an unauthenticated attacker to evade the sandboxing scan via a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46373 | A Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability [CWE-122] in Fortinet FortiClientWindows 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, FortiClientWindows 7.2.0 through 7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46373</link><description>A Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability [CWE-122] in Fortinet FortiClientWindows 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, FortiClientWindows 7.2.0 through 7.2.8 may allow an authenticated local IPSec user to execute arbitrary code or commands via "fortips_74.sys". The attacker would need to bypass the  Windows heap integrity protections</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46775 | A debug messages revealing unnecessary information vulnerability in Fortinet FortiExtender 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, FortiExtender 7.4.0 through ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46775</link><description>A debug messages revealing unnecessary information vulnerability in Fortinet FortiExtender 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, FortiExtender 7.4.0 through 7.4.6, FortiExtender 7.2 all versions, FortiExtender 7.0 all versions may allow an authenticated user to obtain administrator credentials via debug log commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46776 | A buffer copy without checking size of input ('classic buffer overflow') in Fortinet FortiExtender 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, FortiExtender 7.4.0 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46776</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input ('classic buffer overflow') in Fortinet FortiExtender 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, FortiExtender 7.4.0 through 7.4.6, FortiExtender 7.2 all versions, FortiExtender 7.0 all versions may allow an authenticated user to execute arbitrary code or commands via crafted CLI commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47761 | An Exposed IOCTL with Insufficient Access Control vulnerability [CWE-782] in Fortinet FortiClientWindows 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, FortiClientWin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47761</link><description>An Exposed IOCTL with Insufficient Access Control vulnerability [CWE-782] in Fortinet FortiClientWindows 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, FortiClientWindows 7.2.0 through 7.2.9 may allow an authenticated local user to execute unauthorized code via fortips driver.  Success of the attack would require bypassing the Windows memory protections such as Heap integrity and HSP. In addition, it requires a valid and running VPN IPSec connection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48839 | An Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability [CWE-787] in FortiADC 8.0.0, 7.6.0 through 7.6.2, 7.4.0 through 7.4.7, 7.2 all versions, 7.1 all versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48839</link><description>An Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability [CWE-787] in FortiADC 8.0.0, 7.6.0 through 7.6.2, 7.4.0 through 7.4.7, 7.2 all versions, 7.1 all versions, 7.0 all versions, 6.2 all versions may allow an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code via specially crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53843 | A stack-based buffer overflow in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, FortiOS 7.4.0 through 7.4.8, FortiOS 7.2 all versions, FortiOS 7.0 al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53843</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, FortiOS 7.4.0 through 7.4.8, FortiOS 7.2 all versions, FortiOS 7.0 all versions, FortiOS 6.4 all versions allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specially crafted packets</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54660 | An active debug code vulnerability in Fortinet FortiClientWindows 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, FortiClientWindows 7.2.0 through 7.2.10, FortiClientW...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54660</link><description>An active debug code vulnerability in Fortinet FortiClientWindows 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, FortiClientWindows 7.2.0 through 7.2.10, FortiClientWindows 7.0 all versions may allow a local attacker to run the application step by step and retrieve the saved VPN user password</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54821 | An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability [CWE-269] in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, FortiOS 7.4 all versions, FortiOS 7.2 all ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54821</link><description>An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability [CWE-269] in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, FortiOS 7.4 all versions, FortiOS 7.2 all versions, FortiOS 7.0 all versions, FortiOS 6.4 all versions, FortiPAM 1.6.0, FortiPAM 1.5 all versions, FortiPAM 1.4 all versions, FortiPAM 1.3 all versions, FortiPAM 1.2 all versions, FortiPAM 1.1 all versions, FortiPAM 1.0 all versions, FortiProxy 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, FortiProxy 7.4 all versions, FortiProxy 7.2 all versions, FortiProxy 7.0 all versions may allow an authenticated administrator to bypass the trusted host policy via crafted CLI command.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54971 | An exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor vulnerability in Fortinet FortiADC 7.4.0, FortiADC 7.2 all versions, FortiADC ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54971</link><description>An exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor vulnerability in Fortinet FortiADC 7.4.0, FortiADC 7.2 all versions, FortiADC 7.1 all versions, FortiADC 7.0 all versions, FortiADC 6.2 all versions may allow an admin with read-only permission  to get the external resources password via the logs of the product</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54972 | An improper neutralization of crlf sequences ('crlf injection') in Fortinet FortiMail 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, FortiMail 7.4.0 through 7.4.5, Fo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54972</link><description>An improper neutralization of crlf sequences ('crlf injection') in Fortinet FortiMail 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, FortiMail 7.4.0 through 7.4.5, FortiMail 7.2 all versions, FortiMail 7.0 all versions may allow an attacker to inject headers in the response via convincing a user to click on a specifically crafted link</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58034 | An Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability [CWE-78] in Fortinet FortiWeb 8....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58034</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability [CWE-78] in Fortinet FortiWeb 8.0.0 through 8.0.1, FortiWeb 7.6.0 through 7.6.5, FortiWeb 7.4.0 through 7.4.10, FortiWeb 7.2.0 through 7.2.11, FortiWeb 7.0.0 through 7.0.11 may allow an authenticated attacker to execute unauthorized code on the underlying system via crafted HTTP requests or CLI commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58413 | A stack-based buffer overflow in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, FortiOS 7.4.0 through 7.4.8, FortiOS 7.2 all versions, FortiOS 7.0 al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58413</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, FortiOS 7.4.0 through 7.4.8, FortiOS 7.2 all versions, FortiOS 7.0 all versions, FortiOS 6.4 all versions, FortiOS 6.2 all versions, FortiOS 6.0 all versions, FortiSASE 25.3.b allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specially crafted packets</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58692 | An improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL Command ("SQL Injection") vulnerability [CWE-89] in Fortinet FortiVoice 7.2.0 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58692</link><description>An improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL Command ("SQL Injection") vulnerability [CWE-89] in Fortinet FortiVoice 7.2.0 through 7.2.2, FortiVoice 7.0.0 through 7.0.7 allows an authenticated attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specifically crafted HTTP or HTTPS requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59669 | A use of hard-coded credentials vulnerability in Fortinet FortiWeb 7.6.0, FortiWeb 7.4 all versions, FortiWeb 7.2 all versions, FortiWeb 7.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59669</link><description>A use of hard-coded credentials vulnerability in Fortinet FortiWeb 7.6.0, FortiWeb 7.4 all versions, FortiWeb 7.2 all versions, FortiWeb 7.0 all versions may allow an authenticated attacker with shell access to the device to connect to redis service and access its data</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61713 | A Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information in Memory vulnerability [CWE-316] in Fortinet FortiPAM 1.6.0, FortiPAM 1.5 all versions, FortiP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61713</link><description>A Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information in Memory vulnerability [CWE-316] in Fortinet FortiPAM 1.6.0, FortiPAM 1.5 all versions, FortiPAM 1.4 all versions, FortiPAM 1.3 all versions, FortiPAM 1.2 all versions, FortiPAM 1.1 all versions, FortiPAM 1.0 all versions may allow an authenticated attacker with read-write admin privileges to the CLI to obtain other administrators' credentials via diagnose commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13080 | Drupal core - Moderately critical - Denial of Service - SA-CORE-2025-005</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13080</link><description>Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in Drupal Drupal core allows Forceful Browsing.This issue affects Drupal core: from 8.0.0 before 10.4.9, from 10.5.0 before 10.5.6, from 11.0.0 before 11.1.9, from 11.2.0 before 11.2.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13081 | Drupal core - Moderately critical - Gadget chain - SA-CORE-2025-006</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13081</link><description>Improperly Controlled Modification of Dynamically-Determined Object Attributes vulnerability in Drupal Drupal core allows Object Injection.This issue affects Drupal core: from 8.0.0 before 10.4.9, from 10.5.0 before 10.5.6, from 11.0.0 before 11.1.9, from 11.2.0 before 11.2.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63258 | A remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability was discovered in all H3C ERG3/ERG5 series routers and XiaoBei series routers, cloud gateways...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63258</link><description>A remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability was discovered in all H3C ERG3/ERG5 series routers and XiaoBei series routers, cloud gateways, and wireless access points (versions R0162P07, UAP700-WPT330-E2265, UAP672-WPT330-R2262, UAP662E-WPT330-R2262P03, WAP611-WPT330-R1348-OASIS, WAP662-WPT330-R2262, WAP662H-WPT330-R2262, USG300V2-WPT330-R2129, MSG300-WPT330-R1350, and MSG326-WPT330-R2129). Attackers are able to exploit this vulnerability via injecting crafted commands into the sessionid parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63513 | kishan0725 Hospital Management System v4 has an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in the appointment cancellation functi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63513</link><description>kishan0725 Hospital Management System v4 has an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in the appointment cancellation functionality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:10:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34324 | GoSign Desktop &amp;lt; 2.4.1 Insecure Update Mechanism RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34324</link><description>GoSign Desktop versions 2.4.0 and earlier use an unsigned update manifest for distributing application updates. The manifest contains package URLs and SHA-256 hashes but is not digitally signed, so its authenticity relies solely on the underlying TLS channel. In affected versions, TLS certificate validation can be disabled when a proxy is configured, allowing an attacker who can intercept network traffic to supply a malicious update manifest and corresponding package with a matching hash. This can cause the client to download and install a tampered update, resulting in arbitrary code execution with the privileges of the GoSign Desktop user on Windows and macOS, or with elevated privileges on some Linux deployments. A local attacker who can modify proxy settings may also abuse this behavior to escalate privileges by forcing installation of a crafted update.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55796 | The openml/openml.org web application version v2.0.20241110 uses predictable MD5-based tokens for critical user workflows such as signup con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55796</link><description>The openml/openml.org web application version v2.0.20241110 uses predictable MD5-based tokens for critical user workflows such as signup confirmation, password resets, email confirmation resends, and email change confirmation. These tokens are generated by hashing the current timestamp formatted as "%d %H:%M:%S" without incorporating any user-specific data or cryptographic randomness. This predictability allows remote attackers to brute-force valid tokens within a small time window, enabling unauthorized account confirmation, password resets, and email change approvals, potentially leading to account takeover.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:52:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63829 | eProsima Fast-DDS v3.3 and before has an infinite loop vulnerability caused by integer overflow in the Time_t:: fraction() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63829</link><description>eProsima Fast-DDS v3.3 and before has an infinite loop vulnerability caused by integer overflow in the Time_t:: fraction() function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53360 | pluginsGLPI&amp;#x27;s Database Inventory Plugin allows any authenticated user to send agent requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53360</link><description>pluginsGLPI's Database Inventory Plugin "manages" the Teclib' inventory agents in order to perform an inventory of the databases present on the workstation. In versions prior to 1.0.3, any authenticated user could send requests to agents. This issue has been patched in version 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56526 | Cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Kotaemon 0.11.0 allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted PDF.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56526</link><description>Cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Kotaemon 0.11.0 allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted PDF.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56527 | Plaintext password storage in Kotaemon 0.11.0 in the client's localStorage.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56527</link><description>Plaintext password storage in Kotaemon 0.11.0 in the client's localStorage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63512 | kishan0725 Hospital Management System/ v4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in admin-panel1.php, specifically in the deleting doctor logic. The...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63512</link><description>kishan0725 Hospital Management System/ v4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in admin-panel1.php, specifically in the deleting doctor logic. The application fails to properly sanitize or parameterize user-supplied input from the demail parameter before incorporating it directly into a dynamic SQL query.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63800 | The password change endpoint in Open Source Point of Sale 3.4.1 allows users to set their account password to an empty string due to missing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63800</link><description>The password change endpoint in Open Source Point of Sale 3.4.1 allows users to set their account password to an empty string due to missing server-side validation. When an authenticated user omits or leaves the `password` and `repeat_password` parameters empty in the password change request, the backend still returns a successful response and sets the password to an empty string. This effectively disables authentication and may allow unauthorized access to user or administrative accounts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63603 | A command injection vulnerability exists in the MCP Data Science Server's (reading-plus-ai/mcp-server-data-exploration) 0.1.6 in the safe_ev...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63603</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in the MCP Data Science Server's (reading-plus-ai/mcp-server-data-exploration) 0.1.6 in the safe_eval() function (src/mcp_server_ds/server.py:108). The function uses Python's exec() to execute user-supplied scripts but fails to restrict the __builtins__ dictionary in the globals parameter. When __builtins__ is not explicitly defined, Python automatically provides access to all built-in functions including __import__, exec, eval, and open. This allows an attacker to execute arbitrary Python code with full system privileges, leading to complete system compromise. The vulnerability can be exploited by submitting a malicious script to the run_script tool, requiring no authentication or special privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63604 | A code injection vulnerability exists in baryhuang/mcp-server-aws-resources-python 0.1.0 that allows remote code execution through insuffici...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63604</link><description>A code injection vulnerability exists in baryhuang/mcp-server-aws-resources-python 0.1.0 that allows remote code execution through insufficient input validation in the execute_query method. The vulnerability stems from the exposure of dangerous Python built-in functions (__import__, getattr, hasattr) in the execution namespace and the direct use of exec() to execute user-supplied code. An attacker can craft malicious queries to execute arbitrary Python code, leading to AWS credential theft (AWS_ACCESS_KEY_ID, AWS_SECRET_ACCESS_KEY), file system access, environment variable disclosure, and potential system compromise. The vulnerability allows attackers to bypass intended security controls and gain unauthorized access to sensitive AWS resources and credentials stored in the server's environment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9977 | Improper neutralization of input in Times Software E-PAYROLL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9977</link><description>Value provided in one of POST parameters sent during the process of logging in to Times Software E-Payroll is not sanitized properly, which allows an unauthenticated attacker to perform DoS attacks. SQL injection attacks might also be feasible, although so far creating a working exploit has been prevented probably by backend filtering mechanisms.
Additionally, command injection attempts cause the application to return extensive error messages disclosing some information about the internal infrastructure. 
Patching status is unknown because the vendor has not replied to messages sent by the CNA.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:57:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55074 | Channel member objects leak read status</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55074</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.3, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.11 fail to enforce access permissions on the Agents plugin which allows other users to determine when users had read channels via channel member objects</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:46:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63602 | A vulnerability was discovered in Awesome Miner thru 11.2.4 that allows arbitrary read and write to kernel memory and MSRs (such as LSTAR) a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63602</link><description>A vulnerability was discovered in Awesome Miner thru 11.2.4 that allows arbitrary read and write to kernel memory and MSRs (such as LSTAR) as an unprivileged user. This is due to the implementation of an insecure version of WinRing0 (1.2.0.5, renamed to IntelliBreeze.Maintenance.Service.sys) that lacks a properly secured DACL, allowing unprivileged users to interact with the driver and, as a result, the kernel. This can result in local privilege escalation, information disclosure, denial of service, and other unspecified impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:46:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12383 | Race Condition allows Bypass of Trust Restrictions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12383</link><description>In Eclipse Jersey versions 2.45, 3.0.16, 3.1.9 a race condition can cause ignoring of critical SSL configurations - such as mutual authentication, custom key/trust stores, and other security settings. This issue may result in SSLHandshakeException under normal circumstances, but under certain conditions, it could lead to unauthorized trust in insecure servers (see PoC)</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58121 | Insufficient permission validation on multiple REST API endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58121</link><description>Insufficient permission validation on multiple REST API endpoints in Checkmk 2.2.0, 2.3.0, and 2.4.0 before version 2.4.0p16 allows low-privileged users to perform unauthorized actions or obtain sensitive information</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58122 | Insufficient permission validation when configuring notification parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58122</link><description>Insufficient permission validation in Checkmk 2.4.0 before version 2.4.0p16 allows low-privileged users to modify notification parameters via the REST API, which could lead to unauthorized actions or information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63408 | Local Agent DVR versions thru 6.6.1.0 are vulnerable to directory traversal that allows an unauthenticated local attacker to gain access to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63408</link><description>Local Agent DVR versions thru 6.6.1.0 are vulnerable to directory traversal that allows an unauthenticated local attacker to gain access to sensitive information, cause a server-side forgery request (SSRF), or execute OS commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64996 | Overly broad file permissions in the mk_inotify plugin allows reading and manipulating the plugin&amp;#x27;s output</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64996</link><description>In Checkmk versions prior to 2.4.0p16, 2.3.0p41, and all versions of 2.2.0 and older, the mk_inotify plugin creates world-readable and writable files, allowing any local user on the system to read the plugin's output and manipulate it, potentially leading to unauthorized access to or modification of monitoring data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63883 | A DOM-based cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in electic-shop v1.0 (Bhabishya-123/E-commerce). The site's client-side JavaScript rea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63883</link><description>A DOM-based cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in electic-shop v1.0 (Bhabishya-123/E-commerce). The site's client-side JavaScript reads attacker-controlled input (for example, values derived from the URL or page fragment) and inserts it into the DOM via unsafe sinks (innerHTML/insertAdjacentHTML/document.write) without proper sanitization or context-aware encoding. An attacker can craft a malicious URL that, when opened by a victim, causes arbitrary JavaScript to execute in the victim's browser under the electic-shop origin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63892 | A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Student Grades Management System 1.0. Affected is the function create_classroom of the file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63892</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Student Grades Management System 1.0. Affected is the function create_classroom of the file /classroom.php of the component My Classrooms Management Page. This manipulation of the argument name/description causes stored cross site scripting.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:50:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10158 | Rsync: Out of bounds array access via negative index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10158</link><description>A malicious client acting as the receiver of an rsync file transfer can trigger an out of bounds read of a heap based buffer, via a negative array index. The 

malicious 

rsync client requires at least read access to the remote rsync module in order to trigger the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13349 | SourceCodester Student Grades Management System Add New Grade grades.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13349</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Student Grades Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /grades.php of the component Add New Grade Page. The manipulation of the argument Remarks leads to cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:11:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12376 | Icon List Block – Add Icon-Based Lists with Custom Styles &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12376</link><description>The Icon List Block – Add Icon-Based Lists with Custom Styles plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 via the fs_api_request function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services. Only valid JSON objects are rendered in the response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:11:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12545 | Pixel Manager for WooCommerce – Track Conversions and Analytics, Google Ads, TikTok and more &amp;lt;= 1.49.2 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12545</link><description>The Pixel Manager for WooCommerce – Track Conversions and Analytics, Google Ads, TikTok and more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.49.2 via the ajax_pmw_get_product_ids() function due to insufficient restrictions on which products can be included. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract data from password protected, private, or draft products that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55179 | Incomplete validation of rich response messages in WhatsApp for iOS prior to v2.25.23.73, WhatsApp Business for iOS v2.25.23.82, and WhatsAp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55179</link><description>Incomplete validation of rich response messages in WhatsApp for iOS prior to v2.25.23.73, WhatsApp Business for iOS v2.25.23.82, and WhatsApp for Mac v2.25.23.83 could have allowed a user to trigger processing of media content from an arbitrary URL on another user’s device. We have not seen evidence of exploitation in the wild.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59110 | Cross-Site Request Forgery in Windu CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59110</link><description>Windu CMS is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in user editing functionality. Implemented CSRF protection mechanism can be bypassed by using CSRF token of other user. It is worth noting that the registration is open and anyone can create an account.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 4.1 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59111 | Broken Access Control in Windu CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59111</link><description>Windu CMS is vulnerable to Broken Access Control in user editing functionality. Malicious attacker can send a GET request which allows privileged users to delete Super Admins which is not possible with GUI.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 4.1 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59112 | Cross-Site Request Forgery in Windu CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59112</link><description>Windu CMS is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in user editing functionality. Malicious attacker can craft special website, which when visited by the victim, will automatically send POST request that deletes given user.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 4.1 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59113 | Bruteforce Protection Bypass in Windu CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59113</link><description>Windu CMS implements weak client-side brute-force protection by using parameter loginError. Information about attempt count or timeout is not stored on the server, which allows a malicious attacker to bypass this brute-force protection by resetting this parameter.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 4.1 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59114 | Cross-Site Request Forgery in Windu CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59114</link><description>Windu CMS is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in file uploading functionality. Malicious attacker can craft special website, which when visited by the victim, will automatically send malicious file to the server.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 4.1 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59115 | Stored XSS in Windu CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59115</link><description>Windu CMS is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the logon page where input data has no proper validation. Malicious attacker can inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed when visiting logs page by admin.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 4.1 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59116 | User enumeration in Windu CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59116</link><description>Windu CMS is vulnerable to User Enumeration. This issue occurs during logon, where a difference in messages could allow an attacker to determine if the login is valid or not, enabling a brute force attack with valid logins.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 4.1 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59117 | Multiple Stored XSS in Windu CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59117</link><description>Windu CMS is vulnerable to multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the page editing endpoint windu/admin/content/pages/edit/. 
This vulnerability can be exploited by a privileged user and may target users with higher privileges.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 4.1 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13347 | SourceCodester Train Station Ticketing System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13347</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Train Station Ticketing System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /ajax.php?action=save_user. Executing manipulation of the argument Username can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13346 | SourceCodester Train Station Ticketing System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13346</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Train Station Ticketing System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /ajax.php?action=save_station. Performing manipulation of the argument id/station results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:05:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8084 | AI Engine &amp;lt;= 3.1.8 - Authenticated (Editor+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8084</link><description>The AI Engine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.8 via the rest_helpers_create_images function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services. On Cloud instances, this issue allows for metadata retrieving.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:05:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9312 | Improper Certificate-Based Authentication Enforcement in Multiple WSO2 Products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9312</link><description>A missing authentication enforcement vulnerability exists in the mutual TLS (mTLS) implementation used by System REST APIs and SOAP services in multiple WSO2 products. Due to improper validation of client certificate–based authentication in certain default configurations, the affected components may permit unauthenticated requests even when mTLS is enabled. This condition occurs when relying on the default mTLS settings for System REST APIs or when the mTLS authenticator is enabled for SOAP services, causing these interfaces to accept requests without enforcing additional authentication.

Successful exploitation allows a malicious actor with network access to the affected endpoints to gain administrative privileges and perform unauthorized operations. The vulnerability is exploitable only when the impacted mTLS flows are enabled and accessible in a given deployment. Other certificate-based authentication mechanisms—such as Mutual TLS OAuth client authentication and X.509 login flows—are not affected, and APIs served through the API Gateway of WSO2 API Manager remain unaffected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13344 | SourceCodester Train Station Ticketing System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13344</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Train Station Ticketing System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /ajax.php?action=login. This manipulation of the argument Username causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13345 | SourceCodester Train Station Ticketing System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13345</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SourceCodester Train Station Ticketing System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /ajax.php?action=save_ticket. Such manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:22:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13343 | SourceCodester Interview Management System editQuestion.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13343</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in SourceCodester Interview Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /editQuestion.php. The manipulation of the argument Question results in cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41348 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in WinPlus by Informática del Este</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41348</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in WinPlus v24.11.27 by Informática del Este. This vulnerability allows an attacker recover, create, update an delete databases by sendng a POST request using the parameters 'val1' and 'cont in '/WinplusPortal/ws/sWinplus.svc/json/getacumper_post'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41349 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in WinPlus by Informática del Este</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41349</link><description>Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS)vylnerability type in WinPlus v24.11.27 byInformática del Este that consist of an stored XSS of a stored XSS due to a lack of proper validation of user input by sending a POST request using the 'descripcion' parameter in '/WinplusPortal/ws/sWinplus. svc/json/savesolpla_post'. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal their cookie session details.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41350 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in WinPlus by Informática del Este</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41350</link><description>Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS)vylnerability type in WinPlus v24.11.27 byInformática del Este that consist of an stored XSS of a stored XSS due to a lack of proper validation of user input by sending a POST request using the 'descripcion' parameter in '/WinplusPortal/ws/sWinplus.svc/json/savesoldoc_post'. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal their cookie session details.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6670 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in Multiple WSO2 Products via HTTP GET in Admin Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6670</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in multiple WSO2 products due to the use of the HTTP GET method for state-changing operations within admin services, specifically in the event processor of the Carbon console. Although the SameSite=Lax cookie attribute is used as a mitigation, it is ineffective in this context because it allows cookies to be sent with cross-origin top-level navigations using GET requests.

A malicious actor can exploit this vulnerability by tricking an authenticated user into visiting a crafted link, leading the browser to issue unintended state-changing requests. Successful exploitation could result in unauthorized operations such as data modification, account changes, or other administrative actions. According to WSO2 Secure Production Guidelines, exposure of Carbon console services to untrusted networks is discouraged, which may reduce the impact in properly secured deployments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41347 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in WinPlus by Informática del Este</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41347</link><description>Unlimited upload vulnerability for dangerous file types in WinPlus v24.11.27 from Informática del Este. This vulnerability allows an attacker to upload a  'webshell' by sending a POST request to '/WinplusPortal/ws/sWinplus.svc/json/uploadfile'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11427 | WP Migrate Lite &amp;lt;= 2.7.6 - Unauthenticated Blind Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11427</link><description>The WP Migrate Lite – WordPress Migration Made Easy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Blind Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.6 via the wpmdb_flush AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to obtain information about internal services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41733 | Possible malfunction credential injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41733</link><description>The commissioning wizard on the affected devices does not validate if the device is already initialized. An unauthenticated remote attacker can construct POST requests to set root credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 10:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41734 | Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion in php module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41734</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can execute arbitrary php files and gain full access of the affected devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 10:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41735 | Possible arbitrary file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41735</link><description>A low privileged remote attacker can upload any file to an arbitrary location due to missing file check resulting in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 10:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41736 | Possible arbitrary code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41736</link><description>A low privileged remote attacker can upload a new or overwrite an existing python script by using a path traversal of the target filename in php resulting in a remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 10:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41737 | Improper access control via php endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41737</link><description>Due to webserver misconfiguration an unauthenticated remote attacker is able to read the source of php modules.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 10:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41346 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in WinPlus by Informática del Este</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41346</link><description>Faulty authorization control in software WinPlus v24.11.27 by Informática del Este that allows another user to be impersonated simply by knowing their 'numerical ID', meaning that an attacker could compromise another user's account, thereby affecting the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the data stored in the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 10:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11734 | Broken Link Checker by AIOSEO – Easily Fix/Monitor Internal and External links &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Post Trashing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11734</link><description>The Broken Link Checker by AIOSEO – Easily Fix/Monitor Internal and External links plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized post modification due to missing authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5. This is due to the plugin registering a REST API endpoint that only checks for a broad capability (aioseo_blc_broken_links_page) that is granted to contributor level users, without verifying the user's permission to perform actions on the specific post being targeted. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to trash arbitrary posts via the DELETE /wp-json/aioseoBrokenLinkChecker/v1/post endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 09:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12079 | WP Twitter Auto Publish &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via PostMessage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12079</link><description>The WP Twitter Auto Publish plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via PostMessage in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 09:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12088 | Meta Display Block &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12088</link><description>The Meta Display Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Meta Display Block in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 09:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12391 | Restrictions for BuddyPress &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Tracking Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12391</link><description>The Restrictions for BuddyPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the handle_optin_optout() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to opt in and out of tracking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 09:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12392 | Cryptocurrency Payment Gateway for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.0.22 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Tracking Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12392</link><description>The Cryptocurrency Payment Gateway for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'handle_optin_optout' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.22. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to opt in and out of tracking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 09:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12457 | Enable SVG, WebP, and ICO Upload &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12457</link><description>The Enable SVG, WebP, and ICO Upload plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 09:42:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12481 | WP Duplicate Page &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12481</link><description>The WP Duplicate Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.7. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action in the 'saveSettings' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to modify plugin settings that control role capabilities, and subsequently exploit the misconfigured capabilities to duplicate and view password-protected posts containing sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 09:42:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12639 | wModes – Catalog Mode, Product Pricing, Enquiry Forms &amp;amp; Promotions | for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12639</link><description>The wModes – Catalog Mode, Product Pricing, Enquiry Forms &amp; Promotions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in versions up to, and including, 1.2.2. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to access sensitive information via the AJAX endpoint. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to extract sensitive information including user emails, usernames, roles, capabilities, and WooCommerce data such as products and payment methods.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 09:42:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12691 | Photonic Gallery &amp;amp; Lightbox for Flickr, SmugMug &amp;amp; Others &amp;lt;= 3.21 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Caption Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12691</link><description>The Photonic Gallery &amp; Lightbox for Flickr, SmugMug &amp; Others plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's lightbox functionality in all versions up to, and including, 3.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied caption attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 09:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12955 | Live sales notification for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.3.39 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Customer Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12955</link><description>The Live sales notification for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.39. This is due to the "getOrders" function lacking proper authorization and capability checks when the plugin is configured to display recent order information. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive customer information including buyer first names, city, state, country, purchase time and date, and product details.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 09:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13069 | Enable SVG, WebP, and ICO Upload &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload via ICO Upload Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13069</link><description>The Enable SVG, WebP, and ICO Upload plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file upload in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2. This is due to insufficient file type validation detecting ICO files, allowing double extension files with the appropriate magic bytes to bypass sanitization while being accepted as a valid ICO file. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 09:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13133 | Simple User Import Export &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Authenticated (Admin+) CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13133</link><description>The Simple User Import Export plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to CSV Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.7 via the 'Import/export users' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to embed untrusted input into exported CSV files, which can result in code execution when these files are downloaded and opened on a local system with a vulnerable configuration</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 09:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13196 | Element Pack Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 8.3.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Open Street Map widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13196</link><description>The Element Pack Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Open Street Map widget's marker content parameter in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.4. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied attributes in the render function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 09:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4212 | Checkout Files Upload for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4212</link><description>The Checkout Files Upload for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via file uploads in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in image files that will execute whenever a user accesses the injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 09:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40545 | SolarWinds Observability Self-Hosted Open Redirection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40545</link><description>SolarWinds Observability Self-Hosted is susceptible to an open redirection vulnerability. The URL is not properly sanitized, and an attacker could manipulate the string to redirect a user to a malicious site. The attack complexity is high, and authentication is required.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 09:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26391 | SolarWinds Observability Self-Hosted XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26391</link><description>SolarWinds Observability Self-Hosted XSS Vulnerability. The SolarWinds Platform was susceptible to a XSS vulnerability that affects user-created URL fields. This vulnerability requires authentication from a low-level account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:58:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40547 | SolarWinds Serv-U Logic Abuse - Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40547</link><description>A logic error vulnerability exists in Serv-U which when abused could give a malicious actor with access to admin privileges the ability to execute code. 

This issue requires administrative privileges to abuse. On Windows deployments, the risk is scored as a medium because services frequently run under less-privileged service accounts by default.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40548 | SolarWinds Serv-U Broken Access Control - Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40548</link><description>A missing validation process exists in Serv U when abused, could give a malicious actor with access to admin privileges the ability to execute code. 

This issue requires administrative privileges to abuse. On Windows deployments, the risk is scored as a medium because services frequently run under less-privileged service accounts by default.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40549 | SolarWinds Serv-U Path Restriction Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40549</link><description>A Path Restriction Bypass vulnerability exists in Serv-U that when abused, could give a malicious actor with access to admin privileges the ability to execute code on a directory. 

This issue requires administrative privileges to abuse. On Windows systems, this scored as medium due to differences in how paths and home directories are handled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11620 | Multiple Roles per User &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Custom+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11620</link><description>The Multiple Roles per User plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'mrpu_add_multiple_roles_ui' and 'mrpu_save_multiple_user_roles' functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, granted the 'edit_users' capability, to edit any user's role, including promoting users to Administrator and demoting Administrators to lower-privileged roles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11868 | everviz &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11868</link><description>The everviz plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `everviz` shortcode attributes in versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to the plugin not properly sanitizing user input or escaping output when building a `&lt;div id="..."&gt;` from the `type` and `hash` attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12078 | ArtiBot Free Chat Bot for WebSites &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via PostMessage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12078</link><description>The ArtiBot Free Chat Bot for WebSites plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via PostMessage in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12173 | WP Admin Microblog &amp;lt;= 3.1.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Message Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12173</link><description>The WP Admin Microblog plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'wp-admin-microblog' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send messages on behalf of an administrator via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12372 | The Permalinks Cascade &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Missing Authorization To Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12372</link><description>The Permalinks Cascade plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 2.2. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action in the handleTPCAdminAjaxRequest function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to perform unauthorized administrative actions such as enabling or disabling automatic pinging settings and modifying page exclusion settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12404 | Like-it &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12404</link><description>The Like-it plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the likeit_conf() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12406 | Project Honey Pot Spam Trap &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12406</link><description>The Project Honey Pot Spam Trap plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the printAdminPage() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12411 | Premmerce Wholesale Pricing for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.10 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12411</link><description>The Premmerce Wholesale Pricing for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'ID' parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.1.10. This is due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to manipulate SQL queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database and modify price type display names in the database via the admin-post.php "premmerce_update_price_type" action, causing cosmetic corruption of the admin interface. The 'price_type' parameter of the "premmerce_delete_price_type" is also vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12528 | Pie Forms for WP &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12528</link><description>The Pie Forms for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload in all versions up to, and including, 1.6 via the format_classic function. This is due to insufficient file type validation where the validate_classic method validates file extensions and sets error messages but does not prevent the file upload process from continuing. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload files with dangerous extensions such as PHP, which makes remote code execution possible. In order to exploit this vulnerability, the attacker needs to guess the directory in which the file is placed (which is a somewhat predictable hash). In addition to that, the file name is generated using a secure hash method, limiting the exploitability of this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12775 | WP Dropzone &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12775</link><description>The WP Dropzone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authenticated arbitrary file upload in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 via the `ajax_upload_handle` function. This is due to the chunked upload functionality writing files directly to the uploads directory before any file type validation occurs. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12823 | CSV to SortTable &amp;lt;= 4.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12823</link><description>The CSV to SortTable plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'csv' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12827 | Top Friends &amp;lt;= 0.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12827</link><description>The Top Friends plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.3. This is due to missing nonce validation on the top_friends_options_subpanel() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12937 | ACF Flexible Layouts Manager &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Custom Field Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12937</link><description>The ACF Flexible Layouts Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'acf_flm_update_template_with_pasted_layout' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update custom field values on individual posts and pages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12961 | Download Panel &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Plugin Settings Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12961</link><description>The Download Panel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized settings modification due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_save_settings' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.3. This is due to the absence of any capability verification in the `dlpn_save_settings()` function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to arbitrarily modify plugin settings including display text, download links, button colors, and other visual customizations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12962 | Local Syndication &amp;lt;= 1.5a - Authenticated (Contributor+) Server-Side Request Forgery via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12962</link><description>The Local Syndication plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.5a via the `url` parameter in the `[syndicate_local]` shortcode. This is due to the use of `wp_remote_get()` instead of `wp_safe_remote_get()` which lacks protections against requests to internal/private IP addresses and localhost. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application, which can be used to query and modify information from internal services, scan internal networks, and access resources that should not be accessible from external networks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13088 | Category and Product Woocommerce Tabs &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13088</link><description>The Category and Product Woocommerce Tabs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to insufficient input validation on the 'template' parameter in the categoryProductTab() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary .php files on the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8605 | Gutenify - Visual Site Builder Blocks &amp;amp; Site Templates &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Count Up block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8605</link><description>The Gutenify – Visual Site Builder Blocks &amp; Site Templates. plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's block attributes in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8609 | RTMKit Addons &amp;lt;= 1.6.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Accordion Repeater Block Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8609</link><description>The RTMKit Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Accordion Block's attributes in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9625 | Coil Web Monetization &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9625</link><description>The Coil Web Monetization plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the coil-get-css-selector parameter handling in the maybe_restrict_content function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to trigger CSS selector detection functionality via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8727 | A stack buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Supermicro BMC Web function(SSL).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8727</link><description>There is a vulnerability in the Supermicro BMC web function at Supermicro MBD-X13SEDW-F. After logging into the BMC Web server, an attacker can use a specially crafted payload to trigger the Stack buffer overflow vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10089 | Malicious Code Execution Vulnerability in Setting and Operation Application for Lighting Control System MILCO.S</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10089</link><description>Malicious Code Execution Vulnerability in Setting and Operation Application for Lighting Control System MILCO.S Setting Application all versions, MILCO.S Setting Application (IR) all versions, MILCO.S Easy Setting Application (IR) all versions, and MILCO.S Easy Switch Application (IR) all versions allows a local attacker to execute malicious code by having installer to load a malicious DLL. However, if the signer name "Mitsubishi Electric Lighting" appears on the "Digital Signatures" tab of the properties for "MILCO.S Lighting Control.exe", the application is a fixed one. This vulnerability only affects when the installer is run, not after installation. If a user downloads directly from our company website and installs the affected product, there is no risk of malicious code being introduced.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 07:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8404 | Stack buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Supermicro BMC Shared library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8404</link><description>Stack buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Supermicro BMC Shared library. An authenticated attacker with access to the BMC exploit stack buffer via a crafted  header and achieve arbitrary code execution of the BMC’s firmware operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 07:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11265 | VK All in One Expansion Unit &amp;lt;= 9.112.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11265</link><description>The VK All in One Expansion Unit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'vkExUnit_cta_url' and 'vkExUnit_cta_button_text' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 9.112.1. This is due to a logic error in the CTA save function that reads sanitization callbacks from the wrong variable ($custom_field_name instead of $custom_field_options), causing the sanitization to never be applied. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute when a user accesses an injected page.",</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 07:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11267 | VK All in One Expansion Unit &amp;lt;= 9.112.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11267</link><description>The VK All in One Expansion Unit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the '_veu_custom_css' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 9.112.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the user-supplied Custom CSS value. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 07:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8076 | A stack buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Supermicro BMC Web function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8076</link><description>There is a vulnerability in the Supermicro BMC web function at Supermicro MBD-X13SEDW-F. After logging into the BMC Web server, an attacker can use a specially crafted payload to trigger the Stack buffer overflow vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 07:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7623 | Supermicro BMC SMASH services has a Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7623</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow in the SMASH-CLP shell. An authenticated attacker with SSH access to the BMC can overflow a 260-byte stack buffer via a crafted SMASH command, overwrite the return address and registers, and achieve arbitrary code execution on the BMC’s firmware operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 07:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12524 | Post Type Switcher &amp;lt;= 4.0.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Author+) Post Type Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12524</link><description>The Post Type Switcher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in versions up to, and including, 4.0.0 due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to modify the post type of arbitrary posts and pages they do not own, including those created by administrators, which can lead to site disruption, broken navigation, and SEO impact.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 06:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48593 | In bta_hf_client_cb_init of bta_hf_client_main.cc, there is a possible remote code execution due to a use after free. This could lead to rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48593</link><description>In bta_hf_client_cb_init of bta_hf_client_main.cc, there is a possible remote code execution due to a use after free. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 05:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12974 | Gravity Forms &amp;lt;= 2.9.21.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload via Legacy Chunked Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12974</link><description>The Gravity Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the legacy chunked upload mechanism in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.21.1. This is due to the extension blacklist not including .phar files, which can be uploaded through the chunked upload mechanism. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload executable .phar files and achieve remote code execution on the server, granted they can discover or enumerate the upload path. In order for an attacker to achieve RCE, the web server needs to be set up to process .phar file as PHP via file handler mapping or similar.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 03:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52457 | Observable Timing Discrepancy (CWE-208) in HBUS devices may allow an attacker with physical access to the device to extract device-specific ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52457</link><description>Observable Timing Discrepancy (CWE-208) in HBUS devices may allow an attacker with physical access to the device to extract device-specific keys, potentially compromising further site security. 

This issue affects Command Centre Server:

9.30 prior to vCR9.30.251028a (distributed in 9.30.2881 (MR3)), 9.20 prior to vCR9.20.251028a (distributed in 9.20.3265 (MR5)), 9.10 prior to vCR9.10.251028a (distributed in 9.10.4135 (MR8)), all versions of 9.00 and prior.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 03:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52578 | Incorrect Usage of Seeds in Pseudo-Random Number Generator (CWE- 335) vulnerability in the High Sec ELM may allow a sophisticated attacker w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52578</link><description>Incorrect Usage of Seeds in Pseudo-Random Number Generator (CWE- 335) vulnerability in the High Sec ELM may allow a sophisticated attacker with physical access, to compromise internal device communications.

This issue affects Command Centre Server: 

9.30 prior to vCR9.30.251028a (distributed in 9.30.2881 (MR3)), 9.20 prior to vCR9.20.251028a (distributed in 9.20.3265 (MR5)), 9.10 prior to vCR9.10.251028a (distributed in 9.10.4135 (MR8)), all versions of 9.00 and prior.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 03:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64734 | Missing Release of Resource after Effective Lifetime (CWE-772) in the T21 Reader allows an attacker with physical access to the Reader to pe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64734</link><description>Missing Release of Resource after Effective Lifetime (CWE-772) in the T21 Reader allows an attacker with physical access to the Reader to perform a denial-of-service attack against that specific reader, preventing cardholders from badging for entry. 

This issue affects Command Centre Server: 

9.30 prior to vCR9.30.251028a (distributed in 9.30.2881 (MR3)), 9.20 prior to vCR9.20.251028a (distributed in 9.20.3265 (MR5)), 9.10 prior to vCR9.10.251028a (distributed in 9.10.4135 (MR8)),  all versions of 9.00 and prior.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 03:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6599 | An uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in the web server of Zyxel DX3301-T0 firmware version 5.50(ABVY.6.3)C0 and earlier could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6599</link><description>An uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in the web server of Zyxel DX3301-T0 firmware version 5.50(ABVY.6.3)C0 and earlier could allow an attacker to perform Slowloris‑style denial‑of‑service (DoS) attacks. Such attacks may temporarily block legitimate HTTP requests and partially disrupt access to the web management interface, while other networking services remain unaffected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 02:06:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8693 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the "priv" parameter of Zyxel DX3300-T0 firmware version 5.50(ABVY.6.3)C0 and earli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8693</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the "priv" parameter of Zyxel DX3300-T0 firmware version 5.50(ABVY.6.3)C0 and earlier could allow an authenticated attacker to execute operating system (OS) commands on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 02:06:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12792 | The Mac App Store distribution of the Canva for Mac desktop app before 1.117.1 was built without Hardened Runtime. A local threat actor with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12792</link><description>The Mac App Store distribution of the Canva for Mac desktop app before 1.117.1 was built without Hardened Runtime. A local threat actor with unprivileged access could execute arbitrary code that inherits the TCC (Transparency, Consent, and Control) permissions assigned to Canva.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 02:06:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13323 | code-projects Simple Pizza Ordering System listorder.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13323</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Simple Pizza Ordering System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /listorder.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 02:06:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13325 | itsourcecode Student Information System enrollment_edit1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13325</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Student Information System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /enrollment_edit1.php. Executing manipulation of the argument en_id can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 02:06:32 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>