<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:51:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-3884 | Undertow: outofmemory when parsing form data encoding with application/x-www-form-urlencoded</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3884</link><description>A flaw was found in Undertow that can cause remote denial of service attacks. When the server uses the FormEncodedDataDefinition.doParse(StreamSourceChannel) method to parse large form data encoding with application/x-www-form-urlencoded, the method will cause an OutOfMemory issue. This flaw allows unauthorized users to cause a remote denial of service (DoS) attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:51:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63401 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in HCL Technologies Limited HCLTech DRAGON before v.7.6.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63401</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in HCL Technologies Limited HCLTech DRAGON before v.7.6.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via missing directives</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:51:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63402 | An issue in HCL Technologies Limited HCLTech GRAGON before v.7.6.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via APIs do not enforc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63402</link><description>An issue in HCL Technologies Limited HCLTech GRAGON before v.7.6.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via APIs do not enforcing limits on the number or size of requests</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:51:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66220 | Envoy’s TLS certificate matcher for `match_typed_subject_alt_names` may incorrectly treat certificates containing an embedded null byte</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66220</link><description>Envoy is a high-performance edge/middle/service proxy. In 1.33.12, 1.34.10, 1.35.6, 1.36.2, and earlier, Envoy’s mTLS certificate matcher for match_typed_subject_alt_names may incorrectly treat certificates containing an embedded null byte (\0) inside an OTHERNAME SAN value as valid matches.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:51:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66222 | DeepChat Cross-Site Scripting(XSS) escalate to Remote Code Execution(RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66222</link><description>DeepChat is a smart assistant uses artificial intelligence. In 0.5.0 and earlier, there is a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Mermaid diagram renderer allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript within the application context. By leveraging the exposed Electron IPC bridge, this XSS can be escalated to Remote Code Execution (RCE) by registering and starting a malicious MCP (Model Context Protocol) server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33201 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause an improper check for unusual or exceptional conditions ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33201</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause an improper check for unusual or exceptional conditions issue by sending extra large payloads. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33208 | NVIDIA TAO contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause a resource to be loaded via an uncontrolled search path. A successful exploi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33208</link><description>NVIDIA TAO contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause a resource to be loaded via an uncontrolled search path. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to escalation of privileges, data tampering, denial of service, information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:51:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33211 | NVIDIA Triton Server for Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause an improper validation of specified quantity in input. A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33211</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Server for Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause an improper validation of specified quantity in input. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:51:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66032 | Claude Code Command Validation Bypass Allows Arbitrary Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66032</link><description>Claude Code is an agentic coding tool. Prior to 1.0.93, Due to errors in parsing shell commands related to $IFS and short CLI flags, it was possible to bypass the Claude Code read-only validation and trigger arbitrary code execution. Reliably exploiting this requires the ability to add untrusted content into a Claude Code context window. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.0.93.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:51:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66208 | Configuration-Dependent RCE (OS Command Injection) in richdocumentscode proxy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66208</link><description>Collabora Online - Built-in CODE Server (richdocumentscode) provides a built-in server with all of the document editing features of Collabora Online. In versions prior to 25.04.702, Collabora Online has a Configuration-Dependent RCE (OS Command Injection) in richdocumentscode proxy. Users of Nextcloud with Collabora Online - Built-in CODE Server app can be vulnerable to attack via proxy.php and an intermediate reverse proxy. This vulnerability is fixed in 25.04.702.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:51:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64527 | Envoy crashes when JWT authentication is configured with the remote JWKS fetching</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64527</link><description>Envoy is a high-performance edge/middle/service proxy. In 1.33.12, 1.34.10, 1.35.6, 1.36.2, and earlier, Envoy crashes when JWT authentication is configured with the remote JWKS fetching, allow_missing_or_failed is enabled, multiple JWT tokens are present in the request headers and the JWKS fetch fails. This is caused by a re-entry bug in the JwksFetcherImpl. When the first token's JWKS fetch fails, onJwksError() callback triggers processing of the second token, which calls fetch() again on the same fetcher object. The original callback's reset() then clears the second fetch's state (receiver_ and request_) which causes a crash when the async HTTP response arrives.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:20:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64763 | Envoy forwards early CONNECT data in TCP proxy mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64763</link><description>Envoy is a high-performance edge/middle/service proxy. In 1.33.12, 1.34.10, 1.35.6, 1.36.2, and earlier, when Envoy is configured in TCP proxy mode to handle CONNECT requests, it accepts client data before issuing a 2xx response and forwards that data to the upstream TCP connection. If a forwarding proxy upstream from Envoy then responds with a non-2xx status, this can cause a de-synchronized CONNECT tunnel state. By default Envoy continues to allow early CONNECT data to avoid disrupting existing deployments. The envoy.reloadable_features.reject_early_connect_data runtime flag can be set to reject CONNECT requests that send data before a 2xx response when intermediaries upstream from Envoy may reject establishment of a CONNECT tunnel.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:20:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64443 | DNS Rebinding vulnerability present when running MCP Gateway in sse or streaming mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64443</link><description>MCP Gateway allows easy and secure running and deployment of MCP servers. In versions 0.27.0 and earlier, when MCP Gateway runs in sse or streaming transport mode, it is vulnerable to DNS rebinding. An attacker who can get a victim to visit a malicious website or be served a malicious advertisement can perform browser-based exploitation of MCP servers executing behind the gateway, including manipulating tools or other features exposed by those MCP servers. MCP Gateway is not affected when running in the default stdio mode, which does not listen on network ports. Version 0.28.0 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:54:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53965 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53965</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, 1580, 2500, W920, W930, W1000, Modem 5123, Modem 5300, and Modem 5400. The function used to decode the SOR transparent container lacks bounds checking, which can cause a fatal error.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54326 | An issue was discovered in Camera in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1280 and 2200. Unnecessary registration of a hardware IP address in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54326</link><description>An issue was discovered in Camera in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1280 and 2200. Unnecessary registration of a hardware IP address in the Camera device driver can lead to a NULL pointer dereference, resulting in a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54065 | GZDoom engine allows arbitrary code execution via ZScript actor states</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54065</link><description>GZDoom is a feature centric port for all Doom engine games. GZDoom is an open source Doom engine. In versions 4.14.2 and earlier, ZScript actor state handling allows scripts to read arbitrary addresses, write constants into the JIT-compiled code section, and redirect control flow through crafted FState and VMFunction structures. A script can copy FState structures into a writable buffer, modify function pointers and state transitions, and cause execution of attacker-controlled bytecode, leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32643 | Masa CMS vulnerable to authentication bypass with /tag/</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32643</link><description>Masa CMS is an open source Enterprise Content Management platform. Prior to 7.2.8, 7.3.13, and 7.4.6, if the URL to the page is modified to include a /tag/ declaration, the CMS will render the page regardless of group restrictions. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.2.8, 7.3.13, and 7.4.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20381 | SPL commands allowlist controls bypass in Splunk MCP Server app through &amp;quot;run_splunk_query&amp;quot; MCP tool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20381</link><description>In Splunk MCP Server app versions below 0.2.4, a user with access to the "run_splunk_query" Model Context Protocol (MCP) tool could bypass the SPL command allowlist controls in MCP by embedding SPL commands as sub-searches, leading to unauthorized actions beyond the intended MCP restrictions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20382 | URL validation bypass through Views Dashboard in Splunk Enterprise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20382</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 10.0.2, 9.4.6, 9.3.8, and 9.2.10, and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 10.1.2507.10, 10.0.2503.8, and 9.3.2411.120, a low-privileged user that does not hold the "admin" or "power" Splunk roles could create a views dashboard with a custom background using the `data:image/png;base64` protocol that could potentially lead to an unvalidated redirect. This behavior circumvents the Splunk external URL warning mechanism by using a specially crafted URL, allowing for a redirection to an external malicious site. The vulnerability requires the attacker to phish the victim by tricking them into initiating a request within their browser. The authenticated user should not be able to exploit the vulnerability at will.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20383 | Improper access control through push notifications for reports and alerts in Splunk Secure Gateway app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20383</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 10.0.2, 9.4.6, 9.3.8, and 9.2.10, and below 3.9.10, 3.8.58, and 3.7.28 of Splunk Secure Gateway app in Splunk Cloud Platform, a low-privileged user that does not hold the "admin" or "power" Splunk roles and subscribes to mobile push notifications could receive notifications that disclose the title and description of the report or alert even if they do not have access to view the report or alert.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20384 | Unauthenticated Log Injection in Splunk Enterprise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20384</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 10.0.1, 9.4.6, 9.3.8, and 9.2.10, and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 10.1.2507.4, 10.0.2503.6, and 9.3.2411.117.125, an unauthenticated attacker can inject American National Standards Institute (ANSI) escape codes into Splunk log files due to improper validation at the /en-US/static/ web endpoint. This may allow them to poison, forge, or obfuscate sensitive log data through specially crafted HTTP requests, potentially impacting log integrity and detection capabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20385 | Stored Cross-Site scripting (XSS) through Anchor Tag &amp;quot;href&amp;quot; in Navigation Bar Collections in Splunk Enterprise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20385</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 10.0.2, 9.4.6, 9.3.8, and 9.2.10, and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 10.1.2507.6, 10.0.2503.7, and 9.3.2411.117, a user who holds a role with a high privilege capability `admin_all_objects` could craft a malicious payload through the href attribute of an anchor tag within a collection in the navigation bar, which could result in execution of unauthorized JavaScript code in the browser of a user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20386 | Incorrect permission assignment on Splunk Enterprise for Windows during new installation or upgrade</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20386</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise for Windows versions below 10.0.2, 9.4.6, 9.3.8, and 9.2.10, a new installation of or an upgrade to an affected version can result in incorrect permissions assignment in the Splunk Enterprise for Windows Installation directory. This lets non-administrator users on the machine access the directory and all its contents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20387 | Incorrect permissions assignment on Splunk Universal Forwarder for Windows during new installation or upgrade</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20387</link><description>In Splunk Universal Forwarder for Windows versions below 10.0.2, 9.4.6, 9.3.8, and 9.2.10, a new installation of or an upgrade to an affected version can result in incorrect permissions assignment in the Universal Forwarder for Windows Installation directory. This lets non-administrator users on the machine access the directory and all its contents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20388 | Blind Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) through Distributed Search Peers in Splunk Enterprise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20388</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 10.0.1, 9.4.6, 9.3.8, and 9.2.10, and Splunk Cloud Platform versions below 10.1.2507.4, 10.0.2503.7, and 9.3.2411.116, a user who holds a role that contains the high privilege capability `change_authentication` could enumerate internal IP addresses and network ports when adding new search peers to a Splunk search head in a distributed environment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20389 | Improper Input Validation in &amp;quot;label&amp;quot; column field in Splunk Secure Gateway App</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20389</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 10.0.2, 9.4.6, 9.3.8, and 9.2.10, and versions below 3.9.10, 3.8.58 and 3.7.28 of the Splunk Secure Gateway app on Splunk Cloud Platform, a low-privileged user that does not hold the "admin" or "power" Splunk roles could craft a malicious payload through the `label` column field after adding a new device in the Splunk Secure Gateway app. This could potentially lead to a client-side denial of service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34319 | TOTOLINK N300RT &amp;lt;= V2.1.8-B20201030.1539 Boa formWsc RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34319</link><description>TOTOLINK N300RT wireless router firmware versions prior to V3.4.0-B20250430 (discovered in V2.1.8-B20201030.1539) contain an OS command injection vulnerability in the Boa formWsc handling functionality. An unauthenticated attacker can send specially crafted requests to trigger command execution via the targetAPSsid request parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65841 | Aquarius Desktop 3.0.069 for macOS stores user authentication credentials in the local file ~/Library/Application Support/Aquarius/aquarius....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65841</link><description>Aquarius Desktop 3.0.069 for macOS stores user authentication credentials in the local file ~/Library/Application Support/Aquarius/aquarius.settings using a weak obfuscation scheme. The password is "encrypted" through predictable byte-substitution that can be trivially reversed, allowing immediate recovery of the plaintext value. Any attacker who can read this settings file can fully compromise the victim's Aquarius account by importing the stolen configuration into their own client or login through the vendor website. This results in complete account takeover, unauthorized access to cloud-synchronized data, and the ability to perform authenticated actions as the user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65842 | The Aquarius HelperTool (1.0.003) privileged XPC service on macOS contains multiple flaws that allow local privilege escalation. The service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65842</link><description>The Aquarius HelperTool (1.0.003) privileged XPC service on macOS contains multiple flaws that allow local privilege escalation. The service accepts XPC connections from any local process without validating the client's identity, and its authorization logic incorrectly calls AuthorizationCopyRights with a NULL reference, causing all authorization checks to succeed. The executeCommand:authorization:withReply: method then interpolates attacker-controlled input into NSTask and executes it with root privileges. A local attacker can exploit these weaknesses to run arbitrary commands as root, create persistent backdoors, or obtain a fully interactive root shell.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32642 | Host header poisoning allows account takeover via password reset email</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32642</link><description>Masa CMS is an open source Enterprise Content Management platform. Prior to 7.2.8, 7.3.13, and 7.4.6, there is vulnerable to host header poisoning which allows account takeover via password reset email. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.2.8, 7.3.13, and 7.4.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13492 | HP Image Assistant - Potential Escalation of Privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13492</link><description>A potential security vulnerability has been identified in HP Image Assistant for versions prior to 5.3.3. The vulnerability
               could potentially allow a local attacker to escalate privileges via a race condition when installing packages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65843 | Aquarius Desktop 3.0.069 for macOS contains an insecure file handling vulnerability in its support data archive generation feature. The appl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65843</link><description>Aquarius Desktop 3.0.069 for macOS contains an insecure file handling vulnerability in its support data archive generation feature. The application follows symbolic links placed inside the ~/Library/Logs/Aquarius directory and treats them as regular files. When building the support ZIP, Aquarius recursively enumerates logs using a JUCE directory iterator configured to follow symlinks, and later writes file data without validating whether the target is a symbolic link. A local attacker can exploit this behavior by planting symlinks to arbitrary filesystem locations, resulting in unauthorized disclosure or modification of arbitrary files. When chained with the associated HelperTool privilege escalation issue, root-owned files may also be exposed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66431 | WebPros Plesk before 18.0.73.5 and 18.0.74 before 18.0.74.2 on Linux allows remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary code as root via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66431</link><description>WebPros Plesk before 18.0.73.5 and 18.0.74 before 18.0.74.2 on Linux allows remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary code as root via domain creation. The attacker needs "Create and manage sites" with "Domains management" and "Subdomains management."</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32641 | Masa CMS Vulnerable to Pre-Auth RCE via JSON API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32641</link><description>Masa CMS is an open source Enterprise Content Management platform. Masa CMS versions prior to 7.2.8, 7.3.13, and 7.4.6 are vulnerable to remote code execution. The vulnerability exists in the addParam function, which accepts user input via the criteria parameter. This input is subsequently evaluated by setDynamicContent, allowing an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code via the m tag. The vulnerability is patched in versions 7.2.8, 7.3.13, and 7.4.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13751 | Interactive service agent in OpenVPN version 2.5.0 through 2.7_rc2 on Windows allows a local authenticated user to connect to the service an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13751</link><description>Interactive service agent in OpenVPN version 2.5.0 through 2.7_rc2 on Windows allows a local authenticated user to connect to the service and trigger an error causing a local denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55076 | A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the InstallationHelper service included with Plugin Alliance Installation Manager v1.4....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55076</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the InstallationHelper service included with Plugin Alliance Installation Manager v1.4.0 for macOS. The service accepts unauthenticated XPC connections and executes input via system(), which may allow a local user to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62686 | A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Plugin Alliance InstallationHelper service included with Plugin Alliance Installati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62686</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Plugin Alliance InstallationHelper service included with Plugin Alliance Installation Manager v1.4.0 on macOS. Due to the absence of a hardened runtime and a __RESTRICT segment, a local user may exploit the DYLD_INSERT_LIBRARIES environment variable to inject a dynamic library, potentially resulting in code execution with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65320 | Abacre Restaurant Point of Sale (POS) up to 15.0.0.1656 are vulnerable to Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information in Memory. The applicat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65320</link><description>Abacre Restaurant Point of Sale (POS) up to 15.0.0.1656 are vulnerable to Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information in Memory. The application leaves valid device-bound license keys in process memory during an activation attempt.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57202 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the PwdGrp.cgi endpoint of AVTECH SECURITY Corporation DGM1104 FullImg-1015-1004-1006-1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57202</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the PwdGrp.cgi endpoint of AVTECH SECURITY Corporation DGM1104 FullImg-1015-1004-1006-1003 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the username field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55182 | A pre-authentication remote code execution vulnerability exists in React Server Components versions 19.0.0, 19.1.0, 19.1.1, and 19.2.0 inclu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55182</link><description>A pre-authentication remote code execution vulnerability exists in React Server Components versions 19.0.0, 19.1.0, 19.1.1, and 19.2.0 including the following packages: react-server-dom-parcel, react-server-dom-turbopack, and react-server-dom-webpack. The vulnerable code unsafely deserializes payloads from HTTP requests to Server Function endpoints.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57199 | AVTECH SECURITY Corporation DGM1104 FullImg-1015-1004-1006-1003 was discovered to contain an authenticated command injection vulnerability i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57199</link><description>AVTECH SECURITY Corporation DGM1104 FullImg-1015-1004-1006-1003 was discovered to contain an authenticated command injection vulnerability in the NetFailDetectD binary. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7044 | Privilege Escalation in MAAS via Websocket Request Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7044</link><description>An Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists in the user websocket handler of MAAS. An authenticated, unprivileged attacker can intercept a user.update websocket request and inject the is_superuser property set to true. The server improperly validates this input, allowing the attacker to self-promote to an administrator role. This results in full administrative control over the MAAS deployment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57198 | AVTECH SECURITY Corporation DGM1104 FullImg-1015-1004-1006-1003 was discovered to contain an authenticated command injection vulnerability i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57198</link><description>AVTECH SECURITY Corporation DGM1104 FullImg-1015-1004-1006-1003 was discovered to contain an authenticated command injection vulnerability in the Machine.cgi endpoint. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57201 | AVTECH SECURITY Corporation DGM1104 FullImg-1015-1004-1006-1003 was discovered to contain an authenticated command injection vulnerability i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57201</link><description>AVTECH SECURITY Corporation DGM1104 FullImg-1015-1004-1006-1003 was discovered to contain an authenticated command injection vulnerability in the SMB server function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57200 | AVTECH SECURITY Corporation DGM1104 FullImg-1015-1004-1006-1003 was discovered to contain an authenticated command injection vulnerability i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57200</link><description>AVTECH SECURITY Corporation DGM1104 FullImg-1015-1004-1006-1003 was discovered to contain an authenticated command injection vulnerability in the test_mail function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65267 | In ERPNext v15.83.2 and Frappe Framework v15.86.0, improper validation of uploaded SVG avatar images allows attackers to embed malicious Jav...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65267</link><description>In ERPNext v15.83.2 and Frappe Framework v15.86.0, improper validation of uploaded SVG avatar images allows attackers to embed malicious JavaScript. The payload executes when an administrator clicks the image link to view the avatar, resulting in stored cross-site scripting (XSS). Successful exploitation may lead to account takeover, privilege escalation, or full compromise of the affected ERPNext instance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53841 | Akamai Guardicore Platform Agent before 52.1.1 allows an unprivileged user to fully elevate privileges to SYSTEM. This affects versions befo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53841</link><description>Akamai Guardicore Platform Agent before 52.1.1 allows an unprivileged user to fully elevate privileges to SYSTEM. This affects versions before 50.15.0, 51.12.0, and 52.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 14:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13948 | opsre go-ldap-admin JWT docker-compose.yaml hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13948</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in opsre go-ldap-admin up to 20251011. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file docs/docker-compose/docker-compose.yaml of the component JWT Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument secret key can lead to use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The attack can be launched remotely. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 14:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13949 | ProudMuBai GoFilm FileController.go SingleUpload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13949</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in ProudMuBai GoFilm 1.0.0/1.0.1. Impacted is the function SingleUpload of the file /server/controller/FileController.go. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 14:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13354 | Tag, Category, and Taxonomy Manager – AI Autotagger with OpenAI &amp;lt;= 3.40.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Taxonomy Term Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13354</link><description>The Tag, Category, and Taxonomy Manager – AI Autotagger with OpenAI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 3.40.1. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action in the "taxopress_merge_terms_batch" function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to merge or delete arbitrary taxonomy terms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 14:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13359 | Tag, Category, and Taxonomy Manager – AI Autotagger with OpenAI &amp;lt;= 3.40.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13359</link><description>The Tag, Category, and Taxonomy Manager – AI Autotagger with OpenAI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the "getTermsForAjax"  function in all versions up to, and including, 3.40.1. This is due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameters and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database granted they have metabox access for the taxonomy (enabled by default for contributors).</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 14:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13390 | WP Directory Kit &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Authentication Bypass to Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13390</link><description>The WP Directory Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 due to incorrect implementation of the authentication algorithm in the "wdk_generate_auto_login_link" function. This is due to the feature using a cryptographically weak token generation mechanism. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to gain administrative access and achieve full site takeover via the auto-login endpoint with a predictable token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 14:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13401 | Autoptimize &amp;lt;= 3.1.13 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13401</link><description>The Autoptimize plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the LCP Image to preload metabox in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied image attributes in the "create_img_preload_tag" function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 14:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13756 | Fluent Booking – The Ultimate Appointments Scheduling, Events Booking, Events Calendar Solution &amp;lt;= 1.9.11 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Missing Authorization to Calendar Import and Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13756</link><description>The Fluent Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized calendar import and management due to a missing capability check on the "importCalendar" function in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.11. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to import arbitrary calendars and manage them.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 14:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12358 | ShopEngine &amp;lt;= 4.8.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Wishlist Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12358</link><description>The ShopEngine Elementor WooCommerce Builder Addon plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.5. This is due to missing nonce validation on the "post_add_to_list" function as well as an incorrect permissions callback in the "Api/init" function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add or remove products from a user's wishlist via a forged request granted they can trick a site's user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 13:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12887 | Post SMTP – Complete SMTP Solution with Logs, Alerts, Backup SMTP &amp;amp; Mobile App &amp;lt;= 3.6.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) OAuth Token Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12887</link><description>The Post SMTP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.1. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to update OAuth tokens on the 'handle_gmail_oauth_redirect' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to inject invalid or attacker-controlled OAuth credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 13:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13109 | HUSKY – Products Filter Professional for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.3.7.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference via &amp;#x27;woof_add_query/woof_remove_query&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13109</link><description>The HUSKY – Products Filter Professional for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7.2 via the "woof_add_query" and "woof_remove_query" functions due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to insert or remove arbitrary saved search queries into any user's profile, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 13:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13342 | Frontend Admin by DynamiApps &amp;lt;= 3.28.20 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13342</link><description>The Frontend Admin by DynamiApps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of arbitrary WordPress options in all versions up to, and including, 3.28.20. This is due to insufficient capability checks and input validation in the ActionOptions::run() save handler. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify critical WordPress options such as users_can_register, default_role, and admin_email via submitting crafted form data to public frontend forms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 13:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39665 | Livestatus Injection in dynmaps</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39665</link><description>User enumeration in Nagvis' Checkmk MultisiteAuth before version 1.9.48 allows an unauthenticated attacker to enumerate Checkmk usernames.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 10:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13947 | Webkit: webkitgtk: remote user-assisted information disclosure via file drag-and-drop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13947</link><description>A flaw was found in WebKitGTK. This vulnerability allows remote, user-assisted information disclosure that can reveal any file the user is permitted to read via abusing the file drag-and-drop mechanism where WebKitGTK does not verify that drag operations originate from outside the browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 09:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13472 | Missing authorization in BlazeMeter Jenkins Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13472</link><description>A fix was made in BlazeMeter Jenkins Plugin version 4.27 to allow users only with certain permissions to see the list of available resources like credential IDs, bzm workspaces and bzm project Ids. Prior to this fix, anyone could see this list as a dropdown on the Jenkins UI.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 08:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12744 | Abrt: command-injection in abrt leading to local privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12744</link><description>A flaw was found in the ABRT daemon’s handling of user-supplied mount information.ABRT copies up to 12 characters from an untrusted input and places them directly into a shell command (docker inspect %s) without proper validation. An unprivileged local user can craft a payload that injects shell metacharacters, causing the root-running ABRT process to execute attacker-controlled commands and ultimately gain full root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 08:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29864 | Protection Mechanism Failure vulnerability in ESTsoft ALZip on Windows allows SmartScreen bypass.This issue affects ALZip: from 12.01 before...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29864</link><description>Protection Mechanism Failure vulnerability in ESTsoft ALZip on Windows allows SmartScreen bypass.This issue affects ALZip: from 12.01 before 12.29.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 08:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13945 | Improperly Controlled Sequential Memory Allocation in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13945</link><description>HTTP3 dissector crash in Wireshark 4.6.0 and 4.6.1 allows denial of service</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 08:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13946 | Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition (&amp;#x27;Infinite Loop&amp;#x27;) in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13946</link><description>MEGACO dissector infinite loop in Wireshark 4.6.0 to 4.6.1 and 4.4.0 to 4.4.11 allows denial of service</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 08:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13486 | Advanced Custom Fields: Extended 0.9.0.5 - 0.9.1.1 - Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution in prepare_form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13486</link><description>The Advanced Custom Fields: Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in versions 0.9.0.5 through 0.9.1.1 via the prepare_form() function. This is due to the function accepting user input and then passing that through call_user_func_array(). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code on the server, which can be leveraged to inject backdoors or create new administrative user accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 07:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12954 | Timetable and Event Schedule by MotoPress &amp;lt; 2.4.16 - Contributor+ Event Disclosure via IDOR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12954</link><description>The Timetable and Event Schedule by MotoPress WordPress plugin before 2.4.16 does not verify a user has access to a specific event when duplicating, leading to arbitrary event disclosure when to users with a role as low as Contributor.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10304 | Everest Backup – WordPress Cloud Backup, Migration, Restore &amp;amp; Cloning Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.8 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Backup Failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10304</link><description>The Everest Backup – WordPress Cloud Backup, Migration, Restore &amp; Cloning Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the process_status_unlink() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete the back-up progress files and cause a back-up to fail while it is in progress.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 04:01:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12585 | MxChat – AI Chatbot for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.5.5 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12585</link><description>The MxChat – AI Chatbot for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.5 via upload filenames. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract session values that can subsequently be used to access conversation data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 04:01:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13495 | FluentCart A New Era of eCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;groupKey&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13495</link><description>The FluentCart plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'groupKey' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1. This is due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 04:01:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13448 | CSSIgniter Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;element&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13448</link><description>The CSSIgniter Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'element' shortcode attribute in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 03:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13645 | Modula 2.13.1 - 2.13.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13645</link><description>The Modula Image Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the 'ajax_unzip_file' function in versions 2.13.1 to 2.13.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 03:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13646 | Modula 2.13.1 - 2.13.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload via Race Condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13646</link><description>The Modula Image Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'ajax_unzip_file' function in versions 2.13.1 to 2.13.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files with race condition on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 03:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65955 | ImageMagick has a use-after-free/double-free risk in Options::fontFamily when clearing family</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65955</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to 7.1.2-9 and 6.9.13-34, there is a vulnerability in ImageMagick’s Magick++ layer that manifests when Options::fontFamily is invoked with an empty string. Clearing a font family calls RelinquishMagickMemory on _drawInfo-&gt;font, freeing the font string but leaving _drawInfo-&gt;font pointing to freed memory while _drawInfo-&gt;family is set to that (now-invalid) pointer. Any later cleanup or reuse of _drawInfo-&gt;font re-frees or dereferences dangling memory. DestroyDrawInfo and other setters (Options::font, Image::font) assume _drawInfo-&gt;font remains valid, so destruction or subsequent updates trigger crashes or heap corruption. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.1.2-9 and 6.9.13-34.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 23:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55181 | Sending an HTTP request/response body with greater than 2^31 bytes triggers an infinite loop in proxygen::coro::HTTPQuicCoroSession which bl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55181</link><description>Sending an HTTP request/response body with greater than 2^31 bytes triggers an infinite loop in proxygen::coro::HTTPQuicCoroSession which blocks the backing event loop and unconditionally appends data to a std::vector per-loop iteration. This issue leads to unbounded memory growth and eventually causes the process to run out of memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66476 | Vim for Windows Uncontrolled Search Path Element Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66476</link><description>Vim is an open source, command line text editor. Prior to version 9.1.1947, an uncontrolled search path vulnerability on Windows allows Vim to execute malicious executables placed in the current working directory for the current edited file. On Windows, when using cmd.exe as a shell, Vim resolves external commands by searching the current working directory before system paths. When Vim invokes tools such as findstr for :grep, external commands or filters via :!, or compiler/:make commands, it may inadvertently run a malicious executable present in the same directory as the file being edited. The issue affects Vim for Windows prior to version 9.1.1947.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 21:55:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61940 | Mirion Medical EC2 Software NMIS BioDose Use of Client-Side Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61940</link><description>NMIS/BioDose V22.02 and previous versions rely on a common SQL Server user account to access data in the database. User access in the client application is restricted by a password authentication check in the client software but the underlying database connection always has access. The latest version of NMIS/BioDose introduces an option to use Windows user authentication with the database, which would restrict this database connection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 21:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62575 | Mirion Medical EC2 Software NMIS BioDose Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62575</link><description>NMIS/BioDose V22.02 and previous versions rely on a Microsoft SQL Server database. The SQL user account 'nmdbuser' and other created accounts by default have the sysadmin role. This can lead to remote code execution through the use of certain built-in stored procedures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 21:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64298 | Mirion Medical EC2 Software NMIS BioDose Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64298</link><description>NMIS/BioDose V22.02 and previous version installations where the embedded Microsoft SQLServer Express is used are exposed in the Windows share accessed by clients in networked installs. By default, this directory has insecure directory paths that allow access to the SQL Server database and configuration files, which can contain sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 21:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64642 | Mirion Medical EC2 Software NMIS BioDose Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64642</link><description>NMIS/BioDose V22.02 and previous versions' installation directory paths by default have insecure file permissions, which in certain deployment scenarios can enable users on client workstations to modify the program executables and libraries.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 21:27:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64778 | Mirion Medical EC2 Software NMIS BioDose Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64778</link><description>NMIS/BioDose software V22.02 and previous versions contain executable binaries with plain text hard-coded passwords. These hard-coded passwords could allow unauthorized access to both the application and database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 21:27:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65380 | PHPGurukul Billing System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the admin/index.php endpoint. Specifically, the username parameter accepts u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65380</link><description>PHPGurukul Billing System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the admin/index.php endpoint. Specifically, the username parameter accepts unvalidated user input, which is then concatenated directly into a backend SQL query.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 21:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65657 | FeehiCMS version 2.1.1 has a Remote Code Execution via Unrestricted File Upload in Ad Management. FeehiCMS version 2.1.1 allows authenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65657</link><description>FeehiCMS version 2.1.1 has a Remote Code Execution via Unrestricted File Upload in Ad Management. FeehiCMS version 2.1.1 allows authenticated remote attackers to upload files that the server later executes (or stores in an executable location) without sufficient validation, sanitization, or execution restrictions. An authenticated remote attacker can upload a crafted PHP file and cause the application or web server to execute it, resulting in remote code execution (RCE).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 21:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65379 | PHPGurukul Billing System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the /admin/password-recovery.php endpoint. Specifically, the username and mo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65379</link><description>PHPGurukul Billing System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the /admin/password-recovery.php endpoint. Specifically, the username and mobileno parameters accepts unvalidated user input, which is then concatenated directly into a backend SQL query.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 20:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13658 | Industrial Video &amp;amp; Control Longwatch has a Code Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13658</link><description>A vulnerability in Longwatch devices allows unauthenticated HTTP GET requests to execute arbitrary code via an exposed endpoint, due to the absence of code signing and execution controls. Exploitation results in SYSTEM-level privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65877 | Lvzhou CMS before commit c4ea0eb9cab5f6739b2c87e77d9ef304017ed615 (2025-09-22) is vulnerable to SQL injection via the 'title' parameter in c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65877</link><description>Lvzhou CMS before commit c4ea0eb9cab5f6739b2c87e77d9ef304017ed615 (2025-09-22) is vulnerable to SQL injection via the 'title' parameter in com.wanli.lvzhoucms.service.ContentService#findPage. The parameter is concatenated directly into a dynamic SQL query without sanitization or prepared statements, enabling attackers to read sensitive data from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13510 | Iskra iHUB and iHUB Lite has a Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerabilitiy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13510</link><description>The Iskra iHUB and iHUB Lite smart metering gateway exposes its web management interface without requiring authentication, allowing unauthenticated users to access and modify critical device settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13542 | DesignThemes LMS &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13542</link><description>The DesignThemes LMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4. This is due to the 'dtlms_register_user_front_end' function not restricting what user roles a user can register with. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to supply the 'administrator' role during registration and gain administrator access to the site.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13633 | Use after free in Digital Credentials in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13633</link><description>Use after free in Digital Credentials in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:18:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13630 | Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13630</link><description>Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:18:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13631 | Inappropriate implementation in Google Updater in Google Chrome on Mac prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker to perform privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13631</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Google Updater in Google Chrome on Mac prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker to perform privilege escalation via a crafted file. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:18:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13632 | Inappropriate implementation in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a malic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13632</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a malicious extension to potentially perform a sandbox escape via a crafted Chrome Extension. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:18:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13634 | Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome on Windows prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a local attacker to bypass mark of the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13634</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome on Windows prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a local attacker to bypass mark of the web via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13635 | Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a local attacker to perform UI spoofing via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13635</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a local attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13636 | Inappropriate implementation in Split View in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13636</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Split View in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted domain name. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:18:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13637 | Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13637</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to bypass download protections via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:18:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13638 | Use after free in Media Stream in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13638</link><description>Use after free in Media Stream in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:18:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13639 | Inappropriate implementation in WebRTC in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker to perform arbitrary read/write via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13639</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in WebRTC in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker to perform arbitrary read/write via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13640 | Inappropriate implementation in Passwords in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a local attacker to bypass authentication via phys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13640</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Passwords in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a local attacker to bypass authentication via physical access to the device. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13720 | Bad cast in Loader in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to potentially...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13720</link><description>Bad cast in Loader in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13721 | Race in v8 in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13721</link><description>Race in v8 in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.41 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57850 | Codeready-ws: privilege escalation via excessive /etc/passwd permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57850</link><description>A container privilege escalation flaw was found in certain CodeReady Workspaces images. This issue stems from the /etc/passwd file being created with group-writable permissions during build time. In certain conditions, an attacker who can execute commands within an affected container, even as a non-root user, can leverage their membership in the root group to modify the /etc/passwd file. This could allow the attacker to add a new user with any arbitrary UID, including UID 0, leading to full root privileges within the container.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61729 | Excessive resource consumption when printing error string for host certificate validation in crypto/x509</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61729</link><description>Within HostnameError.Error(), when constructing an error string, there is no limit to the number of hosts that will be printed out. Furthermore, the error string is constructed by repeated string concatenation, leading to quadratic runtime. Therefore, a certificate provided by a malicious actor can result in excessive resource consumption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66468 | Aimeos GrapesJS CMS extension possible stores XSS exploitable by authenticated editors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66468</link><description>The Aimeos GrapesJS CMS extension provides page editor for creating content pages based on extensible components. Prior to 2021.10.8, 2022.10.8, 2023.10.8, 2024.10.8, and 2025.10.8, Javascript code can be injected by malicious editors for a stored XSS attack if the standard Content Security Policy is disabled. This vulnerability is fixed in 2021.10.8, 2022.10.8, 2023.10.8, 2024.10.8, and 2025.10.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34352 | JumpCloud Remote Assist &amp;lt; 0.317.0 Arbitrary File Write/Delete via Insecure Temp Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34352</link><description>JumpCloud Remote Assist for Windows versions prior to 0.317.0 include an uninstaller that is invoked by the JumpCloud Windows Agent as NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM during agent uninstall or update operations. The Remote Assist uninstaller performs privileged create, write, execute, and delete actions on predictable files inside a user-writable %TEMP% subdirectory without validating that the directory is trusted or resetting its ACLs when it already exists. A local, low-privileged attacker can pre-create the directory with weak permissions and leverage mount-point or symbolic-link redirection to (a) coerce arbitrary file writes to protected locations, leading to denial of service (e.g., by overwriting sensitive system files), or (b) win a race to redirect DeleteFileW() to attacker-chosen targets, enabling arbitrary file or folder deletion and local privilege escalation to SYSTEM. This issue is fixed in JumpCloud Remote Assist 0.317.0 and affects Windows systems where Remote Assist is installed and managed through the Agent lifecycle.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65896 | SQL injection vulnerability in long2ice assyncmy thru 0.2.10 allows attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via crafted dict keys.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65896</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in long2ice assyncmy thru 0.2.10 allows attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via crafted dict keys.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66454 | Arcade MCP Default Hardcoded Worker Secret Allows Full Unauthorized Access to All HTTP MCP Worker Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66454</link><description>Arcade MCP allows you to to create, deploy, and share MCP Servers. Prior to 1.5.4, the arcade-mcp HTTP server uses a hardcoded default worker secret ("dev") that is never validated or overridden during normal server startup. As a result, any unauthenticated attacker who knows this default key can forge valid JWTs and fully bypass the FastAPI authentication layer. This grants remote access to all worker endpoints—including tool enumeration and tool invocation—without credentials. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66458 | Lookyloo has multiple XSS due to unsafe use of f-strings in Markup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66458</link><description>Lookyloo is a web interface that allows users to capture a website page and then display a tree of domains that call each other. Prior to 1.35.3, there are multiple XSS due to unsafe use of f-strings in Markup. The issue requires a malicious 3rd party server responding with a JSON document containing JS code in a script element. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.35.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66459 | Lookyloo vulnerable to XSS due to unescaped error message passed to innerHTML</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66459</link><description>Lookyloo is a web interface that allows users to capture a website page and then display a tree of domains that call each other. Prior to 1.35.3, a XSS vulnerability can be triggered when a user submits a list of URLs to capture, one of them contains a HTML element, and the capture fails. Then, the error field is populated with an error message that contains the bad URL they tried to capture, triggering the XSS. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.35.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66460 | Lookyloo vulnerable to XSS due to lack of escaping in HTML elements passed to Datatables</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66460</link><description>Lookyloo is a web interface that allows users to capture a website page and then display a tree of domains that call each other. Prior to 1.35.3, Lookyloo passed improperly escaped values to cells rendered in datatables using the orthogonal-data feature. It is definitely exploitable from the popup view, but it is most probably also exploitable in many other places. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.35.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60736 | code-projects Online Medicine Guide 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /login.php via the upass parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60736</link><description>code-projects Online Medicine Guide 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /login.php via the upass parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66409 | ESF-IDF has an Out-of-Bounds Read in ESP32 Bluetooth AVRCP Command Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66409</link><description>ESF-IDF is the Espressif Internet of Things (IOT) Development Framework. In 5.5.1, 5.4.3, 5.3.4, 5.2.6, 5.1.6, and earlier, when AVRCP is enabled on ESP32, receiving a malformed VENDOR DEPENDENT command from a peer device can cause the Bluetooth stack to access memory before validating the command buffer length. This may lead to an out-of-bounds read, potentially exposing unintended memory content or causing unexpected behavior.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66414 | DNS Rebinding Protection Disabled by Default in Model Context Protocol TypeScript SDK for Servers Running on Localhost</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66414</link><description>MCP TypeScript SDK is the official TypeScript SDK for Model Context Protocol servers and clients. Prior to 1.24.0, The Model Context Protocol (MCP) TypeScript SDK does not enable DNS rebinding protection by default for HTTP-based servers. When an HTTP-based MCP server is run on localhost without authentication with StreamableHTTPServerTransport or SSEServerTransport and has not enabled enableDnsRebindingProtection, a malicious website could exploit DNS rebinding to bypass same-origin policy restrictions and send requests to the local MCP server. This could allow an attacker to invoke tools or access resources exposed by the MCP server on behalf of the user in those limited circumstances. Note that running HTTP-based MCP servers locally without authentication is not recommended per MCP security best practices. This issue does not affect servers using stdio transport. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.24.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66416 | DNS Rebinding Protection Disabled by Default in Model Context Protocol Python SDK for Servers Running on Localhost</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66416</link><description>The MCP Python SDK, called `mcp` on PyPI, is a Python implementation of the Model Context Protocol (MCP). Prior to version 1.23.0, tThe Model Context Protocol (MCP) Python SDK does not enable DNS rebinding protection by default for HTTP-based servers. When an HTTP-based MCP server is run on localhost without authentication using FastMCP with streamable HTTP or SSE transport, and has not configured TransportSecuritySettings, a malicious website could exploit DNS rebinding to bypass same-origin policy restrictions and send requests to the local MCP server. This could allow an attacker to invoke tools or access resources exposed by the MCP server on behalf of the user in those limited circumstances. Note that running HTTP-based MCP servers locally without authentication is not recommended per MCP security best practices. This issue does not affect servers using stdio transport. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.23.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52622 | HCL BigFix SaaS Remediate is affected by a security vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52622</link><description>The BigFix SaaS's HTTP responses were missing some security headers. The absence of these headers weakens the application's client-side security posture, making it more vulnerable to common web attacks that these headers are designed to mitigate, such as Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), Clickjacking, and protocol downgrade attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58386 | In Terminalfour 8 through 8.4.1.1, the userLevel parameter in the user management function is not subject to proper server-side authorizatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58386</link><description>In Terminalfour 8 through 8.4.1.1, the userLevel parameter in the user management function is not subject to proper server-side authorization checks. A Power User can intercept and modify this parameter to assign the Administrator role to other existing lower-privileged accounts, or invite a new lower-privileged account and escalate its privileges. While manipulating this request, the Power User can also change the target account's password, effectively taking full control of it.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65844 | EverShop 2.0.1 allows an unauthenticated user to upload files and create directories within the /api/images endpoint.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65844</link><description>EverShop 2.0.1 allows an unauthenticated user to upload files and create directories within the /api/images endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66399 | SNMP Command Injection leads to RCE in Cacti</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66399</link><description>Cacti is an open source performance and fault management framework. Prior to 1.2.29, there is an input-validation flaw in the SNMP device configuration functionality. An authenticated Cacti user can supply crafted SNMP community strings containing control characters (including newlines) that are accepted, stored verbatim in the database, and later embedded into backend SNMP operations. In environments where downstream SNMP tooling or wrappers interpret newline-separated tokens as command boundaries, this can lead to unintended command execution with the privileges of the Cacti process. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.29.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60854 | A vulnerability has been found in D-Link R15 (AX1500) 1.20.01 and below. By manipulating the model name parameter during a password change r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60854</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link R15 (AX1500) 1.20.01 and below. By manipulating the model name parameter during a password change request in the web administrator page, it is possible to trigger a command injection in httpd.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 17:56:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65105 | Apptainer ineffective application of selinux and apparmor --security options</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65105</link><description>Apptainer is an open source container platform. In Apptainer versions less than 1.4.5, a container can disable two of the forms of the little used --security option, in particular the forms --security=apparmor: and --security=selinux:&lt;label&gt; which otherwise put restrictions on operations that containers can do. The --security option has always been mentioned in Apptainer documentation as being a feature for the root user, although these forms do also work for unprivileged users on systems where the corresponding feature is enabled. Apparmor is enabled by default on Debian-based distributions and SElinux is enabled by default on RHEL-based distributions, but on SUSE it depends on the distribution version. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.4.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 17:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65881 | Sourcecodester Zoo Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /classes/Login.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65881</link><description>Sourcecodester Zoo Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /classes/Login.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 17:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65215 | Sourcecodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /product_expiry/add-supplier...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65215</link><description>Sourcecodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /product_expiry/add-supplier.php via the Supplier Name field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 17:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64750 | Singluarity ineffectively applies of selinux / apparmor LSM process labels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64750</link><description>SingularityCE and SingularityPRO are open source container platforms. Prior to SingularityCE 4.3.5 and SingularityPRO 4.1.11 and 4.3.5, if a user relies on LSM restrictions to prevent malicious operations then, under certain circumstances, an attacker can redirect the LSM label write operation so that it is ineffective. The attacker must cause the user to run a malicious container image that redirects the mount of /proc to the destination of a shared mount, either known to be configured on the target system, or that will be specified by the user when running the container. The attacker must also control the content of the shared mount, for example through another malicious container which also binds it, or as a user with relevant permissions on the host system it is bound from. This vulnerability is fixed in SingularityCE 4.3.5 and SingularityPRO 4.1.11 and 4.3.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 17:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13827 | GrapesJsBuilder File Upload allows all file uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13827</link><description>Summary
Arbitrary files can be uploaded via the GrapesJS Builder, as the types of files that can be uploaded are not restricted. 
ImpactIf the media folder is not restricted from running files this can lead to a remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13828 | Mautic user without privileged access to the Marketplace can install and uninstall composer packages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13828</link><description>SummaryA non privileged user can install and remove arbitrary packages via composer for a composer based installed, even if the flag in update settings for enable composer based update is unticked.

ImpactA low-privileged user of the platform can install malicious code to obtain higher privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64070 | Sourcecodester Student Grades Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Add New Subject Description field.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64070</link><description>Sourcecodester Student Grades Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Add New Subject Description field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65656 | dcat-admin v2.2.3-beta and before is vulnerable to file inclusion in admin/src/Extend/VersionManager.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65656</link><description>dcat-admin v2.2.3-beta and before is vulnerable to file inclusion in admin/src/Extend/VersionManager.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65358 | Edoc-doctor-appointment-system v1.0.1 was discovered to contain SQl injection vulnerability via the 'docid' parameter at /admin/appointment....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65358</link><description>Edoc-doctor-appointment-system v1.0.1 was discovered to contain SQl injection vulnerability via the 'docid' parameter at /admin/appointment.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65186 | Grav CMS 1.7.49 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). The page editor allows authenticated users to edit page content via a Markdown ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65186</link><description>Grav CMS 1.7.49 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). The page editor allows authenticated users to edit page content via a Markdown editor. The editor fails to properly sanitize</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13877 | nocobase JWT Service jwt-service.ts hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13877</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in nocobase up to 1.9.4/2.0.0-alpha.37. The affected element is an unknown function of the file nocobase\packages\core\auth\src\base\jwt-service.ts of the component JWT Service. The manipulation of the argument API_KEY results in use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The attack can be launched remotely. A high complexity level is associated with this attack. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12630 | Upload.am File Hosting VPN &amp;lt; 1.0.1 - Contributor+ Arbitrary Option Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12630</link><description>The Upload.am  WordPress plugin before 1.0.1 is vulnerable to arbitrary option disclosure due to a missing capability check on its AJAX request handler, allowing users such as contributor to view site options.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65187 | A Stored Cross Site Scripting vulnerability exists in CiviCRM before v6.7 in the Accounting Batches field. An authenticated user can inject ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65187</link><description>A Stored Cross Site Scripting vulnerability exists in CiviCRM before v6.7 in the Accounting Batches field. An authenticated user can inject malicious JavaScript into this field and it executes whenever the page is viewed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58113 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in the EMF functionality of PDF-XChange Co. Ltd PDF-XChange Editor 10.7.3.401.  By using a specia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58113</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in the EMF functionality of PDF-XChange Co. Ltd PDF-XChange Editor 10.7.3.401.  By using a specially crafted EMF file, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to perform an out-of-bounds read, potentially leading to the disclosure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59703 | Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a Physically Proximate Attacker to access the inter...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59703</link><description>Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a Physically Proximate Attacker to access the internal components of the appliance, without leaving tamper evidence. To exploit this, the attacker needs to remove the tamper label and all fixing screws from the device without damaging it. This is called an F14 attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59704 | Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow an attacker to gain access the the BIOS menu becaus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59704</link><description>Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow an attacker to gain access the the BIOS menu because is has no password.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63872 | DeepSeek V3.2 has a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability, which allows JavaScript execution through model-generated SVG content.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63872</link><description>DeepSeek V3.2 has a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability, which allows JavaScript execution through model-generated SVG content.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13372 | Potential SQL injection in FilteredRelation column aliases on PostgreSQL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13372</link><description>An issue was discovered in 5.2 before 5.2.9, 5.1 before 5.1.15, and 4.2 before 4.2.27.
`FilteredRelation` is subject to SQL injection in column aliases, using a suitably crafted dictionary, with dictionary expansion, as the `**kwargs` passed to `QuerySet.annotate()` or `QuerySet.alias()` on PostgreSQL.
Earlier, unsupported Django series (such as 5.0.x, 4.1.x, and 3.2.x) were not evaluated and may also be affected.
Django would like to thank Stackered for reporting this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64460 | Potential denial-of-service vulnerability in XML serializer text extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64460</link><description>An issue was discovered in 5.2 before 5.2.9, 5.1 before 5.1.15, and 4.2 before 4.2.27.
Algorithmic complexity in `django.core.serializers.xml_serializer.getInnerText()` allows a remote attacker to cause a potential denial-of-service attack triggering CPU and memory exhaustion via specially crafted XML input processed by the XML `Deserializer`.
Earlier, unsupported Django series (such as 5.0.x, 4.1.x, and 3.2.x) were not evaluated and may also be affected.
Django would like to thank Seokchan Yoon for reporting this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13875 | Yohann0617 oci-helper OCI Configuration Upload OciServiceImpl.java addCfg path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13875</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Yohann0617 oci-helper up to 3.2.4. This issue affects the function addCfg of the file src/main/java/com/yohann/ocihelper/service/impl/OciServiceImpl.java of the component OCI Configuration Upload. Executing manipulation of the argument File can lead to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13876 | Rareprob HD Video Player All Formats App com.rocks.music.videoplayer path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13876</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Rareprob HD Video Player All Formats App 12.1.372 on Android. Impacted is an unknown function of the component com.rocks.music.videoplayer. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack needs to be performed locally. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59699 | Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a physically proximate attacker to escalate privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59699</link><description>Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a physically proximate attacker to escalate privileges by booting from a USB device with a valid root filesystem. This occurs because of insecure default settings in the Legacy GRUB Bootloader.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59700 | Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a physically proximate attacker with root access to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59700</link><description>Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a physically proximate attacker with root access to modify the Recovery Partition (because of a lack of integrity protection).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59701 | Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a physically proximate attacker (with elevated priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59701</link><description>Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a physically proximate attacker (with elevated privileges) to read and modify the Appliance SSD contents (because they are unencrypted).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59702 | Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a physically proximate attacker with elevated privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59702</link><description>Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a physically proximate attacker with elevated privileges to falsify tamper events by accessing internal components.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59696 | Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a physically proximate attacker to modify or erase ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59696</link><description>Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a physically proximate attacker to modify or erase tamper events via the Chassis management board.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 14:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59697 | Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a physically proximate attacker to escalate privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59697</link><description>Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a physically proximate attacker to escalate privileges by editing the Legacy GRUB bootloader configuration to start a root shell upon boot of the host OS. This is called F06.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 14:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59698 | Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, might allow a physically proximate attacker to gain acces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59698</link><description>Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, might allow a physically proximate attacker to gain access to the EOL legacy bootloader.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 14:51:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59693 | The Chassis Management Board in Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allows a physically proxi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59693</link><description>The Chassis Management Board in Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allows a physically proximate attacker to obtain debug access and escalate privileges by bypassing the tamper label and opening the chassis without leaving evidence, and accessing the JTAG connector. This is called F02.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 14:51:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59694 | The Chassis Management Board in Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allows a physically proxi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59694</link><description>The Chassis Management Board in Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allows a physically proximate attacker to persistently modify firmware and influence the (insecurely configured) appliance boot process. To exploit this, the attacker must modify the firmware via JTAG or perform an upgrade to the chassis management board firmware. This is called F03.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 14:51:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59695 | Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a user with OS root access to alter firmware on the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59695</link><description>Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a user with OS root access to alter firmware on the Chassis Management Board (without Authentication). This is called F04.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 14:51:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59705 | Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a Physically Proximate Attacker to Escalate Privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59705</link><description>Entrust nShield Connect XC, nShield 5c, and nShield HSMi through 13.6.11, or 13.7, allow a Physically Proximate Attacker to Escalate Privileges by enabling the USB interface through chassis probe insertion during system boot, aka "Unauthorized Reactivation of the USB interface" or F01.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 14:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13505 | Stored XSS in Datateam&amp;#x27;s Datactive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13505</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting'), Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in Datateam Information Technologies Inc. Datactive allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Datactive: from 2.13.34 before 2.14.0.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 14:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41066 | Disclosure of sensitive information in Horde Groupware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41066</link><description>Horde Groupware v5.2.22 has a user enumeration vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker to determine the existence of valid accounts on the system. To exploit the vulnerability, an HTTP request must be sent to ‘/imp/attachment.php’ including the parameters ‘id’ and ‘u’. If the specified user exists, the server will return the download of an empty file; if it does not exist, no download will be initiated, which unequivocally reveals the validity of the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 14:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13731 | Nexter Extension &amp;lt;= 4.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13731</link><description>The Nexter Extension – Site Enhancements Toolkit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'nxt-year' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 14:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65858 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Calibre-Web v0.6.25 allows attackers to inject malicious JavaScript into the 'username'...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65858</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Calibre-Web v0.6.25 allows attackers to inject malicious JavaScript into the 'username' field during user creation. The payload is stored unsanitized and later executed when the /ajax/listusers endpoint is accessed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 14:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13295 | Sensitive Data Exposure in ArgusTech&amp;#x27;s BILGER</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13295</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Argus Technology Inc. BILGER allows Choosing Message Identifier.This issue affects BILGER: before 2.4.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41013 | SQL injection vulnerability in TCMAN GIM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41013</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in TCMAN GIM v11 in version 20250304. This vulnerability allows an attacker to retrieve, create, update, and delete databases by sending a GET request using the 'idmant' parameter in '/PC/frmEPIS.aspx'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41014 | User Enumeration vulnerability in TCMAN GIM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41014</link><description>User Enumeration Vulnerability in TCMAN GIM v11 version 20250304. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to determine whether a user exists on the system. The vulnerability is exploitable through the 'pda:username' parameter with 'soapaction GetLastDatePasswordChange' in '/WS/PDAWebService.asmx'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41015 | User Enumeration vulnerability in TCMAN GIM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41015</link><description>User Enumeration Vulnerability in TCMAN GIM v11 version 20250304. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to determine whether a user exists on the system. The vulnerability is exploitable through the 'pda:username' parameter with 'soapaction GetUserQuestionAndAnswer' in '/WS/PDAWebService.asmx'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41086 | Authorization bypass in GAMS from GAMS Development Corp.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41086</link><description>Vulnerability in the access control system of the GAMS licensing system that allows unlimited valid licenses to be generated, bypassing any usage restrictions. The validator uses an insecure checksum algorithm; knowing this algorithm and the format of the license lines, an attacker can recalculate the checksum and generate a valid license to grant themselves full privileges without credentials or access to the source code, allowing them unrestricted access to GAMS's mathematical models and commercial solvers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11778 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnreability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11778</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50 v0.9.2. This vulnerability allows an attacker to remotely exploit memory corruption through the 'read_packet()' function of the TACACSPLUS implementation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11779 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnreability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11779</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in CircutorSGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50 v9.0.2. The 'SetLan' function is invoked when a new configuration is applied. This new configuration function is activated by a management web request, which can be invoked by a user when making changes to the 'index.cgi' web application. The parameters are not being sanitised, which could lead to command injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11780 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnreability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11780</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50 v9.0.2. In the 'showMeterReport()' function, there is an unlimited user input that is copied to a fixed-size buffer via 'sprintf()'. The 'GetParameter(meter)' function retrieves the user input, which is directly incorporated into a buffer without size validation. An attacker can provide an excessively large input for the “meter” parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11781 | Use of hardcoded cryptographic keys in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11781</link><description>Use of hardcoded cryptographic keys in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50 v9.0.2. The affected firmware contains a hardcoded static authentication key. An attacker with local access to the device can extract this key (e.g., by analysing the firmware image or memory dump) and create valid firmware update packages. This bypasses all intended access controls and grants full administrative privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11782 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11782</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50 v9.0.2. The 'ShowDownload()' function uses “sprintf()” to format a string that includes the user-controlled input of 'GetParameter(meter)' in the fixed-size buffer 'acStack_4c' (64 bytes) without checking the length. An attacker can provide an excessively long value for the 'meter' parameter that exceeds the 64-byte buffer size.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11783 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11783</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50 v9.0.2. The vulnerability is found in the 'AddEvent()' function when copying the user-controlled username input to a fixed-size buffer (48 bytes) without boundary checking. This can lead to memory corruption, resulting in possible remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11784 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11784</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50 v9.0.2. In the 'ShowMeterDatabase()' function, there is an unlimited user input that is copied to a fixed-size buffer via 'sprintf()'. The 'GetParameter(meter)' function retrieves the user input, which is directly incorporated into a buffer without size validation. An attacker can provide an excessively large input for the 'meter' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11785 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11785</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50 v9.0.2. In the 'ShowMeterPasswords()' function, there is an unlimited user input that is copied to a fixed-size buffer via 'sprintf()'. The 'GetParameter(meter)' function retrieves the user input, which is directly incorporated into a buffer without size validation. An attacker can provide an excessively large input for the 'meter' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11786 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11786</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50 v9.0.2. In the 'SetUserPassword()' function, the 'newPassword' parameter is directly embedded in a shell command string using 'sprintf()' without any sanitisation or validation, and then executed using 'system()'. This allows an attacker to inject arbitrary shell commands that will be executed with the same privileges as the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11787 | Command injection vulnerability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11787</link><description>Command injection vulnerability in the operating system in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50 v9.0.2 through the 'GetDNS()', 'CheckPing()' and 'TraceRoute()' functions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11788 | Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11788</link><description>Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50 v9.0.2. In the 'ShowSupervisorParameters()' function, there is an unlimited user input that is copied to a fixed-size buffer via 'sprintf()'. The 'GetParameter(meter)' function retrieves the user input, which is directly incorporated into a buffer without size validation. An attacker can provide an excessively large input for the 'meter' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11789 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11789</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in Circutor SGE-PLC1000/SGE-PLC50 v9.0.2. The 'DownloadFile' function converts a parameter to an integer using 'atoi()' and then uses it as an index in the 'FilesDownload' array with '(&amp;amp;FilesDownload)[iVar2]'. If the parameter is too large, it will access memory beyond the limits.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40700 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Governalia by IDI Eikon</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40700</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in IDI Eikon's Governalia. The vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser when a malicious URL with the 'q' parameter in '/search' is sent to them. This vulnerability can be exploited to steal sensitive information such as session cookies or to perform actions on behalf of the victim.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41012 | Unauthorized access vulnerability in TCMAN GIM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41012</link><description>Unauthorized access vulnerability in TCMAN GIM v11 version 20250304. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to determine whether a user exists on the system by using the 'pda:userId' and 'pda:newPassword' parameters with 'soapaction UnlockUser’ in '/WS/PDAWebService.asmx'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13879 | Directory traversal vulnerability in EfficientIP&amp;#x27;s SOLIDserver IPAM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13879</link><description>Directory traversal vulnerability in SOLIDserver IPAM v8.2.3. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user with administrator privileges to list directories other than those to which the have authorized access using the 'directory' parameter in '/mod/ajax.php?action=sections/list/list'.For examplem setting the 'directory' parameter to '/' displays files outside the 'LOCAL:///' folder.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:07:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12465 | Blind SQL Injection in QuickCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12465</link><description>A Blind SQL injection vulnerability has been identified in QuickCMS. Improper neutralization of input provided by a high-privileged user into aFilesDelete allows for Blind SQL Injection attacks.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 6.8 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 12:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13090 | WP Directory Kit &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13090</link><description>The WP Directory Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'search' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13353 | gokey allows secret recovery from a seed file without the master password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13353</link><description>In gokey versions &lt;0.2.0,
 a flaw in the seed decryption logic resulted in passwords incorrectly 
being derived solely from the initial vector and the AES-GCM 
authentication tag of the key seed.


This issue has been fixed in gokey version 0.2.0. This is a breaking change. The fix has invalidated any passwords/secrets that were derived from the seed file (using the -s option). Even if the input seed file stays the same, version 0.2.0 gokey will generate different secrets.


Impact
This vulnerability impacts generated keys/secrets using a seed file as an entropy input (using the -s option). Keys/secrets generated just from the master password (without the -s
 option) are not impacted. The confidentiality of the seed itself is 
also not impacted (it is not required to regenerate the seed itself). 
Specific impact includes:



  *  keys/secrets generated from a seed file may have lower entropy: it 
was expected that the whole seed would be used to generate keys (240 
bytes of entropy input), where in vulnerable versions only 28 bytes was 
used

  *  a malicious entity could have recovered all passwords, generated 
from a particular seed, having only the seed file in possession without 
the knowledge of the seed master password




Patches
The code logic bug has been fixed in gokey version 0.2.0
 and above. Due to the deterministic nature of gokey, fixed versions 
will produce different passwords/secrets using seed files, as all seed 
entropy will be used now.


System secret rotation guidance
It is advised for users to regenerate passwords/secrets using the patched version of gokey (0.2.0
 and above), and provision/rotate these secrets into respective systems 
in place of the old secret. A specific rotation procedure is 
system-dependent, but most common patterns are described below.


Systems that do not require the old password/secret for rotation
Such systems usually have a "Forgot password" facility or a
 similar facility allowing users to rotate their password/secrets by 
sending a unique "magic" link to the user's email or phone. In such 
cases users are advised to use this facility and input the newly 
generated password secret, when prompted by the system.


Systems that require the old password/secret for rotation
Such systems usually have a modal password rotation window
 usually in the user settings section requiring the user to input the 
old and the new password sometimes with a confirmation. To 
generate/recover the old password in such cases users are advised to:



  *  temporarily download  gokey version 0.1.3 https://github.com/cloudflare/gokey/releases/tag/v0.1.3  for their respective operating system to recover the old password

  *  use gokey version 0.2.0 or above to generate the new password

  *  populate the system provided password rotation form




Systems that allow multiple credentials for the same account to be provisioned
Such systems usually require a secret or a cryptographic 
key as a credential for access, but allow several credentials at the 
same time. One example is SSH: a particular user may have several 
authorized public keys configured on the SSH server for access. For such
 systems users are advised to:



  *  generate a new secret/key/credential using gokey version 0.2.0 or above

  *  provision the new secret/key/credential in addition to the existing credential on the system

  *  verify that the access or required system operation is still possible with the new secret/key/credential

  *  revoke authorization for the existing/old credential from the system




Credit
This vulnerability was found by Théo Cusnir ( @mister_mime https://hackerone.com/mister_mime ) and responsibly disclosed through Cloudflare's bug bounty program.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41742 | Sprecher Automation: SPRECON-E series has a critical vulnerability due to the use of static cryptographic keys in system components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41742</link><description>Sprecher Automations SPRECON-E-C,  SPRECON-E-P, SPRECON-E-T3 is vulnerable to attack by an unauthorized remote attacker via default cryptographic keys. The use of these keys allows the attacker to read, modify, and write projects and data, or to access any device via remote maintenance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 10:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41743 | Sprecher Automation: SPRECON-E series prone to weak encryption of update files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41743</link><description>Insufficient encryption strength in Sprecher Automation SPRECON-E-C, SPRECON-E-P, and SPRECON-E-T3 allows a local unprivileged attacker to extract data from update images and thus obtain limited information about the architecture and internal processes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 10:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41744 | Sprecher Automation: SPRECON-E series has static default key material for TLS connections</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41744</link><description>Sprecher Automations SPRECON-E series uses default cryptographic keys that allow an unprivileged remote attacker to access all encrypted communications, thereby compromising confidentiality and integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 10:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13872 | Blind Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the survey-import feature of ObjectPlanet Opinio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13872</link><description>Blind Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the survey-import feature of 

 ObjectPlanet Opinio 7.26 rev12562 on 

Web-based platforms allows an attacker to force the server to perform HTTP GET requests via crafted import requests 

 to an arbitrary destination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 10:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13873 | The feature to import a survey is prone to stored Cross-Site Script attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13873</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the survey-import feature of ObjectPlanet Opinio 7.26 rev12562 on web application allows an attacker to inject arbitrary JavaScript code, which executes in the browsing context of any visitor accessing the compromised survey.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 10:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13871 | The feature to manage resources is prone to Cross-Site Request Forgery attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13871</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the resource-management feature of 

ObjectPlanet Opinio 7.26 rev12562

 allows to upload 
files on behalf of the connected users and then access such files without authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 09:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13870 | Unauthorized access and subscription vulnerability in Boards</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13870</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.4, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.12 fail to validate the user permission when accessing the files and subscribing to the block in Boards, which allows an authenticated user to access other board files and was able to subscribe to the block from other boards that the user does not have access to</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 09:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10543 | In Eclipse Paho Go MQTT v3.1 library (paho.mqtt.golang) versions &lt;=1.5.0 UTF-8 encoded strings, passed into the library, may be incorrectly ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10543</link><description>In Eclipse Paho Go MQTT v3.1 library (paho.mqtt.golang) versions &lt;=1.5.0 UTF-8 encoded strings, passed into the library, may be incorrectly encoded if their length exceeds 65535 bytes. This may lead to unexpected content in packets sent to the server (for example, part of an MQTT topic may leak into the message body in a PUBLISH packet).


The issue arises because the length of the data passed in was converted from an int64/int32 (depending upon CPU) to an int16 without checks for overflows. The int16 length was then written, followed by the data (e.g. topic). This meant that when the data (e.g. topic) was over 65535 bytes then the amount of data written exceeds what the length field indicates. This could lead to a corrupt packet, or mean that the excess data leaks into another field (e.g. topic leaks into message body).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13516 | SureMail – SMTP and Email Logs Plugin with Amazon SES, Postmark, and Other Providers &amp;lt;= 1.9.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13516</link><description>The SureMail – SMTP and Email Logs Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type in versions up to and including 1.9.0. This is due to the plugin's save_file() function in inc/emails/handler/uploads.php which duplicates all email attachments to a web-accessible directory (wp-content/uploads/suremails/attachments/) without validating file extensions or content types. Files are saved with predictable names derived from MD5 hashes of their content. While the plugin attempts to protect this directory with an Apache .htaccess file to disable PHP execution, this protection is ineffective on nginx, IIS, and Lighttpd servers, or on misconfigured Apache installations. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to achieve Remote Code Execution by uploading malicious PHP files through any public form that emails attachments, calculating the predictable filename, and directly accessing the file to execute arbitrary code granted they are exploiting a site running on an affected web server configuration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13534 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.3.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Privilege Escalation via eh_crm_edit_agent AJAX Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13534</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.2. This is due to missing authorization checks on the eh_crm_edit_agent AJAX action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to escalate their WSDesk privileges from limited "Reply Tickets" permissions to full helpdesk administrator capabilities, gaining unauthorized access to ticket management, settings configuration, agent administration, and sensitive customer data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13724 | VikRentCar Car Rental Management System &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Authenticated (Author+) SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;month&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13724</link><description>The VikRentCar Car Rental Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based blind SQL Injection via the 'month' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10971 | Insecure Storage of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10971</link><description>Insecure Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability in MeetMe on iOS, Android allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects MeetMe: through v2.2.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11726 | Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.9.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Global Preset Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11726</link><description>The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.4. This is due to insufficient capability checks in the REST API endpoints under the 'fl-controls/v1' namespace that control site-wide Global Presets. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level access and above to add, modify, or delete global color and background presets that affect all Beaver Builder content site-wide.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 07:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13696 | Zigaform &amp;lt;= 7.6.5 - Unauthenticated Form Submission Data Disclosure in rocket_front_payment_seesummary AJAX Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13696</link><description>The Zigaform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 7.6.5. This is due to the plugin exposing a public AJAX endpoint that retrieves form submission data without performing authorization checks to verify ownership or access rights. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive form submission data including personal information, payment details, and other private data via the rocket_front_payment_seesummary action by enumerating sequential form_r_id values.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 07:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12483 | Visualizer: Tables and Charts Manager for WordPress &amp;lt;= 3.11.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12483</link><description>The Visualizer: Tables and Charts Manager for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'query' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.11.12 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. Version 3.11.13 raises the minimum user-level for exploitation to administrator. 3.11.14 fully patches the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 07:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13007 | WP Social Ninja – Embed Social Feeds, Customer Reviews, Chat Widgets (Google Reviews, YouTube Feed, Photo Feeds, and More) &amp;lt;= 3.20.3 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via External Content Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13007</link><description>The WP Social Ninja – Embed Social Feeds, Customer Reviews, Chat Widgets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 3.20.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on externally-sourced content. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page, granted they can post malicious content to a connected Google Business Profile or Facebook page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 07:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13140 | SurveyJS: Drag &amp;amp; Drop WordPress Form Builder &amp;lt;= 1.12.20 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Survey Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13140</link><description>The SurveyJS: Drag &amp; Drop WordPress Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.20. This is due to missing nonce validation on the SurveyJS_DeleteSurvey AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete surveys via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 07:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13685 | Photo Gallery by Ays &amp;lt;= 6.4.8 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Bulk Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13685</link><description>The Photo Gallery by Ays plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.8. This is due to missing nonce verification on the bulk action functionality in the 'process_bulk_action()' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to perform bulk operations (delete, publish, or unpublish galleries) via a forged request granted they can trick an administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 07:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13000 | DB Access &amp;lt;= 0.8.7 - Subscriber+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13000</link><description>The db-access WordPress plugin through 0.8.7 does not have authorization in an AJAX action, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber to perform SQLI attacks</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 06:44:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13001 | Donation &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Admin+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13001</link><description>The donation WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing high privilege users, such as admin to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 06:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13387 | Kadence WooCommerce Email Designer &amp;lt;= 1.5.17 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13387</link><description>The Kadence WooCommerce Email Designer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the customer name in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.17 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 04:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13606 | Export All Posts, Products, Orders, Refunds &amp;amp; Users &amp;lt;= 2.19 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13606</link><description>The Export All Posts, Products, Orders, Refunds &amp; Users plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.19. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the `parseData` function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export sensitive information including user data, email addresses, password hashes, and WooCommerce data to an attacker-controlled file path on the server via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 04:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20750 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20750</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01661199; Issue ID: MSV-4296.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20751 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20751</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01661195; Issue ID: MSV-4297.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20752 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20752</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01270690; Issue ID: MSV-4301.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20753 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20753</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01689252; Issue ID: MSV-4841.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20754 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20754</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01689251; Issue ID: MSV-4840.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20755 | In Modem, there is a possible application crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20755</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible application crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY00628396; Issue ID: MSV-4775.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20756 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to a logic error. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rog...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20756</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to a logic error. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01673749; Issue ID: MSV-4643.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20757 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20757</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01673751; Issue ID: MSV-4644.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20758 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20758</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01673755; Issue ID: MSV-4647.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20759 | In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20759</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01673760; Issue ID: MSV-4650.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20763 | In mmdvfs, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20763</link><description>In mmdvfs, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10267218; Issue ID: MSV-5032.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20764 | In smi, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20764</link><description>In smi, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10259774; Issue ID: MSV-5029.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20765 | In aee daemon, there is a possible system crash due to a race condition. This could lead to local denial of service if a malicious actor has...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20765</link><description>In aee daemon, there is a possible system crash due to a race condition. This could lead to local denial of service if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10190802; Issue ID: MSV-4833.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20766 | In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20766</link><description>In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10196993; Issue ID: MSV-4820.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20767 | In display, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malici...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20767</link><description>In display, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10196993; Issue ID: MSV-4807.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20768 | In display, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20768</link><description>In display, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10196993; Issue ID: MSV-4805.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20769 | In display, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20769</link><description>In display, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10196993; Issue ID: MSV-4804.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20770 | In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious act...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20770</link><description>In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10196993; Issue ID: MSV-4803.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20771 | In display, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20771</link><description>In display, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10196993; Issue ID: MSV-4802.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20772 | In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious act...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20772</link><description>In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10196993; Issue ID: MSV-4801.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20773 | In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious act...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20773</link><description>In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10196993; Issue ID: MSV-4797.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20774 | In display, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20774</link><description>In display, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10196993; Issue ID: MSV-4796.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20775 | In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious act...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20775</link><description>In display, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10182914; Issue ID: MSV-4795.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20776 | In display, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20776</link><description>In display, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10184297; Issue ID: MSV-4759.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20777 | In display, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20777</link><description>In display, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10184870; Issue ID: MSV-4752.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20788 | In GPU pdma, there is a possible memory corruption due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local denial of service with no add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20788</link><description>In GPU pdma, there is a possible memory corruption due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10117735; Issue ID: MSV-4539.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20789 | In GPU pdma, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20789</link><description>In GPU pdma, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10117741; Issue ID: MSV-4538.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20790 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20790</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01677581; Issue ID: MSV-4701.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20791 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20791</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01661189; Issue ID: MSV-4298.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20792 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20792</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01717526; Issue ID: MSV-5591.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 03:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45675 | IBM Informix Dynamic Server Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45675</link><description>IBM Informix Dynamic Server 14.10 could allow a local user on the system to log into the Informix server as administrator without a password.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12529 | Cost Calculator Builder &amp;lt;= 3.6.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12529</link><description>The Cost Calculator Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the deleteOrdersFiles() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary file paths into the orders that are removed, when an administrator deletes them. This can lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php). This vulnerability requires the Cost Calculator Builder Pro version to be installed along with the free version in order to be exploitable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13697 | BlockArt Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder Blocks ,WordPress Block Plugin, Sections &amp;amp; Template Library &amp;lt;= 2.2.13 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via `timestamp` Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13697</link><description>The BlockArt Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder Blocks ,WordPress Block Plugin, Sections &amp; Template Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘timestamp’ attribute in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21072 | Out-of-bounds write in decoding metadata in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR Dec-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to write ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21072</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in decoding metadata in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR Dec-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21080 | Improper export of android application components in Dynamic Lockscreen prior to SMR Dec-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21080</link><description>Improper export of android application components in Dynamic Lockscreen prior to SMR Dec-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access files with Dynamic Lockscreen's privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55129 | HackerOne community member Kassem S.(kassem_s94) has reported that username handling in Revive Adserver was still vulnerable to impersonatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55129</link><description>HackerOne community member Kassem S.(kassem_s94) has reported that username handling in Revive Adserver was still vulnerable to impersonation attacks after the fix for CVE-2025-52672, via several alternate techniques. Homoglyphs based impersonation has been independently reported by other HackerOne users, such as  itz_hari_ and khoof.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58475 | Improper input validation in libsec-ril.so prior to SMR Dec-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58475</link><description>Improper input validation in libsec-ril.so prior to SMR Dec-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58476 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in bootloader prior to SMR Dec-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58476</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in bootloader prior to SMR Dec-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58477 | Out-of-bounds write in parsing IFD tag in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Dec-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58477</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in parsing IFD tag in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Dec-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58478 | Out-of-bounds write in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Dec-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58478</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Dec-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58479 | Out-of-bounds read in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Dec-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58479</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Dec-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58480 | Heap-based buffer overflow in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Dec-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58480</link><description>Heap-based buffer overflow in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Dec-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58481 | Improper access control in MPRemoteService of MotionPhoto prior to version 4.1.51 allows local attackers to start privileged service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58481</link><description>Improper access control in MPRemoteService of MotionPhoto prior to version 4.1.51 allows local attackers to start privileged service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58482 | Improper access control in MPLocalService of MotionPhoto prior to version 4.1.51 allows local attackers to start privileged service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58482</link><description>Improper access control in MPLocalService of MotionPhoto prior to version 4.1.51 allows local attackers to start privileged service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58483 | Improper export of android application components in Galaxy Store for Galaxy Watch prior to version 1.0.06.29 allows local attacker to insta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58483</link><description>Improper export of android application components in Galaxy Store for Galaxy Watch prior to version 1.0.06.29 allows local attacker to install arbitrary application on Galaxy Store.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58484 | Incorrect default permissions in Samsung Cloud Assistant prior to version 8.0.03.8 allows local attacker to access partial data in sandbox.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58484</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in Samsung Cloud Assistant prior to version 8.0.03.8 allows local attacker to access partial data in sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58485 | Improper input validation in Samsung Internet prior to version 29.0.0.48 allows local attackers to inject arbitrary script.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58485</link><description>Improper input validation in Samsung Internet prior to version 29.0.0.48 allows local attackers to inject arbitrary script.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58486 | Improper input validation in Samsung Account prior to version 15.5.01.1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary script.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58486</link><description>Improper input validation in Samsung Account prior to version 15.5.01.1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary script.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58487 | Improper authorization in Samsung Account prior to version 15.5.01.1 allows local attacker to launch arbitrary activity with Samsung Account...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58487</link><description>Improper authorization in Samsung Account prior to version 15.5.01.1 allows local attacker to launch arbitrary activity with Samsung Account privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58488 | Improper verification of source of a communication channel in SmartTouchCall prior to version 1.0.1.1 allows remote attackers to access sens...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58488</link><description>Improper verification of source of a communication channel in SmartTouchCall prior to version 1.0.1.1 allows remote attackers to access sensitive information. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66401 | MCP Watch has a Critical Command Injection in cloneRepo allows Remote Code Execution (RCE) via malicious URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66401</link><description>MCP Watch is a comprehensive security scanner for Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers. In 0.1.2 and earlier, the MCPScanner class contains a critical Command Injection vulnerability in the cloneRepo method. The application passes the user-supplied githubUrl argument directly to a system shell via execSync without sanitization. This allows an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the host machine by appending shell metacharacters to the URL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66448 | vLLM vulnerable to remote code execution via transformers_utils/get_config</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66448</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). Prior to 0.11.1, vllm has a critical remote code execution vector in a config class named Nemotron_Nano_VL_Config. When vllm loads a model config that contains an auto_map entry, the config class resolves that mapping with get_class_from_dynamic_module(...) and immediately instantiates the returned class. This fetches and executes Python from the remote repository referenced in the auto_map string. Crucially, this happens even when the caller explicitly sets trust_remote_code=False in vllm.transformers_utils.config.get_config. In practice, an attacker can publish a benign-looking frontend repo whose config.json points via auto_map to a separate malicious backend repo; loading the frontend will silently run the backend’s code on the victim host. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.11.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66412 | Angular Stored XSS Vulnerability via SVG Animation, SVG URL and MathML Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66412</link><description>Angular is a development platform for building mobile and desktop web applications using TypeScript/JavaScript and other languages. Prior to 21.0.2, 20.3.15, and 19.2.17, A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in the Angular Template Compiler. It occurs because the compiler's internal security schema is incomplete, allowing attackers to bypass Angular's built-in security sanitization. Specifically, the schema fails to classify certain URL-holding attributes (e.g., those that could contain javascript: URLs) as requiring strict URL security, enabling the injection of malicious scripts. This vulnerability is fixed in 21.0.2, 20.3.15, and 19.2.17.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66415 | fastify-reply-from bypass of reply forwarding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66415</link><description>fastify-reply-from is a Fastify plugin to forward the current HTTP request to another server. Prior to 12.5.0, by crafting a malicious URL, an attacker could access routes that are not allowed, even though the reply.from is defined for specific routes in @fastify/reply-from. This vulnerability is fixed in 12.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66405 | Portkey.ai Gateway: Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in Custom Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66405</link><description>Portkey.ai Gateway is a blazing fast AI Gateway with integrated guardrails. Prior to 1.14.0, the gateway determined the destination baseURL by prioritizing the value in the x-portkey-custom-host request header. The proxy route then appends the client-specified path to perform an external fetch. This can be maliciously used by users for SSRF attacks. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.14.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:36:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66410 | Gin-vue-admin has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66410</link><description>Gin-vue-admin is a backstage management system based on vue and gin. In 2.8.6 and earlier, attackers can delete any file on the server at will, causing damage or unavailability of server resources. Attackers can control the 'FileMd5' parameter to delete any file and folder.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:36:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66313 | ChurchCRM vulnerable to a time-based blind SQL injection via the 1FieldSec parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66313</link><description>ChurchCRM is an open-source church management system. In ChurchCRM 6.2.0 and earlier, there is a time-based blind SQL injection in the handling of the 1FieldSec parameter. Injecting SLEEP() causes deterministic server-side delays, proving the value is incorporated into a SQL query without proper parameterization. The issue allows data exfiltration and modification via blind techniques.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66400 | mdast-util-to-hast unsanitized class attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66400</link><description>mdast-util-to-hast is an mdast utility to transform to hast. From 13.0.0 to before 13.2.1, multiple (unprefixed) classnames could be added in markdown source by using character references. This could make rendered user supplied markdown code elements appear like the rest of the page. This vulnerability is fixed in 13.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66403 | FileRise Vulnerable to Stored XSS via SVG Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66403</link><description>FileRise is a self-hosted web-based file manager with multi-file upload, editing, and batch operations. Prior to 2.2.3, a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Filerise application due to improper handling of uploaded SVG files. The application accepts user-supplied SVG uploads without sanitizing or restricting embedded script content. When a malicious SVG containing inline JavaScript or event-based payloads is uploaded, it is later rendered directly in the browser whenever viewed within the application. Because SVGs are XML-based and allow scripting, they execute in the origin context of the application, enabling full stored XSS. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66309 | Grav vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Reflected endpoint /admin/pages/[page], parameter data[header][content][items], located in the &amp;quot;Blog Config&amp;quot; tab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66309</link><description>This admin plugin for Grav is an HTML user interface that provides a convenient way to configure Grav and easily create and modify pages. Prior to 1.11.0-beta.1, a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the /admin/pages/[page] endpoint of the Grav application. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into the data[header][content][items] parameter. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.11.0-beta.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66310 | Grav vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Stored endpoint `/admin/pages/[page]` parameter `data[header][template]` in Advanced Tab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66310</link><description>This admin plugin for Grav is an HTML user interface that provides a convenient way to configure Grav and easily create and modify pages. Prior to 1.11.0-beta.1, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the /admin/pages/[page] endpoint of the Grav application. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into the data[header][template] parameter. The script is saved within the page's frontmatter and executed automatically whenever the affected content is rendered in the administrative interface or frontend view. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.11.0-beta.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66311 | Grav vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Stored endpoint `/admin/pages/[page]` in Multiples parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66311</link><description>This admin plugin for Grav is an HTML user interface that provides a convenient way to configure Grav and easily create and modify pages. Prior to 1.11.0-beta.1, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the /admin/pages/[page] endpoint of the Grav application. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into the data[header][metadata], data[header][taxonomy][category], and data[header][taxonomy][tag] parameters. These scripts are stored in the page frontmatter and executed automatically whenever the affected page is accessed or rendered in the administrative interface. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.11.0-beta.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66312 | Grav Admin Plugin vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Stored endpoint `/admin/accounts/groups/[group]` parameter `data[readableName]`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66312</link><description>This admin plugin for Grav is an HTML user interface that provides a convenient way to configure Grav and easily create and modify pages. Prior to 1.11.0-beta.1, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the /admin/accounts/groups/Grupo endpoint of the Grav application. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into the data[readableName] parameter. The injected scripts are stored on the server and executed automatically whenever the affected page is accessed by users, posing a significant security risk. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.11.0-beta.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66308 | Grav Admin Plugin vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Stored endpoint `/admin/config/site` parameter `data[taxonomies]`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66308</link><description>This admin plugin for Grav is an HTML user interface that provides a convenient way to configure Grav and easily create and modify pages. Prior to 1.11.0-beta.1, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the /admin/config/site endpoint of the Grav application. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into the data[taxonomies] parameter. The injected payload is stored on the server and automatically executed in the browser of any user who accesses the affected site configuration, resulting in a persistent attack vector. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.11.0-beta.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66307 | Grav Admin Plugin vulnerable to User Enumeration &amp;amp; Email Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66307</link><description>This admin plugin for Grav is an HTML user interface that provides a convenient way to configure Grav and easily create and modify pages. Prior to 1.11.0-beta.1, a user enumeration and email disclosure vulnerability exists in Grav. The "Forgot Password" functionality at /admin/forgot leaks information about valid usernames and their associated email addresses through distinct server responses. This allows an attacker to enumerate users and disclose sensitive email addresses, which can be leveraged for targeted attacks such as password spraying, phishing, or social engineering. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.11.0-beta.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66306 | Grav vulnerable to Information Disclosure via IDOR in Grav Admin Panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66306</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, there is an IDOR (Insecure Direct Object Reference) vulnerability in the Grav CMS Admin Panel which allows low-privilege users to access sensitive information from other accounts. Although direct account takeover is not possible, admin email addresses and other metadata can be exposed, increasing the risk of phishing, credential stuffing, and social engineering. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:56:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66304 | Grav Exposes Password Hashes Leading to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66304</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, users with read access on the user account management section of the admin panel can view the password hashes of all users, including the admin user. This exposure can potentially lead to privilege escalation if an attacker can crack these password hashes. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66305 | Grav vulnerable to Denial of Service via Improper Input Handling in &amp;#x27;Supported&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66305</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability was identified in the "Languages" submenu of the Grav admin configuration panel (/admin/config/system). Specifically, the Supported parameter fails to properly validate user input. If a malformed value is inserted—such as a single forward slash (/) or an XSS test string—it causes a fatal regular expression parsing error on the server. This leads to application-wide failure due to the use of the preg_match() function with an improperly constructed regular expression, resulting in an error. Once triggered, the site becomes completely unavailable to all users. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66302 | Grav vulnerable to Path Traversal allowing server files backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66302</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, A path traversal vulnerability has been identified in Grav CMS, allowing authenticated attackers with administrative privileges to read arbitrary files on the underlying server filesystem. This vulnerability arises due to insufficient input sanitization in the backup tool, where user-supplied paths are not properly restricted, enabling access to files outside the intended webroot directory. The impact of this vulnerability depends on the privileges of the user account running the application. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66303 | Grav is vulnerable to a DOS on the admin panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66303</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, A Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability has been identified in Grav related to the handling of scheduled_at parameters. Specifically, the application fails to properly sanitize input for cron expressions. By manipulating the scheduled_at parameter with a malicious input, such as a single quote, the application admin panel becomes non-functional, causing significant disruptions to administrative operations. The only way to recover from this issue is to manually access the host server and modify the backup.yaml file to correct the corrupted cron expression. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66301 | Grav ihas Broken Access Control which allows an Editor to modify the page&amp;#x27;s YAML Frontmatter to alter form processing actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66301</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, due to improper authorization checks when modifying critical fields on a POST request to /admin/pages/{page_name}, an editor with only permissions to change basic content on the form is now able to change the functioning of the form through modifying the content of the data[_json][header][form] which is the YAML frontmatter which includes the process section which dictates what happens after a user submits the form which include some important actions that could lead to further vulnerabilities. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:38:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66299 | Security Sandbox Bypass with SSTI (Server Side Template Injection) in the Grav CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66299</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, Grav CMS is vulnerable to a Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) that allows any authenticated user with editor permissions to execute arbitrary code on the remote server, bypassing the existing security sandbox. Since the security sandbox does not fully protect the Twig object, it is possible to interact with it (e.g., call methods, read/write attributes) through maliciously crafted Twig template directives injected into a web page. This allows an authenticated editor to add arbitrary functions to the Twig attribute system.twig.safe_filters, effectively bypassing the Grav CMS sandbox. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66300 | Grav is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66300</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, A low privilege user account with page editing privilege can read any server files using "Frontmatter" form. This includes Grav user account files (/grav/user/accounts/*.yaml), which store hashed user password, 2FA secret, and the password reset token. This can allow an adversary to compromise any registered account by resetting a password for a user to get access to the password reset token from the file or by cracking the hashed password. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65622 | Snipe-IT before 8.3.4 allows stored XSS via the Locations "Country" field, enabling a low-privileged authenticated user to inject JavaScript...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65622</link><description>Snipe-IT before 8.3.4 allows stored XSS via the Locations "Country" field, enabling a low-privileged authenticated user to inject JavaScript that executes in another user's session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66298 | Grav is vulnerable to Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) via Forms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66298</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, having a simple form on site can reveal the whole Grav configuration details (including plugin configuration details) by using the correct POST payload to exploit a Server-Side Template (SST) vulnerability. Sensitive information may be contained in the configuration details. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66296 | Grav vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in Grav Admin: Missing Username Uniqueness Check Allows Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66296</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, a privilege escalation vulnerability exists in Grav’s Admin plugin due to the absence of username uniqueness validation when creating users. A user with the create user permission can create a new account using the same username as an existing administrator account, set a new password/email, and then log in as that administrator. This effectively allows privilege escalation from limited user-manager permissions to full administrator access. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66297 | Grav vulnerable to Privilege Escalation and Authenticated Remote Code Execution via Twig Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66297</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, a user with admin panel access and permissions to create or edit pages in Grav CMS can enable Twig processing in the page frontmatter. By injecting malicious Twig expressions, the user can escalate their privileges to admin or execute arbitrary system commands via the scheduler API. This results in both Privilege Escalation (PE) and Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerabilities. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65621 | Snipe-IT before 8.3.4 allows stored XSS, allowing a low-privileged authenticated user to inject JavaScript that executes in an administrator...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65621</link><description>Snipe-IT before 8.3.4 allows stored XSS, allowing a low-privileged authenticated user to inject JavaScript that executes in an administrator's session, enabling privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66294 | Grav is vulnerable to RCE via SSTI through Twig Sandbox Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66294</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, a Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability exists in Grav that allows authenticated attackers with editor permissions to execute arbitrary commands on the server and, under certain conditions, may also be exploited by unauthenticated attackers. This vulnerability stems from weak regex validation in the cleanDangerousTwig method. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66295 | Grav vulnerable to Path traversal / arbitrary YAML write via user creation leading to Account Takeover / System Corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66295</link><description>Grav is a file-based Web platform. Prior to 1.8.0-beta.27, when a user with privilege of user creation creates a new user through the Admin UI and supplies a username containing path traversal sequences (for example ..\Nijat or ../Nijat), Grav writes the account YAML file to an unintended path outside user/accounts/. The written YAML can contain account fields such as email, fullname, twofa_secret, and hashed_password. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.0-beta.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65840 | PublicCMS V5.202506.b is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the CkEditorAdminController.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65840</link><description>PublicCMS V5.202506.b is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the CkEditorAdminController.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66205 | Frappe has the possibility of SQL Injection due to improper validations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66205</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. Prior to 15.86.0 and 14.99.2, a certain endpoint was vulnerable to error-based SQL injection due to lack of validation of parameters. Some information like version could be retrieved. This vulnerability is fixed in 15.86.0 and 14.99.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66206 | Frappe vulnerable to a path traversal allowing reading certain files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66206</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. Prior to 15.86.0 and 14.99.2, certain requests were vulnerable to path traversal attacks, wherein some files from the server could be retrieved if the full path was known. Sites hosted on Frappe Cloud, and even other setups that are behind a reverse proxy like NGINX are unaffected. This would mainly affect someone directly using werkzeug/gunicorn. In those cases, either an upgrade or changing the setup to use a reverse proxy is recommended. This vulnerability is fixed in 15.86.0 and 14.99.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51999 | express improperly controls modification of query properties</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51999</link><description>Express.js minimalist web framework for node. Prior to 5.2.0 and 4.22.0, when using the extended query parser in express ('query parser': 'extended'), the request.query object inherits all object prototype properties, but these properties can be overwritten by query string parameter keys that match the property names. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.2.0 and 4.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55749 | The XWiki Jetty package (XJetty) allows accessing any application file through URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55749</link><description>XWiki is an open-source wiki software platform. From 16.7.0 to 16.10.11, 17.4.4, or 17.7.0, in an instance which is using the XWiki Jetty package (XJetty), a context is exposed to statically access any file located in the webapp/ folder. It allows accessing files which might contains credentials. Fixed in 16.10.11, 17.4.4, and 17.7.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58044 | JumpServer has an Open Redirect Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58044</link><description>JumpServer is an open source bastion host and an operation and maintenance security audit system. Prior to v3.10.19 and v4.10.5, The /core/i18n// endpoint uses the Referer header as the redirection target without proper validation, which could lead to an Open Redirect vulnerability. This vulnerability is fixed in v3.10.19 and v4.10.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65838 | PublicCMS V5.202506.b is vulnerable to path traversal via the doUploadSitefile method.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65838</link><description>PublicCMS V5.202506.b is vulnerable to path traversal via the doUploadSitefile method.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12756 | Insecure Direct Object Reference in Mattermost Boards Plugin Enables Unauthorised Comment Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12756</link><description>Mattermost versions 11.0.x &lt;= 11.0.2, 10.12.x &lt;= 10.12.1, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.4, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.12 fail to validate user permissions when deleting comments in Boards, which allows an authenticated user with the editor role to delete comments created by other users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:56:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63317 | Todoist v8896 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /api/v1/uploads. Uploaded SVG files have no sanitization applied, so embedded J...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63317</link><description>Todoist v8896 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /api/v1/uploads. Uploaded SVG files have no sanitization applied, so embedded JavaScript executes when a user opens the attachment from a task/comment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65836 | PublicCMS V5.202506.b is vulnerable to SSRF. in the chat interface of SimpleAiAdminController.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65836</link><description>PublicCMS V5.202506.b is vulnerable to SSRF. in the chat interface of SimpleAiAdminController.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51682 | mJobtime 15.7.2 handles authorization on the client side, which allows an attacker to modify the client-side code and gain access to adminis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51682</link><description>mJobtime 15.7.2 handles authorization on the client side, which allows an attacker to modify the client-side code and gain access to administrative features. Additionally, they can craft requests based on the client-side code to call these administrative functions directly.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51683 | A blind SQL Injection (SQLi) vulnerability in mJobtime v15.7.2 allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL statements via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51683</link><description>A blind SQL Injection (SQLi) vulnerability in mJobtime v15.7.2 allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL statements via a crafted POST request to the /Default.aspx/update_profile_Server endpoint .</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11772 | Co-Installer Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11772</link><description>A carefully crafted DLL, copied to 

C:\ProgramData\Synaptics

 folder, allows a local user to execute 
arbitrary code with elevated privileges during driver installation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:20:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34297 | KissFFT Integer Overflow Heap Buffer Overflow via kiss_fft_alloc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34297</link><description>KissFFT versions prior to the fix commit 1b083165 contain an integer overflow in kiss_fft_alloc() in kiss_fft.c on platforms where size_t is 32-bit. The nfft parameter is not validated before being used in a size calculation (sizeof(kiss_fft_cpx) * (nfft - 1)), which can wrap to a small value when nfft is large. As a result, malloc() allocates an undersized buffer and the subsequent twiddle-factor initialization loop writes nfft elements, causing a heap buffer overflow. This vulnerability only affects 32-bit architectures.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63365 | SoftSea EPUB File Reader 1.0.0.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The vulnerability resides in the EPUB file processing component, spec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63365</link><description>SoftSea EPUB File Reader 1.0.0.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The vulnerability resides in the EPUB file processing component, specifically in the functionality responsible for extracting and handling EPUB archive contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65407 | A use-after-free in the MPEG1or2Demux::newElementaryStream() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause a Den...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65407</link><description>A use-after-free in the MPEG1or2Demux::newElementaryStream() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted MPEG Program stream.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13653 | Unauthorized access to documents in data streams with specially crafted requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13653</link><description>In Search Guard FLX versions from 3.1.0 up to 4.0.0 with enterprise modules being disabled, there exists an issue which allows authenticated users to use specially crafted requests to read documents from data streams without having the respective privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:26:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13836 | Excessive read buffering DoS in http.client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13836</link><description>When reading an HTTP response from a server, if no read amount is specified, the default behavior will be to use Content-Length. This allows a malicious server to cause the client to read large amounts of data into memory, potentially causing OOM or other DoS.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13837 | Out-of-memory when loading Plist</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13837</link><description>When loading a plist file, the plistlib module reads data in size specified by the file itself, meaning a malicious file can cause OOM and DoS issues</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13835 | WordPress Arconix Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.19 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13835</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tyche Softwares Arconix Shortcodes allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Arconix Shortcodes: from n/a through 2.1.19.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65408 | A NULL pointer dereference in the ADTSAudioFileServerMediaSubsession::createNewRTPSink() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65408</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference in the ADTSAudioFileServerMediaSubsession::createNewRTPSink() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted ADTS file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7007 | Null pointer dereference in Avast Antivirus on  macOS (16.0.0) or Linux (3.0.3)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7007</link><description>NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in Avast Antivirus on MacOS, Avast Anitvirus on Linux when scanning a malformed Windows PE file causes the antivirus process to crash.This issue affects Antivirus: 16.0.0; Anitvirus: 3.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65406 | A heap overflow in the MatroskaFile::createRTPSinkForTrackNumber() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65406</link><description>A heap overflow in the MatroskaFile::createRTPSinkForTrackNumber() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted MKV file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3500 | Integer Overflow in Avast Antiviurs 25.1.981.6 on Windows may result in privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3500</link><description>Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Avast Antivirus (25.1.981.6) on Windows allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Antivirus: from 25.1.981.6 before 25.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64775 | Apache Struts: File leak in multipart request processing causes disk exhaustion (DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64775</link><description>Denial of Service vulnerability in Apache Struts, file leak in multipart request processing causes disk exhaustion.

This issue affects Apache Struts: from 2.0.0 through 6.7.0, from 7.0.0 through 7.0.3.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 6.8.0 or 7.1.1, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65403 | A buffer overflow in the g_cfg.MaxUsers component of LightFTP v2.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65403</link><description>A buffer overflow in the g_cfg.MaxUsers component of LightFTP v2.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65404 | A buffer overflow in the getSideInfo2() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65404</link><description>A buffer overflow in the getSideInfo2() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted MP3 stream.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65405 | A use-after-free in the ADTSAudioFileSource::samplingFrequency() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65405</link><description>A use-after-free in the ADTSAudioFileSource::samplingFrequency() function of Live555 Streaming Media v2018.09.02 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted ADTS/AAC file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13829 | Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Data Illusion Zumbrunn NGSurveyallows any logged-in user to obtain the private information of any o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13829</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Data Illusion Zumbrunn NGSurveyallows any logged-in user to obtain the private information of any other user.



 Critical information retrieved: 
  *  APIKEY (1 year user Session)
  *  RefreshToken (10 minutes user Session)
  *  Password hashed with bcrypt
  *  User IP
  *  Email
  *  Full Name</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61229 | An issue in Shirt Pocket's SuperDuper! 3.10 and earlier allow a local attacker to modify the default task template to execute an arbitrary p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61229</link><description>An issue in Shirt Pocket's SuperDuper! 3.10 and earlier allow a local attacker to modify the default task template to execute an arbitrary preflight script with root privileges and Full Disk Access, thus bypassing macOS privacy controls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8351 | Heap-based Buffer Overflow, Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in Avast Antivirus on MacOS when scanning a malformed file may allow Local Exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8351</link><description>Heap-based Buffer Overflow, Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in Avast Antivirus on MacOS when scanning a malformed file may allow Local Execution of Code or Denial-of-Service of the anitvirus engine process.This issue affects Antivirus: from 8.3.70.94 before 8.3.70.98.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32384 | Kerlink gateways running KerOS prior to version 5.10 expose their web interface exclusively over HTTP, without HTTPS support. This lack of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32384</link><description>Kerlink gateways running KerOS prior to version 5.10 expose their web interface exclusively over HTTP, without HTTPS support. This lack of transport layer security allows a man-in-the-middle attacker to intercept and modify traffic between the client and the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39148 | The service wmp-agent of KerOS prior 5.12 does not properly validate so-called ‘magic URLs’ allowing an unauthenticated remote attacker to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39148</link><description>The service wmp-agent of KerOS prior 5.12 does not properly validate so-called ‘magic URLs’ allowing an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands as root when the service is reachable over network. Typically, the service is protected via local firewall.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32388 | Due to a firewall misconfiguration, Kerlink devices running KerOS prior to 5.12 incorrectly accept specially crafted UDP packets. This allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32388</link><description>Due to a firewall misconfiguration, Kerlink devices running KerOS prior to 5.12 incorrectly accept specially crafted UDP packets. This allows an attacker to bypass the firewall and access UDP-based services that would otherwise be protected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45370 | An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in the User profile management functionality of Socomec Easy Config System 2.6.1.0. A speciall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45370</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in the User profile management functionality of Socomec Easy Config System 2.6.1.0. A specially crafted database record can lead to unauthorized access. An attacker can modify a local database to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48882 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted network p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48882</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to denial of service. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48894 | A cleartext transmission vulnerability exists in the WEBVIEW-M functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted HTTP ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48894</link><description>A cleartext transmission vulnerability exists in the WEBVIEW-M functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to a disclosure of sensitive information. An attacker can sniff network traffic to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49572 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted network p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49572</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to denial of service and weaken credentials resulting in default documented credentials being applied to the device. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53684 | A cross-site request forgery (csrf) vulnerability exists in the WEBVIEW-M functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53684</link><description>A cross-site request forgery (csrf) vulnerability exists in the WEBVIEW-M functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to unauthorized access. An attacker can stage a malicious webpage to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10101 | Heap-based Buffer Overflow, Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in Avast Antivirus on MacOS of a crafted Mach-O file may allow Local Execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10101</link><description>Heap-based Buffer Overflow, Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in Avast Antivirus on MacOS of a crafted Mach-O file may allow Local Execution of Code or Denial of Service of antivirus protection.
This issue affects Antivirus: from 15.7 before 3.9.2025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20085 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20085</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to denial of service and weaken credentials resulting in default documented credentials being applied to the device. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23417 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23417</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to denial of service. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26858 | A buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted set of netw...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26858</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted set of network packets can lead to denial of service. An attacker can send a sequence of unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54848 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54848</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted series of network requests can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can send a sequence of unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability.An attacker can trigger this denial-of-service condition by sending a sequence of Modbus TCP messages to port 502 using the Write Single Register function code (6). The attack sequence begins with a message to register 58112 with a value of 1000, indicating that a configuration change will follow. Next, a message is sent to register 29440 with a value corresponding to the new Modbus address to be configured. Finally, a message to register 57856 with a value of 161 commits the configuration change. After this configuration change, the device will be in a denial-of-service state.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54849 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54849</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted series of network requests can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can send a sequence of unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability.An attacker can trigger this denial-of-service condition by sending a single Modbus TCP message to port 502 using the Write Single Register function code (6) to write the value 1 to register 4352. This action changes the Modbus address to 15. After this message is sent, the device will be in a denial-of-service state.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54850 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54850</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted series of network requests can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can send a sequence of unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability.An attacker can trigger this denial-of-service condition by sending a sequence of Modbus RTU over TCP messages to port 503 using the Write Single Register function code (6). The attack sequence begins with a message to register 58112 with a value of 1000, indicating that a configuration change will follow. Next, a message is sent to register 29440 with a value corresponding to the new Modbus address to be configured. Finally, a message to register 57856 with a value of 161 commits the configuration change.
After this configuration change, the device will be in a denial-of-service state.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54851 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54851</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted series of network requests can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can send a sequence of unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability.An attacker can trigger this denial-of-service condition by sending a single Modbus TCP message to port 503 using the Write Single Register function code (6) to write the value 1 to register 4352. This action changes the Modbus address to 15. After this message is sent, the device will be in a denial-of-service state.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55221 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP USB Function functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55221</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP USB Function functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability is specific to the malicious message sent via Modbus TCP over port 502.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55222 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP USB Function functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55222</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Modbus TCP and Modbus RTU over TCP USB Function functionality of Socomec DIRIS Digiware M-70 1.6.9. A specially crafted network packet can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability is specific to the malicious message sent via Modbus RTU over TCP on port 503.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57489 | Incorrect access control in the SDAgent component of Shirt Pocket SuperDuper! v3.10 allows attackers to escalate privileges to root due to t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57489</link><description>Incorrect access control in the SDAgent component of Shirt Pocket SuperDuper! v3.10 allows attackers to escalate privileges to root due to the improper use of a setuid binary.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61228 | An issue in Shirt Pocket SuperDuper! V.3.10 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the software update mechanism</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61228</link><description>An issue in Shirt Pocket SuperDuper! V.3.10 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the software update mechanism</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11699 | CVE-2025-11699</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11699</link><description>nopCommerce v4.70 and prior, and version 4.80.3, does not invalidate session cookies after logout or session termination, allowing an attacker who has a 
a valid session cookie access to privileged endpoints (such as /admin) even after the legitimate user has logged out, enabling session hijacking. Any version above 4.70 that is not 4.80.3 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63095 | Improper input validation in the BitstreamWriter::write_bits() function of Tempus Ex hello-video-codec v0.1.0 allows attackers to cause a De...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63095</link><description>Improper input validation in the BitstreamWriter::write_bits() function of Tempus Ex hello-video-codec v0.1.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63532 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the cancel.php component. The application fails to prope...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63532</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the cancel.php component. The application fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input in SQL queries, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary SQL code. By manipulating the search field, an attacker can bypass authentication and gain unauthorized access to the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63533 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the updateprofile.php and rprofile.php comp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63533</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the updateprofile.php and rprofile.php components. The application fails to properly sanitize or encode user-supplied input before rendering it in response. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript payloads into the rname, remail, rpassword, rphone, rcity parameters, which are then executed in the victim's browser when the page is viewed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63534 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the login.php component. The application fa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63534</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the login.php component. The application fails to properly sanitize or encode user-supplied input before rendering it in response. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript payloads into the msg and error parameters, which are then executed in the victim's browser when the page is viewed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63535 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the abs.php component. The application fails to properly...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63535</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the abs.php component. The application fails to properly sanitize usersupplied input in SQL queries, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary SQL code. By manipulating the search field, an attacker can bypass authentication and gain unauthorized access to the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63525 | An issue was discovered in Blood Bank Management System 1.0 allowing authenticated attackers to perform actions with escalated privileges vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63525</link><description>An issue was discovered in Blood Bank Management System 1.0 allowing authenticated attackers to perform actions with escalated privileges via crafted request to delete.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63526 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System within the abs.php component. The application fails to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63526</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System within the abs.php component. The application fails to properly sanitize or encode user-supplied input before rendering it in response. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript payloads into the msg parameter, which is then executed in the victim's browser when the page is viewed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63527 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the updateprofile.php and hprofile.php comp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63527</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the updateprofile.php and hprofile.php components. The application fails to properly sanitize or encode user-supplied input before rendering it in response. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript payloads into the hname, hemail, hpassword, hphone, hcity parameters, which are then executed in the victim's browser when the page is viewed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63528 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the blooddinfo.php component. The applicati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63528</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the blooddinfo.php component. The application fails to properly sanitize or encode user-supplied input before rendering it in response. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript payloads into the error parameter, which is then executed in the victim's browser when the page is viewed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63529 | A session fixation vulnerability exists in Blood Bank Management System 1.0 in login.php that allows an attacker to set or predict a user's ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63529</link><description>A session fixation vulnerability exists in Blood Bank Management System 1.0 in login.php that allows an attacker to set or predict a user's session identifier prior to authentication. When the victim logs in, the application continues to use the attacker-supplied session ID rather than generating a new one, enabling the attacker to hijack the authenticated session and gain unauthorized access to the victim's account.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63531 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the receiverLogin.php component. The application fails t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63531</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the Blood Bank Management System 1.0 within the receiverLogin.php component. The application fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input in SQL queries, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary SQL code. By manipulating the remail and rpassword fields, an attacker can bypass authentication and gain unauthorized access to the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63520 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in FeehiCMS 2.1.1 via the id parameter of the User Update function (?r=user%2Fupdate).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63520</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in FeehiCMS 2.1.1 via the id parameter of the User Update function (?r=user%2Fupdate).</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63522 | Reverse Tabnabbing vulnerability in FeehiCMS 2.1.1 in the Comments Management function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63522</link><description>Reverse Tabnabbing vulnerability in FeehiCMS 2.1.1 in the Comments Management function</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63523 | FeehiCMS version 2.1.1 fails to enforce server-side immutability for parameters that are presented to clients as "read-only." An authenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63523</link><description>FeehiCMS version 2.1.1 fails to enforce server-side immutability for parameters that are presented to clients as "read-only." An authenticated attacker can intercept and modify the parameter in transit and the backend accepts the changes. This can lead to unintended username changes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64030 | Eximbills Enterprise 4.1.5 (Built on 2020-10-30) is vulnerable to authenticated stored cross-site scripting (CWE-79) via the /EximBillWeb/se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64030</link><description>Eximbills Enterprise 4.1.5 (Built on 2020-10-30) is vulnerable to authenticated stored cross-site scripting (CWE-79) via the /EximBillWeb/servlets/WSTrxManager endpoint. Unsanitized user input in the TMPL_INFO parameter is stored server-side and rendered to other users, enabling arbitrary JavaScript execution in their browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 14:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56089 | An issue in Technitium through v13.2.2 enables attackers to conduct a DNS cache poisoning attack and inject fake responses by reviving the b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56089</link><description>An issue in Technitium through v13.2.2 enables attackers to conduct a DNS cache poisoning attack and inject fake responses by reviving the birthday attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 14:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13129 | Business Logic Error in Seneka Software&amp;#x27;s Onaylarım</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13129</link><description>Improper Enforcement of Behavioral Workflow vulnerability in Seneka Software Hardware Information Technology Trade Contracting and Industry Ltd. Co. Onaylarım allows Functionality Misuse.This issue affects Onaylarım: from 25.09.26.01 through 18112025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 14:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49642 | Agent builds for AIX vulnerable to library loading hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49642</link><description>Library loading on AIX Zabbix Agent builds can be hijacked by local users with write access to the /home/cecuser directory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49643 | Frontend DoS vulnerability due to asymmetric resource consumption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49643</link><description>An authenticated Zabbix user (including Guest) is able to cause disproportionate CPU load on the webserver by sending specially crafted parameters to /imgstore.php, leading to potential denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12106 | Insufficient argument validation in OpenVPN 2.7_alpha1 through 2.7_rc1 allows an attacker to trigger a heap buffer over-read when parsing IP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12106</link><description>Insufficient argument validation in OpenVPN 2.7_alpha1 through 2.7_rc1 allows an attacker to trigger a heap buffer over-read when parsing IP addresses</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:10:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27232 | Frontend arbitrary file read in oauth.authorize action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27232</link><description>An authenticated Zabbix Super Admin can exploit the oauth.authorize action to read arbitrary files from the webserver leading to potential confidentiality loss.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:10:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13296 | CSRF in Tekrom Technology&amp;#x27;s T-Soft E-Commerce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13296</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Tekrom Technology Inc. T-Soft E-Commerce allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects T-Soft E-Commerce: through 28112025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 11:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58408 | GPU DDK - KASAN Read UAF in the PVRSRVBridgeRGXSubmitTransfer2 due to improper error handling code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58408</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to trigger reads of stale data that can lead to kernel exceptions and write use-after-free.

The Use After Free common weakness enumeration was chosen as the stale data can include handles to resources in which the reference counts can become unbalanced. This can lead to the premature destruction of a resource while in use.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 11:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41070 | Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in Sanoma&amp;#x27;s Clickedu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41070</link><description>Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sanoma's Clickedu. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending them a malicious URL in '/students/carpetes_varies.php'. This vulnerability can be exploited to steal sensitive user data, such as session cookies, or to perform actions on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2879 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2879</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user process to perform improper GPU processing operations to expose sensitive data.This issue affects Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r29p0 through r49p4, from r50p0 through r54p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r49p4, from r50p0 through r54p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59789 | Apache bRPC: Stack Exhaustion via Unbounded Recursion in JSON Parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59789</link><description>Uncontrolled recursion in the json2pb component in Apache bRPC (version &lt; 1.15.0) on all platforms allows remote attackers to make the server crash via sending deep recursive json data.

Root Cause:
The bRPC json2pb component uses rapidjson to parse json data from the network. The rapidjson parser uses a recursive parsing method by default. If the input json has a large depth of recursive structure, the parser function may run into stack overflow.

Affected Scenarios:
Use bRPC server with protobuf message to serve http+json requests from untrusted network. Or directly use JsonToProtoMessage to convert json from untrusted input.



How to Fix: 
(Choose one of the following options) 
1. Upgrade bRPC to version 1.15.0, which fixes this issue.
2. Apply this patch:  https://github.com/apache/brpc/pull/3099 



Note:
No matter which option 

you choose, you should know that the fix introduces a recursion depth limit with default value 100. It affects these functions: 

ProtoMessageToJson, ProtoMessageToProtoJson, JsonToProtoMessage, and ProtoJsonToProtoMessage.

 If your requests contain json or protobuf messages that have a depth exceeding the limit, the request will be failed after applying the fix. You can modify the gflag json2pb_max_recursion_depth to change the limit.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6349 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU memory processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6349</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user process to perform improper GPU memory processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r53p0 through r54p1; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r53p0 through r54p1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8045 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8045</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user process to perform improper GPU processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r53p0 through r54p1; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r53p0 through r54p1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41700 | CODESYS Development System - Deserialization of Untrusted Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41700</link><description>An unauthenticated attacker can trick a local user into executing arbitrary code by opening a deliberately manipulated CODESYS project file with a CODESYS development system. This arbitrary code is executed in the user context.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41738 | CODESYS Control - Invalid type usage in visualization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41738</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker may cause the visualisation server of the CODESYS Control runtime system to access a resource with a pointer of wrong type, potentially leading to a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41739 | CODESYS Control - Linux/QNX SysSocket flaw</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41739</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker, who beats a race condition, can exploit a flaw in the communication servers of the CODESYS Control runtime system on Linux and QNX to trigger an out-of-bounds read via crafted socket communication, potentially causing a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13819 | Open redirect in web server of MiR robots and MiR fleet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13819</link><description>Open redirect in the web server component of MiR Robot and Fleet software allows a remote attacker to redirect users to arbitrary external websites via a crafted parameter, facilitating phishing or social engineering attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 09:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13816 | moxi159753 Mogu Blog v2 ZIP File unzipFile FileOperation.unzip path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13816</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in moxi159753 Mogu Blog v2 up to 5.2. The impacted element is the function FileOperation.unzip of the file /networkDisk/unzipFile of the component ZIP File Handler. Such manipulation of the argument fileUrl leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 08:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13815 | moxi159753 Mogu Blog v2 pictures unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13815</link><description>A weakness has been identified in moxi159753 Mogu Blog v2 up to 5.2. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /file/pictures. This manipulation of the argument filedatas causes unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 08:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11131 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11131</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11132 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11132</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11133 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11133</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3012 | In dpc modem, there is a possible system crash due to null pointer dereference. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3012</link><description>In dpc modem, there is a possible system crash due to null pointer dereference. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61607 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61607</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61608 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61608</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61609 | In modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61609</link><description>In modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61610 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61610</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61617 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61617</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61618 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61618</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61619 | In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61619</link><description>In nr modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13814 | moxi159753 Mogu Blog v2 uploadPicsByUrl LocalFileServiceImpl.uploadPictureByUrl server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13814</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in moxi159753 Mogu Blog v2 up to 5.2. Impacted is the function LocalFileServiceImpl.uploadPictureByUrl of the file /file/uploadPicsByUrl. The manipulation results in server-side request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13813 | moxi159753 Mogu Blog v2 Storage Management Endpoint storage authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13813</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in moxi159753 Mogu Blog v2 up to 5.2. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /storage/ of the component Storage Management Endpoint. The manipulation leads to missing authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13811 | jsnjfz WebStack-Guns PageFactory.java sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13811</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in jsnjfz WebStack-Guns 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file src/main/java/com/jsnjfz/manage/core/common/constant/factory/PageFactory.java. Executing manipulation of the argument sort can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:02:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13810 | jsnjfz WebStack-Guns KaptchaController.java renderPicture path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13810</link><description>A vulnerability was found in jsnjfz WebStack-Guns 1.0. This affects the function renderPicture of the file src/main/java/com/jsnjfz/manage/modular/system/controller/KaptchaController.java. Performing manipulation results in path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 06:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13809 | orionsec orion-ops SSH Connection MachineInfoController.java server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13809</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in orionsec orion-ops up to 5925824997a3109651bbde07460958a7be249ed1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file orion-ops-api/orion-ops-web/src/main/java/cn/orionsec/ops/controller/MachineInfoController.java of the component SSH Connection Handler. Such manipulation of the argument host/sshPort/username/password/authType leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 05:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13808 | orionsec orion-ops User Profile UserController.java update improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13808</link><description>A flaw has been found in orionsec orion-ops up to 5925824997a3109651bbde07460958a7be249ed1. Affected by this vulnerability is the function update of the file orion-ops-api/orion-ops-web/src/main/java/cn/orionsec/ops/controller/UserController.java of the component User Profile Handler. This manipulation of the argument ID causes improper authorization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 05:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13807 | orionsec orion-ops API MachineKeyController.java MachineKeyController improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13807</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in orionsec orion-ops up to 5925824997a3109651bbde07460958a7be249ed1. Affected is the function MachineKeyController of the file orion-ops-api/orion-ops-web/src/main/java/cn/orionsec/ops/controller/MachineKeyController.java of the component API. The manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 05:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13806 | nutzam NutzBoot Transaction API EthModule.java improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13806</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in nutzam NutzBoot up to 2.6.0-SNAPSHOT. This impacts an unknown function of the file nutzboot-demo/nutzboot-demo-simple/nutzboot-demo-simple-web3j/src/main/java/io/nutz/demo/simple/module/EthModule.java of the component Transaction API. The manipulation of the argument from/to/wei leads to improper authorization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 05:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13805 | nutzam NutzBoot LiteRpc-Serializer HttpServletRpcEndpoint.java getInputStream deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13805</link><description>A weakness has been identified in nutzam NutzBoot up to 2.6.0-SNAPSHOT. This affects the function getInputStream of the file nutzcloud/nutzcloud-literpc/src/main/java/org/nutz/boot/starter/literpc/impl/endpoint/http/HttpServletRpcEndpoint.java of the component LiteRpc-Serializer. Executing manipulation can lead to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is reported as difficult. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 04:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13804 | nutzam NutzBoot Ethereum Wallet EthModule.java information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13804</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in nutzam NutzBoot up to 2.6.0-SNAPSHOT. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file nutzboot-demo/nutzboot-demo-simple/nutzboot-demo-simple-web3j/src/main/java/io/nutz/demo/simple/module/EthModule.java of the component Ethereum Wallet Handler. Performing manipulation results in information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 04:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13802 | jairiidriss RestaurantWebsite Make a Reservation cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13802</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in jairiidriss RestaurantWebsite up to e7911f12d035e8e2f9a75e7a28b59e4ef5c1d654. Impacted is an unknown function of the component Make a Reservation. This manipulation of the argument selected_date causes cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 03:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13803 | MediaCrush Header paths.py http headers for scripting syntax</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13803</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in MediaCrush 1.0.0/1.0.1. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /mediacrush/paths.py of the component Header Handler. Such manipulation of the argument Host leads to improper neutralization of http headers for scripting syntax. The attack can be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 03:04:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13800 | ADSLR NBR1005GPEV2 send_order.cgi set_mesh_disconnect command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13800</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ADSLR NBR1005GPEV2 250814-r037c. This issue affects the function set_mesh_disconnect of the file /send_order.cgi. The manipulation of the argument mac results in command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 03:04:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13799 | ADSLR NBR1005GPEV2 send_order.cgi ap_macfilter_del command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13799</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in ADSLR NBR1005GPEV2 250814-r037c. This vulnerability affects the function ap_macfilter_del of the file /send_order.cgi. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 03:04:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13797 | ADSLR B-QE2W401 send_order.cgi parameterdel_swifimac command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13797</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in ADSLR B-QE2W401 250814-r037c. Affected by this issue is the function parameterdel_swifimac of the file /send_order.cgi. Performing manipulation of the argument del_swifimac results in command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13798 | ADSLR NBR1005GPEV2 send_order.cgi ap_macfilter_add command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13798</link><description>A flaw has been found in ADSLR NBR1005GPEV2 250814-r037c. This affects the function ap_macfilter_add of the file /send_order.cgi. Executing manipulation of the argument mac can lead to command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64772 | The installer of INZONE Hub 1.0.10.3 to 1.0.17.0 contains an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to insecurely loading Dynamic Li...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64772</link><description>The installer of INZONE Hub 1.0.10.3 to 1.0.17.0 contains an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to insecurely loading Dynamic Link Libraries. As a result, arbitrary code may be executed with the privilege of the user invoking the installer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>