<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 05:11:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-11591 | CodeAstro Gym Management System delete-member.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11591</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in CodeAstro Gym Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/actions/delete-member.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 05:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58284 | Permission control vulnerability in the network module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58284</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the network module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 04:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58285 | Permission control vulnerability in the media module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58285</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the media module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 04:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58278 | Identity authentication bypass vulnerability in the Gallery app. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58278</link><description>Identity authentication bypass vulnerability in the Gallery app. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 03:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58282 | Permission control vulnerability in the camera module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58282</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the camera module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 03:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58283 | Permission control vulnerability in the Wi-Fi module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58283</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the Wi-Fi module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 03:55:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58277 | Permission verification bypass vulnerability in the Camera app. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58277</link><description>Permission verification bypass vulnerability in the Camera app. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 03:55:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11380 | Everest Backup &amp;lt;= 2.3.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11380</link><description>The Everest Backup – WordPress Cloud Backup, Migration, Restore &amp; Cloning Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'everest_process_status' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve back-up file locations that can be subsequently accessed and downloaded. This does require a back-up to be running in order for an attacker to retrieve the back-up location.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 03:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9560 | Colibri Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.0.334 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via colibri_newsletter Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9560</link><description>The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's colibri_newsletter shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.334 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 03:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54654 | Permission control vulnerability in the Gallery module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54654</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the Gallery module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:34:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11590 | CodeAstro Gym Management System equipment-entry.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11590</link><description>A weakness has been identified in CodeAstro Gym Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/equipment-entry.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ename can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 01:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31717 | In modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31717</link><description>In modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 01:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31718 | In modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no addit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31718</link><description>In modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 01:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11626 | Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition (&amp;#x27;Infinite Loop&amp;#x27;) in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11626</link><description>MONGO dissector infinite loop in Wireshark 4.4.0 to 4.4.9 and 4.2.0 to 4.2.13 allows denial of service</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62159 | External Secrets Operator&amp;#x27;s BeyondTrust Provider has Insecure Secret Retrieval</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62159</link><description>External Secrets Operator reads information from a third-party service and automatically injects the values as Kubernetes Secrets. A vulnerability was discovered in the BeyondTrust provider implementation for External Secrets Operator versions 0.10.1 through 0.19.2. The provider previously retrieved Kubernetes secrets directly, without validating the namespace context or the type of secret store. This allowed unauthorized cross-namespace secret access, violating security boundaries and potentially exposing sensitive credentials. In version 0.20.0, the provider code was updated to use the `resolvers.SecretKeyRef` utility, which enforces namespace validation and only allows cross-namespace access for `ClusterSecretStore` types. This ensures secrets are only retrieved from the correct namespace, mitigating the risk of unauthorized access. All users should upgrade to the latest version containing this fix. As a workaround, use a policy engine such as Kyverno or OPA to prevent using BeyondTrust provider and/or validate the `(Cluster)SecretStore` and ensure the namespace may only be set when using a `ClusterSecretStore`.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62162 | cel-rust May Panic During Parsing of Invalid CEL Expressions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62162</link><description>cel-rust is a Common Expression Language interpreter written in Rust. Starting in version 0.10.0 and prior to version 0.11.4, parsing certain malformed CEL expressions can cause the parser to panic, terminating the process. When the crate is used to evaluate untrusted expressions (e.g., user-supplied input over an API), an attacker can send crafted input to trigger a denial of service (DoS). Version 0.11.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8093 | Authenticator Login - Moderately critical - Access bypass - SA-CONTRIB-2025-098</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8093</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Drupal Authenticator Login allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Authenticator Login: from 0.0.0 before 2.1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9549 | Facets - Moderately critical - Information Disclosure - SA-CONTRIB-2025-099</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9549</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Drupal Facets allows Forceful Browsing.This issue affects Facets: from 0.0.0 before 2.0.10, from 3.0.0 before 3.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9550 | Facets - Moderately critical - Cross Site Scripting - SA-CONTRIB-2025-100</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9550</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Drupal Facets allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Facets: from 0.0.0 before 2.0.10, from 3.0.0 before 3.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9551 | Protected Pages - Moderately critical - Access bypass - SA-CONTRIB-2025-101</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9551</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Drupal Protected Pages allows Brute Force.This issue affects Protected Pages: from 0.0.0 before 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9552 | Synchronize composer.json With Contrib Modules - Critical - Unsupported - SA-CONTRIB-2025-102</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9552</link><description>Vulnerability in Drupal Synchronize composer.Json With Contrib Modules.This issue affects Synchronize composer.Json With Contrib Modules: *.*.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9553 | API Key manager - Critical - Unsupported - SA-CONTRIB-2025-103</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9553</link><description>Vulnerability in Drupal API Key manager.This issue affects API Key manager: *.*.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9554 | Owl Carousel 2 - Critical - Unsupported - SA-CONTRIB-2025-104</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9554</link><description>Vulnerability in Drupal Owl Carousel 2.This issue affects Owl Carousel 2: *.*.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52647 | HCL BigFix WebUI is affected by a host header poisoning vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52647</link><description>The BigFix WebUI application responds with HOST information from the HTTP header field making it vulnerable to Host Header Poisoning Attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52885 | GHSL-2025-042: Poppler has Use-After-Free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52885</link><description>Poppler ia a library for rendering PDF files, and examining or modifying their structure. A use-after-free (write) vulnerability has been detected in versions Poppler prior to 25.10.0 within the StructTreeRoot class. The issue arises from the use of raw pointers to elements of a `std::vector`, which can lead to dangling pointers when the vector is resized. The vulnerability stems from the way that refToParentMap stores references to `std::vector` elements using raw pointers. These pointers may become invalid when the vector is resized. This vulnerability is a common security problem involving the use of raw pointers to `std::vectors`. Internally, `std::vector `stores its elements in a dynamically allocated array. When the array reaches its capacity and a new element is added, the vector reallocates a larger block of memory and moves all the existing elements to the new location. At this point if any pointers to elements are stored before a resize occurs, they become dangling pointers once the reallocation happens. Version 25.10.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61911 | python-ldap has sanitization bypass in ldap.filter.escape_filter_chars</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61911</link><description>python-ldap is a lightweight directory access protocol (LDAP) client API for Python. In versions prior to 3.4.5, the sanitization method `ldap.filter.escape_filter_chars` can be tricked to skip escaping of special characters when a crafted `list` or `dict` is supplied as the `assertion_value` parameter, and the non-default `escape_mode=1` is configured. The method `ldap.filter.escape_filter_chars` supports 3 different escaping modes. `escape_mode=0` (default) and `escape_mode=2` happen to raise exceptions when a `list` or `dict` object is supplied as the `assertion_value` parameter. However, `escape_mode=1` computes without performing adequate logic to ensure a fully escaped return value. If an application relies on the vulnerable method in the `python-ldap` library to escape untrusted user input, an attacker might be able to abuse the vulnerability to launch ldap injection attacks which could potentially disclose or manipulate ldap data meant to be inaccessible to them. Version 3.4.5 fixes the issue by adding a type check at the start of the `ldap.filter.escape_filter_chars` method to raise an exception when the supplied `assertion_value` parameter is not of type `str`.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:11:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61912 | python-ldap Vulnerable to Improper Encoding or Escaping of Output and Improper Null Termination</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61912</link><description>python-ldap is a lightweight directory access protocol (LDAP) client API for Python. In versions prior to 3.4.5, ldap.dn.escape_dn_chars() escapes \x00 incorrectly by emitting a backslash followed by a literal NUL byte instead of the RFC-4514 hex form \00. Any application that uses this helper to construct DNs from untrusted input can be made to consistently fail before a request is sent to the LDAP server (e.g., AD), resulting in a client-side denial of service. Version 3.4.5 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:11:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11588 | CodeAstro Gym Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11588</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in CodeAstro Gym Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /customer/index.php. Such manipulation of the argument fullname leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 21:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11589 | CodeAstro Gym Management System user-payment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11589</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in CodeAstro Gym Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/user-payment.php. Performing manipulation of the argument plan results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 21:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11585 | code-projects Project Monitoring System useredit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11585</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Project Monitoring System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /useredit.php. The manipulation of the argument uid results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 21:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11586 | Tenda AC7 setNotUpgrade stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11586</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda AC7 15.03.06.44. This affects an unknown function of the file /goform/setNotUpgrade. This manipulation of the argument newVersion causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 21:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11584 | code-projects Online Job Search Engine searchjob.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11584</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Online Job Search Engine 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /searchjob.php. The manipulation of the argument txtspecialization leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11582 | code-projects Online Job Search Engine registration.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11582</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Online Job Search Engine 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /registration.php. Performing manipulation of the argument txtusername results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11583 | code-projects Online Job Search Engine postjob.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11583</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Online Job Search Engine 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /postjob.php. Executing manipulation of the argument txtjobID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61930 | Emlog Pro has CSRF issue that Enables Admin Password Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61930</link><description>Emlog is an open source website building system. Emlog Pro versions 2.5.19 and earlier are vulnerable to Cross‑Site Request Forgery (CSRF) on the password change endpoint. An attacker can trick a logged‑in administrator into submitting a crafted POST request to change the admin password without consent. Impact is account takeover of privileged users. Severity: High. As of time of publication, no known patched versions exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62158 | Frappe had attachments made by students to their assignments of type Text set to public</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62158</link><description>Frappe Learning is a learning system that helps users structure their content. In versions prior to 2.38.0, the system did stored the attachments uploaded by the students in their assignments as public files. This issue potentially exposed student-uploaded files to the public. Anyone with the file URL could access these files without authentication. The issue has been fixed in version 2.38.0 by ensuring all student-uploaded assignment attachments are stored as private files by default.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61929 | Cherry Studio allows one-click on a specific URL to cause a command to execute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61929</link><description>Cherry Studio is a desktop client that supports for multiple LLM providers. Cherry Studio registers a custom protocol called `cherrystudio://`. When handling the MCP installation URL, it parses the base64-encoded configuration data and directly executes the command within it. In the files `src/main/services/ProtocolClient.ts` and `src/main/services/urlschema/mcp-install.ts`, when receiving a URL of the `cherrystudio://mcp` type, the `handleMcpProtocolUrl` function is called for processing. If an attacker crafts malicious content and posts it on a website or elsewhere (there are many exploitation methods, such as creating a malicious website with a button containing this malicious content), when the user clicks it, since the pop-up window contains normal content, the direct click is considered a scene action, and the malicious command is directly triggered, leading to the user being compromised. As of time of publication, no known patched versions exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 19:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61927 | Happy-DOM has VM Context Escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61927</link><description>Happy DOM is a JavaScript implementation of a web browser without its graphical user interface. Happy DOM v19 and lower contains a security vulnerability that puts the owner system at the risk of RCE (Remote Code Execution) attacks. A Node.js VM Context is not an isolated environment, and if the user runs untrusted JavaScript code within the Happy DOM VM Context, it may escape the VM and get access to process level functionality. It seems like what the attacker can get control over depends on if the process is using ESM or CommonJS. With CommonJS the attacker can get hold of the `require()` function to import modules. Happy DOM has JavaScript evaluation enabled by default. This may not be obvious to the consumer of Happy DOM and can potentially put the user at risk if untrusted code is executed within the environment. Version 20.0.0 patches the issue by changing JavaScript evaluation to be disabled by default.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 19:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61925 | Astro&amp;#x27;s `X-Forwarded-Host` is reflected with no validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61925</link><description>Astro is a web framework. Prior to version 5.14.2, Astro reflects the value in `X-Forwarded-Host` in output when using `Astro.url` without any validation. It is common for web servers such as nginx to route requests via the `Host` header, and forward on other request headers. As such as malicious request can be sent with both a `Host` header and an `X-Forwarded-Host` header where the values do not match and the `X-Forwarded-Host` header is malicious. Astro will then return the malicious value. This could result in any usages of the `Astro.url` value in code being manipulated by a request. For example if a user follows guidance and uses `Astro.url` for a canonical link the canonical link can be manipulated to another site. It is theoretically possible that the value could also be used as a login/registration or other form URL as well, resulting in potential redirecting of login credentials to a malicious party. As this is a per-request attack vector the surface area would only be to the malicious user until one considers that having a caching proxy is a common setup, in which case any page which is cached could persist the malicious value for subsequent users. Many other frameworks have an allowlist of domains to validate against, or do not have a case where the headers are reflected to avoid such issues. This could affect anyone using Astro in an on-demand/dynamic rendering mode behind a caching proxy. Version 5.14.2 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61921 | Sinatra has ReDoS vulnerability in ETag header value generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61921</link><description>Sinatra is a domain-specific language for creating web applications in Ruby. In versions prior to 4.2.0, there is a denial of service vulnerability in the `If-Match` and `If-None-Match` header parsing component of Sinatra, if the `etag` method is used when constructing the response. Carefully crafted input can cause `If-Match` and `If-None-Match` header parsing in Sinatra to take an unexpected amount of time, possibly resulting in a denial of service attack vector. This header is typically involved in generating the `ETag` header value. Any applications that use the `etag` method when generating a response are impacted. Version 4.2.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 19:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55903 | A HTML injection vulnerability exists in Perfex CRM v3.3.1. The application fails to sanitize user input in the "Bill To" address field with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55903</link><description>A HTML injection vulnerability exists in Perfex CRM v3.3.1. The application fails to sanitize user input in the "Bill To" address field within the estimate module. As a result, arbitrary HTML can be injected and rendered unescaped in client-facing documents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 19:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61919 | Rack is vulnerable to a memory-exhaustion DoS through unbounded URL-encoded body parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61919</link><description>Rack is a modular Ruby web server interface. Prior to versions 2.2.20, 3.1.18, and 3.2.3, `Rack::Request#POST` reads the entire request body into memory for `Content-Type: application/x-www-form-urlencoded`, calling `rack.input.read(nil)` without enforcing a length or cap. Large request bodies can therefore be buffered completely into process memory before parsing, leading to denial of service (DoS) through memory exhaustion. Users should upgrade to Rack version 2.2.20, 3.1.18, or 3.2.3, anu of which enforces form parameter limits using `query_parser.bytesize_limit`, preventing unbounded reads of `application/x-www-form-urlencoded` bodies. Additionally, enforce strict maximum body size at the proxy or web server layer (e.g., Nginx `client_max_body_size`, Apache `LimitRequestBody`).</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 19:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61920 | Authlib is vulnerable to Denial of Service via Oversized JOSE Segments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61920</link><description>Authlib is a Python library which builds OAuth and OpenID Connect servers. Prior to version 1.6.5, Authlib’s JOSE implementation accepts unbounded JWS/JWT header and signature segments. A remote attacker can craft a token whose base64url‑encoded header or signature spans hundreds of megabytes. During verification, Authlib decodes and parses the full input before it is rejected, driving CPU and memory consumption to hostile levels and enabling denial of service. Version 1.6.5 patches the issue. Some temporary workarounds are available. Enforce input size limits before handing tokens to Authlib and/or use application-level throttling to reduce amplification risk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 19:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62245 | Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.1 through 7.4.3.112, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62245</link><description>Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.1 through 7.4.3.112, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.10, and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows remote attackers to add and edit publication comments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 19:22:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11581 | PowerJob OpenAPIController runJob authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11581</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in PowerJob up to 5.1.2. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /openApi/runJob of the component OpenAPIController. Such manipulation leads to missing authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 19:22:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60880 | An authenticated stored XSS vulnerability exists in the Bagisto 2.3.6 admin panel's product creation path, allowing an attacker to upload a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60880</link><description>An authenticated stored XSS vulnerability exists in the Bagisto 2.3.6 admin panel's product creation path, allowing an attacker to upload a crafted SVG file containing malicious JavaScript code. This vulnerability can be exploited by an authenticated admin user to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the browser, potentially leading to session hijacking, data theft, or unauthorized actions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 18:51:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61505 | e107 CMS thru 2.3.3 are vulnerable to insecure deserialization in the `install.php` script. The script processes user-controlled input in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61505</link><description>e107 CMS thru 2.3.3 are vulnerable to insecure deserialization in the `install.php` script. The script processes user-controlled input in the `previous_steps` POST parameter using `unserialize(base64_decode())` without validation, allowing attackers to craft malicious serialized data. This could lead to remote code execution, arbitrary file operations, or denial of service, depending on available PHP object gadgets in the codebase.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 18:51:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11580 | PowerJob list authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11580</link><description>A weakness has been identified in PowerJob up to 5.1.2. This affects the function list of the file /user/list. This manipulation causes missing authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 18:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60838 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in MCMS v6.0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60838</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in MCMS v6.0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 18:00:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60268 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in JeeWMS 20250820, which is caused by the lack of file checking in the saveFiles function in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60268</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in JeeWMS 20250820, which is caused by the lack of file checking in the saveFiles function in /jeewms/cgUploadController.do. An attacker with normal privileges was able to upload a malicious file that would lead to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 18:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23282 | NVIDIA Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker might be able to use a race condition to escalate privileges. A s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23282</link><description>NVIDIA Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker might be able to use a race condition to escalate privileges. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, data tampering, denial of service, and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23280 | NVIDIA Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause a use-after-free. A successful exploit of this vulner...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23280</link><description>NVIDIA Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause a use-after-free. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, data tampering, denial of service, and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23309 | NVIDIA Display Driver contains a vulnerability where an uncontrolled DLL loading path might lead to arbitrary denial of service, escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23309</link><description>NVIDIA Display Driver contains a vulnerability where an uncontrolled DLL loading path might lead to arbitrary denial of service, escalation of privileges, code execution, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11616 | Buffer Over-read when receiving improperly sized ICMPv6 packets in FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11616</link><description>A missing validation check in FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP's ICMPv6 packet processing code can lead to an out-of-bounds read when receiving ICMPv6 packets of certain message types which are smaller than the expected size. These issues only affect applications using IPv6.

Users should upgrade to the latest version and ensure any forked or derivative code is patched to incorporate the new fixes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11617 | Buffer Over-read when receiving IPv6 packets with incorrect payload length in FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11617</link><description>A missing validation check in FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP's IPv6 packet processing code can lead to an out-of-bounds read when receiving a IPv6 packet with incorrect payload lengths in the packet header. This issue only affects applications using IPv6.

We recommend users upgrade to the latest version and ensure any forked or derivative code is patched to incorporate the new fixes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11618 | Invalid Pointer Dereference when receiving UDP/IPv6 packets in FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11618</link><description>A missing validation check in FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP's UDP/IPv6 packet processing code can lead to an invalid pointer dereference when receiving a UDP/IPv6 packet with an incorrect IP version field in the packet header. This issue only affects applications using IPv6.

We recommend upgrading to the latest version and ensure any forked or derivative code is patched to incorporate the new fixes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61780 | Rack has Possible Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61780</link><description>Rack is a modular Ruby web server interface. Prior to versions 2.2.20, 3.1.18, and 3.2.3, a possible information disclosure vulnerability existed in `Rack::Sendfile` when running behind a proxy that supports `x-sendfile` headers (such as Nginx). Specially crafted headers could cause `Rack::Sendfile` to miscommunicate with the proxy and trigger unintended internal requests, potentially bypassing proxy-level access restrictions. When `Rack::Sendfile` received untrusted `x-sendfile-type` or `x-accel-mapping` headers from a client, it would interpret them as proxy configuration directives. This could cause the middleware to send a "redirect" response to the proxy, prompting it to reissue a new internal request that was not subject to the proxy's access controls. An attacker could exploit this by setting a crafted `x-sendfile-type: x-accel-redirect` header, setting a crafted `x-accel-mapping` header, and requesting a path that qualifies for proxy-based acceleration. Attackers could bypass proxy-enforced restrictions and access internal endpoints intended to be protected (such as administrative pages). The vulnerability did not allow arbitrary file reads but could expose sensitive application routes. This issue only affected systems meeting all of the following conditions: The application used `Rack::Sendfile` with a proxy that supports `x-accel-redirect` (e.g., Nginx); the proxy did **not** always set or remove the `x-sendfile-type` and `x-accel-mapping` headers; and the application exposed an endpoint that returned a body responding to `.to_path`. Users should upgrade to Rack versions 2.2.20, 3.1.18, or 3.2.3, which require explicit configuration to enable `x-accel-redirect`. Alternatively, configure the proxy to always set or strip the header, or in Rails applications, disable sendfile completely.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60269 | JEEWMS 20250820 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the exportXls function located in the src/main/java/org/jeecgframework/web/cgreport/contro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60269</link><description>JEEWMS 20250820 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the exportXls function located in the src/main/java/org/jeecgframework/web/cgreport/controller/excel/CgExportExcelController.java file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 16:58:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60308 | code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0 has a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Add Room function of the onli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60308</link><description>code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0 has a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Add Room function of the online hotel reservation system. Malicious JavaScript code is entered in the Description field, which can leak the administrator's cookie information when browsing this room information</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 16:58:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61689 | HTTP.jl vulnerable to Header injection/Response splitting via header construction.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61689</link><description>HTTP.jl is an HTTP client and server functionality for the Julia programming language. Prior to version 1.10.19, HTTP.jl did not validate header names/values for illegal characters, allowing CRLF-based header injection and response splitting. This enables HTTP response splitting and header injection, leading to cache poisoning, XSS, session fixation, and more. This issue is fixed in HTTP.jl  `v1.10.19`.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 16:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60306 | code-projects Simple Car Rental System 1.0 has a permission bypass issue where low privilege users can forge high privilege sessions and per...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60306</link><description>code-projects Simple Car Rental System 1.0 has a permission bypass issue where low privilege users can forge high privilege sessions and perform sensitive operations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 16:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59530 | quic-go has Client Crash Due to Premature HANDSHAKE_DONE Frame</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59530</link><description>quic-go is an implementation of the QUIC protocol in Go. In versions prior to 0.49.0, 0.54.1, and 0.55.0, a misbehaving or malicious server can cause a denial-of-service (DoS) attack on the quic-go client by triggering an assertion failure, leading to a process crash. This requires no authentication and can be exploited during the handshake phase. This was observed in the wild with certain server implementations. quic-go needs to be able to handle misbehaving server implementations, including those that prematurely send a HANDSHAKE_DONE frame. Versions 0.49.0, 0.54.1, and 0.55.0 discard Initial keys when receiving a HANDSHAKE_DONE frame, thereby correctly handling premature HANDSHAKE_DONE frames.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 16:12:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48043 | Bypass and runtime policies that can never pass may be incorrectly applied in filter authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48043</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in ash-project ash allows Authentication Bypass. This vulnerability is associated with program files lib/ash/policy/authorizer/authorizer.ex and program routines 'Elixir.Ash.Policy.Authorizer':strict_filters/2.

This issue affects ash: from pkg:hex/ash@0 before pkg:hex/ash@3.6.2, before 3.6.2, before 66d81300065b970da0d2f4528354835d2418c7ae.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 16:12:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60305 | SourceCodester Online Student Clearance System 1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The application contains a logic flaw which al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60305</link><description>SourceCodester Online Student Clearance System 1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The application contains a logic flaw which allows low privilege users can forge high privileged sessions and perform sensitive operations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60307 | code-projects Computer Laboratory System 1.0 has a SQL injection vulnerability, where entering a universal password in the Password field on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60307</link><description>code-projects Computer Laboratory System 1.0 has a SQL injection vulnerability, where entering a universal password in the Password field on the login page can bypass login attempts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60869 | Publii CMS v0.46.5 (build 17089) allows persistent Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via unsanitized input in configuration fields such as "Site De...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60869</link><description>Publii CMS v0.46.5 (build 17089) allows persistent Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via unsanitized input in configuration fields such as "Site Description" and "Footer Follow Buttons". An attacker can inject arbitrary JavaScript, which is stored in the project and executed in the browsers of remote visitors viewing the generated static site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60378 | Stored HTML injection in RISE Ultimate Project Manager &amp; CRM allows authenticated users to inject arbitrary HTML into invoices and messages....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60378</link><description>Stored HTML injection in RISE Ultimate Project Manager &amp; CRM allows authenticated users to inject arbitrary HTML into invoices and messages. Injected content renders in emails, PDFs, and messaging/chat modules sent to clients or team members, enabling phishing, credential theft, and business email compromise. Automated recurring invoices and messaging amplify the risk by distributing malicious content to multiple recipients.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60868 | The Alt Redirect 1.6.3 addon for Statamic fails to consistently strip query string parameters when the "Query String Strip" feature is enabl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60868</link><description>The Alt Redirect 1.6.3 addon for Statamic fails to consistently strip query string parameters when the "Query String Strip" feature is enabled. Case variations, encoded keys, and duplicates are not removed, allowing attackers to bypass sanitization. This may lead to cache poisoning, parameter pollution, or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8887 | IDOR in Usta Information Systems&amp;#x27; Aybs Interaktif</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8887</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key, Missing Authorization, Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Usta Information Systems Inc. Aybs Interaktif allows Forceful Browsing, Parameter Injection, Input Data Manipulation.This issue affects Aybs Interaktif: from 2024 through 28082025.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61152 | python-jose thru 3.3.0 allows JWT tokens with 'alg=none' to be decoded and accepted without any cryptographic signature verification. A mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61152</link><description>python-jose thru 3.3.0 allows JWT tokens with 'alg=none' to be decoded and accepted without any cryptographic signature verification. A malicious actor can craft a forged token with arbitrary claims (e.g., is_admin=true) and bypass authentication checks, leading to privilege escalation or unauthorized access in applications that rely on python-jose for token validation. This issue is exploitable unless developers explicitly reject 'alg=none' tokens, which is not enforced by the library.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 13:57:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61319 | ReNgine thru 2.2.0 is vulnerable to a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Vulnerabilities module. When scanning a target ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61319</link><description>ReNgine thru 2.2.0 is vulnerable to a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Vulnerabilities module. When scanning a target with an XSS payload, the unsanitized payload is rendered in the ReNgine web UI, resulting in arbitrary JavaScript execution in the victim's browser. This can be abused to steal session cookies, perform unauthorized actions, or compromise the ReNgine administrator's account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 13:57:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8886 | Authorization Bypass in Usta Information Systems&amp;#x27; Aybs Interaktif</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8886</link><description>Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource, Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor, Missing Authorization, Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Usta Information Systems Inc. Aybs Interaktif allows Privilege Abuse, Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Aybs Interaktif: from 2024 through 28082025.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 13:57:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62237 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Commerce’s view order page in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.8 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62237</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Commerce’s view order page in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.8 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, and 7.4 update 8 through update 92 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into an Account’s “Name” text field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 13:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62238 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the Membership page in Account Settings in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.21 through 7.4.3.111, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62238</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the Membership page in Account Settings in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.21 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, and 7.4 update 21 through update 92 allows remote authenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into a Account's “Name“ text field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 13:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62239 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in workflow process builder in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.21 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62239</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in workflow process builder in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.21 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, and 7.4 update 21 through update 92 allows remote authenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the crafted input in a workflow definition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 12:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11579 | DoS via Out Of Memory Crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11579</link><description>github.com/nwaples/rardecode versions &lt;=2.1.1 fail to restrict the dictionary size when reading large RAR dictionary sizes, which allows an attacker to provide a specially crafted RAR file and cause Denial of Service via an Out Of Memory Crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:29:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7374 | WP JobHunt &amp;lt;= 7.6 Authenticated (Custom+) Authorization Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7374</link><description>The WP JobHunt plugin for WordPress, used by the JobCareer theme, is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 7.6. This is due to insufficient login restrictions on inactive and pending accounts. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Candidate- and Employer-level access and above, to log in to the site even if their account is inactive or pending.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:29:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7781 | WP JobHunt &amp;lt;= 7.6 - Authenticated (Candidate+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via ‘cs_job_title’</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7781</link><description>The WP JobHunt plugin for WordPress, used by the JobCareer theme, is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘cs_job_title’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 7.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Candidate-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11188 | CVE-2025-11188</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11188</link><description>The Kiwire Captive Portal contains a blind SQL injection in the nas-id parameter, allowing for SQL commands to be issued and to compromise the corresponding database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11189 | CVE-2025-11189</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11189</link><description>The Kiwire Captive Portal contains a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability within the login-url parameter, allowing for Javascript execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11190 | CVE-2025-11190</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11190</link><description>The Kiwire Captive Portal contains an open redirection issue via the login-url parameter, allowing an attacker to redirect users to an attacker controlled website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61863 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in VS6ComFile!CSaveData::delete_mem of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening specially crafted V-SF...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61863</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in VS6ComFile!CSaveData::delete_mem of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening specially crafted V-SFT files may lead to information disclosure, affected system's abnormal end (ABEND), and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61864 | A use after free vulnerability exists in VS6ComFile!load_link_inf of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening specially crafted V-SFT files may l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61864</link><description>A use after free vulnerability exists in VS6ComFile!load_link_inf of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening specially crafted V-SFT files may lead to information disclosure, affected system's abnormal end (ABEND), and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61861 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in VS6ComFile!load_link_inf of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening specially crafted V-SFT files ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61861</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in VS6ComFile!load_link_inf of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening specially crafted V-SFT files may lead to information disclosure, affected system's abnormal end (ABEND), and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61862 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in VS6ComFile!get_ovlp_element_size of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening specially crafted V-SF...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61862</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in VS6ComFile!get_ovlp_element_size of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening specially crafted V-SFT files may lead to information disclosure, affected system's abnormal end (ABEND), and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61859 | An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in VS6ComFile!CItemDraw::is_motion_tween of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening specially crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61859</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in VS6ComFile!CItemDraw::is_motion_tween of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening specially crafted V-SFT files may lead to information disclosure, affected system's abnormal end (ABEND), and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:48:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61860 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in VS6MemInIF!set_temp_type_default of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening specially crafted V-SF...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61860</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in VS6MemInIF!set_temp_type_default of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening specially crafted V-SFT files may lead to information disclosure, affected system's abnormal end (ABEND), and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:48:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52624 | HCL AION is susceptible to Bypass of the script allow list configuration vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52624</link><description>A vulnerability  Bypass of the script allowlist configuration in HCL AION. 

An incorrectly configured Content-Security-Policy header may allow unauthorized scripts to execute, increasing the risk of cross-site scripting and other injection-based attacks.This issue affects AION: 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52625 | HCL AION is susceptible to Cacheable SSL Page Found vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52625</link><description>A vulnerability 

Cacheable SSL Page Found vulnerability has been identified

 in HCL AION. 

Cached data may expose credentials, system identifiers, or internal file paths to attackers with access to the device or browser

This issue affects AION: 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52635 | HCL AION is susceptible to Trusted types in scripts not enforced in CSP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52635</link><description>A 

rusted types in scripts not enforced in CSP vulnerability has been identified

 in HCL AION.This issue affects AION: 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61856 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in VS6ComFile!CV7BaseMap::WriteV7DataToRom of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening special...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61856</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in VS6ComFile!CV7BaseMap::WriteV7DataToRom of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening specially crafted V-SFT files may lead to information disclosure, affected system's abnormal end (ABEND), and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61857 | An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in VS6ComFile!CItemExChange::WinFontDynStrCheck of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening specially...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61857</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in VS6ComFile!CItemExChange::WinFontDynStrCheck of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening specially crafted V-SFT files may lead to information disclosure, affected system's abnormal end (ABEND), and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61858 | An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in VS6ComFile!set_AnimationItem of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening specially crafted V-SFT f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61858</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in VS6ComFile!set_AnimationItem of V-SFT v6.2.7.0 and earlier. Opening specially crafted V-SFT files may lead to information disclosure, affected system's abnormal end (ABEND), and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52632 | HCL AION is susceptible to Missing Secure Attribute in Encrypted Session (SSL) Cookie vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52632</link><description>A Missing Secure Attribute in Encrypted Session (SSL) Cookie vulnerability in HCL AION.This issue affects AION: 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25017 | Kibana Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25017</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation in Kibana can lead to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30001 | Apache StreamPark: Authenticated users can trigger remote command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30001</link><description>Incorrect Execution-Assigned Permissions vulnerability in Apache StreamPark.

This issue affects Apache StreamPark: from 2.1.4 before 2.1.6.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.1.6, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37727 | Elasticsearch Insertion of sensitive information in log file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37727</link><description>Insertion of sensitive information in log file in Elasticsearch can lead to loss of confidentiality under specific preconditions when auditing requests to the  reindex API https://www.elastic.co/docs/api/doc/elasticsearch/operation/operation-reindex</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52630 | HCL AION is susceptible to Missing or insecure &amp;quot;X-Content-Type-Options&amp;quot; header vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52630</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in HCL AION.This issue affects AION: 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25018 | Kibana Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25018</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation in Kibana can lead to stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52634 | HCL AION is susceptible to  Spring Boot Actuator Endpoints Exposed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52634</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in HCL AION This issue affects HCL AION: 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52650 | HCL AION is susceptible to Inline script execution allowed in CSP vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52650</link><description>Inline script execution allowed in CSP vulnerability has been identified in HCL AION v2.0</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41088 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41088</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Xibo Signage's Xibo CMS v4.1.2, due to a lack of proper validation of user input. To exploit the vulnerability, the attacker must create a template in the 'Templates' section, then add a text element in the 'Global Elements' section, and finally modify the 'Text' field in the section with the malicious payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41089 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41089</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Xibo CMS v4.1.2 from Xibo Signage, due to a lack of proper validation of user input. To exploit the vulnerability, the attacker must create a template in the 'Templates' section, then add an element that has the 'Configuration Name' field, such as the 'Clock' widget. Next, modify the 'Configuration Name' field in the left-hand section.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52655 | HCL MyXalytics is affected by a Cross-Domain Script Include vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52655</link><description>Inclusion of Functionality from Untrusted Control Sphere vulnerability in HCL MyXalytics. v6.6
allows Loading third-party scripts without integrity checks or validation can allow external code run in the application's context, risking data exposure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40640 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Energy CRM by Status Tracker</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40640</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Energy CRM v2025 by Status Tracker Ltd, consisting of a stored XSS due to lack of proper validation of user input by sending a POST request to “/crm/create_invoice_submit.php”, using the “customerName_0” parameter. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal their cookie session details.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21050 | Improper input validiation in Contacts prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access data across multiple user profiles.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21050</link><description>Improper input validiation in Contacts prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access data across multiple user profiles.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21044 | Out-of-bounds write in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21044</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21045 | Insecure storage of sensitive information in Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21045</link><description>Insecure storage of sensitive information in Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21046 | Improper access control in WindowManager in Samsung DeX prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to temporarily access to r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21046</link><description>Improper access control in WindowManager in Samsung DeX prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to temporarily access to recent app list.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21047 | Improper access control in KnoxGuard prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to use the privileged APIs.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21047</link><description>Improper access control in KnoxGuard prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to use the privileged APIs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21048 | Relative path traversal in Knox Enterprise prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21048</link><description>Relative path traversal in Knox Enterprise prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21049 | Improper access control in SecSettings prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive information. User interact...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21049</link><description>Improper access control in SecSettings prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive information. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21051 | Out-of-bounds write in the pre-processing of JPEG decoding in libpadm.so prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21051</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in the pre-processing of JPEG decoding in libpadm.so prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21052 | Out-of-bounds write under specific condition in the pre-processing of JPEG decoding in libpadm.so prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21052</link><description>Out-of-bounds write under specific condition in the pre-processing of JPEG decoding in libpadm.so prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to cause memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21053 | Out-of-bounds write in the parsing header for JPEG decoding in libpadm.so prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to cause me...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21053</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in the parsing header for JPEG decoding in libpadm.so prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to cause memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21054 | Out-of-bounds read in the parsing header for JPEG decoding in libpadm.so prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21054</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in the parsing header for JPEG decoding in libpadm.so prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to potentially access out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21055 | Out-of-bounds read and write in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bounds memor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21055</link><description>Out-of-bounds read and write in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Oct-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21057 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.30.63 allows local attackers to access shared notes...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21057</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.30.63 allows local attackers to access shared notes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21058 | Improper access control in Routines prior to version 4.8.7.1 in Android 15 and 4.9.6.0 in Android 16 allows local attackers to potentially e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21058</link><description>Improper access control in Routines prior to version 4.8.7.1 in Android 15 and 4.9.6.0 in Android 16 allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code with SystemUI privilege.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21059 | Improper authorization in Samsung Health prior to version 6.30.5.105 allows local attackers to access data in Samsung Health.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21059</link><description>Improper authorization in Samsung Health prior to version 6.30.5.105 allows local attackers to access data in Samsung Health.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21060 | Cleartext storage of sensitive information in Smart Switch prior to version 3.7.67.2 allows local attackers to access backup data from appli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21060</link><description>Cleartext storage of sensitive information in Smart Switch prior to version 3.7.67.2 allows local attackers to access backup data from applications. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21061 | Cleartext storage of sensitive information in Smart Switch prior to version 3.7.67.2 allows local attackers to access sensitive data. User i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21061</link><description>Cleartext storage of sensitive information in Smart Switch prior to version 3.7.67.2 allows local attackers to access sensitive data. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21062 | Use of a broken or risky cryptographic algorithm in Smart Switch prior to version 3.7.67.2 allows local attackers to replace the restoring a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21062</link><description>Use of a broken or risky cryptographic algorithm in Smart Switch prior to version 3.7.67.2 allows local attackers to replace the restoring application. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21063 | Improper access control in Samsung Voice Recorder prior to version 21.5.73.12 in Android 15 and 21.5.81.40 in Android 16 allows physical att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21063</link><description>Improper access control in Samsung Voice Recorder prior to version 21.5.73.12 in Android 15 and 21.5.81.40 in Android 16 allows physical attackers to access recording files on the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21064 | Improper authentication in Smart Switch prior to version 3.7.66.6 allows adjacent attackers to access transferring data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21064</link><description>Improper authentication in Smart Switch prior to version 3.7.66.6 allows adjacent attackers to access transferring data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21065 | Improper input validation in Retail Mode prior to version 5.59.11 allows self attackers to execute privileged commands on their own devices.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21065</link><description>Improper input validation in Retail Mode prior to version 5.59.11 allows self attackers to execute privileged commands on their own devices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21066 | Out-of-bounds read in the SPI decoder in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.30.63 allows local attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21066</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in the SPI decoder in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.30.63 allows local attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21067 | Out-of-bounds read in the allocation of image buffer in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.30.63 allows local attackers to access out-of-bou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21067</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in the allocation of image buffer in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.30.63 allows local attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21068 | Out-of-bounds read in the reading of image data in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.30.63 allows local attackers to access out-of-bounds m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21068</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in the reading of image data in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.30.63 allows local attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21069 | Out-of-bounds read in the parsing of image data in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.30.63 allows local attackers to access out-of-bounds m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21069</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in the parsing of image data in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.30.63 allows local attackers to access out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21070 | Out-of-bounds write in the SPI decoder in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.30.63 allows local attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21070</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in the SPI decoder in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.30.63 allows local attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62292 | In SonarQube before 25.6, 2025.3 Commercial, and 2025.1.3 LTA, authenticated low-privileged users can query the /api/v2/users-management/use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62292</link><description>In SonarQube before 25.6, 2025.3 Commercial, and 2025.1.3 LTA, authenticated low-privileged users can query the /api/v2/users-management/users endpoint and obtain user fields intended for administrators only, including the email addresses of other accounts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10124 | Booking Manager &amp;lt; 2.1.15 - Contributor+ Booking Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10124</link><description>The Booking Manager  WordPress plugin before 2.1.15 registers a shortcode that deletes bookings and makes that shortcode available to anyone with contributor and above privileges. When a page containing the shortcode is visited, the bookings are deleted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 06:16:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11569 | All versions of the package cross-zip are vulnerable to Directory Traversal via consecutive usage of zipSync() and unzipSync () functions th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11569</link><description>All versions of the package cross-zip are vulnerable to Directory Traversal via consecutive usage of zipSync() and unzipSync () functions that allow arguments such as __dirname. An attacker can access system files by selectively doing zip/unzip operations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 05:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11570 | Versions of the package drupal-pattern-lab/unified-twig-extensions from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) due to insufficie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11570</link><description>Versions of the package drupal-pattern-lab/unified-twig-extensions from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) due to insufficient filtering of data.&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;This is exploitable only if the code is executed outside of Drupal; the function is intended to be shared between Drupal and Pattern Lab.&#13;&#13;The package drupal-pattern-lab/unified-twig-extensions is unmaintained, the fix for this issue exists in version 1.1.1 of [drupal/unified_twig_ext](https://www.drupal.org/project/unified_twig_ext)</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 05:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61871 | NAS Navigator2 Windows version by BUFFALO INC. registers a Windows service with an unquoted file path. A user with the write permission on t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61871</link><description>NAS Navigator2 Windows version by BUFFALO INC. registers a Windows service with an unquoted file path. A user with the write permission on the root directory of the system drive may execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privilege.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:56:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11449 | Reflected Cross Site Scripting in ServiceNow AI Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11449</link><description>ServiceNow has addressed a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability that was identified in the ServiceNow AI Platform. This vulnerability could result in arbitrary code being executed within the browsers of ServiceNow users who click on a specially crafted link.   





ServiceNow has addressed this vulnerability by deploying a relevant security update to the majority of hosted instances.  Relevant security updates also have been provided to ServiceNow self-hosted customers, partners, and hosted customers with unique configuration. Further, the vulnerability is addressed in the listed patches and hot fixes. We recommend customers promptly apply appropriate updates or upgrade if they have not already done so.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11450 | Reflected Cross Site Scripting in ServiceNow AI Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11450</link><description>ServiceNow has addressed a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability that was identified in the ServiceNow AI Platform. This vulnerability could result in arbitrary code being executed within the browsers of ServiceNow users who click on a specially crafted link.  

ServiceNow has addressed this vulnerability by deploying a relevant security update to the majority of hosted instances.  Relevant security updates also have been provided to ServiceNow self-hosted customers, partners, and hosted customers with unique configurations. Further, the vulnerability is addressed in the listed patches and hot fixes. We recommend customers promptly apply appropriate updates or upgrade if they have not already done so.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61928 | Better Auth: Unauthenticated API key creation through api-key plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61928</link><description>Better Auth is an authentication and authorization library for TypeScript. In versions prior to 1.3.26, unauthenticated attackers can create or modify API keys for any user by passing that user's id in the request body to the `api/auth/api-key/create` route. `session?.user ?? (authRequired ? null : { id: ctx.body.userId })`. When no session exists but `userId` is present in the request body, `authRequired` becomes false and the user object is set to the attacker-controlled ID. Server-only field validation only executes when `authRequired` is true (lines 280-295), allowing attackers to set privileged fields. No additional authentication occurs before the database operation, so the malicious payload is accepted. The same pattern exists in the update endpoint. This is a critical authentication bypass enabling full an unauthenticated attacker can generate an API key for any user and immediately gain complete authenticated access. This allows the attacker to perform any action as the victim user using the api key, potentially compromise the user data and the application depending on the victim's privileges. Version 1.3.26 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61926 | Allstar Reviewbot has Authentication Bypass via Hard-coded Webhook Secret</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61926</link><description>Allstar is a GitHub App to set and enforce security policies. In versions prior to 4.5, a vulnerability in Allstar’s Reviewbot component caused inbound webhook requests to be validated against a hard-coded, shared secret. The value used for the secret token was compiled into the Allstar binary and could not be configured at runtime. In practice, this meant that every deployment using Reviewbot would validate requests with the same secret unless the operator modified source code and rebuilt the component - an expectation that is not documented and is easy to miss. All Allstar releases prior to v4.5 that include the Reviewbot code path are affected. Deployments on v4.5 and later are not affected. Those who have not enabled or exposed the Reviewbot endpoint are not exposed to this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:28:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15047 | AVTECH CloudSetup.cgi Authenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15047</link><description>AVTECH devices that include the CloudSetup.cgi management endpoint are vulnerable to authenticated OS command injection. The `exefile` parameter in CloudSetup.cgi is passed to the underlying system command execution without proper validation or whitelisting. An authenticated attacker who can invoke this endpoint can supply crafted input to execute arbitrary system commands as root. Successful exploitation grants full control of the device, and - depending on deployment and whether the device stores credentials or has network reachability to internal systems - may enable credential theft, lateral movement, or data exfiltration. The archived SEARCH-LAB disclosure implies that this vulnerability was remediated in early 2017, but AVTECH has not defined an affected version range.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55321 | Azure Monitor Log Analytics Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55321</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59218 | Azure Entra ID Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59218</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59246 | Azure Entra ID Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59246</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59247 | Azure PlayFab Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59247</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59252 | M365 Copilot Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59252</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59271 | Redis Enterprise Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59271</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59272 | Copilot Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59272</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59286 | Copilot Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59286</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62240 | Multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities with Calendar events in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.35 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62240</link><description>Multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities with Calendar events in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.35 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.7, 7.4 update 35 through update 92, and 7.3 update 25 through update 36 allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into a user’s (1) First Name, (2) Middle Name or (3) Last Name text field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11557 | projectworlds Gate Pass Management System add-pass.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11557</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in projectworlds Gate Pass Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /add-pass.php. Such manipulation of the argument fullname leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11558 | code-projects E-Commerce Website user_index_search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11558</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects E-Commerce Website 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /pages/user_index_search.php. Performing manipulation of the argument Search results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61783 | Python Social Auth - Django has unsafe account association</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61783</link><description>Python Social Auth is a social authentication/registration mechanism. In versions prior to 5.6.0, upon authentication, the user could be associated by e-mail even if the `associate_by_email` pipeline was not included. This could lead to account compromise when a third-party authentication service does not validate provided e-mail addresses or doesn't require unique e-mail addresses. Version 5.6.0 contains a patch. As a workaround, review the authentication service policy on e-mail addresses; many will not allow exploiting this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61779 | Trustee&amp;#x27;s attestation-policy endpoint is not protected by admin autentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61779</link><description>Confidential Containers's Trustee project contains tools and components for attesting confidential guests and providing secrets to them. In versions prior to 0.15.0, the attestation-policy endpoint didn't check if the kbs-client submitting the request was actually authenticated (had the right key). This allowed any kbs-client to actually change the attestation policy. Version 0.15.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43296 | A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26. An app may bypass Gatekeeper checks.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43296</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26. An app may bypass Gatekeeper checks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60375 | The authentication mechanism in Perfex CRM before 3.3.1 allows attackers to bypass login credentials due to insufficient server-side validat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60375</link><description>The authentication mechanism in Perfex CRM before 3.3.1 allows attackers to bypass login credentials due to insufficient server-side validation. By sending empty username and password parameters in the login request, an attacker can gain unauthorized access to user accounts, including administrative accounts, without providing valid credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61773 | pyLoad CNL and captcha handlers allow code Injection via unsanitized parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61773</link><description>pyLoad is a free and open-source download manager written in Python. In versions prior to 0.5.0b3.dev91, pyLoad web interface contained insufficient input validation in both the Captcha script endpoint and the Click'N'Load (CNL) Blueprint. This flaw allowed untrusted user input to be processed unsafely, which could be exploited by an attacker to inject arbitrary content into the web UI or manipulate request handling. The vulnerability could lead to client-side code execution (XSS) or other unintended behaviors when a malicious payload is submitted. user-supplied parameters from HTTP requests were not adequately validated or sanitized before being passed into the application logic and response generation. This allowed crafted input to alter the expected execution flow. CNL (Click'N'Load) blueprint exposed unsafe handling of untrusted parameters in HTTP requests. The application did not consistently enforce input validation or encoding, making it possible for an attacker to craft malicious requests. Version 0.5.0b3.dev91 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34248 | D-Link Nuclias Connect &amp;lt; v1.3.1.4 Directory Traversal to Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34248</link><description>D-Link Nuclias Connect firmware versions &lt; 1.3.1.4 contain a directory traversal vulnerability within /api/web/dnc/global/database/deleteBackup due to improper sanitization of the deleteBackupList parameter. This can allow an authenticated attacker to delete arbitrary files impacting the integrity and availability of the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61602 | BigBlueButton vulnerable to Chat DoS via invalid reactionEmojiId</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61602</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom. A denial-of-service (DoS) vulnerability in versions prior to 3.0.13 allows any authenticated user to crash the chat functionality for all participants in a meeting by sending a malformed `reactionEmojiId` in the GraphQL mutation `chatSendMessageReaction`. Version 3.0.13 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11555 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System calendar_of_events.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11555</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/calendar_of_events.php. The manipulation of the argument date_start results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11556 | code-projects Simple Leave Manager user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11556</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Simple Leave Manager 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /user.php. This manipulation of the argument table causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61601 | BigBlueButton vulnerable to DoS via PollSubmitVote GraphQL mutation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61601</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom. A Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in versions prior to 3.0.13 allows any authenticated user to freeze or crash the entire server by abusing the polling feature's `Choices` response type. By submitting a malicious payload with a massive array in the `answerIds` field, the attacker can cause the current meeting — and potentially all meetings on the server — to become unresponsive. Version 3.0.13 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35050 | Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) .NET unauthenticated deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35050</link><description>Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) accepts serialized .NET data via the '/remoteweb/remote.rem' endpoint, allowing a remote, unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code with 'NT AUTHORITY\NetworkService' privileges. The vulnerable endpoint is used by Newforma Project Center Server (NPCS), so a compromised NIX system can be used to attack an associated NPCS system. To mitigate this vulnerability, restrict network access to the '/remoteweb/remote.rem' endpoint, for example using the IIS URL Rewrite Module.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35051 | Newforma Project Center Server (NPCS) .NET unauthenticated deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35051</link><description>Newforma Project Center Server (NPCS) accepts serialized .NET data via the '/ProjectCenter.rem' endpoint on 9003/tcp, allowing a remote, unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code with 'NT AUTHORITY\NetworkService' privileges. According to the recommended architecture, the vulnerable NPCS endpoint is only accessible on an internal network. To mitigate this vulnerability, restrict network access to NPCS.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35052 | Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) shared hard-coded secret key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35052</link><description>Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) uses a hard-coded key to encrypt certain query parameters. Some encrypted parameter values can specify paths to download files, potentially bypassing authentication and authorization, for example, the 'qs' parameter used in '/DownloadWeb/download.aspx'. This key is shared across NIX installations. NIX 2023.3 and 2024.1 limit the use of hard-coded keys.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35053 | Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) arbitrary file read and delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35053</link><description>Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) accepts requests to '/UserWeb/Common/MarkupServices.ashx' specifying the 'DownloadExportedPDF' command that allow an authenticated user to read and delete arbitrary files with 'NT AUTHORITY\NetworkService' privileges.

In Newforma before 2023.1, anonymous access is enabled by default (CVE-2025-35062), allowing an otherwise unauthenticated attacker to effectively authenticate as 'anonymous' and exploit this file upload vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35054 | Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) insufficiently protected credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35054</link><description>Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) stores credentials  used to configure NPCS in 'HKLM\Software\WOW6432Node\Newforma\\Credentials'. The credentials are encrypted but the encryption key is stored in the same registry location. Authenticated users can access both the credentials and the encryption key. If these are Active Directory credentials, an attacker may be able to gain access to additional systems and resources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35055 | Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) insecure file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35055</link><description>Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) '/UserWeb/Common/UploadBlueimp.ashx' allows an authenticated attacker to upload an arbitrary file to any location writable by the NIX application. An attacker can upload and run a web shell or other content executable by the web server. An attacker can also delete directories.  In Newforma before 2023.1, anonymous access is enabled by default (CVE-2025-35062), allowing an otherwise unauthenticated attacker to effectively authenticate as 'anonymous' and exploit this file upload vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35056 | Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) limited file read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35056</link><description>Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) '/UserWeb/Common/MarkupServices.ashx' 'StreamStampImage' accepts an encrypted file path and returns an image of the specified file. An authenticated attacker can read arbitrary files subject to the privileges of NIX, typically 'NT AUTHORITY\NetworkService', and the ability of StreamStampImage to process the file. The encrypted file path can be generated using the shared, hard-coded secret key described in CVE-2025-35052. This vulnerability cannot be exploited as an 'anonymous' user as described in CVE-2025-35062.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35057 | Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) forced NTLMv2 authentication via /RemoteWeb/IntegrationServices.ashx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35057</link><description>Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) '/RemoteWeb/IntegrationServices.ashx' allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to cause NIX to make an SMB connection to an attacker-controlled system. The attacker can capture the NTLMv2 hash of the NIX service account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35058 | Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) forced NTLMv2 authentication via /UserWeb/Common/MarkupServices.ashx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35058</link><description>Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) '/UserWeb/Common/MarkupServices.ashx' allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to cause NIX to make an SMB connection to an attacker-controlled system. The attacker can capture the NTLMv2 hash of the customer-configured NIX service account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35059 | Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) open URL redirect via /DownloadWeb/hyperlinkredirect.aspx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35059</link><description>Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) '/DownloadWeb/hyperlinkredirect.aspx' provides an unauthenticated URL redirect via the 'nhl' parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35060 | Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) stored XSS via SVG file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35060</link><description>Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) provides a 'Send a File Transfer' feature that allows a remote, authenticated attacker to upload SVG files that contain JavaScript or other content that may be executed or rendered by a web browser using a mobile user agent.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35061 | Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) forced NTLMv2 authentication via /NPCSRemoteWeb/LegacyIntegrationServices.asmx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35061</link><description>Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) '/NPCSRemoteWeb/LegacyIntegrationServices.asmx' allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to cause NIX to make an SMB connection to an attacker-controlled system. The attacker can capture the NTLMv2 hash of the user-configured NIX service account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35062 | Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) default anonymous access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35062</link><description>Newforma Info Exchange (NIX) before version 2023.1 by default allows anonymous authentication which allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit additional vulnerabilities that require authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11554 | Portabilis i-Educar User Type AccessLevelController.php insecure inherited permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11554</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.9.10. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file app/Http/Controllers/AccessLevelController.php of the component User Type Handler. The manipulation leads to insecure inherited permissions. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11553 | code-projects Courier Management System add-courier.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11553</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Courier Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /add-courier.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Shippername can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 19:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60316 | SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in admin/view_customer.php via the ID parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60316</link><description>SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in admin/view_customer.php via the ID parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 19:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11552 | code-projects Online Complaint Site category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11552</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Online Complaint Site 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/category.php. Such manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 19:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59146 | New API has Authenticated Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59146</link><description>New API is a large language mode (LLM) gateway and artificial intelligence (AI) asset management system. An authenticated Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 0.9.0.5. A feature within the application allows authenticated users to submit a URL for the server to process its content. The application fails to properly validate this user-supplied URL before making a server-side request. This vulnerability is not limited to image URLs and can be triggered with any link provided to the vulnerable endpoint. Since user registration is often enabled by default, any registered user can exploit this. By crafting a malicious URL, an attacker can coerce the server to send requests to arbitrary internal or external services. The vulnerability has been patched in version 0.9.0.5. The patch introduces a comprehensive, user-configurable SSRF protection module, which is enabled by default to protect server security. This new feature provides administrators with granular control over outbound requests made by the server. For users who cannot upgrade immediately, some temporary mitigation options are available. Enable new-api image processing worker (new-api-worker) and/or configure egress firewall rules.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 19:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55200 | BigBlueButton vulnerable to Stored XSS via name of user at Shared Notes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55200</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom. In versions prior to 3.0.13, the "Shared Notes" feature contains a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability with the input location being the "Username" field and the output location on the "Shared Notes" page, when a user with a malicious username is editing content. This vulnerability allows a low-privileged user to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of higher-privileged users (e.g., Admins) who open the Shared Notes page. Version 3.0.13 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4615 | PAN-OS: Improper Neutralization of Input in the Management Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4615</link><description>An improper input neutralization vulnerability in the management web interface of the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS® software enables an authenticated administrator to bypass system restrictions and execute arbitrary commands.

The security risk posed by this issue is significantly minimized when CLI access is restricted to a limited group of administrators.

Cloud NGFW and Prisma® Access are not affected by this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4614 | PAN-OS: Session Token Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4614</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS® software enables an authenticated administrator to view session tokens of users authenticated to the firewall web UI. This may allow impersonation of users whose session tokens are leaked.  

The security risk posed by this issue is significantly minimized when CLI access is restricted to a limited group of administrators.

Cloud NGFW and Prisma® Access are not affected by this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11550 | Tenda W12 HTTP Request modules wifiScheduledSet null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11550</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W12 3.0.0.6(3948). The impacted element is the function wifiScheduledSet of the file /goform/modules of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument wifiScheduledSet results in null pointer dereference. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11551 | code-projects Student Result Manager Database.java sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11551</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Student Result Manager 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file src/students/Database.java. This manipulation of the argument roll/name/gpa causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11573 | Denial of Service issue in Amazon.IonDotnet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11573</link><description>An infinite loop issue in Amazon.IonDotnet library versions &lt;v1.3.2 may allow a threat actor to cause a denial of service through a specially crafted text input.

To mitigate this issue, users should upgrade to version v1.3.2. As of August 20, 2025, this library has been deprecated and will not receive further updates.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60267 | In xckk v9.6, there is a SQL injection vulnerability in which the cond parameter in notice/list is not securely filtered, resulting in a SQL...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60267</link><description>In xckk v9.6, there is a SQL injection vulnerability in which the cond parameter in notice/list is not securely filtered, resulting in a SQL injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20203 | NetSarang v5.0 Malicious Backdoor Supply Chain Compromise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20203</link><description>NetSarang Xmanager Enterprise 5.0 Build 1232, Xmanager 5.0 Build 1045, Xshell 5.0 Build 1322, Xftp 5.0 Build 1218, and Xlpd 5.0 Build 1220 contain a malicious nssock2.dll that implements a multi-stage, DNS-based backdoor. The dormant library contacts a C2 DNS server via a specially crafted TXT record for a month‑generated domain. After receiving a decryption key, it then downloads and executes arbitrary code, creates an encrypted virtual file system (VFS) in the registry, and grants the attacker full remote code execution, data exfiltration, and persistence. NetSarang released builds for each product line that remediated the compromise: Xmanager Enterprise Build 1236, Xmanager Build 1049, Xshell Build 1326, Xftp Build 1222, and Xlpd Build 1224. Kaspersky Lab identified an instance of exploitation in the wild in August 2017.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:25:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11549 | Tenda W12 HTTP Request modules wifiMacFilterSet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11549</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda W12 3.0.0.6(3948). The affected element is the function wifiMacFilterSet of the file /goform/modules of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11371 | Gladinet CentreStack and TrioFox Local File Inclusion Flaw</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11371</link><description>In the default installation and configuration of Gladinet CentreStack and TrioFox, there is an unauthenticated Local File Inclusion Flaw that allows unintended disclosure of system files. Exploitation of this vulnerability has been observed in the wild. 

This issue impacts Gladinet CentreStack and Triofox: All versions prior to and including 16.7.10368.56560</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:01:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60266 | In xckk v9.6, there is a SQL injection vulnerability in which the orderBy parameter in address/list is not securely filtered, resulting in a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60266</link><description>In xckk v9.6, there is a SQL injection vulnerability in which the orderBy parameter in address/list is not securely filtered, resulting in a SQL injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60304 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the Subject Description field.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60304</link><description>code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the Subject Description field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59998 | Junos Space: Archive Logs screen is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59998</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the Archive Log screen that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.
This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59999 | Junos Space: API Access Profiles page is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59999</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the API Access Profiles page that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.
This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60000 | Junos Space: Generate Report page is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60000</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the Generate Report page that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.
This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60001 | Junos Space: Create Quick Template page is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60001</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the Generate Report page that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.
This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60002 | Junos Space: Template Definitions page is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60002</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the Template Definitions page that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.
This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60004 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Specific BGP EVPN update message causes rpd crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60004</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the routing protocol daemon (rpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial-Of-Service (DoS).

When an affected system receives a specific BGP EVPN update message over an established BGP session, this causes an rpd crash and restart.

A BGP EVPN configuration is not necessary to be vulnerable. If peers are not configured to send BGP EVPN updates to a vulnerable device, then this issue can't occur.

This issue affects iBGP and eBGP, over IPv4 and IPv6.


This issue affects:
Junos OS:
  *  23.4 versions from 

23.4R2-S3 before 23.4R2-S5,
  *  24.2 versions from 

24.2R2 

before 24.2R2-S1,
  *  24.4 versions before 24.4R1-S3, 24.4R2;



Junos OS Evolved:
  *  23.4-EVO versions from 23.4R2-S2-EVO before 23.4R2-S5-EVO,
  *  24.2-EVO versions from 24.2R2-EVO before 24.2R2-S1-EVO,
  *  24.4-EVO versions before 24.4R1-S3-EVO, 24.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60006 | Junos OS Evolved: OS command injection vulnerabilities fixed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60006</link><description>Multiple instances of an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') 

vulnerability in the CLI of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved could be used to elevate privileges and/or execute unauthorized commands.

When an attacker executes crafted CLI commands, the options are processed via a script in some cases. These scripts are not hardened so injected commands might be executed via the shell, which allows an attacker to perform operations, which they should not be able to do according to their assigned permissions.

This issue affects Junos OS Evolved:



  *  24.2 versions before 24.2R2-S2-EVO,
  *  24.4 versions before 24.4R2-EVO.




This issue does not affect Junos OS Evolved versions earlier than 24.2R1-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60009 | Junos Space: CLI Configlet page is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60009</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the 

CLI Configlet

 page that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.

This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60010 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Device allows login for user with expired password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60010</link><description>A password aging vulnerability in the RADIUS client of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an authenticated, network-based attacker to access the device without enforcing the required password change.

Affected devices allow logins by users for whom the RADIUS server has responded with a reject and required the user to change the password as their password was expired. Therefore the policy mandating the password change is not enforced.
This does not allow users to login with a wrong password, but only with the correct but expired one.




This issue affects:

Junos OS: 



  *  all versions before 22.4R3-S8,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2-S4,
  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R2-S5,
  *  24.2 versions before 24.2R2-S1,
  *  24.4 versions before 24.4R1-S3, 24.4R2;




Junos OS Evolved:



  *  all versions before 22.4R3-S8-EVO,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2-S4-EVO,
  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R2-S5-EVO,
  *  24.2 versions before 24.2R2-S1-EVO,
  *  24.4 versions before 24.4R1-S3-EVO, 24.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59978 | Junos Space: Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in web application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59978</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to store script tags directly in web pages that, when viewed by another user, enable the attacker to execute commands with the target's administrative permissions.
This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59980 | Junos OS: When a user with the name ftp or anonymous is configured unauthenticated filesystem access is allowed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59980</link><description>An Authentication Bypass by Primary Weakness

in the FTP server of Juniper Networks Junos OS allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to get limited read-write access to files on the device.
When the FTP server is enabled and a user named "ftp" or "anonymous" is configured, that user can login without providing the configured password and then has read-write access to their home directory.

This issue affects Junos OS: 



  *  all versions before 22.4R3-S8,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2-S3,
  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59981 | Junos Space: Device Template Definition page is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59981</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the Device Template Definition page that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59982 | Junos Space: Dashboard Search field is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59982</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the dashboard search field that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59983 | Junos Space: Template Definition page is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59983</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the  Template Definition page, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59984 | Junos Space: Global Search is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59984</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in Global Search that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59985 | Junos Space: Purging Policy field is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59985</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in a field on the Purging Policy page that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59986 | Junos Space: Input fields in Model Devices are vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59986</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the input fields in Model Devices that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59987 | Junos Space: The arbitrary device search field is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59987</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the arbitrary device search field that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59988 | Junos Space: Generate Report page is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59988</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the Generate Report page that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.
This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59989 | Junos Space: Device Discovery page is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59989</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the Device Discovery page that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.
This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59990 | Junos Space: Template creation pages are vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59990</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the template creation pages that, when visited by another user, enable the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.
This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59991 | Junos Space: Device Management pages are vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59991</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the Device Management pages that, when visited by another user, enable the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.
This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59992 | Junos Space: Secure Console page is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59992</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the Secure Console page that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.
This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59993 | Junos Space: Space Node Setting fields are vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59993</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the Space Node Setting fields that, when visited by another user, enable the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.
This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59994 | Junos Space: Quick Template page is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59994</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the Quick Template page that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.
This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59995 | Junos Space: Template creation through Definition is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59995</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the Quick Template page that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.
This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59996 | Junos Space: Configuration View page is vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59996</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the Configuration View page that, when visited by another user, enables the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.
This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59997 | Junos Space: Fields in the CLI Configlets are vulnerable to reflected cross-site script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59997</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an attacker to inject script tags in the CLI Configlets pages that, when visited by another user, enable the attacker to execute commands with the target's permissions, including an administrator.
This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59974 | Junos Space Security Director: Persistent Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59974</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Junos Space Security Director allows an attacker to inject malicious scripts into the application, which are then stored and executed in the context of other users' browsers when they access affected pages.This issue affects Juniper Security Director: 

  *  All versions before 24.1R4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59975 | Junos Space: Flooding device with inbound API calls leads to WebUI and CLI management access DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59975</link><description>An Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in the HTTP daemon (httpd) of Juniper Networks Junos Space allows an unauthenticated network-based attacker flooding the device with inbound API calls to consume all resources on the system, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS).

After continuously flooding the system with inbound connection requests, all available file handles become consumed, blocking access to the system via SSH and the web user interface (WebUI), resulting in a management interface DoS. A manual reboot of the system is required to restore functionality.

This issue affects Junos Space: 
  *  all versions before 22.2R1 Patch V3, 
  *  from 23.1 before 23.1R1 Patch V3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59976 | Junos Space: Arbitrary file download vulnerability in web interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59976</link><description>An arbitrary file download vulnerability in the web interface of Juniper Networks Junos Space allows a network-based authenticated attacker using a crafted GET method to access any file on the file system. Using specially crafted GET methods, an attacker can gain access to files beyond the file path normally allowed by the JBoss daemon. These files could contain sensitive information restricted from access by low-privileged users.This issue affects all versions of Junos Space before 24.1R3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59967 | Junos OS Evolved: ACX7024, ACX7024X, ACX7100-32C,  ACX7100-48L, ACX7348, ACX7509: When specific valid multicast traffic is received on the L3 interface on a vulnerable device evo-pfemand crashes and restarts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59967</link><description>A NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in the PFE management daemon (evo-pfemand) of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved on ACX7024, ACX7024X, ACX7100-32C, ACX7100-48L, ACX7348, ACX7509 devices allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a 

Denial-of-Service (DoS).

Whenever specific valid multicast traffic is received on any layer 3 interface the evo-pfemand process crashes and restarts.

Continued receipt of specific valid multicast traffic results in a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) attack. 
This issue affects Junos OS Evolved on ACX7024, ACX7024X, ACX7100-32C, ACX7100-48L, ACX7348, ACX7509: 



  *  from 23.2R2-EVO before 23.2R2-S4-EVO, 
  *  from 23.4R1-EVO before 23.4R2-EVO.


This issue affects IPv4 and IPv6. 

This issue does not affect  Junos OS Evolved ACX7024, ACX7024X, ACX7100-32C, ACX7100-48L, ACX7348, ACX7509 versions before 23.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:00:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59968 | Junos Space Security Director: Insufficient authorization for sensitive resources in web interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59968</link><description>A Missing Authorization vulnerability in the Juniper Networks Junos Space Security Director allows an unauthenticated network-based attacker to read or modify metadata via the web interface. 




Tampering with this metadata can result in managed SRX Series devices permitting network traffic that should otherwise be blocked by policy, effectively bypassing intended security controls.



This issue affects Junos Space Security Director 
  *   all versions prior to 24.1R3 Patch V4


This issue does not affect managed cSRX Series devices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:00:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10281 | Insecure URL Handling in git_clone Leading to Leaked API Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10281</link><description>BBOT's git_clone module could be abused to disclose a GitHub API key to an attacker controlled server with a malicious formatted git URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10282 | GitLab Domain Confusion in gitlab Leaks API Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10282</link><description>BBOT's gitlab module could be abused to disclose a GitLab API key to an attacker controlled server with a malicious formatted git URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10283 | Improper .git Sanitization in gitdumper Enables RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10283</link><description>BBOT's gitdumper module could be abused to execute commands through a malicious git repository.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10284 | Improper Archive Extraction in unarchive Enables RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10284</link><description>BBOT's unarchive module could be abused by supplying malicious archives files and when extracted can then perform an arbitrary file write, resulting in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11198 | Security Director Policy Enforcer: An unrestricted API allows a network-based unauthenticated attacker to deploy malicious vSRX images to VMWare NSX Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11198</link><description>A Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in Juniper Networks Security Director Policy Enforcer allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to replace legitimate vSRX images with malicious ones.



If a trusted user initiates deployment, Security Director Policy Enforcer will deliver the attacker's uploaded image to VMware NSX instead of a legitimate one.





This issue affects Security Director Policy Enforcer:  



  *  All versions before 23.1R1 Hotpatch v3.


This issue does not affect Junos Space Security Director Insights.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52960 | Junos OS: SRX Series and MX Series: Receipt of specific SIP packets in a high utilization situation causes a flowd crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52960</link><description>A Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input vulnerability in the 

Session Initialization Protocol (SIP) ALG of Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series and SRX Series allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

When memory utilization is high, and specific SIP packets are received, flowd crashes. While the system recovers automatically, the disruption can significantly impact service stability. Continuous receipt of these specific SIP packets, while high utilization is present, will cause a sustained DoS condition. The utilization is outside the attackers control, so they would not be able to deterministically exploit this.
This issue affects Junos OS on SRX Series and MX Series: 


  *  All versions before 22.4R3-S7,
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-S4, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R2-S5, 
  *  from 24.2 before 24.2R2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52961 | Junos OS Evolved: PTX Series except PTX10003: An unauthenticated adjacent attacker sending specific valid traffic can cause a memory leak in cfmman leading to FPC crash and restart</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52961</link><description>An Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in the Connectivity Fault Management (CFM) daemon and the Connectivity Fault Management Manager (cfmman) of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved on PTX10001-36MR, PTX10002-36QDD, PTX10004, PTX10008, PTX10016  allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).

An attacker on an adjacent device sending specific valid traffic can cause cfmd to spike the CPU to 100% and cfmman's memory to leak, eventually to cause the FPC crash and restart.

Continued receipt and processes of these specific valid packets will sustain the Denial of Service (DoS) condition.

An indicator of compromise is to watch for an increase in cfmman memory rising over time by issuing the following command and evaluating the RSS number. If the RSS is growing into GBs then consider restarting the device to temporarily clear memory.
 
  user@device&gt; show system processes node fpc detail | match cfmman

Example: 

  show system processes node fpc0 detail | match cfmman 
  F S UID        PID       PPID  PGID   SID   C PRI  NI  ADDR SZ    WCHAN    RSS     PSR STIME TTY          TIME     CMD
  4 S root      15204     1    15204  15204  0  80  0   - 90802     -      113652   4  Sep25 ?           00:15:28 /usr/bin/cfmman -p /var/pfe -o -c /usr/conf/cfmman-cfg-active.xml
This issue affects Junos OS Evolved on PTX10001-36MR, PTX10002-36QDD, PTX10004, PTX10008, PTX10016:

  *  from 23.2R1-EVO before 23.2R2-S4-EVO, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R2-S4-EVO, 
  *  from 24.2 before 24.2R2-EVO, 
  *  from 24.4 before 24.4R1-S2-EVO, 24.4R2-EVO.


This issue does not affect Junos OS Evolved on PTX10001-36MR, PTX10002-36QDD, PTX10004, PTX10008, PTX10016  before 23.2R1-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59957 | Junos OS: EX4600 Series and QFX5000 Series: An attacker with physical access can open a persistent backdoor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59957</link><description>An Origin Validation Error vulnerability in an insufficient protected file of Juniper Networks Junos OS on EX4600 Series and QFX5000 Series allows an unauthenticated attacker with physical access to the device to create a backdoor which allows complete control of the system.

When a device isn't configured with a root password, an attacker can modify a specific file. It's contents will be added to the Junos configuration of the device without being visible. This allows for the addition of any configuration unknown 

to the actual operator, which includes users, IP addresses and other configuration which could allow unauthorized access to the device.
This exploit is persistent across reboots and even zeroization.

The indicator of compromise is a modified /etc/config/-defaults[-flex].conf file. Review that file for unexpected configuration statements, or compare it to an unmodified version which can be extracted from the original Juniper software image file. For details on the extraction procedure please contact Juniper Technical Assistance Center (JTAC).

To restore the device to a trusted initial configuration the system needs to be reinstalled from physical media. 

This issue affects Junos OS on EX4600 Series and QFX5000 Series:



  *  All versions before 21.4R3,
  *  22.2 versions before 22.2R3-S3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59958 | Junos OS Evolved: PTX Series: When a firewall filter rejects traffic these packets are erroneously sent to the RE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59958</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved on PTX Series allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause impact to confidentiality and availability.

When an output firewall filter is configured with one or more terms where the action is 'reject', packets matching these terms are erroneously sent to the Routing Engine (RE) and further processed there. Processing of these packets will consume limited RE resources. Also responses from the RE back to the source of this traffic could reveal confidential information about the affected device.
This issue only applies to firewall filters applied to WAN or revenue interfaces, so not the mgmt or lo0 interface of the routing-engine, nor any input filters.

This issue affects Junos OS Evolved on PTX Series:



  *  all versions before 22.4R3-EVO,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59962 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: With BGP sharding enabled, change in indirect next-hop can cause RPD crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59962</link><description>An Access of Uninitialized Pointer vulnerability in the routing protocol daemon (rpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved with BGP sharding configured allows an attacker triggering indirect next-hop updates, along with timing outside the attacker's control, to cause rpd to crash and restart, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS).

With BGP sharding enabled, triggering route resolution of an indirect next-hop (e.g., an IGP route change over which a BGP route gets resolved), may cause rpd to crash and restart. An attacker causing continuous IGP route churn, resulting in repeated route re-resolution, will increase the likelihood of triggering this issue, leading to a potentially extended DoS condition.

This issue affects:

Junos OS:



  *  all versions before 21.4R3-S6, 
  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R3-S6, 
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S3, 
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S3, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2; 




Junos OS Evolved: 



  *  all versions before 22.3R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-EVO, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-EVO.




Versions before Junos OS 21.3R1 and Junos OS Evolved 21.3R1-EVO are unaffected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59964 | Junos OS: SRX4700: When forwarding-options sampling is enabled any traffic destined to the RE will cause the forwarding line card to crash and restart</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59964</link><description>A Use of Uninitialized Resource vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX4700 devices allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

When forwarding-options sampling is enabled, receipt of any traffic destined to the Routing Engine (RE) by the PFE line card leads to an FPC crash and restart, resulting in a Denial of Service (DoS). 

Continued receipt and processing of any traffic leading to the RE by the PFE line card will create a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition to the PFE line card.


This issue affects Junos OS on SRX4700: 



  *  from 24.4 before 24.4R1-S3, 24.4R2


This issue affects IPv4 and IPv6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60265 | In xckk v9.6, there is a SQL injection vulnerability in which the orderBy parameter in user/list is not securely filtered, resulting in a SQ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60265</link><description>In xckk v9.6, there is a SQL injection vulnerability in which the orderBy parameter in user/list is not securely filtered, resulting in a SQL injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56426 | An issue WebKul Bagisto v.2.3.6 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Cart/Checkout API endpoint, specifically, the pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56426</link><description>An issue WebKul Bagisto v.2.3.6 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Cart/Checkout API endpoint, specifically, the price calculation logic fails to validate quantity inputs properly.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60302 | code-projects Client Details System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). When adding customer information, the client details sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60302</link><description>code-projects Client Details System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). When adding customer information, the client details system fills in malicious JavaScript code in the username field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61532 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in SVX Portal v.2.7A to execute arbitrary code via the TG parameter on last_heard_page.php component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61532</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in SVX Portal v.2.7A to execute arbitrary code via the TG parameter on last_heard_page.php component</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61577 | D-Link DIR-816A2_FWv1.10CNB05 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the statuscheckpppoeuser parameter in the dir_setWanWifi functi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61577</link><description>D-Link DIR-816A2_FWv1.10CNB05 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the statuscheckpppoeuser parameter in the dir_setWanWifi function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32916 | Sensitive form data in URL query parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32916</link><description>Potential use of sensitive information in GET requests in Checkmk GmbH's Checkmk versions &lt;2.4.0p13, &lt;2.3.0p38, &lt;2.2.0p46, and 2.1.0 (EOL) may cause sensitive form data to be included in URL query parameters, which may be logged in various places such as browser history or web server logs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32919 | Privilege Escalation in Windows License plugin for Checkmk Windows Agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32919</link><description>Use of an insecure temporary directory in the Windows License plugin for the Checkmk Windows Agent allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Checkmk: from 2.4.0 before 2.4.0p13, from 2.3.0 before 2.3.0p38, from 2.2.0 before 2.2.0p46, and all versions of 2.1.0 (EOL).</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39664 | Path-Traversal in report scheduler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39664</link><description>Insufficient escaping in the report scheduler within Checkmk &lt;2.4.0p13, &lt;2.3.0p38, &lt;2.2.0p46 and 2.1.0 (EOL) allows authenticated attackers to define the storage location of report file pairs beyond their intended root directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:15:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56683 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /app/marketplace.html of Logseq v0.10.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56683</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /app/marketplace.html of Logseq v0.10.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via injecting arbitrary Javascript into a crafted README.md file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:15:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45095 | Lavasoft Web Companion (also known as Ad-Aware WebCompanion) versions 8.9.0.1091 through 12.1.3.1037 installs the DCIService.exe service wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45095</link><description>Lavasoft Web Companion (also known as Ad-Aware WebCompanion) versions 8.9.0.1091 through 12.1.3.1037 installs the DCIService.exe service with an unquoted service path vulnerability. An attacker with write access to the file system could potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges by placing a malicious executable in the unquoted path.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36171 | IBM Aspera Faspex denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36171</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.13.1 could allow a privileged user to cause a denial of service from improperly validated API input due to excessive resource consumption.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37401 | IBM Aspera Faspex cross-origin resource sharing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37401</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.13.1 uses a cross-domain policy file that includes domains that should not be trusted.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36225 | IBM Aspera Faspex information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36225</link><description>IBM Aspera 5.0.0 through 5.0.13.1 

could disclose sensitive user information from the system to an authenticated user due to an observable discrepancy of returned data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11561 | Sssd: sssd default kerberos configuration allows privilege escalation on ad-joined linux systems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11561</link><description>A flaw was found in the integration of Active Directory and the System Security Services Daemon (SSSD) on Linux systems. In default configurations, SSSD does not enable the Kerberos local authentication plugin (sssd_krb5_localauth_plugin), allowing an attacker with permission to modify certain AD attributes (such as userPrincipalName or samAccountName) to impersonate privileged users. This can result in unauthorized access or privilege escalation on domain-joined Linux hosts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62228 | Apache Flink CDC, Apache Flink CDC, Apache Flink CDC, Apache Flink CDC, Apache Flink CDC: SQL injection via maliciously crafted identifiers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62228</link><description>Apache Flink CDC version 3.4.0 was vulnerable to a SQL injection via maliciously crafted identifiers eg. crafted database name or crafted table name. Even through only the logged-in database user can trigger the attack, we recommend users update Flink CDC version to 3.5.0 which address this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10239 | Unintended command execution via troubleshooting scripts in Progress Flowmon</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10239</link><description>In Flowmon versions prior to 12.5.5, a vulnerability has been identified that allows a user with administrator privileges and access to the management interface to execute additional unintended commands within scripts intended for troubleshooting purposes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10240 | Possibility of unintended actions when a user clicks a malicious link in the Progress Flowmon web application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10240</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the Progress Flowmon web application prior to version 12.5.5, whereby a user who clicks a malicious link provided by an attacker may inadvertently trigger unintended actions within their authenticated session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39960 | gpiolib: acpi: initialize acpi_gpio_info struct</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39960</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

gpiolib: acpi: initialize acpi_gpio_info struct

Since commit 7c010d463372 ("gpiolib: acpi: Make sure we fill struct
acpi_gpio_info"), uninitialized acpi_gpio_info struct are passed to
__acpi_find_gpio() and later in the call stack info-&gt;quirks is used in
acpi_populate_gpio_lookup. This breaks the i2c_hid_cpi driver:

[   58.122916] i2c_hid_acpi i2c-UNIW0001:00: HID over i2c has not been provided an Int IRQ
[   58.123097] i2c_hid_acpi i2c-UNIW0001:00: probe with driver i2c_hid_acpi failed with error -22

Fix this by initializing the acpi_gpio_info pass to __acpi_find_gpio()</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 12:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39961 | iommu/amd/pgtbl: Fix possible race while increase page table level</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39961</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

iommu/amd/pgtbl: Fix possible race while increase page table level

The AMD IOMMU host page table implementation supports dynamic page table levels
(up to 6 levels), starting with a 3-level configuration that expands based on
IOVA address. The kernel maintains a root pointer and current page table level
to enable proper page table walks in alloc_pte()/fetch_pte() operations.

The IOMMU IOVA allocator initially starts with 32-bit address and onces its
exhuasted it switches to 64-bit address (max address is determined based
on IOMMU and device DMA capability). To support larger IOVA, AMD IOMMU
driver increases page table level.

But in unmap path (iommu_v1_unmap_pages()), fetch_pte() reads
pgtable-&gt;[root/mode] without lock. So its possible that in exteme corner case,
when increase_address_space() is updating pgtable-&gt;[root/mode], fetch_pte()
reads wrong page table level (pgtable-&gt;mode). It does compare the value with
level encoded in page table and returns NULL. This will result is
iommu_unmap ops to fail and upper layer may retry/log WARN_ON.

CPU 0                                         CPU 1
------                                       ------
map pages                                    unmap pages
alloc_pte() -&gt; increase_address_space()      iommu_v1_unmap_pages() -&gt; fetch_pte()
  pgtable-&gt;root = pte (new root value)
                                             READ pgtable-&gt;[mode/root]
					       Reads new root, old mode
  Updates mode (pgtable-&gt;mode += 1)

Since Page table level updates are infrequent and already synchronized with a
spinlock, implement seqcount to enable lock-free read operations on the read path.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 12:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39962 | rxrpc: Fix untrusted unsigned subtract</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39962</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

rxrpc: Fix untrusted unsigned subtract

Fix the following Smatch static checker warning:

   net/rxrpc/rxgk_app.c:65 rxgk_yfs_decode_ticket()
   warn: untrusted unsigned subtract. 'ticket_len - 10 * 4'

by prechecking the length of what we're trying to extract in two places in
the token and decoding for a response packet.

Also use sizeof() on the struct we're extracting rather specifying the size
numerically to be consistent with the other related statements.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 12:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39963 | io_uring: fix incorrect io_kiocb reference in io_link_skb</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39963</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

io_uring: fix incorrect io_kiocb reference in io_link_skb

In io_link_skb function, there is a bug where prev_notif is incorrectly
assigned using 'nd' instead of 'prev_nd'. This causes the context
validation check to compare the current notification with itself instead
of comparing it with the previous notification.

Fix by using the correct prev_nd parameter when obtaining prev_notif.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 12:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10004 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10004</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 13.12 to 18.2.8, 18.3 to 18.3.4, and 18.4 to 18.4.2 that could make the GitLab instance unresponsive or severely degraded by sending crafted GraphQL queries requesting large repository blobs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 12:51:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11340 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11340</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 18.3 to 18.3.4, 18.4 to 18.4.2 that, under certain conditions, could have allowed authenticated users with read-only API tokens to perform unauthorized write operations on vulnerability records by exploiting incorrectly scoped GraphQL mutations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 12:51:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2934 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2934</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 5.2 prior to 18.2.8, 18.3 prior to 18.3.4, and 18.4 prior to 18.4.2 that could have allowed an authenticated attacker to create a denial of service condition by configuring malicious webhook endpoints that send crafted HTTP responses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 11:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10249 | Slider Revolution &amp;lt;= 6.7.37 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10249</link><description>The Slider Revolution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data due to a missing capability check on several functions in all versions up to, and including, 6.7.37. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to install and activate plugin add-ons, create sliders, and download arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 11:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9371 | Betheme &amp;lt;= 28.1.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;page_title&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9371</link><description>The Betheme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘page_title’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 28.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping of theme breadcrumbs. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 11:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39954 | clk: sunxi-ng: mp: Fix dual-divider clock rate readback</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39954</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

clk: sunxi-ng: mp: Fix dual-divider clock rate readback

When dual-divider clock support was introduced, the P divider offset was
left out of the .recalc_rate readback function. This causes the clock
rate to become bogus or even zero (possibly due to the P divider being
1, leading to a divide-by-zero).

Fix this by incorporating the P divider offset into the calculation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 09:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39955 | tcp: Clear tcp_sk(sk)-&amp;gt;fastopen_rsk in tcp_disconnect().</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39955</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tcp: Clear tcp_sk(sk)-&gt;fastopen_rsk in tcp_disconnect().

syzbot reported the splat below where a socket had tcp_sk(sk)-&gt;fastopen_rsk
in the TCP_ESTABLISHED state. [0]

syzbot reused the server-side TCP Fast Open socket as a new client before
the TFO socket completes 3WHS:

  1. accept()
  2. connect(AF_UNSPEC)
  3. connect() to another destination

As of accept(), sk-&gt;sk_state is TCP_SYN_RECV, and tcp_disconnect() changes
it to TCP_CLOSE and makes connect() possible, which restarts timers.

Since tcp_disconnect() forgot to clear tcp_sk(sk)-&gt;fastopen_rsk, the
retransmit timer triggered the warning and the intended packet was not
retransmitted.

Let's call reqsk_fastopen_remove() in tcp_disconnect().

[0]:
WARNING: CPU: 2 PID: 0 at net/ipv4/tcp_timer.c:542 tcp_retransmit_timer (net/ipv4/tcp_timer.c:542 (discriminator 7))
Modules linked in:
CPU: 2 UID: 0 PID: 0 Comm: swapper/2 Not tainted 6.17.0-rc5-g201825fb4278 #62 PREEMPT(voluntary)
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.16.3-debian-1.16.3-2 04/01/2014
RIP: 0010:tcp_retransmit_timer (net/ipv4/tcp_timer.c:542 (discriminator 7))
Code: 41 55 41 54 55 53 48 8b af b8 08 00 00 48 89 fb 48 85 ed 0f 84 55 01 00 00 0f b6 47 12 3c 03 74 0c 0f b6 47 12 3c 04 74 04 90 &lt;0f&gt; 0b 90 48 8b 85 c0 00 00 00 48 89 ef 48 8b 40 30 e8 6a 4f 06 3e
RSP: 0018:ffffc900002f8d40 EFLAGS: 00010293
RAX: 0000000000000002 RBX: ffff888106911400 RCX: 0000000000000017
RDX: 0000000002517619 RSI: ffffffff83764080 RDI: ffff888106911400
RBP: ffff888106d5c000 R08: 0000000000000001 R09: ffffc900002f8de8
R10: 00000000000000c2 R11: ffffc900002f8ff8 R12: ffff888106911540
R13: ffff888106911480 R14: ffff888106911840 R15: ffffc900002f8de0
FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffff88907b768000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 00007f8044d69d90 CR3: 0000000002c30003 CR4: 0000000000370ef0
Call Trace:
 
 tcp_write_timer (net/ipv4/tcp_timer.c:738)
 call_timer_fn (kernel/time/timer.c:1747)
 __run_timers (kernel/time/timer.c:1799 kernel/time/timer.c:2372)
 timer_expire_remote (kernel/time/timer.c:2385 kernel/time/timer.c:2376 kernel/time/timer.c:2135)
 tmigr_handle_remote_up (kernel/time/timer_migration.c:944 kernel/time/timer_migration.c:1035)
 __walk_groups.isra.0 (kernel/time/timer_migration.c:533 (discriminator 1))
 tmigr_handle_remote (kernel/time/timer_migration.c:1096)
 handle_softirqs (./arch/x86/include/asm/jump_label.h:36 ./include/trace/events/irq.h:142 kernel/softirq.c:580)
 irq_exit_rcu (kernel/softirq.c:614 kernel/softirq.c:453 kernel/softirq.c:680 kernel/softirq.c:696)
 sysvec_apic_timer_interrupt (arch/x86/kernel/apic/apic.c:1050 (discriminator 35) arch/x86/kernel/apic/apic.c:1050 (discriminator 35))</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 09:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39956 | igc: don&amp;#x27;t fail igc_probe() on LED setup error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39956</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

igc: don't fail igc_probe() on LED setup error

When igc_led_setup() fails, igc_probe() fails and triggers kernel panic
in free_netdev() since unregister_netdev() is not called. [1]
This behavior can be tested using fault-injection framework, especially
the failslab feature. [2]

Since LED support is not mandatory, treat LED setup failures as
non-fatal and continue probe with a warning message, consequently
avoiding the kernel panic.

[1]
 kernel BUG at net/core/dev.c:12047!
 Oops: invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] SMP NOPTI
 CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 937 Comm: repro-igc-led-e Not tainted 6.17.0-rc4-enjuk-tnguy-00865-gc4940196ab02 #64 PREEMPT(voluntary)
 Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS 1.16.3-debian-1.16.3-2 04/01/2014
 RIP: 0010:free_netdev+0x278/0x2b0
 [...]
 Call Trace:
  
  igc_probe+0x370/0x910
  local_pci_probe+0x3a/0x80
  pci_device_probe+0xd1/0x200
 [...]

[2]
 #!/bin/bash -ex

 FAILSLAB_PATH=/sys/kernel/debug/failslab/
 DEVICE=0000:00:05.0
 START_ADDR=$(grep " igc_led_setup" /proc/kallsyms \
         | awk '{printf("0x%s", $1)}')
 END_ADDR=$(printf "0x%x" $((START_ADDR + 0x100)))

 echo $START_ADDR &gt; $FAILSLAB_PATH/require-start
 echo $END_ADDR &gt; $FAILSLAB_PATH/require-end
 echo 1 &gt; $FAILSLAB_PATH/times
 echo 100 &gt; $FAILSLAB_PATH/probability
 echo N &gt; $FAILSLAB_PATH/ignore-gfp-wait

 echo $DEVICE &gt; /sys/bus/pci/drivers/igc/bind</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 09:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39957 | wifi: mac80211: increase scan_ies_len for S1G</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39957</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: mac80211: increase scan_ies_len for S1G

Currently the S1G capability element is not taken into account
for the scan_ies_len, which leads to a buffer length validation
failure in ieee80211_prep_hw_scan() and subsequent WARN in
__ieee80211_start_scan(). This prevents hw scanning from functioning.
To fix ensure we accommodate for the S1G capability length.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 09:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39958 | iommu/s390: Make attach succeed when the device was surprise removed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39958</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

iommu/s390: Make attach succeed when the device was surprise removed

When a PCI device is removed with surprise hotplug, there may still be
attempts to attach the device to the default domain as part of tear down
via (__iommu_release_dma_ownership()), or because the removal happens
during probe (__iommu_probe_device()). In both cases zpci_register_ioat()
fails with a cc value indicating that the device handle is invalid. This
is because the device is no longer part of the instance as far as the
hypervisor is concerned.

Currently this leads to an error return and s390_iommu_attach_device()
fails. This triggers the WARN_ON() in __iommu_group_set_domain_nofail()
because attaching to the default domain must never fail.

With the device fenced by the hypervisor no DMAs to or from memory are
possible and the IOMMU translations have no effect. Proceed as if the
registration was successful and let the hotplug event handling clean up
the device.

This is similar to how devices in the error state are handled since
commit 59bbf596791b ("iommu/s390: Make attach succeed even if the device
is in error state") except that for removal the domain will not be
registered later. This approach was also previously discussed at the
link.

Handle both cases, error state and removal, in a helper which checks if
the error needs to be propagated or ignored. Avoid magic number
condition codes by using the pre-existing, but never used, defines for
PCI load/store condition codes and rename them to reflect that they
apply to all PCI instructions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 09:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39959 | ASoC: amd: acp: Fix incorrect retrival of acp_chip_info</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39959</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ASoC: amd: acp: Fix incorrect retrival of acp_chip_info

Use dev_get_drvdata(dev-&gt;parent) instead of dev_get_platdata(dev)
to correctly obtain acp_chip_info members in the acp I2S driver.
Previously, some members were not updated properly due to incorrect
data access, which could potentially lead to null pointer
dereferences.

This issue was missed in the earlier commit
("ASoC: amd: acp: Fix NULL pointer deref in acp_i2s_set_tdm_slot"),
which only addressed set_tdm_slot(). This change ensures that all
relevant functions correctly retrieve acp_chip_info, preventing
further null pointer dereference issues.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 09:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10862 | Popup builder with Gamification, Multi-Step Popups, Page-Level Targeting, and WooCommerce Triggers &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;id&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10862</link><description>The Popup builder with Gamification, Multi-Step Popups, Page-Level Targeting, and WooCommerce Triggers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.3. This is due to insufficient escaping on the 'id' parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 08:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11522 | Search &amp;amp; Go - Directory WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.7 - Authentication Bypass to Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11522</link><description>The Search &amp; Go - Directory WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 2.7. This is due to insufficient user validation in the search_and_go_elated_check_facebook_user() function This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to gain access to other user's accounts, including administrators, when Facebook login is enabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 07:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11539 | Arbitrary Code Execution in Grafana Image Renderer Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11539</link><description>Grafana Image Renderer is vulnerable to remote code execution due to an arbitrary file write vulnerability. This is due to the fact that the /render/csv endpoint lacked validation of the filePath parameter that allowed an attacker to save a shared object to an arbitrary location that is then loaded by the Chromium process.

Instances are vulnerable if:

1. The default token ("authToken") is not changed, or is known to the attacker.
2. The attacker can reach the image renderer endpoint.
This issue affects grafana-image-renderer: from 1.0.0 through 4.0.16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 07:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7526 | WP Travel Engine – Tour Booking Plugin – Tour Operator Software &amp;lt;= 6.6.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion via File Renaming</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7526</link><description>The WP Travel Engine – Tour Booking Plugin – Tour Operator Software plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion (via renaming) due to insufficient file path validation in the set_user_profile_image function in all versions up to, and including, 6.6.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 05:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7634 | WP Travel Engine – Tour Booking Plugin – Tour Operator Software &amp;lt;= 6.6.7 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7634</link><description>The WP Travel Engine – Tour Booking Plugin – Tour Operator Software plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 6.6.7 via the mode parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary .php files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where .php file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 05:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11530 | code-projects Online Complaint Site state.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11530</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Online Complaint Site 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /cms/admin/state.php. This manipulation of the argument state causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27039 | Detection of Error Condition Without Action in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27039</link><description>Memory corruption may occur while processing IOCTL call for DMM/WARPNCC CONFIG request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27040 | Improper Input Validation in TZ Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27040</link><description>Information disclosure may occur while processing the hypervisor log.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27041 | Buffer Over-read in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27041</link><description>Transient DOS while processing video packets received from video firmware.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27045 | Buffer Over-read in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27045</link><description>Information disclosure while processing batch command execution in Video driver.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27048 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27048</link><description>Memory corruption while processing camera platform driver IOCTL calls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27049 | Buffer Over-read in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27049</link><description>Transient DOS while processing IOCTL call for image encoding.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27053 | Incorrect Calculation of Buffer Size in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27053</link><description>Memory corruption during PlayReady APP usecase while processing TA commands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27054 | Out-of-bounds Write in Display</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27054</link><description>Memory corruption while processing a malformed license file during reboot.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27059 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in TZ Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27059</link><description>Memory corruption while performing SCM call.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27060 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in TZ Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27060</link><description>Memory corruption while performing SCM call with malformed inputs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47338 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47338</link><description>Memory corruption while processing escape commands from userspace.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47340 | Out-of-bounds Write in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47340</link><description>Memory corruption while processing IOCTL call to get the mapping.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47341 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47341</link><description>memory corruption while processing an image encoding completion event.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47342 | Use After Free in BT Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47342</link><description>Transient DOS may occur when multi-profile concurrency arises with QHS enabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47347 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow in Automotive Software platform based on QNX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47347</link><description>Memory corruption while processing control commands in the virtual memory management interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47349 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47349</link><description>Memory corruption while processing an escape call.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47351 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47351</link><description>Memory corruption while processing user buffers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47354 | Use After Free in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47354</link><description>Memory corruption while allocating buffers in DSP service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47355 | Out-of-bounds Write in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47355</link><description>Memory corruption while invoking remote procedure IOCTL calls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6038 | Lisfinity Core - Lisfinity Core plugin used for pebas® Lisfinity WordPress theme &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6038</link><description>The Lisfinity Core - Lisfinity Core plugin used for pebas® Lisfinity WordPress theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via password update in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their password. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change arbitrary user's passwords, including those of administrators.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11528 | Tenda AC7 saveAutoQos stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11528</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda AC7 15.03.06.44. This affects an unknown function of the file /goform/saveAutoQos. The manipulation of the argument enable leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11529 | ChurchCRM API Endpoint AuthMiddleware.php AuthMiddleware missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11529</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in ChurchCRM up to 5.18.0. This impacts the function AuthMiddleware of the file src/ChurchCRM/Slim/Middleware/AuthMiddleware.php of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation results in missing authentication. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The patch is identified as 3a1cffd2aea63d884025949cfbcfd274d06216a4. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11526 | Tenda AC7 WifiMacFilterSet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11526</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC7 15.03.06.44. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /goform/WifiMacFilterSet. Performing manipulation of the argument wifi_chkHz results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11527 | Tenda AC7 fast_setting_pppoe_set stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11527</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda AC7 15.03.06.44. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /goform/fast_setting_pppoe_set. Executing manipulation of the argument Password can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 03:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10496 | Cookie Notice &amp;amp; Consent &amp;lt;= 1.6.5 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10496</link><description>The Cookie Notice &amp; Consent plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the uuid parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 02:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10586 | Community Events &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10586</link><description>The Community Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘event_venue’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 02:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11166 | WP Go Maps (formerly WP Google Maps) &amp;lt;= 9.0.46 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11166</link><description>The WP Go Maps (formerly WP Google Maps) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in all versions up to, and including, 9.0.46. This is due to the plugin exposing state-changing REST actions through an AJAX bridge without proper CSRF token validation, and having destructive logic reachable via GET requests with no permission_callback. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to force logged-in administrators to create, update, or delete markers and geometry features via CSRF attacks, and allows anonymous users to trigger mass deletion of markers via unsafe GET requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 02:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11523 | Tenda AC7 AdvSetLanip command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11523</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda AC7 15.03.06.44. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/AdvSetLanip. The manipulation of the argument lanIp results in command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 02:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11524 | Tenda AC7 SetDDNSCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11524</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda AC7 15.03.06.44. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/SetDDNSCfg. This manipulation of the argument ddnsEn causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 02:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11525 | Tenda AC7 SetUpnpCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11525</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC7 15.03.06.44. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /goform/SetUpnpCfg. Such manipulation of the argument upnpEn leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 02:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11514 | code-projects Online Complaint Site index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11514</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Online Complaint Site 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /cms/users/index.php. Such manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11515 | code-projects Online Complaint Site register-complaint.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11515</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Online Complaint Site 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /cms/users/register-complaint.php. Performing manipulation of the argument cid results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11516 | code-projects Online Complaint Site complaint-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11516</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Online Complaint Site 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /cms/users/complaint-details.php. Executing manipulation of the argument cid can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>