<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 13:57:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-27134 | Excessive directory permissions in MLflow leads to local privilege escalation when using spark_udf</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27134</link><description>Excessive directory permissions in MLflow leads to local privilege escalation when using spark_udf. This behavior can be exploited by a local attacker to gain elevated permissions by using a ToCToU attack. The issue is only relevant when the spark_udf() MLflow API is called.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 13:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11403 | Out of Bounds Memory Read/Write in libjxl</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11403</link><description>There exists an out of bounds read/write in LibJXL versions prior to commit 9cc451b91b74ba470fd72bd48c121e9f33d24c99. The JPEG decoder used by the JPEG XL encoder when doing JPEG recompression (i.e. if using JxlEncoderAddJPEGFrame on untrusted input) does not properly check bounds in the presence of incomplete codes. This could lead to an out-of-bounds write. In jpegli which is released as part of the same project, the same vulnerability is present. However, the relevant buffer is part of a bigger structure, and the code makes no assumptions on the values that could be overwritten. The issue could however cause jpegli to read uninitialised memory, or addresses of functions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11498 | Resource exhaustion via Stack overflow in libjxl</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11498</link><description>There exists a stack buffer overflow in libjxl. A specifically-crafted file can cause the JPEG XL decoder to use large amounts of stack space (up to 256mb is possible, maybe 512mb), potentially exhausting the stack. An attacker can craft a file that will cause excessive memory usage. We recommend upgrading past commit 65fbec56bc578b6b6ee02a527be70787bbd053b0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-12491 | Framework Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12491</link><description>Improper control of framework service permissions with possibility of some sensitive device information leakage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 10:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-12492 | Wifi information acquisition vulnerability in Framework Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12492</link><description>Improper handling of WiFi information by framework services can allow certain malicious applications to obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 10:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-33862 | Improper access control mechanism in IPP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33862</link><description>IPP software prior to v1.71 is vulnerable to default credential vulnerability. This could
lead attackers to identify and access vulnerable systems.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 09:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11664 | eNMS TGZ File controller.py multiselect_filtering path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11664</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in eNMS up to 4.2. Affected by this issue is the function multiselect_filtering of the file eNMS/controller.py of the component TGZ File Handler. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is identified as 22b0b443acca740fc83b5544165c1f53eff3f529. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 09:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-33861 | Insufficient verification of authenticity in IPP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33861</link><description>IPP software versions prior to v1.71 do not sufficiently verify the authenticity of data, in a
way that causes it to accept invalid data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 09:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-23282 | Stored Cross-site Scripting reported in Intelligent Power Manager v1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23282</link><description>Eaton Intelligent Power Manager (IPM) prior to 1.70 is vulnerable to stored Cross site scripting. The
vulnerability exists due to insufficient validation of input from certain resources by the IPM software.
The attacker would need access to the local Subnet and an administrator interaction to compromise
the system</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 08:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11663 | Codezips E-Commerce Site search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11663</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Codezips E-Commerce Site 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file search.php. The manipulation of the argument keywords leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 08:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11662 | welliamcao OpsManage API Endpoint deploy_api.py deploy_host_vars deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11662</link><description>A vulnerability was found in welliamcao OpsManage 3.0.1/3.0.2/3.0.3/3.0.4/3.0.5. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function deploy_host_vars of the file /apps/api/views/deploy_api.py of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 08:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10270 | Org.keycloak:keycloak-services: keycloak denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10270</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the Keycloak-services package. If untrusted data is passed to the SearchQueryUtils method, it could lead to a denial of service (DoS) scenario by exhausting system resources due to a Regex complexity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10451 | Org.keycloak:keycloak-quarkus-server: sensitive data exposure in keycloak build process</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10451</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. This issue occurs because sensitive runtime values, such as passwords, may be captured during the Keycloak build process and embedded as default values in bytecode, leading to unintended information disclosure. In Keycloak 26, sensitive data specified directly in environment variables during the build process is also stored as a default values, making it accessible during runtime. Indirect usage of environment variables for SPI options and Quarkus properties is also vulnerable due to unconditional expansion by PropertyMapper logic, capturing sensitive data as default values in all Keycloak versions up to 26.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10492 | Keycloak-quarkus-server: keycloak path trasversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10492</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Keycloak. A user with high privileges could read sensitive information from a Vault file that is not within the expected context. This attacker must have previous high access to the Keycloak server in order to perform resource creation, for example, an LDAP provider configuration and set up a Vault read file, which will only inform whether that file exists or not.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11661 | Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System Profile Image profile.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11661</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file profile.php of the component Profile Image Handler. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The researcher submit confuses the vulnerability class of this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9666 | Org.keycloak/keycloak-quarkus-server: keycloak proxy header handling denial-of-service (dos) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9666</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the Keycloak Server. The Keycloak Server is vulnerable to a denial of service (DoS) attack due to improper handling of proxy headers. When Keycloak is configured to accept incoming proxy headers, it may accept non-IP values, such as obfuscated identifiers, without proper validation. This issue can lead to costly DNS resolution operations, which an attacker could exploit to tie up IO threads and potentially cause a denial of service.
The attacker must have access to send requests to a Keycloak instance that is configured to accept proxy headers, specifically when reverse proxies do not overwrite incoming headers, and Keycloak is configured to trust these headers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11660 | code-projects Farmacia usuario.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11660</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Farmacia 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file usuario.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11659 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_iperf command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11659</link><description>A vulnerability was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/network/diag_iperf. The manipulation of the argument iperf leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6538 | Openshift-console: openshift console:  server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6538</link><description>A flaw was found in OpenShift Console. A Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) attack can happen if an attacker supplies all or part of a URL to the server to query. The server is considered to be in a privileged network position and can often reach exposed services that aren't readily available to clients due to network filtering. Leveraging such an attack vector, the attacker can have an impact on other services and potentially disclose information or have other nefarious effects on the system.
The /api/dev-console/proxy/internet endpoint on the OpenShit Console allows authenticated users to have the console's pod perform arbitrary and fully controlled HTTP(s) requests. The full response to these requests is returned by the endpoint.
While the name of this endpoint suggests the requests are only bound to the internet, no such checks are in place. An authenticated user can therefore ask the console to perform arbitrary HTTP requests from outside the cluster to a service inside the cluster.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10709 | YaDisk Files &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Contributor+ Stored XSS via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10709</link><description>The YaDisk Files WordPress plugin through 1.2.5 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10710 | YaDisk Files &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10710</link><description>The YaDisk Files WordPress plugin through 1.2.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11658 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT ajax_getChannelList command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11658</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/network/ajax_getChannelList. The manipulation of the argument countryCode leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6393 | NextGEN Gallery &amp;lt; 3.59.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6393</link><description>The Photo Gallery, Sliders, Proofing and   WordPress plugin before 3.59.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its Images settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7056 | WPForms &amp;lt; 1.9.1.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7056</link><description>The WPForms  WordPress plugin before 1.9.1.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11657 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_nslookup command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11657</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/network/diag_nslookup. The manipulation of the argument diag_nslookup leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 05:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11656 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_ping6 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11656</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/network/diag_ping6. The manipulation of the argument diag_ping6 leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 05:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-11311 | Information Exposure in Kernel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11311</link><description>This record is rejected as duplicate. All references should point to CVE-2021-1904.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 04:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11655 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_pinginterface command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11655</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/network/diag_pinginterface. The manipulation of the argument diag_ping leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 04:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11654 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_traceroute6 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11654</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/network/diag_traceroute6. The manipulation of the argument diag_traceroute6 leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 04:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11483 | Automation-gateway: improper scope handling in oauth2 tokens for aap 2.5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11483</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the Ansible Automation Platform (AAP). This flaw allows attackers to escalate privileges by improperly leveraging read-scoped OAuth2 tokens to gain write access. This issue affects API endpoints that rely on ansible_base.oauth2_provider for OAuth2 authentication. While the impact is limited to actions within the user’s assigned permissions, it undermines scoped access controls, potentially allowing unintended modifications in the application and consuming services.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 04:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11653 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_traceroute command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11653</link><description>A vulnerability was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/network/diag_traceroute. The manipulation of the argument diag_traceroute leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 03:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11652 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT sn_https command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11652</link><description>A vulnerability was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/sn_package/sn_https. The manipulation of the argument https_enable leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 03:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53930 | WikiDocs before 1.0.65 allows stored XSS by authenticated users via data that comes after $$\\, which is mishandled by a KaTeX parser.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53930</link><description>WikiDocs before 1.0.65 allows stored XSS by authenticated users via data that comes after $$\\, which is mishandled by a KaTeX parser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 03:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11651 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT wifi_schedule command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11651</link><description>A vulnerability was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/network/wifi_schedule. The manipulation of the argument wifi_schedule_day_em_5 leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 03:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11650 | Tenda i9 GetIPTV websReadEvent null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11650</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda i9 1.0.0.8(3828) and classified as critical. This issue affects the function websReadEvent of the file /goform/GetIPTV. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 02:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11649 | 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System search-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11649</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/search-appointment.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 02:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11648 | 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System add-customer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11648</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/add-customer.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 01:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11647 | 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System view-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11647</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/view-appointment.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 01:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11646 | 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System edit-services.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11646</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-services.php. The manipulation of the argument sername leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 23:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53916 | In OpenStack Neutron through 25.0.0, neutron/extensions/tagging.py can use an incorrect ID during policy enforcement. NOTE: 935883 has the "...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53916</link><description>In OpenStack Neutron through 25.0.0, neutron/extensions/tagging.py can use an incorrect ID during policy enforcement. NOTE: 935883 has the "Work in Progress" status as of 2024-11-24.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 23:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11665 | Unauthenticated Remote Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11665</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability in hardy-barth cph2_echarge_firmware allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects cph2_echarge_firmware: through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 22:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11666 | Unauthenticated Remote Command Injection in eCharge Salia PLCC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11666</link><description>Affected devices beacon to eCharge cloud infrastructure asking if there are any command they should run. This communication is established over an insecure channel since peer verification is disabled everywhere. Therefore, remote unauthenticated users  suitably positioned on the network between an EV charger controller and eCharge infrastructure can execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges on affected devices.

This issue affects cph2_echarge_firmware: through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 22:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53909 | An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24334. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53909</link><description>An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24334. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code because untrusted data, received on a .NET Remoting TCP port, is deserialized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 21:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53910 | An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24336. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53910</link><description>An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24336. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code because untrusted data, received on a .NET Remoting TCP port, is deserialized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 21:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53911 | An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24339. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53911</link><description>An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24339. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code because untrusted data, received on a .NET Remoting TCP port, is deserialized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 21:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53912 | An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24341. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53912</link><description>An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24341. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code because untrusted data, received on a .NET Remoting TCP port, is deserialized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 21:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53913 | An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24343. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53913</link><description>An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24343. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code because untrusted data, received on a .NET Remoting TCP port, is deserialized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 21:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53914 | An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24344. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53914</link><description>An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24344. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code because untrusted data, received on a .NET Remoting TCP port, is deserialized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 21:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53915 | An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24405. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53915</link><description>An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24405. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code because untrusted data, received on a .NET Remoting TCP port, is deserialized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 21:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53901 | The Imager package before 1.025 for Perl has a heap-based buffer overflow leading to denial of service, or possibly unspecified other impact...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53901</link><description>The Imager package before 1.025 for Perl has a heap-based buffer overflow leading to denial of service, or possibly unspecified other impact, when the trim() method is called on a crafted input image.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 16:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53899 | virtualenv before 20.26.6 allows command injection through the activation scripts for a virtual environment. Magic template strings are not ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53899</link><description>virtualenv before 20.26.6 allows command injection through the activation scripts for a virtual environment. Magic template strings are not quoted correctly when replacing. NOTE: this is not the same as CVE-2024-9287.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 16:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11233 | Single byte overread with convert.quoted-printable-decode filter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11233</link><description>In PHP versions 8.1.* before 8.1.31, 8.2.* before 8.2.26, 8.3.* before 8.3.14, due to an error in convert.quoted-printable-decode filter certain data can lead to buffer overread by one byte, which can in certain circumstances lead to crashes or disclose content of other memory areas.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 02:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11234 | Configuring a proxy in a stream context might allow for CRLF injection in URIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11234</link><description>In PHP versions 8.1.* before 8.1.31, 8.2.* before 8.2.26, 8.3.* before 8.3.14, when using streams with configured proxy and "request_fulluri" option, the URI is not properly sanitized which can lead to HTTP request smuggling and allow the attacker to use the proxy to perform arbitrary HTTP requests originating from the server, thus potentially gaining access to resources not normally available to the external user.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 02:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11236 | Integer overflow in the firebird and dblib quoters causing OOB writes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11236</link><description>In PHP versions 8.1.* before 8.1.31, 8.2.* before 8.2.26, 8.3.* before 8.3.14, uncontrolled long string inputs to ldap_escape() function on 32-bit systems can cause an integer overflow, resulting in an out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 02:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35160 | IBM Watson Query on Cloud Pak for Data and IBM Db2 Big SQL on Cloud Pak for Data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35160</link><description>IBM Watson Query on Cloud Pak for Data 1.8, 2.0, 2.1, 2.2 and IBM Db2 Big SQL on Cloud Pak for Data 7.3, 7.4, 7.5, and 7.6 could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive information due to insufficient session expiration.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 13:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11632 | code-projects Simple Car Rental System book_car.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11632</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Car Rental System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /book_car.php. The manipulation of the argument fname/id_no/gender/email/phone/location leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "fname" to be affected. Further analysis indicates that other arguments might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 13:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7299 | DataGear resolveSql sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7299</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DataGear up to 4.60. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /dataSet/resolveSql. The manipulation of the argument sql leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 4.7.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 13:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11228 | 워드프레스 결제 심플페이 – 우커머스 결제 플러그인 &amp;lt;= 5.1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting pafw_instant_payment Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11228</link><description>The 워드프레스 결제 심플페이 – 우커머스 결제 플러그인 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's pafw_instant_payment shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 11:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11229 | 코드엠샵 소셜톡 &amp;lt;= 1.1.18 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via add_plus_friends and add_plus_talk Shortcodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11229</link><description>The 코드엠샵 소셜톡 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's add_plus_friends and add_plus_talk shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.18 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 11:46:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11631 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System expedit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11631</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /expedit.php. The manipulation of the argument expcat leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 11:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11034 | Request a Quote for WooCommerce and Elementor – Get a Quote Button – Product Enquiry Form Popup – Product Quotation &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via fire_contact_form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11034</link><description>The The Request a Quote for WooCommerce and Elementor – Get a Quote Button – Product Enquiry Form Popup – Product Quotation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution via fire_contact_form AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.4. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 11:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11231 | 우커머스 네이버페이 &amp;lt;= 3.3.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via mnp_purchase Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11231</link><description>The 우커머스 네이버페이 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's mnp_purchase shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 11:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10519 | Wishlist for WooCommerce: Multi Wishlists Per Customer PRO 3.0.8 - 3.1.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via wtab Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10519</link><description>The Wishlist for WooCommerce: Multi Wishlists Per Customer PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'wtab' parameter in versions 3.0.8 to 3.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Note: Only WordPress installations with versions of PHP &lt;=7.4 are affected by this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 09:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11199 | Rescue Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 2.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via rescue_progressbar Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11199</link><description>The Rescue Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's rescue_progressbar shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 09:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11227 | Memberlite Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 1.3.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via memberlite_accordion Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11227</link><description>The Memberlite Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's memberlite_accordion shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 09:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10803 | MP3 Sticky Player &amp;lt;= 8.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read/Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10803</link><description>The MP3 Sticky Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 8.0 via the content/downloader.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information. Please note the vendor released the patched version as the same version as the affected version.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 07:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9511 | FluentSMTP – WP SMTP Plugin with Amazon SES, SendGrid, MailGun, Postmark, Google and Any SMTP Provider &amp;lt;= 2.2.82 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9511</link><description>The FluentSMTP – WP SMTP Plugin with Amazon SES, SendGrid, MailGun, Postmark, Google and Any SMTP Provider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.82 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'formatResult' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 2.2.82.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 07:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9659 | School Management &amp;lt;= 91.5.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9659</link><description>The School Management System for Wordpress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the mj_smgt_user_avatar_image_upload() function in all versions up to, and including, 91.5.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 07:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9660 | School Management &amp;lt;= 91.5.0 - Authenticated (Student+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9660</link><description>The School Management System for Wordpress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the mj_smgt_load_documets_new() and mj_smgt_load_documets() functions in all versions up to, and including, 91.5.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Student-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 07:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9941 | WPGYM &amp;lt;= 67.1.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9941</link><description>The WPGYM - Wordpress Gym Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the MJ_gmgt_add_staff_member() function in all versions up to, and including, 67.1.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to create new user accounts with the administrator role.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 07:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9942 | WPGYM &amp;lt;= 67.1.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9942</link><description>The WPGYM - Wordpress Gym Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the MJ_gmgt_user_avatar_image_upload() function in all versions up to, and including, 67.1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 07:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11330 | Custom CSS, JS &amp;amp; PHP &amp;lt;= 2.3.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11330</link><description>The Custom CSS, JS &amp; PHP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 07:14:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11446 | Chessgame Shizzle &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11446</link><description>The Chessgame Shizzle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'cs_nonce' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 07:14:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9635 | Checkout with Cash App on WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 6.0.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9635</link><description>The Checkout with Cash App on WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the '_wp_http_referer' parameter in several files in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 07:14:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11188 | Formidable Forms – Contact Form Plugin, Survey, Quiz, Payment, Calculator Form &amp;amp; Custom Form Builder &amp;lt;= 6.16.1.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via Custom HTML Form Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11188</link><description>The Formidable Forms – Contact Form Plugin, Survey, Quiz, Payment, Calculator Form &amp; Custom Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to POST-Based Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the Custom HTML Form parameters in all versions up to, and including, 6.16.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 05:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11265 | Wp Maximum Upload File Size &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Authenticated (Author+) Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11265</link><description>The Increase Maximum Upload File Size | Increase Execution Time plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.3. This is due to returning image upload error messages with full path information. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level permissions and above, to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 05:47:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10606 | WP Travel Engine &amp;lt;= 6.2.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10606</link><description>The WP Travel Engine – Tour Booking Plugin – Tour Operator Software plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the wpte_onboard_save_function_callback() function in all versions up to, and including, 6.2.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to modify several settings that could have an impact such as lost revenue and page updates.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 04:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10873 | LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10873</link><description>The LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2 via the _load_template function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 04:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10880 | JobBoardWP – Job Board Listings and Submissions &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10880</link><description>The JobBoardWP – Job Board Listings and Submissions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 04:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11332 | HIPAA Compliant Forms with Drag’n’Drop HIPAA Form Builder. Sign HIPAA documents &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11332</link><description>The HIPAA Compliant Forms with Drag’n’Drop HIPAA Form Builder. Sign HIPAA documents plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'hipaatizer' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 04:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11361 | PDF Invoices &amp;amp; Packing Slips Generator for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11361</link><description>The PDF Invoices &amp; Packing Slips Generator for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 04:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11387 | Easy Liveblogs &amp;lt;= 2.3.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11387</link><description>The Easy Liveblogs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'elb_liveblog' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 04:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11408 | Slotti Ajanvaraus &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11408</link><description>The Slotti Ajanvaraus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'slotti' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 04:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11426 | AutoListicle: Automatically Update Numbered List Articles &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11426</link><description>The AutoListicle: Automatically Update Numbered List Articles plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'auto-list-number' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 04:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10116 | Twitter Follow Button &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via username Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10116</link><description>The Twitter Follow Button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'username' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 03:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10216 | WP User Manager – User Profile Builder &amp;amp; Membership &amp;lt;= 2.9.11 - Missing Authorization to Carbon Fields Custom Sidebar Addition/Removal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10216</link><description>The WP User Manager – User Profile Builder &amp; Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'add_sidebar' and 'remove_sidebar' functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.11. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to add or remove a Carbon Fields custom sidebar if the Carbon Fields (carbon-fields) plugin is installed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 03:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10537 | WP User Manager – User Profile Builder &amp;amp; Membership &amp;lt;= 2.9.11 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) User Meta Key Enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10537</link><description>The WP User Manager – User Profile Builder &amp; Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the validate_user_meta_key() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.11. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to enumerate user meta keys.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 03:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10813 | Product Table for WooCommerce by CodeAstrology (wooproducttable.com) &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10813</link><description>The Product Table for WooCommerce by CodeAstrology (wooproducttable.com) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.1 via the var_dump_table parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers var data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 03:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10868 | Enter Addons – Ultimate Template Builder for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10868</link><description>The Enter Addons – Ultimate Template Builder for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.9 via the Advanced Tabs widget due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private or draft posts created by Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 03:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10869 | GuardGiant Brute Force Protection &amp;lt;= 2.2.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10869</link><description>The WordPress Brute Force Protection – Stop Brute Force Attacks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 03:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10874 | Quotes llama &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10874</link><description>The Quotes llama plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'quotes-llama' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 03:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10886 | Tribute Testimonials – WordPress Testimonial Grid/Slider &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10886</link><description>The Tribute Testimonials – WordPress Testimonial Grid/Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tribute_testimonials_slider' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 03:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10961 | Social Login &amp;lt;= 5.9.0 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10961</link><description>The Social Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.0. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being returned by the social login token. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the email and the user does not have an already-existing account for the service returning the token.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 03:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11362 | Payments Plugin and Checkout Plugin for WooCommerce: Stripe, PayPal, Square, Authorize.net &amp;lt;= 1.112.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11362</link><description>The Payments Plugin and Checkout Plugin for WooCommerce: Stripe, PayPal, Square, Authorize.net plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.112.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 03:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11415 | WP-Orphanage Extended &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Orphan Account Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11415</link><description>The WP-Orphanage Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the wporphanageex_menu_settings() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to escalate the privileges of all orphan accounts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 03:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11463 | DeBounce Email Validator &amp;lt;= 5.6.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11463</link><description>The DeBounce Email Validator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'from', 'to', and 'key' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 03:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9223 | WPDash Notes &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9223</link><description>The WPDash Notes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_post_it_list_comment' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view comments on any post, including private and password protected posts, and pending and draft posts if they were previously published. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 03:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11586 | Ubuntu's implementation of pulseaudio can be crashed by a malicious program if a bluetooth headset is connected.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11586</link><description>Ubuntu's implementation of pulseaudio can be crashed by a malicious program if a bluetooth headset is connected.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 03:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41761 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41761</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.5, 11.1, and 11.5 is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 03:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>