<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 06:14:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-32489 | TCPDF before 6.7.4 mishandles calls that use HTML syntax.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32489</link><description>TCPDF before 6.7.4 mishandles calls that use HTML syntax.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 06:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32488 | In Foxit PDF Reader and Editor before 2024.1, Local Privilege Escalation could occur during update checks because weak permissions on the up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32488</link><description>In Foxit PDF Reader and Editor before 2024.1, Local Privilege Escalation could occur during update checks because weak permissions on the update-service folder allow attackers to place crafted DLL files there.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3771 | PHPGurukul Student Record System edit-subject.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3771</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /edit-subject.php. The manipulation of the argument sub1/sub2/sub3/sub4/udate leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-260618 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6067 | WP User Profile Avatar &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6067</link><description>The WP User Profile Avatar WordPress plugin through 1.0.1 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7201 | Everest Backup &amp;lt; 2.2.5 - Admin+ Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7201</link><description>The Everest Backup  WordPress plugin before 2.2.5 does not properly validate backup files to be uploaded, allowing high privilege users such as admin to upload arbitrary files on the server even when they should not be allowed to (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0399 | WooCommerce Customers Manager &amp;lt; 29.7 - Subscriber+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0399</link><description>The WooCommerce Customers Manager WordPress plugin before 29.7 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, leading to an SQL injection exploitable by Subscriber+ role.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0902 | Fancy Product Designer &amp;lt; 6.1.81 - Admin+ Cross Site Scripting via Product Title</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0902</link><description>The Fancy Product Designer WordPress plugin before 6.1.81 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1204 | Meta Box &amp;lt; 5.9.4 - Contributor+ Arbitrary Posts&amp;#x27; Custom Field Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1204</link><description>The Meta Box  WordPress plugin before 5.9.4 does not prevent users with at least the contributor role from access arbitrary custom fields assigned to other user's posts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1306 | Smart Forms &amp;lt; 2.6.94 - Edit Entries via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1306</link><description>The Smart Forms  WordPress plugin before 2.6.94 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged-in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks, such as editing entries, and we consider it a medium risk.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1307 | Smart Forms &amp;lt; 2.6.94 - Subscriber+ Edit Entries via Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1307</link><description>The Smart Forms  WordPress plugin before 2.6.94 does not have proper authorization in some actions, which could allow users with a role as low as a subscriber to call them and perform unauthorized actions</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1310 | WooCommerce &amp;lt; 8.6 - Contributor+ Private/Draft Products Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1310</link><description>The WooCommerce WordPress plugin before 8.6 does not prevent users with at least the contributor role from leaking products they shouldn't have access to. (e.g. private, draft and trashed products)</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1660 | Top Bar &amp;lt; 3.0.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1660</link><description>The Top Bar WordPress plugin before 3.0.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1712 | Carousel Slider &amp;lt; 2.2.7 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1712</link><description>The Carousel Slider WordPress plugin before 2.2.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1746 | Testimonial Slider &amp;lt; 2.3.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1746</link><description>The Testimonial Slider WordPress plugin before 2.3.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1754 | NPS computy &amp;lt;= 2.7.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1754</link><description>The NPS computy WordPress plugin through 2.7.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1755 | NPS computy &amp;lt;= 2.7.5 - Results Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1755</link><description>The NPS computy WordPress plugin through 2.7.5 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1846 | Responsive Tabs &amp;lt; 4.0.7 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1846</link><description>The Responsive Tabs WordPress plugin before 4.0.7 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1849 | WP Customer Reviews &amp;lt; 3.7.1 - Malicious Redirect via HTTP-EQUIV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1849</link><description>The WP Customer Reviews WordPress plugin before 3.7.1 does not validate a parameter allowing contributor and above users to redirect a page to a malicious URL</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2739 | Advance Search &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Shortcode Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2739</link><description>The Advanced Search WordPress plugin through 1.1.6 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2836 | Super Socializer &amp;lt; 7.13.64 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2836</link><description>The Social Share, Social Login and Social Comments Plugin  WordPress plugin before 7.13.64 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as editors to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2857 | Simple Buttons Creator &amp;lt;= 1.04 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2857</link><description>The Simple Buttons Creator WordPress plugin through 1.04 does not have any authorisation as well as CSRF in its add button function, allowing unauthenticated users to call them either directly or via CSRF attacks. Furthermore, due to the lack of sanitisation and escaping, it could also allow them to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks against logged in admins.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2858 | Simple Buttons Creator &amp;lt;= 1.04 - Aribtrary Button Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2858</link><description>The Simple Buttons Creator WordPress plugin through 1.04 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3770 | PHPGurukul Student Record System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3770</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /manage-courses.php?del=1. The manipulation of the argument del leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-260617 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1655 | ASUS WiFi Router - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1655</link><description>Certain ASUS WiFi routers models has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing an authenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary system commands by sending a specially crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 04:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3769 | PHPGurukul Student Record System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3769</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20. Affected is an unknown function of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument id/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260616.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 04:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3767 | PHPGurukul News Portal edit-post.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3767</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul News Portal 4.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit-post.php. The manipulation of the argument posttitle leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-260614 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 04:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3768 | PHPGurukul News Portal search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3768</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul News Portal 4.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchtitle leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260615.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 04:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3775 | aEnrich Technology a+HRD - Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3775</link><description>aEnrich Technology a+HRD's functionality for downloading files using youtube-dl.exe does not properly restrict user input. This allows attackers to pass arbitrary arguments to youtube-dl.exe, leading to the download of partial unauthorized files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 04:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3776 | Netvision airPASS - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3776</link><description>The parameter used in the login page of Netvision airPASS is not properly filtered for user input. An unauthenticated remote attacker can insert JavaScript code to the parameter for Reflected Cross-site scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 04:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3777 | Ai3 QbiBot - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3777</link><description>The password reset feature of Ai3 QbiBot lacks proper access control, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to reset any user's password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 04:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3778 | Ai3 QbiBot - Unrestricted File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3778</link><description>The file upload functionality of Ai3 QbiBot does not properly restrict types of uploaded files, allowing remote attackers with administrator privilege to upload files with dangerous type containing malicious code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 04:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3772 | Regular expression denial of service in Pydantic &amp;lt; 2.4.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3772</link><description>Regular expression denial of service in Pydanic &lt; 2.4.0, &lt; 1.10.13 allows remote attackers to cause denial of service via a crafted email string.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 02:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3774 | aEnrich Technology a+HRD - Exposure of Sensitive Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3774</link><description>aEnrich Technology a+HRD's functionality for front-end retrieval of system configuration values lacks proper restrictions on a specific parameter, allowing attackers to modify this parameter to access certain sensitive system configuration values.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 02:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29836 | Broken Authentication on USER_CHANGE in Evolution Controller allows unauthenticated account creation and takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29836</link><description>The Web interface of Evolution Controller Versions 2.04.560.31.03.2024 and below contains poorly configured access control, allowing for an unauthenticated attacker to update and add user profiles within the application, and gain full access of the site.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 02:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29837 | Poor session management in Evolution Controller allows administrator functionality for unauthenticated connections</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29837</link><description>The Web interface of Evolution Controller Versions 2.04.560.31.03.2024 and below uses poor session management, allowing for an unauthenticated attacker to access administrator functionality if any other user is already signed in.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 02:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29838 | Unsanitised variable on DAL_ADD in Evolution Controller causes application level denial of service and crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29838</link><description>The Web interface of Evolution Controller Versions 2.04.560.31.03.2024 and below does not proper sanitize user input,  allowing for an unauthenticated attacker to crash the controller software</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 02:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29839 | Broken Access control on DESKTOP_EDIT_USER_GET_CARD in Evolution Controller allows unauthenticated attackers to retrieve card data values.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29839</link><description>The Web interface of Evolution Controller Versions 2.04.560.31.03.2024 and below contains poorly configured access control on DESKTOP_EDIT_USER_GET_CARD, allowing for an unauthenticated attacker to return the card value data of any user</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 02:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29840 | Broken Access control on DESKTOP_EDIT_USER_GET_PIN_FIELDS in Evolution Controller allows unauthenticated attackers to retrieve PIN field values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29840</link><description>The Web interface of Evolution Controller Versions 2.04.560.31.03.2024 and below contains poorly configured access control on DESKTOP_EDIT_USER_GET_PIN_FIELDS, allowing for an unauthenticated attacker to return the pin value of any user</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 02:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29841 | Broken Access control on DESKTOP_EDIT_USER_GET_KEYS_FIELDS in Evolution Controller allows unauthenticated attackers to retrieve keys values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29841</link><description>The Web interface of Evolution Controller Versions 2.04.560.31.03.2024 and below contains poorly configured access control on DESKTOP_EDIT_USER_GET_KEYS_FIELDS, allowing for an unauthenticated attacker to return the keys value of any user</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 02:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29842 | Broken Access control on DESKTOP_EDIT_USER_GET_ABACARD_FIELDS in Evolution Controller allows unauthenticated attackers to retrieve ABACARD values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29842</link><description>The Web interface of Evolution Controller Versions 2.04.560.31.03.2024 and below contains poorly configured access control on DESKTOP_EDIT_USER_GET_ABACARD_FIELDS, allowing for an unauthenticated attacker to return the abacard field of any user</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 02:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29843 | Broken Access control on MOBILE_GET_USERS_LIST in Evolution Controller allows unauthenticated user enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29843</link><description>The Web interface of Evolution Controller Versions 2.04.560.31.03.2024 and below contains poorly configured access control on MOBILE_GET_USERS_LIST, allowing for an unauthenticated attacker to enumerate all users and their access levels</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 02:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29844 | Default credentials on web interface of Evolution Controller Versions allows attackers to login and perform administrative functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29844</link><description>Default credentials on the Web Interface of Evolution Controller 2.x (123 and 123) allows anyone to log in to the server directly to perform administrative functions. Upon installation or upon first login, the application does not ask the user to change the password. There is no warning or prompt to ask the user to change the default password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 02:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3766 | slowlyo OwlAdmin Image File Upload upload_image cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3766</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in slowlyo OwlAdmin up to 3.5.7. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin-api/upload_image of the component Image File Upload. The manipulation of the argument file leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-260606 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 23:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3763 | Emlog Pro Post Tag tag.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3763</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Emlog Pro 2.2.10. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/tag.php of the component Post Tag Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260603. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 23:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3764 | Tuya Camera MQTT Packet denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3764</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Tuya Camera 3.2.9. Affected is an unknown function of the component MQTT Packet Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260604. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 23:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3765 | Xiongmai AHB7804R-MH-V2 Sofia Service access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3765</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Xiongmai AHB7804R-MH-V2, AHB8004T-GL, AHB8008T-GL, AHB7004T-GS-V3, AHB7004T-MHV2, AHB8032F-LME and XM530_R80X30-PQ_8M. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Sofia Service. The manipulation with the input ff00000000000000000000000000f103250000007b202252657422203a203130302c202253657373696f6e494422203a202230783022207d0a leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-260605 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 23:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3762 | Emlog Pro Whisper Page twitter.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3762</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Emlog Pro 2.2.10. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/twitter.php of the component Whisper Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-260602 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 22:17:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24862 | NULL-pointer dereference in Linux kernel spi driver in function pci1xxxx_spi_probe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24862</link><description>In function pci1xxxx_spi_probe, there is a potential null pointer that
may be caused by a failed memory allocation by the function devm_kzalloc.
Hence, a null pointer check needs to be added to prevent null pointer
dereferencing later in the code.

To fix this issue, spi_bus-&gt;spi_int[iter] should be checked. The memory
allocated by devm_kzalloc will be automatically released, so just directly
return -ENOMEM without worrying about memory leaks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 14:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24863 | NULL pointer deference in __drm_atomic_helper_connector_destroy_state in drm/arm/malidp of Linux kernel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24863</link><description>In malidp_mw_connector_reset, new memory is allocated with kzalloc, but 
no check is performed. In order to prevent null pointer dereferencing, 
ensure that mw_state is checked before calling 
__drm_atomic_helper_connector_reset.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 14:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3740 | cym1102 nginxWebUI reload exec deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3740</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in cym1102 nginxWebUI up to 3.9.9. This issue affects the function exec of the file /adminPage/conf/reload. The manipulation of the argument nginxExe leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260579.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 20:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3739 | cym1102 nginxWebUI upload os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3739</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in cym1102 nginxWebUI up to 3.9.9. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /adminPage/main/upload. The manipulation of the argument file leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-260578 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 18:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3738 | cym1102 nginxWebUI saveCmd handlePath certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3738</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in cym1102 nginxWebUI up to 3.9.9. This affects the function handlePath of the file /adminPage/conf/saveCmd. The manipulation of the argument nginxPath leads to improper certificate validation. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-260577 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3737 | cym1102 nginxWebUI addOver findCountByQuery path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3737</link><description>A vulnerability was found in cym1102 nginxWebUI up to 3.9.9. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function findCountByQuery of the file /adminPage/www/addOver. The manipulation of the argument dir leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260576.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 16:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32487 | less through 653 allows OS command execution via a newline character in the name of a file, because quoting is mishandled in filename.c. Exp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32487</link><description>less through 653 allows OS command execution via a newline character in the name of a file, because quoting is mishandled in filename.c. Exploitation typically requires use with attacker-controlled file names, such as the files extracted from an untrusted archive. Exploitation also requires the LESSOPEN environment variable, but this is set by default in many common cases.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 14:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3736 | cym1102 nginxWebUI upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3736</link><description>A vulnerability was found in cym1102 nginxWebUI up to 3.9.9. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function upload of the file /adminPage/main/upload. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260575.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 14:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3735 | Smart Office Main.aspx weak password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3735</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Smart Office up to 20240405. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file Main.aspx. The manipulation of the argument New Password/Confirm Password with the input 1 leads to weak password requirements. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-260574 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 13:11:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3721 | TBK DVR-4104/DVR-4216 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3721</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TBK DVR-4104 and DVR-4216 up to 20240412 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /device.rsp?opt=sys&amp;amp;cmd=___S_O_S_T_R_E_A_MAX___. The manipulation of the argument mdb/mdc leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-260573 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 12:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3720 | Tianwell Fire Intelligent Command Platform API Interface page sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3720</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tianwell Fire Intelligent Command Platform 1.1.1.1 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /mfsNotice/page of the component API Interface. The manipulation of the argument gsdwid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260572.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 11:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26817 | amdkfd: use calloc instead of kzalloc to avoid integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26817</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

amdkfd: use calloc instead of kzalloc to avoid integer overflow

This uses calloc instead of doing the multiplication which might
overflow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 11:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3719 | Campcodes House Rental Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3719</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes House Rental Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file ajax.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260571.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 11:12:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6494 | The WPC Smart Quick View for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6494</link><description>The WPC Smart Quick View for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 08:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3662 | The WPZOOM Social Feed Widget &amp; Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the wpz...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3662</link><description>The WPZOOM Social Feed Widget &amp; Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the wpzoom_instagram_clear_data() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to delete all Instagram images installed on the site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 08:55:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2583 | Shortcodes Ultimate &amp;lt; 7.0.5 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2583</link><description>The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate WordPress plugin before 7.0.5 does not properly escape some of its shortcodes attributes before they are echoed back to users, making it possible for users with the contributor role to conduct Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 05:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1957 | The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1957</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'give_form' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 02:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3027 | The Smart Slider 3 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the upload f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3027</link><description>The Smart Slider 3 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the upload function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.1.22. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to upload files, including SVG files, which can be used to conduct stored cross-site scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 02:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>