<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-1368 | Video Conferencing with Zoom API &amp;lt; 4.6.6 - Unauthenticated SDK Signature Generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1368</link><description>The Video Conferencing with Zoom WordPress plugin before 4.6.6 contains an AJAX handler that has its nonce verification commented out, allowing unauthenticated attackers to generate valid Zoom SDK signatures for any meeting ID and retrieve the site's Zoom SDK key.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11737 | VK All in One Expansion Unit &amp;lt;= 9.112.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SNS Title</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11737</link><description>The VK All in One Expansion Unit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'vkExUnit_sns_title' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 9.112.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12122 | Popup Box – Easily Create WordPress Popups &amp;lt;= 3.2.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12122</link><description>The Popup Box – Easily Create WordPress Popups plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'iframeBox' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12356 | Tickera – WordPress Event Ticketing &amp;lt;= 3.5.6.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Event/Post Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12356</link><description>The Tickera – Sell Tickets &amp; Manage Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_change_ticket_status' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.6.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update post/event statuses.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1072 | Keybase.io Verification &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1072</link><description>The Keybase.io Verification plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.5. This is due to missing nonce validation when updating plugin settings. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the Keybase verification text via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1304 | Membership Plugin – Restrict Content &amp;lt;= 3.2.18 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Invoice Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1304</link><description>The Membership Plugin – Restrict Content for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple invoice settings fields in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.18 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1639 | Taskbuilder &amp;lt;= 5.0.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;order&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;sort_by&amp;#x27; Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1639</link><description>The Taskbuilder – WordPress Project Management &amp; Task Management plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based blind SQL Injection via the 'order' and 'sort_by' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1906 | PDF Invoices &amp;amp; Packing Slips for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.6.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Peppol Identifier Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1906</link><description>The PDF Invoices &amp; Packing Slips for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.0 via the `wpo_ips_edi_save_order_customer_peppol_identifiers` AJAX action due to missing capability checks and order ownership validation. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify Peppol/EDI endpoint identifiers (`peppol_endpoint_id`, `peppol_endpoint_eas`) for any customer by specifying an arbitrary `order_id` parameter on systems using Peppol invoicing. This can affect order routing on the Peppol network and may result in payment disruptions and data leakage.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2023 | WP Plugin Info Card &amp;lt;= 6.2.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Custom Plugin Entry Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2023</link><description>The WP Plugin Info Card plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.2.0. This is due to missing nonce validation in the ajax_save_custom_plugin() function, which is disabled by prefixing the check with 'false &amp;&amp;'. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create or modify custom plugin entries via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2641 | universal-ctags V Language v.c parseExprList recursion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2641</link><description>A weakness has been identified in universal-ctags ctags up to 6.2.1. The affected element is the function parseExpression/parseExprList of the file parsers/v.c of the component V Language Parser. Executing a manipulation can lead to uncontrolled recursion. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12037 | WP 404 Auto Redirect &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12037</link><description>The WP 404 Auto Redirect to Similar Post plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12071 | Frontend User Notes &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Note Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12071</link><description>The Frontend User Notes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.0 via the 'funp_ajax_modify_notes' AJAX endpoint due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify arbitrary notes that do not belong to them.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12074 | Context Blog &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Unauthenticated Private Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12074</link><description>The Context Blog theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5 via the 'context_blog_modal_popup' due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12075 | Order Splitter for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.3.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Order Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12075</link><description>The Order Splitter for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wos_troubleshooting' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view information pertaining to other user's orders.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13959 | Filestack &amp;lt;= 2.0.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13959</link><description>The Filestack plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'filepicker' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6460 | Display During Conditional Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via message Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6460</link><description>The Display During Conditional Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘message’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1277 | URL Shortify &amp;lt;= 1.12.1 - Unauthenticated Open Redirect via &amp;#x27;redirect_to&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1277</link><description>The URL Shortify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Open Redirect in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.1 due to insufficient validation on the 'redirect_to' parameter in the promotional dismissal handler. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users to potentially malicious sites via a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1296 | Frontend Post Submission Manager Lite &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 - Unauthenticated Open Redirect via &amp;#x27;requested_page&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1296</link><description>The Frontend Post Submission Manager Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Open Redirection in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.7 due to insufficient validation on the 'requested_page' POST parameter in the verify_username_password function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users to potentially malicious sites if they can successfully trick them into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1714 | ShopLentor &amp;lt;= 3.3.2 - Unauthenticated Email Relay Abuse via &amp;#x27;woolentor_suggest_price_action&amp;#x27; AJAX Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1714</link><description>The ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg +21 Modules – All in One Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Email Relay Abuse in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.2. This is due to the lack of validation on the 'send_to', 'product_title', 'wlmessage', and 'wlemail' parameters in the 'woolentor_suggest_price_action' AJAX endpoint. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send arbitrary emails to any recipient with full control over the subject line, message content, and sender address (via CRLF injection in the 'wlemail' parameter), effectively turning the website into a full email relay for spam or phishing campaigns.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1925 | EmailKit – Email Customizer for WooCommerce &amp;amp; WP &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Title Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1925</link><description>The EmailKit – Email Customizer for WooCommerce &amp; WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized data modification due to a missing capability check on the 'update_template_data' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify the title of any post on the site, including posts, pages, and custom post types.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1931 | Rent Fetch &amp;lt;= 0.32.4 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;keyword&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1931</link><description>The Rent Fetch plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'keyword' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.32.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2576 | Business Directory Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.21 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via payment Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2576</link><description>The Business Directory Plugin – Easy Listing Directories for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the 'payment' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27171 | zlib before 1.3.2 allows CPU consumption via crc32_combine64 and crc32_combine_gen64 because x2nmodp can do right shifts within a loop that ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27171</link><description>zlib before 1.3.2 allows CPU consumption via crc32_combine64 and crc32_combine_gen64 because x2nmodp can do right shifts within a loop that has no termination condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 03:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1344 | Insecure file permissions in Enforce Recovery Key Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1344</link><description>Tanium addressed an insecure file permissions vulnerability in Enforce Recovery Key Portal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22048 | StorageGRID (formerly StorageGRID Webscale) versions prior to 11.9.0.12 and 12.0.0.4 with Single Sign-on enabled and configured to use Micro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22048</link><description>StorageGRID (formerly StorageGRID Webscale) versions prior to 11.9.0.12 and 12.0.0.4 with Single Sign-on enabled and configured to use Microsoft Entra ID (formerly Azure AD) as an IdP are susceptible to a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability. Successful exploit could allow an authenticated attacker with low privileges to delete configuration data or deny access to some resources.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23599 | Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability in HPE Aruba Networking Clear Pass Policy Manager OnGuard for Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23599</link><description>A local privilege-escalation vulnerability has been discovered in the HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass OnGuard Software for Linux. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow a local attacker to achieve arbitrary code execution with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62183 | Pega Platform versions 8.1.0 through 25.1.1 are affected by a Stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in a user interface component. Requires an administrative user and given extensive access rights, impact to Confidentiality and Integrity are low.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62183</link><description>Pega Platform versions 8.1.0 through 25.1.1 are affected by a Stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in a user interface component.  Requires an administrative user and given extensive access rights, impact to Confidentiality and Integrity are low.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1670 | Honeywell CCTV Products Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1670</link><description>The affected products are vulnerable to an unauthenticated API endpoint exposure, which may allow an attacker to remotely change the "forgot password" recovery email address.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26119 | Windows Admin Center Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26119</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13333 | IBM WebSphere Application Server could provide weaker than expected security</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13333</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 9.0, and 8.5 could provide weaker than expected security during system administration of security settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 22:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13689 | DataStage on Cloud Pak for Data is vulnerable to arbitrary code injection due to runtime environment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13689</link><description>IBM DataStage on Cloud Pak for Data could allow an authenticated user to execute arbitrary commands and gain access to sensitive information due to unrestricted file uploads.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 22:53:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2629 | jishi node-sonos-http-api TTS Provider mac-os.js Promise os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2629</link><description>A weakness has been identified in jishi node-sonos-http-api up to 3776f0ee2261c924c7b7204de121a38100a08ca7. Affected is the function Promise of the file lib/tts-providers/mac-os.js of the component TTS Provider. This manipulation of the argument phrase causes os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 22:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38005 | Improper Access Control and Exposure of Information Through Directory Listing vulnerabilities affect IBM Cloud Pak System[, ]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38005</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak System 2.3.3.6, 2.3.3.7, 2.3.4.0, 2.3.4.1, and 2.3.5.0 could allow an authenticated user to perform unauthorized tasks due to improper access controls.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 22:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33088 | Multiple Vulnerabilities in IBM Concert Software.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33088</link><description>IBM Concert 1.0.0 through 2.1.0 could allow a local user with specific knowledge about the system's architecture to escalate their privileges due to incorrect file permissions for critical resources.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33135 | IBM Financial Transaction Manager for ACH Services and Check Services is impacted by multiple vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33135</link><description>IBM Financial Transaction Manager for ACH Services and Check Services for Multi-Platform 3.0.0.0 through 3.0.5.4 Interim Fix 027 IBM Financial Transaction Manager for Check Services v3 (Multiplatforms) is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36183 | Privileged User File Upload Vulnerability Leading to Limited Server-Side Execution affects watsonx.data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36183</link><description>IBM watsonx.data 2.2 through 2.2.1 IBM Lakehouse could allow a privileged user to upload malicious files that could be executed server to modify limited files or data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36348 | The Dashboard of IBM Sterling B2B Integrator and IBM Sterling File Gateway is Vulnerable to Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36348</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator versions 6.1.0.0 through 6.1.2.7_2, 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.5, and 6.2.1.0 through 6.2.1.1, and IBM Sterling File Gateway versions 6.1.0.0 through 6.1.2.7_2, 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.5, and 6.2.1.0 through 6.2.1.1 may expose sensitive information to a remote privileged attacker due to the application returning detailed technical error messages in the browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2627 | Softland FBackup Backup/Restore HID.dll link following</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2627</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Softland FBackup up to 9.9. This impacts an unknown function in the library C:\Program Files\Common Files\microsoft shared\ink\HID.dll of the component Backup/Restore. The manipulation results in link following. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55271 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability has been identified in phpgurukul Gym Management System 1.0. This issue is present in the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55271</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability has been identified in phpgurukul Gym Management System 1.0. This issue is present in the profile update functionality of the User Panel, specifically the /profile.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-41650 | WordPress Custom Content by Country plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41650</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Paul Custom Content by Country (by Shield Security) custom-content-by-country.This issue affects Custom Content by Country (by Shield Security): from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31118 | WordPress SP Project &amp;amp; Document Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 4.70 - Broken Access Control to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31118</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Smartypants SP Project &amp; Document Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects SP Project &amp; Document Manager: from n/a through 4.70.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70829 | An information exposure vulnerability in Datart v1.0.0-rc.3 allows authenticated attackers to access sensitive data via a custom H2 JDBC con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70829</link><description>An information exposure vulnerability in Datart v1.0.0-rc.3 allows authenticated attackers to access sensitive data via a custom H2 JDBC connection string.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2616 | Beetel 777VR1 Web Management hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2616</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Beetel 777VR1 up to 01.00.09. The impacted element is an unknown function of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. The attack needs to be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is advisable to modify the configuration settings. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22208 | OpenS100 Portrayal Engine Unrestricted Lua Standard Library Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22208</link><description>OpenS100 (the reference implementation S-100 viewer) prior to commit 753cf29 contain a remote code execution vulnerability via an unrestricted Lua interpreter. The Portrayal Engine initializes Lua using luaL_openlibs() without sandboxing or capability restrictions, exposing standard libraries such as 'os' and 'io' to untrusted portrayal catalogues. An attacker can provide a malicious S-100 portrayal catalogue containing Lua scripts that execute arbitrary commands with the privileges of the OpenS100 process when a user imports the catalogue and loads a chart.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23861 | Dell Unisphere for PowerMax vApp, version(s) 9.2.4.x, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23861</link><description>Dell Unisphere for PowerMax vApp, version(s) 9.2.4.x, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a victim user's web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application. Exploitation may lead to information disclosure, session theft, or client-side request forgery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7706 | Improper Access Control in TUBITAK BILGEM&amp;#x27;s Liderahenk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7706</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in TUBITAK BILGEM Software Technologies Research Institute Liderahenk allows Remote Code Inclusion.This issue affects Liderahenk: from 3.0.0 to 3.3.1 before 3.5.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25087 | Apache Arrow: Potential use-after-free when reading IPC file with pre-buffering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25087</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Apache Arrow C++.

This issue affects Apache Arrow C++ from 15.0.0 through 23.0.0. It can be triggered when reading an Arrow IPC file (but not an IPC stream) with pre-buffering enabled, if the IPC file contains data with variadic buffers (such as Binary View and String View data). Depending on the number of variadic buffers in a record batch column and on the temporal sequence of multi-threaded IO, a write to a dangling pointer could occur. The value (a `std::shared_ptr` object) that is written to the dangling pointer is not under direct control of the attacker.

Pre-buffering is disabled by default but can be enabled using a specific C++ API call (`RecordBatchFileReader::PreBufferMetadata`). The functionality is not exposed in language bindings (Python, Ruby, C GLib), so these bindings are not vulnerable.

The most likely consequence of this issue would be random crashes or memory corruption when reading specific kinds of IPC files. If the application allows ingesting IPC files from untrusted sources, this could plausibly be exploited for denial of service. Inducing more targeted kinds of misbehavior (such as confidential data extraction from the running process) depends on memory allocation and multi-threaded IO temporal patterns that are unlikely to be easily controlled by an attacker.

Advice for users of Arrow C++:

1. check whether you enable pre-buffering on the IPC file reader (using `RecordBatchFileReader::PreBufferMetadata`)

2. if so, either disable pre-buffering (which may have adverse performance consequences), or switch to Arrow 23.0.1 which is not vulnerable</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2615 | Wavlink WL-NU516U1 firewall.cgi singlePortForwardDelete command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2615</link><description>A flaw has been found in Wavlink WL-NU516U1 up to 20251208. The affected element is the function singlePortForwardDelete of the file /cgi-bin/firewall.cgi. Executing a manipulation of the argument del_flag can lead to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8303 | XSS in EKA Software&amp;#x27;s Real Estate Script V5 (With Doping Module – Store Module – New Language System)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8303</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in EKA Software Computer Information Advertising Services Ltd. Real Estate Script V5 (With Doping Module – Store Module – New Language System) allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Real Estate Script V5 (With Doping Module – Store Module – New Language System): through 17022026.

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7631 | Time-Based Blind SQLi in Tumeva Internet Technologies&amp;#x27; Tumeva News Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7631</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Tumeva Internet Technologies Software Information Advertising and Consulting Services Trade Ltd. Co. Tumeva News Software allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Tumeva News Software: through 17022026. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2247 | SQL Injection in Clickedu&amp;#x27;s SaaS platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2247</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability (SQLi) in Clicldeu SaaS, specifically in the generation of reports, which occurs when a previously authenticated remote attacker executes a malicious payload in the URL generated after downloading the student's report card in the ‘Day-to-day’ section from the mobile application.

In the URL of the generated PDF, the session token used does not expire, so it remains valid for days after its generation, and unusual characters can be entered after the ‘id_alu’ parameter, resulting in two types of SQLi: boolean-based blind and time-based blind. Exploiting this vulnerability could allow an attacker to access confidential information in the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2608 | Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks &amp;lt;= 3.5.32 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2608</link><description>The Kadence Blocks — Page Builder Toolkit for Gutenberg Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on a function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.32. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to perform an unauthorized action.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25903 | Apache NiFi: Missing Authorization of Restricted Permissions for Component Updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25903</link><description>Apache NiFi 1.1.0 through 2.7.2 are missing authorization when updating configuration properties on extension components that have specific Required Permissions based on the Restricted annotation. The Restricted annotation indicates additional privileges required to add the annotated component to the flow configuration, but framework authorization did not check restricted status when updating a component previously added. The missing authorization requires a more privileged user to add a restricted component to the flow configuration, but permits a less privileged user to make property configuration changes. Apache NiFi installations that do not implement different levels of authorization for Restricted components are not subject to this vulnerability because the framework enforces write permissions as the security boundary. Upgrading to Apache NiFi 2.8.0 is the recommended mitigation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:03:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1216 | RSS Aggregator &amp;lt;= 5.0.10 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;template&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1216</link><description>The RSS Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'template' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 10:06:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0829 | Frontend File Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 23.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Email Sending</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0829</link><description>The Frontend File Manager Plugin WordPress plugin through 23.5 allows unauthenticated users to send emails through the site without any security checks. This lets attackers use the WordPress site as an open relay for spam or phishing emails to anyone. Attackers can also guess file IDs to access and share uploaded files without permission, exposing sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1657 | EventPrime &amp;lt;= 4.2.8.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Image Upload via &amp;#x27;ep_upload_file_media&amp;#x27; AJAX Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1657</link><description>The EventPrime plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized image file upload in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.8.4. This is due to the plugin registering the upload_file_media AJAX action as publicly accessible (nopriv-enabled) without implementing any authentication, authorization, or nonce verification despite a nonce being created. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload image files to the WordPress uploads directory and create Media Library attachments via the ep_upload_file_media endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2002 | Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp;amp; Custom Form Builder &amp;lt;= 1.50.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2002</link><description>The Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp; Custom Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the form_name parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.50.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The plugin allows admins to give form management permissions to lower level users, which could make this exploitable by users such as subscribers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2592 | Zarinpal Gateway for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.0.16 - Improper Access Control to Payment Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2592</link><description>The Zarinpal Gateway for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Improper Access Control to Payment Status Update in all versions up to and including 5.0.16. This is due to the payment callback handler 'Return_from_ZarinPal_Gateway' failing to validate that the authority token provided in the callback URL belongs to the specific order being marked as paid. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to potentially mark orders as paid without proper payment by reusing a valid authority token from a different transaction of the same amount.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26220 | LightLLM &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 PD Mode Unsafe Deserialization RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26220</link><description>LightLLM version 1.1.0 and prior contain an unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability in PD (prefill-decode) disaggregation mode. The PD master node exposes WebSocket endpoints that receive binary frames and pass the data directly to pickle.loads() without authentication or validation. A remote attacker who can reach the PD master can send a crafted payload to achieve arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 02:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12062 | WP Maps &amp;lt;= 4.8.6 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12062</link><description>The WP Maps – Store Locator,Google Maps,OpenStreetMap,Mapbox,Listing,Directory &amp; Filters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.6 via the fc_load_template function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary .html files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where .html file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2001 | WowRevenue &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Plugin Installation/Activation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2001</link><description>The WowRevenue plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin installation due to a missing capability check in the 'Notice::install_activate_plugin' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to install arbitrary plugins on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25378 | Smoothwall Express 3.1 &amp;#x27;proxy.cgi&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25378</link><description>Smoothwall Express 3.1-SP4-polar-x86_64-update9 contains multiple cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in the proxy.cgi endpoint that allow attackers to inject malicious scripts through parameters including CACHE_SIZE, MAX_SIZE, MIN_SIZE, MAX_OUTGOING_SIZE, and MAX_INCOMING_SIZE. Attackers can submit POST requests with script payloads to store or reflect arbitrary JavaScript code that executes in users' browsers when the proxy configuration page is accessed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25379 | Smoothwall Express 3.1 &amp;#x27;urlfilter.cgi&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25379</link><description>Smoothwall Express 3.1-SP4-polar-x86_64-update9 contains stored and reflected cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in the urlfilter.cgi endpoint that allow attackers to inject malicious scripts. Attackers can submit POST requests with script payloads in the REDIRECT_PAGE or CHILDREN parameters to execute arbitrary JavaScript in user browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25380 | Smoothwall Express 3.1 &amp;#x27;dhcp.cgi&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25380</link><description>Smoothwall Express 3.1-SP4-polar-x86_64-update9 contains multiple reflected cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in the dhcp.cgi script that allow attackers to inject malicious scripts through multiple parameters. Attackers can submit POST requests to dhcp.cgi with script payloads in parameters such as BOOT_SERVER, BOOT_FILE, BOOT_ROOT, START_ADDR, END_ADDR, DNS1, DNS2, NTP1, NTP2, WINS1, WINS2, DEFAULT_LEASE_TIME, MAX_LEASE_TIME, DOMAIN_NAME, NIS_DOMAIN, NIS1, NIS2, STATIC_HOST, STATIC_DESC, STATIC_MAC, and STATIC_IP to execute arbitrary JavaScript in user browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25381 | Smoothwall Express 3.1 &amp;#x27;hosts.cgi&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25381</link><description>Smoothwall Express 3.1-SP4-polar-x86_64-update9 contains multiple reflected cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in the hosts.cgi script that allow attackers to inject malicious scripts through unvalidated parameters. Attackers can submit POST requests to the hosts.cgi endpoint with script payloads in the IP, HOSTNAME, or COMMENT parameters to execute arbitrary JavaScript in users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25382 | Smoothwall Express 3.1 &amp;#x27;time.cgi&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25382</link><description>Smoothwall Express 3.1-SP4-polar-x86_64-update9 contains a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious scripts by manipulating the NTP_SERVER parameter. Attackers can send POST requests to the time.cgi endpoint with script payloads in the NTP_SERVER parameter to execute arbitrary JavaScript in users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25383 | Smoothwall Express 3.1 &amp;#x27;apcupsd.cgi&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25383</link><description>Smoothwall Express 3.1-SP4-polar-x86_64-update9 contains multiple reflected cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in the apcupsd.cgi script that allow attackers to inject malicious scripts through multiple POST parameters. Attackers can submit crafted POST requests with script payloads in parameters like BATTLEVEL, RTMIN, BATTDELAY, TO, ANNOY, UPSIP, UPSNAME, UPSPORT, POLLTIME, UPSUSER, NISPORT, UPSAUTH, EMAIL, FROM, CC, SMSEMAIL, SMTPSERVER, PORT, USER, and EMAIL_PASSWORD to execute arbitrary JavaScript in victim browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25384 | Smoothwall Express 3.1 &amp;#x27;portfw.cgi&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25384</link><description>Smoothwall Express 3.1-SP4-polar-x86_64-update9 contains multiple reflected cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in the portfw.cgi script that allow attackers to inject malicious scripts through unvalidated parameters. Attackers can submit POST requests with script payloads in the EXT, SRC_PORT_SEL, SRC_PORT, DEST_IP, DEST_PORT_SEL, or COMMENT parameters to execute arbitrary JavaScript in users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25385 | Smoothwall Express 3.1 &amp;#x27;outgoing.cgi&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25385</link><description>Smoothwall Express 3.1-SP4-polar-x86_64-update9 contains a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts by manipulating the MACHINE and MACHINECOMMENT parameters. Attackers can send POST requests to the outgoing.cgi endpoint with script payloads to execute arbitrary JavaScript in users' browsers and steal session data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25386 | Smoothwall Express 3.1 &amp;#x27;dmzholes.cgi&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25386</link><description>Smoothwall Express 3.1-SP4-polar-x86_64-update9 contains multiple reflected cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in the dmzholes.cgi script that allow attackers to inject malicious scripts through unvalidated parameters. Attackers can submit POST requests with script payloads in the SRC_IP, DEST_IP, or COMMENT parameters to execute arbitrary JavaScript in users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25387 | Smoothwall Express 3.1 &amp;#x27;xtaccess.cgi&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25387</link><description>Smoothwall Express 3.1-SP4-polar-x86_64-update9 contains a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious scripts by submitting crafted input to the xtaccess.cgi endpoint. Attackers can inject script payloads through the EXT, DEST_PORT, or COMMENT parameters via POST requests to execute arbitrary JavaScript in victim browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25388 | Smoothwall Express 3.1 &amp;#x27;ipblock.cgi&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25388</link><description>Smoothwall Express 3.1-SP4-polar-x86_64-update9 contains a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious scripts by submitting crafted input to the ipblock.cgi endpoint. Attackers can inject script tags through the SRC_IP and COMMENT parameters in POST requests to execute arbitrary JavaScript in users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25389 | Smoothwall Express 3.1 &amp;#x27;timedaccess.cgi&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25389</link><description>Smoothwall Express 3.1-SP4-polar-x86_64-update9 contains a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious scripts by manipulating the MACHINES parameter. Attackers can craft requests to the timedaccess.cgi endpoint with script payloads in the MACHINES parameter to execute arbitrary JavaScript in users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25390 | Smoothwall Express 3.1 &amp;#x27;interfaces.cgi&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25390</link><description>Smoothwall Express 3.1-SP4-polar-x86_64-update9 contains multiple reflected cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in the interfaces.cgi script that allow attackers to inject malicious scripts through multiple parameters including GREEN_ADDRESS, GREEN_NETMASK, RED_DHCP_HOSTNAME, RED_ADDRESS, DNS1_OVERRIDE, DNS2_OVERRIDE, RED_MAC, RED_NETMASK, DEFAULT_GATEWAY, DNS1, and DNS2. Attackers can craft POST requests to interfaces.cgi with script payloads in these parameters to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of authenticated administrator sessions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25392 | Smoothwall Express 3.1 &amp;#x27;iptools.cgi&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25392</link><description>Smoothwall Express 3.1-SP4-polar-x86_64-update9 contains a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious scripts by manipulating the IP parameter. Attackers can send POST requests to the iptools.cgi endpoint with script payloads in the IP parameter to execute arbitrary JavaScript in victim browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25393 | Smoothwall Express 3.1 &amp;#x27;smoothinfo.cgi&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25393</link><description>Smoothwall Express 3.1-SP4-polar-x86_64-update9 contains a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious scripts by exploiting insufficient input validation. Attackers can submit POST requests to the smoothinfo.cgi endpoint with script payloads in the WRAP or SECTIONTITLE parameters to execute arbitrary JavaScript in victim browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25394 | Smoothwall Express 3.1 &amp;#x27;modem.cgi&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25394</link><description>Smoothwall Express 3.1-SP4-polar-x86_64-update9 contains multiple stored cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in the modem.cgi script that allow attackers to inject malicious scripts through POST parameters. Attackers can submit crafted payloads in parameters like INIT, HANGUP, SPEAKER_ON, SPEAKER_OFF, TONE_DIAL, and PULSE_DIAL to execute arbitrary JavaScript in users' browsers when the stored data is retrieved.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25395 | Smoothwall Express 3.1 &amp;#x27;preferences.cgi&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25395</link><description>Smoothwall Express 3.1-SP4-polar-x86_64-update9 contains multiple stored cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in the preferences.cgi script that allow attackers to inject malicious scripts through the HOSTNAME, KEYMAP, and OPENNESS parameters. Attackers can submit POST requests with script payloads to preferences.cgi to store malicious code that executes in the browsers of users accessing the preferences page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2566 | Wavlink WL-NU516U1 adm.cgi sub_406194 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2566</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Wavlink WL-NU516U1 up to 130/260. This affects the function sub_406194 of the file /cgi-bin/adm.cgi. Such manipulation of the argument firmware_url leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26930 | SmarterTools SmarterMail before 9526 allows XSS via MAPI requests.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26930</link><description>SmarterTools SmarterMail before 9526 allows XSS via MAPI requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2565 | Wavlink WL-NU516U1 adm.cgi sub_40785C stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2565</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Wavlink WL-NU516U1 20251208. Affected by this issue is the function sub_40785C of the file /cgi-bin/adm.cgi. This manipulation of the argument time_zone causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2032 | Interrupted page loads in new tabs could allow website spoofing under trusted domains in Firefox iOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2032</link><description>Malicious scripts that interrupt new tab page loading could cause desynchronization between the address bar and page content, allowing the attacker to spoof arbitrary HTML under a trusted domain. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 147.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:33:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2447 | Heap buffer overflow in libvpx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2447</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in libvpx. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 147.0.4, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.7.1, and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.32.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2560 | kalcaddle kodbox Media File Preview Plugin VideoResize.class.php run os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2560</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in kalcaddle kodbox up to 1.64.05. The impacted element is the function run of the file plugins/fileThumb/lib/VideoResize.class.php of the component Media File Preview Plugin. Such manipulation of the argument localFile leads to os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1333 | Use of Uninitialized Variable vulnerability affecting the EPRT file reading procedure in SOLIDWORKS eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS Desktop 2025 through Release SOLIDWORKS Desktop 2026</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1333</link><description>A Use of Uninitialized Variable vulnerability affecting the EPRT file reading procedure in SOLIDWORKS eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS Desktop 2025 through Release SOLIDWORKS Desktop 2026 could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code while opening a specially crafted EPRT file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1334 | Out-Of-Bounds Read vulnerability affecting the EPRT file reading procedure in SOLIDWORKS eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS Desktop 2025 through Release SOLIDWORKS Desktop 2026</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1334</link><description>An Out-Of-Bounds Read vulnerability affecting the EPRT file reading procedure in SOLIDWORKS eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS Desktop 2025 through Release SOLIDWORKS Desktop 2026 could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code while opening a specially crafted EPRT file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1335 | Out-Of-Bounds Write vulnerability affecting the EPRT file reading procedure in SOLIDWORKS eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS Desktop 2025 through Release SOLIDWORKS Desktop 2026</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1335</link><description>An Out-Of-Bounds Write vulnerability affecting the EPRT file reading procedure in SOLIDWORKS eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS Desktop 2025 through Release SOLIDWORKS Desktop 2026 could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code while opening a specially crafted EPRT file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2558 | GeekAI net_handler.go Download server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2558</link><description>A flaw has been found in GeekAI up to 4.2.4. The affected element is the function Download of the file api/handler/net_handler.go. This manipulation of the argument url causes server-side request forgery. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2557 | cskefu File Upload MediaController.java upload cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2557</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in cskefu up to 8.0.1. Impacted is the function Upload of the file com/cskefu/cc/controller/resource/MediaController.java of the component File Upload. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2556 | cskefu Endpoint MediaController.java server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2556</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in cskefu up to 8.0.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file com/cskefu/cc/controller/resource/MediaController.java of the component Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:47:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14350 | Information disclosure via channel mentions in posts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14350</link><description>Mattermost versions 11.1.x &lt;= 11.1.2, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.9, 11.2.x &lt;= 11.2.1 fail to properly validate team membership when processing channel mentions which allows authenticated users to determine the existence of teams and their URL names via posting channel shortlinks and observing the channel_mentions property in the API response. Mattermost Advisory ID: MMSA-2025-00563</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14573 | Team Admin Bypass of Invite Permissions via allow_open_invite Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14573</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.9 fail to enforce invite permissions when updating team settings, which allows team administrators without proper permissions to bypass restrictions and add users to their team via API requests. Mattermost Advisory ID: MMSA-2025-00561</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1046 | Arbitrary application execution via unvalidated server-controlled URLs in Help menu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1046</link><description>Mattermost Desktop App versions &lt;=6.0 6.2.0 5.2.13.0 fail to validate help links which allows a malicious Mattermost server to execute arbitrary executables on a user’s system via the user clicking on certain items in the Help menu Mattermost Advisory ID: MMSA-2026-00577</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13821 | User profile update exposes password hash and MFA secrets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13821</link><description>Mattermost versions 11.1.x &lt;= 11.1.2, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.9, 11.2.x &lt;= 11.2.1 fail to sanitize sensitive data in WebSocket messages which allows authenticated users to exfiltrate password hashes and MFA secrets via profile nickname updates or email verification events. Mattermost Advisory ID: MMSA-2025-00560</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2555 | JeecgBoot Retrieval-Augmented Generation AiragKnowledgeController.java importDocumentFromZip deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2555</link><description>A weakness has been identified in JeecgBoot 3.9.1. This vulnerability affects the function importDocumentFromZip of the file org/jeecg/modules/airag/llm/controller/AiragKnowledgeController.java of the component Retrieval-Augmented Generation. Executing a manipulation can lead to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2418 | Open Redirect in TR7&amp;#x27;s Web Application Firewall</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2418</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in TR7 Cyber ​​Defense Inc. Web Application Firewall allows Phishing.This issue affects Web Application Firewall: from 4.30 through 16022026.

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2553 | tushar-2223 Hotel-Management-System HTTP POST Request home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2553</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in tushar-2223 Hotel-Management-System up to bb1f3b3666124b888f1e4bcf51b6fba9fbb01d15. This affects an unknown part of the file /home.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. Performing a manipulation of the argument Name/Email results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2552 | ZenTao Editor control.php delete path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2552</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in ZenTao up to 21.7.8. Affected by this issue is the function delete of the file editor/control.php of the component Committer. Such manipulation of the argument filePath leads to path traversal. Upgrading to version 21.7.9 can resolve this issue. The affected component should be upgraded.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2415 | Unsafe variable evaluation in email templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2415</link><description>Emails sent by pretix can utilize placeholders that will be filled with customer data. For example, when {name}
 is used in an email template, it will  be replaced with the buyer's 
name for the final email. This mechanism contained two security-relevant
 bugs:



  *  
It was possible to exfiltrate information about the pretix system through specially crafted placeholder names such as {{event.__init__.__code__.co_filename}}.
 This way, an attacker with the ability to control email templates 
(usually every user of the pretix backend) could retrieve sensitive 
information from the system configuration, including even database 
passwords or API keys. pretix does include mechanisms to prevent the usage of such 
malicious placeholders, however due to a mistake in the code, they were 
not fully effective for the email subject.




  *  
Placeholders in subjects and plain text bodies of emails were 
wrongfully evaluated twice. Therefore, if the first evaluation of a 
placeholder again contains a placeholder, this second placeholder was 
rendered. This allows the rendering of placeholders controlled by the 
ticket buyer, and therefore the exploitation of the first issue as a 
ticket buyer. Luckily, the only buyer-controlled placeholder available 
in pretix by default (that is not validated in a way that prevents the 
issue) is {invoice_company}, which is very unusual (but not
 impossible) to be contained in an email subject template. In addition 
to broadening the attack surface of the first issue, this could 
theoretically also leak information about an order to one of the 
attendees within that order. However, we also consider this scenario 
very unlikely under typical conditions.


Out of caution, we recommend that you rotate all passwords and API keys contained in your  pretix.cfg https://docs.pretix.eu/self-hosting/config/  file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:03:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2451 | Unsafe variable evaluation in email templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2451</link><description>Emails sent by pretix can utilize placeholders that will be filled with customer data. For example, when {name}
 is used in an email template, it will  be replaced with the buyer's 
name for the final email. This mechanism contained a security-relevant bug:

It was possible to exfiltrate information about the pretix system through specially crafted placeholder names such as {{event.__init__.__code__.co_filename}}.
 This way, an attacker with the ability to control email templates 
(usually every user of the pretix backend) could retrieve sensitive 
information from the system configuration, including even database 
passwords or API keys. pretix does include mechanisms to prevent the usage of such 
malicious placeholders, however due to a mistake in the code, they were 
not fully effective for this plugin.

Out of caution, we recommend that you rotate all passwords and API keys contained in your pretix.cfg file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:03:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2452 | Unsafe variable evaluation in email templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2452</link><description>Emails sent by pretix can utilize placeholders that will be filled with customer data. For example, when {name}
 is used in an email template, it will  be replaced with the buyer's 
name for the final email. This mechanism contained a security-relevant bug:

It was possible to exfiltrate information about the pretix system through specially crafted placeholder names such as {{event.__init__.__code__.co_filename}}.
 This way, an attacker with the ability to control email templates 
(usually every user of the pretix backend) could retrieve sensitive 
information from the system configuration, including even database 
passwords or API keys. pretix does include mechanisms to prevent the usage of such 
malicious placeholders, however due to a mistake in the code, they were 
not fully effective for this plugin.

Out of caution, we recommend that you rotate all passwords and API keys contained in your  pretix.cfg https://docs.pretix.eu/self-hosting/config/  file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:03:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2551 | ZenTao Backup control.php delete path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2551</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in ZenTao up to 21.7.8. Affected by this vulnerability is the function delete of the file editor/control.php of the component Backup Handler. This manipulation of the argument fileName causes path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:03:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59903 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Kubysoft</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59903</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Kubysoft, where uploaded SVG images are not properly sanitized. This allows attackers to embed malicious scripts within SVG files as visual content, which are then stored on the server and executed in the context of any user accessing the compromised resource.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:03:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59904 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Kubysoft</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59904</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Kubysoft, which is triggered through multiple parameters in the '/kForms/app' endpoint. This issue allows malicious scripts to be injected and executed persistently in the context of users accessing the affected resource.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:03:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0997 | Mattermost Zoom Plugin channel preference API lacks authorization checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0997</link><description>Mattermost versions 11.1.x &lt;= 11.1.2, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.9, 11.2.x &lt;= 11.2.1 and Mattermost Plugin Zoom versions &lt;=1.11.0 fail to validate the authenticated user when processing {{/plugins/zoom/api/v1/channel-preference}}, which allows any logged-in user to change Zoom meeting restrictions for arbitrary channels via crafted API requests.. Mattermost Advisory ID: MMSA-2025-00558</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:03:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0998 | Mattermost Zoom Plugin allows unauthorized meeting creation and post modification via insufficient API access controls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0998</link><description>Mattermost versions 11.1.x &lt;= 11.1.2, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.9, 11.2.x &lt;= 11.2.1 and Mattermost Plugin Zoom versions &lt;=1.11.0 fail to validate user identity and post ownership in the {{/api/v1/askPMI}} endpoint which allows unauthorized users to start Zoom meetings as any user and overwrite arbitrary posts via direct API calls with manipulated user IDs and post data.. Mattermost Advisory ID: MMSA-2025-00534</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:03:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2550 | EFM iptime A6004MX timepro.cgi commit_vpncli_file_upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2550</link><description>A vulnerability was found in EFM iptime A6004MX 14.18.2. Affected is the function commit_vpncli_file_upload of the file /cgi/timepro.cgi. The manipulation results in unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:03:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2577 | Nanobot Unauthenticated WhatsApp Session Hijack via WebSocket Bridge</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2577</link><description>The WhatsApp bridge component in Nanobot binds the WebSocket server to all network interfaces (0.0.0.0) on port 3001 by default and does not require authentication for incoming connections. An unauthenticated remote attacker with network access to the bridge can connect to the WebSocket server to hijack the WhatsApp session. This allows the attacker to send messages on behalf of the user, intercept all incoming messages and media in real-time, and capture authentication QR codes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:03:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59905 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Kubysoft</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59905</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability reflected in Kubysoft, which occurs through multiple parameters within the endpoint ‘/node/kudaby/nodeFN/procedure’. This flaw allows the injection of arbitrary client-side scripts, which are immediately reflected in the HTTP response and executed in the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0999 | Authentication bypass via userID login when email and username login are disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0999</link><description>Mattermost versions 11.1.x &lt;= 11.1.2, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.9, 11.2.x &lt;= 11.2.1 fail to properly validate login method restrictions which allows an authenticated user to bypass SSO-only login requirements via userID-based authentication. Mattermost Advisory ID: MMSA-2025-00548</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2549 | zhanghuanhao LibrarySystem 图书馆管理系统 BookController.java access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2549</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in zhanghuanhao LibrarySystem 图书馆管理系统 up to 1.1.1. This impacts an unknown function of the file BookController.java. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2548 | WAYOS FBM-220G rc sub_40F820 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2548</link><description>A flaw has been found in WAYOS FBM-220G 24.10.19. This affects the function sub_40F820 of the file rc. Executing a manipulation of the argument upnp_waniface/upnp_ssdp_interval/upnp_max_age can lead to command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:05:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2547 | LigeroSmart index.pl AgentDashboard cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2547</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in LigeroSmart up to 6.1.26. The impacted element is the function AgentDashboard of the file /otrs/index.pl. Performing a manipulation of the argument Subaction results in cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:02:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2546 | LigeroSmart index.pl cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2546</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in LigeroSmart up to 6.1.26. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /otrs/index.pl. Such manipulation of the argument SortBy leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:02:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2544 | yued-fe LuLu UI run.js child_process.exec os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2544</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in yued-fe LuLu UI up to 3.0.0. This issue affects the function child_process.exec of the file run.js. The manipulation results in os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:03:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2545 | LigeroSmart index.pl cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2545</link><description>A weakness has been identified in LigeroSmart up to 6.1.26. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /otrs/index.pl?Action=AgentTicketSearch. This manipulation of the argument Profile causes cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:03:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2543 | vichan-devel vichan Password Change pages.php unverified password change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2543</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in vichan-devel vichan up to 5.1.5. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file inc/mod/pages.php of the component Password Change Handler. The manipulation of the argument Password leads to unverified password change. The attack can be initiated remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 07:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2542 | Total VPN win-service.exe unquoted search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2542</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Total VPN 0.5.29.0 on Windows. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file C:\Program Files\Total VPN\win-service.exe. Executing a manipulation can lead to unquoted search path. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 07:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0929 | RegistrationMagic &amp;lt; 6.0.7.2 - Subscriber+ Form Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0929</link><description>The RegistrationMagic  WordPress plugin before 6.0.7.2 does not have proper capability checks, allowing subscribers and above to create forms on the site.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 07:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2538 | Flos Freeware Notepad2 Msimg32.dll uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2538</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Flos Freeware Notepad2 4.2.22/4.2.23/4.2.24/4.2.25. Affected is an unknown function in the library Msimg32.dll. Performing a manipulation results in uncontrolled search path. Attacking locally is a requirement. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 07:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2537 | Comfast CF-E4 HTTP POST Request mbox-config command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2537</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Comfast CF-E4 2.6.0.1. This impacts an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/mbox-config?method=SET&amp;amp;section=ntp_timezone of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. Such manipulation of the argument timestr leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:03:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2536 | opencc JFlow Workflow WF_Admin_AttrFlow.java Imp_Done xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2536</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in opencc JFlow up to 20260129. This affects the function Imp_Done of the file src/main/java/bp/wf/httphandler/WF_Admin_AttrFlow.java of the component Workflow Engine. This manipulation of the argument File causes xml external entity reference. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:03:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2535 | Comfast CF-N1 V2 mbox-config sub_44AB9C command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2535</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Comfast CF-N1 V2 2.6.0.2. The impacted element is the function sub_44AB9C of the file /cgi-bin/mbox-config?method=SET&amp;amp;section=ptest_channel. The manipulation of the argument channel results in command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2533 | Tosei Self-service Washing Machine tosei_datasend.php command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2533</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tosei Self-service Washing Machine 4.02. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/tosei_datasend.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument adr_txt_1 can lead to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2534 | Comfast CF-N1 V2 mbox-config sub_44AC4C command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2534</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Comfast CF-N1 V2 2.6.0.2. The affected element is the function sub_44AC4C of the file /cgi-bin/mbox-config?method=SET&amp;amp;section=ptest_bandwidth. The manipulation of the argument bandwidth leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2530 | Wavlink WL-WN579A3 wireless.cgi AddMac command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2530</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Wavlink WL-WN579A3 up to 20210219. This affects the function AddMac of the file /cgi-bin/wireless.cgi. This manipulation of the argument macAddr causes command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2531 | MindsDB File Upload security.py clear_filename server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2531</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in MindsDB up to 25.14.1. This vulnerability affects the function clear_filename of the file mindsdb/utilities/security.py of the component File Upload. Such manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The name of the patch is 74d6f0fd4b630218519a700fbee1c05c7fd4b1ed. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2532 | lintsinghua DeepAudit IP Address embedding_config.py server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2532</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in lintsinghua DeepAudit up to 3.0.3. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file backend/app/api/v1/endpoints/embedding_config.py of the component IP Address Handler. Performing a manipulation results in server-side request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 3.0.4 and 3.1.0 is capable of addressing this issue. The patch is named da853fdd8cbe9d42053b45d83f25708ba29b8b27. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2527 | Wavlink WL-WN579A3 login.cgi command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2527</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Wavlink WL-WN579A3 up to 20210219. Affected is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/login.cgi. Executing a manipulation of the argument key can lead to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2528 | Wavlink WL-WN579A3 wireless.cgi Delete_Mac_list command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2528</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Wavlink WL-WN579A3 up to 20210219. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Delete_Mac_list of the file /cgi-bin/wireless.cgi. The manipulation of the argument delete_list leads to command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2529 | Wavlink WL-WN579A3 wireless.cgi DeleteMac command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2529</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Wavlink WL-WN579A3 up to 20210219. Affected by this issue is the function DeleteMac of the file /cgi-bin/wireless.cgi. The manipulation of the argument delete_list results in command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2525 | Free5GC PFCP UDP Endpoint denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2525</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Free5GC up to 4.1.0. This affects an unknown function of the component PFCP UDP Endpoint. Such manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2526 | Wavlink WL-WN579A3 wireless.cgi multi_ssid command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2526</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Wavlink WL-WN579A3 up to 20210219. This impacts the function multi_ssid of the file /cgi-bin/wireless.cgi. Performing a manipulation of the argument SSID2G2 results in command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2523 | Open5GS SMF gn-handler.c smf_gn_handle_create_pdp_context_request assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2523</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. The affected element is the function smf_gn_handle_create_pdp_context_request of the file /src/smf/gn-handler.c of the component SMF. The manipulation results in reachable assertion. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2524 | Open5GS MME mme_s11_handle_create_session_response denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2524</link><description>A flaw has been found in Open5GS 2.7.6. The impacted element is the function mme_s11_handle_create_session_response of the component MME. This manipulation causes denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>