<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:09:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-24480 | FactoryTalk® View Machine Editon - Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24480</link><description>A Remote Code Execution Vulnerability exists in the product and version listed above. The vulnerability is due to lack of input sanitation and could allow a remote attacker to run commands or code as a high privileged user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24479 | FactoryTalk® View Machine Edition - Local Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24479</link><description>A Local Code Execution Vulnerability exists in the product and version listed above. The vulnerability is due to a default setting in Windows and allows access to the Command Prompt as a higher privileged user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 18:56:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24478 | A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the affected products. The vulnerability could allow a remote, non-privileged user to send malic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24478</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the affected products. The vulnerability could allow a remote, non-privileged user to send malicious requests resulting in a major nonrecoverable fault causing a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 18:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0783 | pankajindevops scale API Endpoint access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0783</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in pankajindevops scale up to 20241113. This affects an unknown part of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 18:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22217 | Avi Load Balancer contains an unauthenticated blind SQL Injection vulnerability which was privately reported to VMware. Patches are availabl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22217</link><description>Avi Load Balancer contains an unauthenticated blind SQL Injection vulnerability which was privately reported to VMware. Patches are available to remediate this vulnerability in affected VMware products. 

A malicious user with network access may be able to use specially crafted SQL queries to gain database access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 18:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0631 | PowerFlex® 755 Credential Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0631</link><description>A Credential Exposure Vulnerability exists in the above-mentioned product and version. The vulnerability is due to using HTTP resulting in credentials being sent in clear text.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 18:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13484 | Argocd: namespace isolation break</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13484</link><description>A flaw was found in ArgoCD. The openshift.io/cluster-monitoring label is applied to all namespaces that deploy an ArgoCD CR instance, allowing the namespace to create a rogue PrometheusRule. This issue can have adverse effects on the platform monitoring stack, as the rule is rolled out cluster-wide when the label is applied.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23053 | Authenticated privilege escalation via broken access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23053</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the web-based management interface of HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composer. Successful exploitation could allow an authenticated low privilege operator user to change the state of certain settings of a vulnerable system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:29:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23054 | Authenticated Response Manipulation allows Unauthorized Actions in Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23054</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composer could allow an authenticated low privilege operator user to perform operations not allowed by their privilege level. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to manipulate user generated files, potentially leading to unauthorized changes in critical system configurations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23055 | Authenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composer Web Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23055</link><description>A vulnerability in the web management interface of HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composer could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack. If successfully exploited, a threat actor could run arbitrary script code in a victim's web browser within the context of the compromised interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23056 | Authenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composer Web Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23056</link><description>A vulnerability in the web management interface of HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composer could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack. If successfully exploited, a threat actor could run arbitrary script code in a victim's web browser within the context of the compromised interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23057 | Authenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composer Web Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23057</link><description>A vulnerability in the web management interface of HPE Aruba Networking Fabric Composer could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack. If successfully exploited, a threat actor could run arbitrary script code in a victim's web browser within the context of the compromised interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-13317 | In HeifDecoderImpl::getScanline of HeifDecoderImpl.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper input validation. This could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13317</link><description>In HeifDecoderImpl::getScanline of HeifDecoderImpl.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-13318 | In HeifDataSource::readAt of HeifDecoderImpl.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an integer overflow. This could lead to remo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13318</link><description>In HeifDataSource::readAt of HeifDecoderImpl.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an integer overflow. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9373 | In TdlsexRxFrameHandle of the MTK WLAN driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9373</link><description>In TdlsexRxFrameHandle of the MTK WLAN driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9378 | In BnAudioPolicyService::onTransact of IAudioPolicyService.cpp, there is a possible information disclosure due to uninitialized data. This c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9378</link><description>In BnAudioPolicyService::onTransact of IAudioPolicyService.cpp, there is a possible information disclosure due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8401 | CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (‘Cross-site Scripting’)
vulnerability exists when an authenticated atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8401</link><description>CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (‘Cross-site Scripting’)
vulnerability exists when an authenticated attacker modifies folder names within the context of
the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 16:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0781 | Incorrect Authorization in SimGear</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0781</link><description>An attacker can bypass the sandboxing of Nasal scripts and arbitrarily write to any file path that the user has permission to modify at the operating-system level.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 16:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23385 | In JetBrains ReSharper before 2024.3.4, 2024.2.8, and 2024.1.7, Rider before 2024.3.4, 2024.2.8, and 2024.1.7, dotTrace before 2024.3.4, 202...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23385</link><description>In JetBrains ReSharper before 2024.3.4, 2024.2.8, and 2024.1.7, Rider before 2024.3.4, 2024.2.8, and 2024.1.7, dotTrace before 2024.3.4, 2024.2.8, and 2024.1.7, ETW Host Service before 16.43, Local Privilege Escalation via the ETW Host Service was possible</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 16:13:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0432 | HMS Networks Ewon Flexy 202 Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0432</link><description>EWON Flexy 202 transmits user credentials in clear text with no encryption when a user is added, or user credentials are changed via its webpage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 16:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24800 | Critical vulnerability in `ismp-grandpa` &amp;lt;v15.0.1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24800</link><description>Hyperbridge is a hyper-scalable coprocessor for verifiable, cross-chain interoperability. A critical vulnerability was discovered in the ismp-grandpa crate, that allowed a malicious prover easily convince the verifier of the finality of arbitrary headers. This could be used to steal funds or compromise other kinds of cross-chain applications. This vulnerability is fixed in 15.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 15:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23212 | Tandoor Recipes - Local file disclosure - Users can read the content of any file on the server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23212</link><description>Tandoor Recipes is an application for managing recipes, planning meals, and building shopping lists. The external storage feature allows any user to enumerate the name and content of files on the server. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.28.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 15:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23213 | Tandoor Recipes - Stored XSS through Unrestricted File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23213</link><description>Tandoor Recipes is an application for managing recipes, planning meals, and building shopping lists. The file upload feature allows to upload arbitrary files, including html and svg. Both can contain malicious content (XSS Payloads). This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.28.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 15:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23045 | CVAT allows remote code execution via tracker Nuclio functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23045</link><description>Computer Vision Annotation Tool (CVAT) is an interactive video and image annotation tool for computer vision. An attacker with an account on an affected CVAT instance is able to run arbitrary code in the context of the Nuclio function container. This vulnerability affects CVAT deployments that run any of the serverless functions of type tracker from the CVAT Git repository, namely TransT and SiamMask. Deployments with custom functions of type tracker may also be affected, depending on how they handle state serialization. If a function uses an unsafe serialization library such as pickle or jsonpickle, it's likely to be vulnerable. Upgrade to CVAT 2.26.0 or later. If you are unable to upgrade, shut down any instances of the TransT or SiamMask functions you're running.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 15:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23211 | Tandoor Recipes - SSTI - Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23211</link><description>Tandoor Recipes is an application for managing recipes, planning meals, and building shopping lists. A Jinja2 SSTI vulnerability allows any user to execute commands on the server. In the case of the provided Docker Compose file as root. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.24.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 15:32:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0659 | Path Traversal and Rockwell Automation Third-party Vulnerability in DataMosaix™ Private Cloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0659</link><description>A path
traversal vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation DataEdge Platform DataMosaix Private Cloud. By specifying the character
sequence in the body of the vulnerable endpoint, it is possible to overwrite
files outside of the intended directory. A threat actor with admin privileges could
leverage this vulnerability to overwrite reports including user projects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 15:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7881 | An unprivileged context can trigger a data
memory-dependent prefetch engine to fetch the contents of a privileged location
and consume those...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7881</link><description>An unprivileged context can trigger a data
memory-dependent prefetch engine to fetch the contents of a privileged location
and consume those contents as an address that is also dereferenced.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 15:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6351 | Malformed packet leads to denial of service in NWK/APS layer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6351</link><description>A malformed packet can cause a buffer overflow in the NWK/APS layer of the Ember ZNet stack and lead to an assert</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 14:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11956 | Pimcore customer-data-framework list sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11956</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Pimcore customer-data-framework up to 4.2.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/customermanagementframework/customers/list. The manipulation of the argument filterDefinition/filter leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.2.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 13:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11954 | Pimcore Search Document cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11954</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Pimcore 11.4.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Search Document. The manipulation leads to basic cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 13:34:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0065 | Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in TeamViewer Clients</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0065</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in the TeamViewer_service.exe component of TeamViewer Clients prior version 15.62 for Windows allows an attacker with local unprivileged access on a Windows system to elevate privileges via argument injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 10:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0754 | Envoyproxy: openshift service mesh 2.6.3 and 2.5.6 envoy header handling allows log injection and potential spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0754</link><description>The vulnerability was found in OpenShift Service Mesh 2.6.3 and 2.5.6. This issue occurs due to improper sanitization of HTTP headers by Envoy, particularly the x-forwarded-for header. This lack of sanitization can allow attackers to inject malicious payloads into service mesh logs, leading to log injection and spoofing attacks. Such injections can mislead logging mechanisms, enabling attackers to manipulate log entries or execute reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 09:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0750 | Cri-o: cri-o path traversal in log handling functions allows arbitrary unmounting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0750</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CRI-O. A path traversal issue in the log management functions (UnMountPodLogs and LinkContainerLogs) may allow an attacker with permissions to create and delete Pods to unmount arbitrary host paths, leading to node-level denial of service by unmounting critical system directories.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 09:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0752 | Envoyproxy: openshift service mesh envoy http header sanitization bypass leading to dos and unauthorized access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0752</link><description>A flaw was found in OpenShift Service Mesh 2.6.3 and 2.5.6. Rate-limiter avoidance, access-control bypass, CPU and memory exhaustion, and replay attacks may be possible due to improper HTTP header sanitization in Envoy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 09:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23953 | Apache Hive: Timing Attack Against Signature in LLAP util</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23953</link><description>Use of Arrays.equals() in LlapSignerImpl in Apache Hive to compare message signatures allows attacker to forge a valid signature for an arbitrary message byte by byte. The attacker should be an authorized user of the product to perform this attack. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.0.0, which fixes this issue.

The problem occurs when an application doesn’t use a constant-time algorithm for validating a signature. The method Arrays.equals() returns false right away when it sees that one of the input’s bytes are different. It means that the comparison time depends on the contents of the arrays. This little thing may allow an attacker to forge a valid signature for an arbitrary message byte by byte. So it might allow malicious users to submit splits/work with selected signatures to LLAP without running as a privileged user, potentially leading to DDoS attack.

More details in the reference section.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 09:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0736 | Org.infinispan-infinispan-parent: exposure of sensitive information in application logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0736</link><description>A flaw was found in Infinispan, when using JGroups with JDBC_PING. This issue occurs when an application inadvertently exposes sensitive information, such as configuration details or credentials, through logging mechanisms. This exposure can lead to unauthorized access and exploitation by malicious actors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 09:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0290 | Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition (&amp;#x27;Infinite Loop&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0290</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.0 prior to 17.5.5, from 17.6 prior to 17.6.3, and from 17.7 prior to 17.7.1. Under certain conditions, processing of CI artifacts metadata could cause background jobs to become unresponsive.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 08:53:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13527 | Philantro – Donations and Donor Management &amp;lt;= 5.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via donate Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13527</link><description>The Philantro – Donations and Donor Management plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes like 'donate' in all versions up to, and including, 5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 08:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13521 | MailUp Auto Subscription &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13521</link><description>The MailUp Auto Subscription plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the mas_options function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 07:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0321 | ElementsKit Pro &amp;lt;= 3.7.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via url Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0321</link><description>The ElementsKit Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 07:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13448 | ThemeREX Addons &amp;lt;= 2.32.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload in trx_addons_uploads_save_data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13448</link><description>The ThemeREX Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'trx_addons_uploads_save_data' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.32.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 06:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13509 | WS Form LITE – Drag &amp;amp; Drop Contact Form Builder for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.10.13 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13509</link><description>The WS Form LITE – Drag &amp; Drop Contact Form Builder for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the url parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.10.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. NOTE: This vulnerability is partially fixed in 1.10.13 and completely fixed in 1.10.14.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 06:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12723 | Infility Global &amp;lt;= 2.9.8 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12723</link><description>The Infility Global WordPress plugin through 2.9.8 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 06:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12807 | Social Share Buttons for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12807</link><description>The Social Share Buttons for WordPress plugin through 2.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 06:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24810 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Simple Image Sizes 3.2.3 and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24810</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Simple Image Sizes 3.2.3 and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who is logging in to the product with the administrative privilege and accessing the settings screen.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 04:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23084 | A vulnerability has been identified in Node.js, specifically affecting the handling of drive names in the Windows environment. Certain Node....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23084</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Node.js, specifically affecting the handling of drive names in the Windows environment. Certain Node.js functions do not treat drive names as special on Windows. As a result, although Node.js assumes a relative path, it actually refers to the root directory.

On Windows, a path that does not start with the file separator is treated as relative to the current directory. 

This vulnerability affects Windows users of `path.join` API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 04:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11135 | Eventer &amp;lt;= 3.9.8 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11135</link><description>The Eventer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'event' parameter in the 'eventer_get_attendees' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.8 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 04:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0146 | NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where a malicious guest could cause memory corruption. A successfu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0146</link><description>NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where a malicious guest could cause memory corruption. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, or data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 04:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53869 | NVIDIA Unified Memory driver for Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker could leak uninitialized memory. A successful exploit of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53869</link><description>NVIDIA Unified Memory driver for Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker could leak uninitialized memory. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 04:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53881 | NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the host driver, where it can allow a guest to cause an interrupt storm on the host, which ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53881</link><description>NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the host driver, where it can allow a guest to cause an interrupt storm on the host, which may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 04:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0149 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability which could allow an attacker unauthorized access to files. A successful exploi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0149</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability which could allow an attacker unauthorized access to files. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to limited information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 04:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0147 | NVIDIA GPU display driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where referencing memory after it has been freed can lead to denial...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0147</link><description>NVIDIA GPU display driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where referencing memory after it has been freed can lead to denial of service or data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 03:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0150 | NVIDIA GPU display driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where data is written past the end or before the beginning of a buf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0150</link><description>NVIDIA GPU display driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where data is written past the end or before the beginning of a buffer. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, denial of service, or data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 03:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0140 | NVIDIA RAPIDS contains a vulnerability in cuDF and cuML, where a user could cause a deserialization of untrusted data issue. A successful ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0140</link><description>NVIDIA RAPIDS contains a vulnerability in cuDF and cuML, where a user could cause a deserialization of untrusted data issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, data tampering, denial of service, and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 03:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0135 | NVIDIA Container Toolkit contains an improper isolation vulnerability where a specially crafted container image could lead to modification o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0135</link><description>NVIDIA Container Toolkit contains an improper isolation vulnerability where a specially crafted container image could lead to modification of a host binary. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 03:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0136 | NVIDIA Container Toolkit contains an improper isolation vulnerability where a specially crafted container image could lead to untrusted code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0136</link><description>NVIDIA Container Toolkit contains an improper isolation vulnerability where a specially crafted container image could lead to untrusted code obtaining read and write access to host devices. This vulnerability is present only when the NVIDIA Container Toolkit is configured in a nondefault way. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 03:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0137 | NVIDIA Container Toolkit contains an improper isolation vulnerability where a specially crafted container image could lead to untrusted code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0137</link><description>NVIDIA Container Toolkit contains an improper isolation vulnerability where a specially crafted container image could lead to untrusted code running in the host’s network namespace. This vulnerability is present only when the NVIDIA Container Toolkit is configured in a nondefault way. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service and escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 03:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22315 | IBM Fusion improper communication restriction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22315</link><description>IBM Fusion and IBM Fusion HCI 2.3.0 through 2.8.2 is vulnerable to insecure network connection by allowing an attacker who gains access to a Fusion container to establish an external network connection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 02:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45336 | Sensitive headers incorrectly sent after cross-domain redirect in net/http</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45336</link><description>The HTTP client drops sensitive headers after following a cross-domain redirect. For example, a request to a.com/ containing an Authorization header which is redirected to b.com/ will not send that header to b.com. In the event that the client received a subsequent same-domain redirect, however, the sensitive headers would be restored. For example, a chain of redirects from a.com/, to b.com/1, and finally to b.com/2 would incorrectly send the Authorization header to b.com/2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 02:14:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45339 | Vulnerability when creating log files in github.com/golang/glog</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45339</link><description>When logs are written to a widely-writable directory (the default), an unprivileged attacker may predict a privileged process's log file path and pre-create a symbolic link to a sensitive file in its place. When that privileged process runs, it will follow the planted symlink and overwrite that sensitive file. To fix that, glog now causes the program to exit (with status code 2) when it finds that the configured log file already exists.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 02:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45340 | GOAUTH credential leak in cmd/go</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45340</link><description>Credentials provided via the new GOAUTH feature were not being properly segmented by domain, allowing a malicious server to request credentials they should not have access to. By default, unless otherwise set, this only affected credentials stored in the users .netrc file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 02:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45341 | Usage of IPv6 zone IDs can bypass URI name constraints in crypto/x509</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45341</link><description>A certificate with a URI which has a IPv6 address with a zone ID may incorrectly satisfy a URI name constraint that applies to the certificate chain. Certificates containing URIs are not permitted in the web PKI, so this only affects users of private PKIs which make use of URIs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 02:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22865 | ParsePKCS1PrivateKey panic with partial keys in crypto/x509</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22865</link><description>Using ParsePKCS1PrivateKey to parse a RSA key that is missing the CRT values would panic when verifying that the key is well formed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 02:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12647 | Buffer overflow in CPCA font download processing of Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12647</link><description>Buffer overflow in CPCA font download processing of Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code. *: Satera MF656Cdw/Satera MF654Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in Japan. Color imageCLASS MF656Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF654Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF653Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF652Cdw/Color imageCLASS LBP633Cdw/Color imageCLASS LBP632Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in US. i-SENSYS MF657Cdw/i-SENSYS MF655Cdw/i-SENSYS MF651Cdw/i-SENSYS LBP633Cdw/i-SENSYS LBP631Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 01:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12648 | Buffer overflow in TIFF data EXIF tag processing of Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12648</link><description>Buffer overflow in TIFF data EXIF tag processing of Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code. *: Satera MF656Cdw/Satera MF654Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in Japan. Color imageCLASS MF656Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF654Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF653Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF652Cdw/Color imageCLASS LBP633Cdw/Color imageCLASS LBP632Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in US. i-SENSYS MF657Cdw/i-SENSYS MF655Cdw/i-SENSYS MF651Cdw/i-SENSYS LBP633Cdw/i-SENSYS LBP631Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 01:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12649 | Buffer overflow in XPS data font processing of Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12649</link><description>Buffer overflow in XPS data font processing of Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code. *: Satera MF656Cdw/Satera MF654Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in Japan. Color imageCLASS MF656Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF654Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF653Cdw/Color imageCLASS MF652Cdw/Color imageCLASS LBP633Cdw/Color imageCLASS LBP632Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in US. i-SENSYS MF657Cdw/i-SENSYS MF655Cdw/i-SENSYS MF651Cdw/i-SENSYS LBP633Cdw/i-SENSYS LBP631Cdw firmware v05.04 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 01:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-3365 | Emote Interactive Remote Mouse Server command injection due to weak encoding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3365</link><description>Due to reliance on a trivial substitution cipher, sent in cleartext, and the reliance on a default password when the user does not set a password, the Remote Mouse Server by Emote Interactive can be abused by attackers to inject OS commands over theproduct's custom control protocol. A Metasploit module was written and tested against version 4.110, the current version when this CVE was reserved.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 01:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50316 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50316</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.5 and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.1
is vulnerable to SQL injection. A remote attacker could send specially crafted SQL statements, which could allow the attacker to view, add, modify or delete information in the back-end database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 01:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27263 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27263</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.5 and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.1 could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive information from the dashboard UI using man in the middle techniques.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 01:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28786 | IBM QRadar SIEM information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28786</link><description>IBM QRadar SIEM 7.5 transmits sensitive or security-critical data in cleartext in a communication channel that could be obtained by an unauthorized actor using man in the middle techniques.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 23:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-31749 | Authenticated arbitrary file read/write in WatchGuard Fireware OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31749</link><description>An argument injection vulnerability in the diagnose and import pac commands in WatchGuard Fireware OS before 12.8.1, 12.1.4, and 12.5.10 allows an authenticated remote attacker with unprivileged credentials to upload or read files to limited, arbitrary locations on WatchGuard Firebox and XTM appliances</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 23:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24369 | Anubis has a bot protection bypass when a sophisticated attacker asks to pass a challenge of difficulty 0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24369</link><description>Anubis is a tool that allows administrators to protect bots against AI scrapers through bot-checking heuristics and a proof-of-work challenge to discourage scraping from multiple IP addresses. Anubis allows attackers to bypass the bot protection by requesting a challenge, formulates any nonce (such as 42069), and then passes the challenge with difficulty zero. Commit e09d0226a628f04b1d80fd83bee777894a45cd02 fixes this behavior by not using a client-specified difficulty value.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 23:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57052 | An issue in youdiancms v.9.5.20 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the sessionID parameter in the index.php file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57052</link><description>An issue in youdiancms v.9.5.20 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the sessionID parameter in the index.php file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 23:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56178 | An issue was discovered in Couchbase Server 7.6.x through 7.6.3. A user with the security_admin_local role can create a new user in a group ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56178</link><description>An issue was discovered in Couchbase Server 7.6.x through 7.6.3. A user with the security_admin_local role can create a new user in a group that has the admin role.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 22:53:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56316 | In AXESS ACS (Auto Configuration Server) through 5.2.0, unsanitized user input in the TR069 API allows remote unauthenticated attackers to c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56316</link><description>In AXESS ACS (Auto Configuration Server) through 5.2.0, unsanitized user input in the TR069 API allows remote unauthenticated attackers to cause a permanent Denial of Service via crafted TR069 requests on TCP port 9675 or 7547. Rebooting does not resolve the permanent Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 22:53:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57547 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in CMSimple v.5.16 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the F...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57547</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in CMSimple v.5.16 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the Functionality of downloading php backup files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 22:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57548 | CMSimple 5.16 allows the user to edit log.php file via print page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57548</link><description>CMSimple 5.16 allows the user to edit log.php file via print page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 22:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57549 | CMSimple 5.16 allows the user to read cms source code through manipulation of the file name in the file parameter of a GET request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57549</link><description>CMSimple 5.16 allows the user to read cms source code through manipulation of the file name in the file parameter of a GET request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 22:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57546 | An issue in CMSimple v.5.16 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the validate link function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57546</link><description>An issue in CMSimple v.5.16 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the validate link function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 22:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48662 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in AdGuard Application v.7.18.1 (4778) and before allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48662</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in AdGuard Application v.7.18.1 (4778) and before allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the fontMatrix component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 22:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54728 | Incorrect access control in BYD QIN PLUS DM-i Dilink OS 3.0_13.1.7.2204050.1 allows unauthorized attackers to access system logcat logs.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54728</link><description>Incorrect access control in BYD QIN PLUS DM-i Dilink OS 3.0_13.1.7.2204050.1 allows unauthorized attackers to access system logcat logs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 22:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57373 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in LifestyleStore v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary cod and obtain sensitive info...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57373</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in LifestyleStore v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary cod and obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 22:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37526 | IBM Watson Query on Cloud Pak for Data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37526</link><description>IBM Watson Query on Cloud Pak for Data (IBM Data Virtualization 1.8, 2.0, 2.1, 2.2, and 3.0.0) could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive information from objects published using Watson Query due to an improper data protection mechanism.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44172 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonom...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44172</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access contacts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54468 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.2, tvOS 18.2, watchOS 11.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54468</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.2, tvOS 18.2, watchOS 11.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2, iPadOS 17.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54475 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54475</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, macOS Ventura 13.7.2. An app may be able to determine a user’s current location.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54478 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, visionOS 2.2, tvOS 18.2, wa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54478</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, visionOS 2.2, tvOS 18.2, watchOS 11.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2, macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54488 | A logic issue was addressed with improved file handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2, iPadOS 17.7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54488</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved file handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2, iPadOS 17.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2. Photos in the Hidden Photos Album may be viewed without authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54497 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.2,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54497</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.2, tvOS 18.2, watchOS 11.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2. Processing web content may lead to a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54499 | A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.2, tvOS 18.2, watchOS 11.2, iOS 18.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54499</link><description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.2, tvOS 18.2, watchOS 11.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54507 | A type confusion issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2. An ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54507</link><description>A type confusion issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2. An attacker with user privileges may be able to read kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54509 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54509</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or write kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54512 | The issue was addressed by removing the relevant flags. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2. A system binary could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54512</link><description>The issue was addressed by removing the relevant flags. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2. A system binary could be used to fingerprint a user's Apple Account.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54516 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2. An app may b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54516</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2. An app may be able to approve a launch daemon without user consent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54517 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2, watchOS 11.2, tvOS 18.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54517</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2, watchOS 11.2, tvOS 18.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2. An app may be able to corrupt coprocessor memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54518 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2, watchOS 11.2, tvOS 18.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54518</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2, watchOS 11.2, tvOS 18.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2. An app may be able to corrupt coprocessor memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54519 | The issue was resolved by sanitizing logging. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2. An app may be able to read sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54519</link><description>The issue was resolved by sanitizing logging. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2. An app may be able to read sensitive location information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54520 | A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, macOS Ventura ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54520</link><description>A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, macOS Ventura 13.7.2. An app may be able to overwrite arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54522 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2, watchOS 11.2, tvOS 18.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54522</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2, watchOS 11.2, tvOS 18.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2. An app may be able to corrupt coprocessor memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54523 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2, watchOS 11.2, tvOS 18.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54523</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2, watchOS 11.2, tvOS 18.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2. An app may be able to corrupt coprocessor memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54530 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2, watchOS 11.2, visionOS 2.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54530</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2, watchOS 11.2, visionOS 2.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2. Password autofill may fill in passwords after failing authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54536 | The issue was addressed with improved validation of environment variables. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2. An app may be able to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54536</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved validation of environment variables. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2. An app may be able to edit NVRAM variables.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54537 | This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, macOS Ventura 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54537</link><description>This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, macOS Ventura 13.7.2. An app may be able to read and write files outside of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54539 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, macOS Ventura 13...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54539</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, macOS Ventura 13.7.2. An app may be able to capture keyboard events from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54541 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.2, visionOS 2.2, tvOS 18.2, watchOS 11...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54541</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.2, visionOS 2.2, tvOS 18.2, watchOS 11.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2, macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54542 | An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 18.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, watchOS 11.2, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54542</link><description>An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 18.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, watchOS 11.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2. Private Browsing tabs may be accessed without authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54543 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.2, tvOS 18.2, Safari 18.2, watchOS 11.2, iOS 18.2 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54543</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.2, tvOS 18.2, Safari 18.2, watchOS 11.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54547 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, macOS Ventura 13.7.2. An app m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54547</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, macOS Ventura 13.7.2. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54549 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2. An app may be able to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54549</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54550 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54550</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2, iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2. An app may be able to view autocompleted contact information from Messages and Mail in system logs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54557 | A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, macOS Ventura 13.7.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54557</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, macOS Ventura 13.7.2. An attacker may gain access to protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24085 | A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24085</link><description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3. A malicious application may be able to elevate privileges. Apple is aware of a report that this issue may have been actively exploited against versions of iOS before iOS 17.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24086 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24086</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3. Processing an image may lead to a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24087 | The issue was addressed with additional permissions checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. An app may be able to access protecte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24087</link><description>The issue was addressed with additional permissions checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24092 | This issue was addressed with improved data protection. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24092</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved data protection. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to read sensitive location information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24093 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24093</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to access removable volumes without user consent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24094 | A race condition was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24094</link><description>A race condition was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24096 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. A malicious app may be able to access...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24096</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. A malicious app may be able to access arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24100 | A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24100</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to access information about a user's contacts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24101 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. An app may be able to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24101</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24102 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, macOS Ventura 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24102</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, macOS Ventura 13.7.3. An app may be able to determine a user’s current location.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24103 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24103</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24104 | This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. Restoring a mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24104</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. Restoring a maliciously crafted backup file may lead to modification of protected system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24106 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. Parsing ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24106</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. Parsing a file may lead to an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24107 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, tvOS 18.3, watchOS 11.3, iOS 18.3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24107</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, tvOS 18.3, watchOS 11.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. A malicious app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24108 | An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. An app may be able to access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24108</link><description>An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24109 | A downgrade issue was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24109</link><description>A downgrade issue was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24112 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. Parsing a file may lead to an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24112</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. Parsing a file may lead to an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24113 | The issue was addressed with improved UI. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, Safari 18.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, visionOS 2.3. Vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24113</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved UI. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, Safari 18.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, visionOS 2.3. Visiting a malicious website may lead to user interface spoofing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24114 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonom...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24114</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24115 | A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24115</link><description>A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to read files outside of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24116 | An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24116</link><description>An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to bypass Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24117 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24117</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3. An app may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24118 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24118</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or write kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24120 | This issue was addressed by improved management of object lifetimes. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24120</link><description>This issue was addressed by improved management of object lifetimes. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An attacker may be able to cause unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24121 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24121</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24122 | A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24122</link><description>A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24123 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24123</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3. Parsing a file may lead to an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24124 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24124</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3. Parsing a file may lead to an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24126 | An input validation issue was addressed. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3, tv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24126</link><description>An input validation issue was addressed. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3. An attacker on the local network may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24127 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24127</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, tvOS 18.3. Parsing a file may lead to an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24128 | The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, Safari 18.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. Visiti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24128</link><description>The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, Safari 18.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. Visiting a malicious website may lead to address bar spoofing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24129 | A type confusion issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24129</link><description>A type confusion issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3. A remote attacker may cause an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24130 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24130</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24131 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, wa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24131</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3. An attacker in a privileged position may be able to perform a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24134 | An information disclosure issue was addressed with improved privacy controls. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. An app may be able ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24134</link><description>An information disclosure issue was addressed with improved privacy controls. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24135 | This issue was addressed with improved message validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. An app may be able to gain elevated pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24135</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved message validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. An app may be able to gain elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24136 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24136</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. A malicious app may be able to create symlinks to protected regions of the disk.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24137 | A type confusion issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24137</link><description>A type confusion issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3. A remote attacker may cause an unexpected application termination or arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24138 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24138</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. A malicious application may be able to leak sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24139 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. Parsing ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24139</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. Parsing a maliciously crafted file may lead to an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24140 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. Files downloaded from the internet ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24140</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. Files downloaded from the internet may not have the quarantine flag applied.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24141 | An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. An attacker with phys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24141</link><description>An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. An attacker with physical access to an unlocked device may be able to access Photos while the app is locked.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24143 | The issue was addressed with improved access restrictions to the file system. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, Safari 18.3, iOS 18...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24143</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved access restrictions to the file system. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, Safari 18.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, visionOS 2.3. A maliciously crafted webpage may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24145 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, iOS 18.3 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24145</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. An app may be able to view a contact's phone number in system logs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24146 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24146</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. Deleting a conversation in Messages may expose user contact information in system logging.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24149 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24149</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3. Parsing a file may lead to disclosure of user information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24150 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of files. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, Safari 18.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24150</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of files. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, Safari 18.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. Copying a URL from Web Inspector may lead to command injection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24151 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24151</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24152 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. An app may be able to cause unexpected sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24152</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24153 | A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. An app with root privileges ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24153</link><description>A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3. An app with root privileges may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24154 | An out-of-bounds write was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24154</link><description>An out-of-bounds write was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3. An attacker may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24156 | An integer overflow was addressed through improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24156</link><description>An integer overflow was addressed through improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to elevate privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24158 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.3, Safari 18.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Seq...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24158</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.3, Safari 18.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3. Processing web content may lead to a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24159 | A validation issue was addressed with improved logic. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24159</link><description>A validation issue was addressed with improved logic. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24160 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24160</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3. Parsing a file may lead to an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24161 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24161</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3. Parsing a file may lead to an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24162 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.3, Safari 18.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24162</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.3, Safari 18.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24163 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24163</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3. Parsing a file may lead to an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24166 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24166</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, visionOS 2.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24169 | A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, Safari 18.3. A malicious app may be a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24169</link><description>A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, Safari 18.3. A malicious app may be able to bypass browser extension authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24174 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24174</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to bypass Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24176 | A permissions issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24176</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. A local attacker may be able to elevate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24177 | A null pointer dereference was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24177</link><description>A null pointer dereference was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. A remote attacker may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0753 | Axiomatic Bento4 mp42aac ReadPartial heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0753</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Axiomatic Bento4 up to 1.6.0. This vulnerability affects the function AP4_StdcFileByteStream::ReadPartial of the component mp42aac. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0751 | Axiomatic Bento4 mp42aac ReadBits heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0751</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Axiomatic Bento4 up to 1.6.0. This affects the function AP4_BitReader::ReadBits of the component mp42aac. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 19:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48841 | Remote Code Execution (RCE) Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48841</link><description>Network access can be used to execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges. 





This
issue affects FLXEON 9.3.4 and older.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 19:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0734 | y_project RuoYi Whitelist getBeanName deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0734</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in y_project RuoYi up to 4.8.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function getBeanName of the component Whitelist. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 19:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56947 | An issue in Xiamen Meitu Technology Co., Ltd. BeautyCam iOS v12.3.60 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56947</link><description>An issue in Xiamen Meitu Technology Co., Ltd. BeautyCam iOS v12.3.60 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56948 | An issue in KuGou Technology CO. LTD KuGou Music iOS v20.0.0 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56948</link><description>An issue in KuGou Technology CO. LTD KuGou Music iOS v20.0.0 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56949 | An issue in Guangzhou Polar Future Culture Technology Co., Ltd University Search iOS 2.27.0 allows attackers to access sensitive user inform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56949</link><description>An issue in Guangzhou Polar Future Culture Technology Co., Ltd University Search iOS 2.27.0 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56950 | An issue in KuGou Technology Co., Ltd KuGou Concept iOS 4.0.61 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56950</link><description>An issue in KuGou Technology Co., Ltd KuGou Concept iOS 4.0.61 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56951 | An issue in Hangzhou Bobo Technology Co Ltd UU Game Booster iOS 10.6.13 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56951</link><description>An issue in Hangzhou Bobo Technology Co Ltd UU Game Booster iOS 10.6.13 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56952 | An issue in Beijing Baidu Netcom Science &amp; Technology Co Ltd Baidu Lite app (iOS version) 6.40.0 allows attackers to access user information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56952</link><description>An issue in Beijing Baidu Netcom Science &amp; Technology Co Ltd Baidu Lite app (iOS version) 6.40.0 allows attackers to access user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56953 | An issue in Baidu (China) Co Ltd Baidu Input Method (iOS version) v12.6.13 allows attackers to access user information via supplying a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56953</link><description>An issue in Baidu (China) Co Ltd Baidu Input Method (iOS version) v12.6.13 allows attackers to access user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56954 | An issue in Beijing Baidu Netcom Science &amp; Technology Co Ltd Haokan Video iOS 7.70.0 allows attackers to access sensitive user information v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56954</link><description>An issue in Beijing Baidu Netcom Science &amp; Technology Co Ltd Haokan Video iOS 7.70.0 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56955 | An issue in Tencent Technology (Shenzhen) Company Limited QQMail iOS 6.6.4 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplyi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56955</link><description>An issue in Tencent Technology (Shenzhen) Company Limited QQMail iOS 6.6.4 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56957 | An issue in Kingsoft Office Software Corporation Limited WPS Office iOS 12.20.0 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via su...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56957</link><description>An issue in Kingsoft Office Software Corporation Limited WPS Office iOS 12.20.0 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56959 | An issue in Mashang Consumer Finance Co., Ltd Anyihua iOS 3.6.2 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56959</link><description>An issue in Mashang Consumer Finance Co., Ltd Anyihua iOS 3.6.2 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56960 | An issue in Tianjin Xiaowu Information technology Co., Ltd BeiKe Holdings iOS 1.3.50 allows attackers to access sensitive user information v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56960</link><description>An issue in Tianjin Xiaowu Information technology Co., Ltd BeiKe Holdings iOS 1.3.50 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56962 | An issue in Tencent Technology (Shanghai) Co., Ltd WeSing iOS v9.3.39 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56962</link><description>An issue in Tencent Technology (Shanghai) Co., Ltd WeSing iOS v9.3.39 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56963 | An issue in Beijing Sogou Technology Development Co., Ltd Sogou Input iOS 12.2.0 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56963</link><description>An issue in Beijing Sogou Technology Development Co., Ltd Sogou Input iOS 12.2.0 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56964 | An issue in Che Hao Duo Used Automobile Agency (Beijing) Co., Ltd Guazi Used Car iOS 10.15.1 allows attackers to access sensitive user infor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56964</link><description>An issue in Che Hao Duo Used Automobile Agency (Beijing) Co., Ltd Guazi Used Car iOS 10.15.1 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56965 | An issue in Shanghai Shizhi Information Technology Co., Ltd Shihuo iOS 8.16.0 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56965</link><description>An issue in Shanghai Shizhi Information Technology Co., Ltd Shihuo iOS 8.16.0 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56966 | An issue in Shanghai Xuan Ting Entertainment Information &amp; Technology Co., Ltd Qidian Reader iOS 5.9.384 allows attackers to access sensitiv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56966</link><description>An issue in Shanghai Xuan Ting Entertainment Information &amp; Technology Co., Ltd Qidian Reader iOS 5.9.384 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56967 | An issue in Cloud Whale Interactive Technology LLC. PolyBuzz iOS 2.0.20 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56967</link><description>An issue in Cloud Whale Interactive Technology LLC. PolyBuzz iOS 2.0.20 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56968 | An issue in Shenzhen Intellirocks Tech Co. Ltd Govee Home iOS 6.5.01 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56968</link><description>An issue in Shenzhen Intellirocks Tech Co. Ltd Govee Home iOS 6.5.01 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56969 | An issue in Pixocial Technology (Singapore) Pte. Ltd BeautyPlus iOS 7.8.010 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supply...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56969</link><description>An issue in Pixocial Technology (Singapore) Pte. Ltd BeautyPlus iOS 7.8.010 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56971 | An issue in Zhiyuan Yuedu (Guangzhou) Literature Information Technology Co., Ltd Shuqi Novel iOS 5.3.8 allows attackers to access sensitive ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56971</link><description>An issue in Zhiyuan Yuedu (Guangzhou) Literature Information Technology Co., Ltd Shuqi Novel iOS 5.3.8 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56972 | An issue in Midea Group Co., Ltd Midea Home iOS 9.3.12 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56972</link><description>An issue in Midea Group Co., Ltd Midea Home iOS 9.3.12 allows attackers to access sensitive user information via supplying a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:49:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0732 | Discord profapi.dll untrusted search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0732</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Discord up to 1.0.9177 on Windows. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality in the library profapi.dll. The manipulation leads to untrusted search path. The attack needs to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:27:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0733 | Postman profapi.dll untrusted search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0733</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Postman up to 11.20 on Windows. This affects an unknown part in the library profapi.dll. The manipulation leads to untrusted search path. An attack has to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:27:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24365 | vaultwarden allows escalation of privilege via variable confusion in OrgHeaders trait</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24365</link><description>vaultwarden is an unofficial Bitwarden compatible server written in Rust, formerly known as bitwarden_rs. Attacker can obtain owner rights of other organization. Hacker should know the ID of victim organization (in real case the user can be a part of the organization as an unprivileged user) and be the owner/admin of other organization (by default you can create your own organization) in order to attack. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.33.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:53:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24364 | vaultwarden allows RCE in the admin panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24364</link><description>vaultwarden is an unofficial Bitwarden compatible server written in Rust, formerly known as bitwarden_rs. Attacker with authenticated access to the vaultwarden admin panel can execute arbitrary code in the system. The attacker could then change some settings to use sendmail as mail agent but adjust the settings in such a way that it would use a shell command. It then also needed to craft a special favicon image which would have the commands embedded to run during for example sending a test email. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.33.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:53:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24357 | vLLM allows a malicious model RCE by torch.load in hf_model_weights_iterator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24357</link><description>vLLM is a library for LLM inference and serving. vllm/model_executor/weight_utils.py implements hf_model_weights_iterator to load the model checkpoint, which is downloaded from huggingface. It uses the torch.load function and the weights_only parameter defaults to False. When torch.load loads malicious pickle data, it will execute arbitrary code during unpickling. This vulnerability is fixed in v0.7.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24356 | UDP traffic amplification via fastd&amp;#x27;s fast reconnect feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24356</link><description>fastd is a VPN daemon which tunnels IP packets and Ethernet frames over UDP. When receiving a data packet from an unknown IP address/port combination, fastd will assume that one of its connected peers has moved to a new address and initiate a reconnect by sending a handshake packet. This "fast reconnect" avoids having to wait for a session timeout (up to ~90s) until a new connection is established. Even a 1-byte UDP packet just containing the fastd packet type header can trigger a much larger handshake packet (~150 bytes of UDP payload). Including IPv4 and UDP headers, the resulting amplification factor is roughly 12-13. By sending data packets with a spoofed source address to fastd instances reachable on the internet, this amplification of UDP traffic might be used to facilitate a Distributed Denial of Service attack. This vulnerability is fixed in v23.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26317 | In illumos illumos-gate 2024-02-15, an error occurs in the elliptic curve point addition algorithm that uses mixed Jacobian-affine coordinat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26317</link><description>In illumos illumos-gate 2024-02-15, an error occurs in the elliptic curve point addition algorithm that uses mixed Jacobian-affine coordinates, causing the algorithm to yield a result of POINT_AT_INFINITY when it should not. A man-in-the-middle attacker could use this to interfere with a connection, resulting in an attacked party computing an incorrect shared secret.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23197 | matrix-hookshot has a Potential Denial of Service when Hookshot is configured with GitHub support</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23197</link><description>matrix-hookshot is a Matrix bot for connecting to external services like GitHub, GitLab, JIRA, and more. When Hookshot 6 version 6.0.1 or below, or Hookshot 5 version 5.4.1 or below, is configured with GitHub support, it is vulnerable to a Denial of Service (DoS) whereby it can crash on restart due to a missing check. The impact is greater to you untrusted users can add their own GitHub organizations to Hookshot in order to connect their room to a repository. This vulnerability is fixed in 6.0.2 and 5.4.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24354 | imgproxy is vulnerable to SSRF against 0.0.0.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24354</link><description>imgproxy is server for resizing, processing, and converting images. Imgproxy does not block the 0.0.0.0 address, even with IMGPROXY_ALLOW_LOOPBACK_SOURCE_ADDRESSES set to false. This can expose services on the local host. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.27.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12740 | Dependency on Vulnerable Third-Party Component exposes Vulnerabilities in NI Vision Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12740</link><description>Vision related software from NI used a third-party library for image processing that exposes several vulnerabilities.  These vulnerabilities may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24367 | Cacti allows Arbitrary File Creation leading to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24367</link><description>Cacti is an open source performance and fault management framework. An authenticated Cacti user can abuse graph creation and graph template functionality to create arbitrary PHP scripts in the web root of the application, leading to remote code execution on the server. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.29.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24368 | Cacti has a SQL Injection vulnerability when using tree rules through Automation API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24368</link><description>Cacti is an open source performance and fault management framework. Some of the data stored in automation_tree_rules.php is not thoroughly checked and is used to concatenate the SQL statement in build_rule_item_filter() function from lib/api_automation.php, resulting in SQL injection. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.29.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48417 | Edimax AC1200 Wi-Fi 5 Dual-Band Router BR-6476AC 1.06 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in : /bin/goahead via /goform/setStaticRou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48417</link><description>Edimax AC1200 Wi-Fi 5 Dual-Band Router BR-6476AC 1.06 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in : /bin/goahead via /goform/setStaticRoute, /goform/fromSetFilterUrlFilter, and /goform/fromSetFilterClientFilter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:18:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48418 | In Edimax AC1200 Wi-Fi 5 Dual-Band Router BR-6476AC 1.06, the request /goform/fromSetDDNS does not properly handle special characters in any...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48418</link><description>In Edimax AC1200 Wi-Fi 5 Dual-Band Router BR-6476AC 1.06, the request /goform/fromSetDDNS does not properly handle special characters in any of user provided parameters, allowing an attacker with access to the web interface to inject and execute arbitrary shell commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48419 | Edimax AC1200 Wi-Fi 5 Dual-Band Router BR-6476AC 1.06 suffers from Command Injection issues in /bin/goahead. Specifically, these issues can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48419</link><description>Edimax AC1200 Wi-Fi 5 Dual-Band Router BR-6476AC 1.06 suffers from Command Injection issues in /bin/goahead. Specifically, these issues can be triggered through /goform/tracerouteDiagnosis, /goform/pingDiagnosis, and /goform/fromSysToolPingCmd Each of these issues allows an attacker with access to the web interface to inject and execute arbitrary shell commands, with "root" privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54145 | Cacti has a SQL Injection vulnerability when request automation devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54145</link><description>Cacti is an open source performance and fault management framework. Cacti has a SQL injection vulnerability in the get_discovery_results function of automation_devices.php using the network parameter. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.29.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54146 | Cacti has a SQL Injection vulnerability when view host template</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54146</link><description>Cacti is an open source performance and fault management framework. Cacti has a SQL injection vulnerability in the template function of host_templates.php using the graph_template parameter. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.29.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22604 | Cacti has Authenticated RCE via multi-line SNMP responses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22604</link><description>Cacti is an open source performance and fault management framework. Due to a flaw in multi-line SNMP result parser, authenticated users can inject malformed OIDs in the response. When processed by ss_net_snmp_disk_io() or ss_net_snmp_disk_bytes(), a part of each OID will be used as a key in an array that is used as part of a system command, causing a command execution vulnerability. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.29.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48416 | Edimax AC1200 Wi-Fi 5 Dual-Band Router BR-6476AC 1.06 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via /goform/fromSetLanDhcpsClientbinding.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48416</link><description>Edimax AC1200 Wi-Fi 5 Dual-Band Router BR-6476AC 1.06 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via /goform/fromSetLanDhcpsClientbinding.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48420 | Edimax AC1200 Wi-Fi 5 Dual-Band Router BR-6476AC 1.06 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via /goform/getWifiBasic.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48420</link><description>Edimax AC1200 Wi-Fi 5 Dual-Band Router BR-6476AC 1.06 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via /goform/getWifiBasic.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0729 | TP-Link TL-SG108E clickjacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0729</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TP-Link TL-SG108E 1.0.0 Build 20201208 Rel. 40304. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation leads to clickjacking. The attack may be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 1.0.0 Build 20250124 Rel. 54920(Beta) is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The vendor was contacted early. They reacted very professional and provided a pre-fix version for their customers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0730 | TP-Link TL-SG108E HTTP GET Request usr_account_set.cgi get request method with sensitive query strings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0730</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in TP-Link TL-SG108E 1.0.0 Build 20201208 Rel. 40304. Affected is an unknown function of the file /usr_account_set.cgi of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to use of get request method with sensitive query strings. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.0.0 Build 20250124 Rel. 54920(Beta) is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The vendor was contacted early. They reacted very professional and provided a pre-fix version for their customers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57272 | SecuSTATION Camera V2.5.5.3116-S50-SMA-B20160811A and lower is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57272</link><description>SecuSTATION Camera V2.5.5.3116-S50-SMA-B20160811A and lower is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 16:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27256 | IBM MQ Operator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27256</link><description>IBM MQ Container 3.0.0, 3.0.1, 3.1.0 through 3.1.3 CD, 2.0.0 LTS through 2.0.22 LTS and 2.4.0 through 2.4.8, 2.3.0 through 2.3.3, 2.2.0 through 2.2.2 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 16:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55227 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Events/Agenda module of Dolibarr v21.0.0-beta allows attackers to execute arbitrary web sc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55227</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Events/Agenda module of Dolibarr v21.0.0-beta allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTMl via a crafted payload injected into the Title parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 16:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55228 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Product module of Dolibarr v21.0.0-beta allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55228</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Product module of Dolibarr v21.0.0-beta allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTMl via a crafted payload injected into the Title parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 16:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57276 | In Electronic Arts Dragon Age Origins 1.05, the DAUpdaterSVC service contains an unquoted service path vulnerability. This service is config...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57276</link><description>In Electronic Arts Dragon Age Origins 1.05, the DAUpdaterSVC service contains an unquoted service path vulnerability. This service is configured with insecure permissions, allowing users to modify the executable file path used by the service. The service runs with NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM privileges, enabling attackers to escalate privileges by replacing or placing a malicious executable in the service path.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 16:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47159 | IBM Sterling File Gateway information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47159</link><description>IBM Sterling File Gateway 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.5 and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.1 could allow an authenticated user to enumerate usernames due to an observable discrepancy in request responses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 16:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52292 | IBM Sterling File Gateway cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52292</link><description>IBM Sterling File Gateway 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.5 and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.3 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 16:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22316 | IBM Sterling File Gateway improper access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22316</link><description>IBM Sterling File Gateway 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.5 and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.1 could allow an authenticated user to perform unauthorized actions to another user's data due to improper access controls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 16:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37527 | IBM OpenPages with Watson cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37527</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 15:51:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45598 | Cacti has a Local File Inclusion (LFI) Vulnerability via Poller Standard Error Log Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45598</link><description>Cacti is an open source performance and fault management framework. Prior to 1.2.29, an administrator can change the `Poller Standard Error Log Path` parameter in either Installation Step 5 or in Configuration-&gt;Settings-&gt;Paths tab to a local file inside the server. Then simply going to Logs tab and selecting the name of the local file will show its content on the web UI. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.29.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 15:51:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38320 | IBM Storage Protect for Virtual Environments: Data Protection for VMware information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38320</link><description>IBM Storage Protect for Virtual Environments: Data Protection for VMware and Storage Protect Backup-Archive Client 8.1.0.0 through 8.1.23.0 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 15:51:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38325 | IBM Storage Defender information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38325</link><description>IBM Storage Defender 2.0.0 through 2.0.7 on-prem defender-sensor-cmd CLI 

could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by sending network requests over an insecure channel. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information using man in the middle techniques.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 15:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24783 | Apache Cocoon: continuations may not be private</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24783</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Incorrect Usage of Seeds in Pseudo-Random Number Generator (PRNG) vulnerability in Apache Cocoon.

This issue affects Apache Cocoon: all versions.

When a continuation is created, it gets a random identifier. Because the random number generator used to generate these identifiers was seeded with the startup time, it may not have been sufficiently unpredictable, and an attacker could use this to guess continuation ids and look up continuations they should not have had access to.

As a mitigation, you may enable the "session-bound-continuations" option to make sure continuations are not shared across sessions.


As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57595 | DLINK DIR-825 REVB 2.03 devices have an OS command injection vulnerability in the CGl interface apc_client_pin.cgi, which allows remote atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57595</link><description>DLINK DIR-825 REVB 2.03 devices have an OS command injection vulnerability in the CGl interface apc_client_pin.cgi, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands via the parameter "wps_pin" passed to the apc_client_pin.cgi binary through a POST request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57590 | TRENDnet TEW-632BRP v1.010B31 devices have an OS command injection vulnerability in the CGl interface "ntp_sync.cgi",which allows remote att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57590</link><description>TRENDnet TEW-632BRP v1.010B31 devices have an OS command injection vulnerability in the CGl interface "ntp_sync.cgi",which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands via parameter "ntp_server" passed to the "ntp_sync.cgi" binary through a POST request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23529 | WordPress Minterpress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23529</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Blokhaus Minterpress allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Minterpress: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23531 | WordPress RSVPMaker Volunteer Roles plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23531</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in David F. Carr RSVPMaker Volunteer Roles allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects RSVPMaker Volunteer Roles: from n/a through 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23574 | WordPress CubePM plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23574</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jonathan Lau CubePM allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects CubePM: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23656 | WordPress Donate visa plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23656</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Saul Morales Pacheco Donate visa allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Donate visa: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23669 | WordPress WP Smart Tooltip plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23669</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nurul Amin, Mohammad Saiful Islam WP Smart Tooltip allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Smart Tooltip: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23752 | WordPress CGD Arrange Terms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23752</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound CGD Arrange Terms allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects CGD Arrange Terms: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23754 | WordPress The Loops plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23754</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ulrich Sossou The Loops allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects The Loops: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23756 | WordPress LawPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23756</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ivan Chernyakov LawPress – Law Firm Website Management allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects LawPress – Law Firm Website Management: from n/a through 1.4.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23849 | WordPress PAPERCITE plugin &amp;lt;= 0.5.18 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23849</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Benjamin Piwowarski PAPERCITE allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects PAPERCITE: from n/a through 0.5.18.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23982 | WordPress Fare Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23982</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Marian Kanev Cab fare calculator allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Cab fare calculator: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24537 | WordPress The Events Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 6.7.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24537</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in The Events Calendar The Events Calendar allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects The Events Calendar: from n/a through 6.7.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24538 | WordPress BuddyPress Groups Extras plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.10 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24538</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in slaFFik BuddyPress Groups Extras allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects BuddyPress Groups Extras: from n/a through 3.6.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24540 | WordPress Website Builder by SeedProd plugin &amp;lt;= 6.18.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24540</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SeedProd Coming Soon Page, Under Construction &amp; Maintenance Mode by SeedProd allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Coming Soon Page, Under Construction &amp; Maintenance Mode by SeedProd: from n/a through 6.18.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24590 | WordPress picu – Online Photo Proofing Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24590</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Haptiq picu – Online Photo Proofing Gallery allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects picu – Online Photo Proofing Gallery: from n/a through 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24593 | WordPress Edwiser Bridge plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24593</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WisdmLabs Edwiser Bridge allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Edwiser Bridge: from n/a through 3.0.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24600 | WordPress RSVPMaker plugin &amp;lt;= 11.4.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24600</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in David F. Carr RSVPMarker . This issue affects RSVPMarker : from n/a through 11.4.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24603 | WordPress Print Labels with Barcodes. Create price tags, product labels, order labels for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24603</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in UkrSolution Print Barcode Labels for your WooCommerce products/orders. This issue affects Print Barcode Labels for your WooCommerce products/orders: from n/a through 3.4.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24606 | WordPress Client Invoicing by Sprout Invoices – Easy Estimates and Invoices for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;=20.8.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24606</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Sprout Invoices Client Invoicing by Sprout Invoices allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Client Invoicing by Sprout Invoices: from n/a through 20.8.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24626 | WordPress Music Store – WordPress eCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.19 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24626</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodePeople Music Store allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Music Store: from n/a through 1.1.19.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24628 | WordPress reCaptcha by BestWebSoft Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.78 - Captcha Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24628</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in BestWebSoft Google Captcha allows Identity Spoofing. This issue affects Google Captcha: from n/a through 1.78.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24653 | WordPress Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6.1.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24653</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in NotFound Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) Pro: from n/a through 7.6.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24662 | WordPress LearnDash LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.20.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24662</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in NotFound LearnDash LMS allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects LearnDash LMS: from n/a through 4.20.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24665 | WordPress Small Package Quotes Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.8 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24665</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Eniture Technology Small Package Quotes – Unishippers Edition allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Small Package Quotes – Unishippers Edition: from n/a through 2.4.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24667 | WordPress Small Package Quotes Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.17 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24667</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Eniture Technology Small Package Quotes – Worldwide Express Edition allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Small Package Quotes – Worldwide Express Edition: from n/a through 5.2.17.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24671 | WordPress Save as PDF Plugin by Pdfcrowd Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24671</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Pdfcrowd Save as PDF plugin by Pdfcrowd allows Object Injection. This issue affects Save as PDF plugin by Pdfcrowd: from n/a through 4.4.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24680 | WordPress WP Multi Store Locator Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24680</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in WpMultiStoreLocator WP Multi Store Locator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Multi Store Locator: from n/a through 2.4.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24689 | WordPress Import and export users and customers plugin 1.27.12 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24689</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Externally-Accessible File or Directory vulnerability in codection Import and export users and customers allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Import and export users and customers: from n/a through 1.27.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24708 | WordPress WP Dynamics CRM plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24708</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CRM Perks WP Dynamics CRM for Contact Form 7, WPForms, Elementor, Formidable and Ninja Forms allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Dynamics CRM for Contact Form 7, WPForms, Elementor, Formidable and Ninja Forms: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24734 | WordPress Better Find and Replace plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.7 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24734</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CodeSolz Better Find and Replace allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Better Find and Replace: from n/a through 1.6.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24740 | WordPress Learnpress plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.7.1 - Open Redirection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24740</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in ThimPress LearnPress. This issue affects LearnPress: from n/a through 4.2.7.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24741 | WordPress KB Support plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.7 - Open Redirection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24741</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in KB Support KB Support. This issue affects KB Support: from n/a through 1.6.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24742 | WordPress WP Google Maps plugin &amp;lt;= 9.0.40 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24742</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP Go Maps (formerly WP Google Maps) WP Go Maps. This issue affects WP Go Maps: from n/a through 9.0.40.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24743 | WordPress RomethemeKit For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24743</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Rometheme RomethemeKit For Elementor. This issue affects RomethemeKit For Elementor: from n/a through 1.5.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24744 | WordPress Bridge Core plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24744</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in NotFound Bridge Core. This issue affects Bridge Core: from n/a through 3.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24747 | WordPress Houzez theme &amp;lt;= 3.4.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24747</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Houzez.co Houzez. This issue affects Houzez: from n/a through 3.4.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24782 | WordPress Post Grid, Slider &amp;amp; Carousel Ultimate – with Shortcode, Gutenberg Block &amp;amp; Elementor Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.10 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24782</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in wpWax Post Grid, Slider &amp; Carousel Ultimate allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Post Grid, Slider &amp; Carousel Ultimate: from n/a through 1.6.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22513 | WordPress Simple Locator Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22513</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Simple Locator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Simple Locator: from n/a through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:12:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23457 | WordPress Shipdeo plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23457</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Clodeo Shipdeo allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Shipdeo: from n/a through 1.2.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:12:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23792 | WordPress Passwordless WP – Login with your glance or fingerprint Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23792</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Busters Passwordless WP – Login with your glance or fingerprint allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Passwordless WP – Login with your glance or fingerprint: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24533 | WordPress MetaSlider plugin &amp;lt;= 3.92.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24533</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in MetaSlider Responsive Slider by MetaSlider allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Responsive Slider by MetaSlider: from n/a through 3.92.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24584 | WordPress Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24584</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BdThemes Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons: from n/a through 2.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:12:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24601 | WordPress FundPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24601</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ThimPress FundPress allows Object Injection. This issue affects FundPress: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:12:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24612 | WordPress Shipping for Nova Poshta plugin &amp;lt;= 1.19.6 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24612</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in MORKVA Shipping for Nova Poshta allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Shipping for Nova Poshta: from n/a through 1.19.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24664 | WordPress LTL Freight Quotes Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.20 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24664</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Eniture Technology LTL Freight Quotes – Worldwide Express Edition allows SQL Injection. This issue affects LTL Freight Quotes – Worldwide Express Edition: from n/a through 5.0.20.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24685 | WordPress Morkva UA Shipping plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.18 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24685</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in MORKVA Morkva UA Shipping allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Morkva UA Shipping: from n/a through 1.0.18.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24754 | WordPress Houzez theme &amp;lt;= 3.4.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24754</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Houzez.co Houzez. This issue affects Houzez: from n/a through 3.4.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4975 | Rhacs: cross-site scripting in portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4975</link><description>A flaw was found in the Red Hat Advanced Cluster Security (RHACS) portal. When rendering a table view in the portal, for example, on any of the /main/configmanagement/* endpoints, the front-end generates a DOM table-element (id="pdf-table"). This information is then populated with unsanitized data using innerHTML. An attacker with some control over the data rendered can trigger a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 13:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11348 | Reflected XSS in Eura7 CMSmanager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11348</link><description>Eura7 CMSmanager in version 4.6 and below is vulnerable to Reflected XSS attacks through manipulation of return GET request parameter sent to a specific endpoint.
The vulnerability has been fixed by a patche patch 17012022 addressing all affected versions in use.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 13:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55931 | Token stored in session storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55931</link><description>Xerox Workplace Suite stores tokens in session storage, which may expose them to potential access if a user's session is compromised. 

The patch for this vulnerability will be included in a future release of Workplace Suite, and customers will be notified through an update to the security bulletin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 11:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0695 | An Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in Cesanta Frozen versions less than 1.7 allows an attacker to induce ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0695</link><description>An Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in Cesanta Frozen versions less than 1.7 allows an attacker to induce a crash of the component embedding the library by supplying a maliciously crafted JSON as input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 11:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0696 | A NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in Cesanta Frozen versions less than 1.7 allows an attacker to induce a crash of the component embe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0696</link><description>A NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in Cesanta Frozen versions less than 1.7 allows an attacker to induce a crash of the component embedding the library by supplying a maliciously crafted JSON as input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 11:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12345 | INW Krbyyyzo Daily Huddle Site gbo.aspx resource consumption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12345</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in INW Krbyyyzo 25.2002. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /gbo.aspx of the component Daily Huddle Site. The manipulation of the argument s leads to resource consumption. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. Other endpoints might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 11:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24814 | Apache Solr: Core-creation with &amp;quot;trusted&amp;quot; configset can use arbitrary untrusted files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24814</link><description>Core creation allows users to replace "trusted" configset files with arbitrary configuration

Solr instances that (1) use the "FileSystemConfigSetService" component (the default in "standalone" or "user-managed" mode), and (2) are running without authentication and authorization are vulnerable to a sort of privilege escalation wherein individual "trusted" configset files can be ignored in favor of potentially-untrusted replacements available elsewhere on the filesystem.  These replacement config files are treated as "trusted" and can use "" tags to add to Solr's classpath, which an attacker might use to load malicious code as a searchComponent or other plugin.

This issue affects all Apache Solr versions up through Solr 9.7.  Users can protect against the vulnerability by enabling authentication and authorization on their Solr clusters or switching to SolrCloud (and away from "FileSystemConfigSetService").  Users are also recommended to upgrade to Solr 9.8.0, which mitigates this issue by disabling use of "" tags by default.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 09:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52012 | Apache Solr: Configset upload on Windows allows arbitrary path write-access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52012</link><description>Relative Path Traversal vulnerability in Apache Solr.

Solr instances running on Windows are vulnerable to arbitrary filepath write-access, due to a lack of input-sanitation in the "configset upload" API.  Commonly known as a "zipslip", maliciously constructed ZIP files can use relative filepaths to write data to unanticipated parts of the filesystem.  
This issue affects Apache Solr: from 6.6 through 9.7.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 9.8.0, which fixes the issue.  Users unable to upgrade may also safely prevent the issue by using Solr's "Rule-Based Authentication Plugin" to restrict access to the configset upload API, so that it can only be accessed by a trusted set of administrators/users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 09:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12280 | WP Customer Area &amp;lt;= 8.2.4 - Event Log Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12280</link><description>The WP Customer Area WordPress plugin through 8.2.4 does not have CSRF check in place when deleting its logs, which could allow attackers to make a logged in to delete them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 06:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12321 | WC Affiliate &amp;lt;= 2.3.9 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12321</link><description>The WC Affiliate  WordPress plugin through 2.3.9 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 06:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12436 | WP Customer Area &amp;lt;= 8.2.4 - Bulk Delete via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12436</link><description>The WP Customer Area WordPress plugin through 8.2.4 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 06:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12773 | Altra Side Menu &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12773</link><description>The Altra Side Menu WordPress plugin through 2.0 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 06:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12774 | Altra Side Menu &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Abitrary Menu Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12774</link><description>The Altra Side Menu WordPress plugin through 2.0 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in admins delete arbitrary menu via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 06:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13052 | Dental Optimizer Patient Generator App &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13052</link><description>The Dental Optimizer Patient Generator App WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 06:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13055 | Dyn Business Panel &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13055</link><description>The Dyn Business Panel WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 06:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13056 | Dyn Business Panel &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13056</link><description>The Dyn Business Panel WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 06:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13057 | Dyn Business Panel &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13057</link><description>The Dyn Business Panel WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 06:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13094 | WP Triggers Lite &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13094</link><description>The WP Triggers Lite WordPress plugin through 2.5.3 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 06:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13095 | WP Triggers Lite &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13095</link><description>The WP Triggers Lite WordPress plugin through 2.5.3 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 06:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13116 | Crelly Slider &amp;lt; 1.4.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13116</link><description>The Crelly Slider WordPress plugin before 1.4.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 06:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13117 | Social Share Buttons for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.7 - Unauthenticated Image Upload &amp;amp; Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13117</link><description>The Social Share Buttons for WordPress plugin through 2.7 allows an unauthenticated user to upload arbitrary images and change the path where they are uploaded</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 06:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43445 | Missing X-Content-Type-Options: nosniff Header Allows MIME Type Sniffing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43445</link><description>A vulnerability exists in OTRS and ((OTRS Community Edition)) that fail to set the HTTP response header X-Content-Type-Options to nosniff. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading or inserting content that would be treated as a different MIME type than intended. 

This issue affects: 

  *  OTRS 7.0.X

  *  OTRS 8.0.X
  *  OTRS 2023.X
  *  OTRS 2024.X

  *  ((OTRS)) Community Edition: 6.0.x

Products based on the ((OTRS)) Community Edition also very likely to be affected</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 06:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43446 | Improper check of permissions in Generic Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43446</link><description>An improper privilege management vulnerability in OTRS Generic Interface module allows change of the Ticket status even if the user only has ro permissions. 

This issue affects: 

  *  OTRS 7.0.X

  *  OTRS 8.0.X
  *  OTRS 2023.X
  *  OTRS 2024.X

  *  ((OTRS)) Community Edition: 6.0.x

Products based on the ((OTRS)) Community Edition also very likely to be affected</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 06:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24389 | SMTP Password will be shown in cleartext on some SMTP errors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24389</link><description>Certain errors of the upstream libraries will insert sensitive information in the OTRS or ((OTRS)) Community Edition log mechanism and mails send to the system administrator.

This issue affects: 

  *  OTRS 7.0.X

  *  OTRS 8.0.X
  *  OTRS 2023.X
  *  OTRS 2024.X

  *  ((OTRS)) Community Edition: 6.0.x

Products based on the ((OTRS)) Community Edition also very likely to be affected</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 06:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24390 | Missing Cookie Flags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24390</link><description>A vulnerability in OTRS Application Server and reverse proxy settings allows session hijacking due to missing attributes for sensitive cookie settings in HTTPS sessions.

This issue affects: 

  *  OTRS 7.0.X

  *  OTRS 8.0.X
  *  OTRS 2023.X
  *  OTRS 2024.X</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 06:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46187 | IBM InfoSphere Master Data Management cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46187</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Master Data Management 11.6, 12.0, and 14.0 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 02:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28766 | IBM Security Directory Integrator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28766</link><description>IBM Security Directory Integrator 7.2.0 and IBM Security Verify Directory Integrator 10.0.0 could disclose sensitive information about directory contents that could aid in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 02:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28770 | IBM Security Directory Integrator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28770</link><description>IBM Security Directory Integrator 7.2.0 and IBM Security Verify Directory Integrator 10.0.0 does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may be able to get the cookie values by sending a http:// link to a user or by planting this link in a site the user goes to. The cookie will be sent to the insecure link and the attacker can then obtain the cookie value by snooping the traffic.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28771 | IBM Security Directory Integrator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28771</link><description>IBM Security Directory Integrator 7.2.0 and IBM Security Verify Directory Integrator 10.0.0 does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may be able to get the cookie values by sending a http:// link to a user or by planting this link in a site the user goes to. The cookie will be sent to the insecure link and the attacker can then obtain the cookie value by snooping the traffic.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0721 | needyamin image_gallery view.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0721</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in needyamin image_gallery 1.0. This affects the function image_gallery of the file /view.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 23:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0722 | needyamin image_gallery Cover Image gallery.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0722</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in needyamin image_gallery 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/gallery.php of the component Cover Image Handler. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 23:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0720 | Microword eScan Antivirus Folder Watch List rtscanner removeExtraSlashes stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0720</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Microword eScan Antivirus 7.0.32 on Linux. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function removeExtraSlashes of the file /opt/MicroWorld/sbin/rtscanner of the component Folder Watch List Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 23:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20196 | Itechscripts School Management Software notice-edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20196</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Itechscripts School Management Software 2.75. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /notice-edit.php. The manipulation of the argument aid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 18:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38009 | IBM Cognos Analytics Mobile information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38009</link><description>IBM Cognos Mobile Client 1.1 iOS may be vulnerable to information disclosure through man in the middle techniques due to the lack of certificate pinning.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 16:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50946 | IBM Common Licensing information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50946</link><description>IBM Common Licensing 9.0  could allow an authenticated user to modify a configuration file that they should not have access to due to a broken authorization mechanism.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 15:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50945 | IBM Common Licensing information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50945</link><description>IBM Common Licensing 9.0 stores user credentials in plain clear text which can be read by a local user.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 15:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31906 | IBM Automation Decision Services information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31906</link><description>IBM Automation Decision Services 23.0.2 allows web pages to be stored locally which can be read by another user on the system.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 14:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13505 | Survey Maker &amp;lt;= 5.1.3.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Survey Question</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13505</link><description>The Survey Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘ays_sections[5][questions][8][title]’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 11:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11641 | VikBooking Hotel Booking Engine &amp;amp; PMS &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11641</link><description>The VikBooking Hotel Booking Engine &amp; PMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'save' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change plugin access privileges via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Successful exploitation allows attackers with subscriber-level privileges and above to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 11:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11936 | Zox News &amp;lt;= 3.16.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11936</link><description>The Zox News theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the 'backup_options' and 'restore_options' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.16.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 11:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12334 | WC Affiliate – A Complete WooCommerce Affiliate Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12334</link><description>The WC Affiliate – A Complete WooCommerce Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via any parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 11:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10705 | Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG &amp;lt;= 4.0.5 - Authenticated (Editor+) Server-Side Request Forgery via fileUrl</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10705</link><description>The Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.5 via the 'mpg_download_file_by_link' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 06:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11090 | Membership Plugin – Restrict Content &amp;lt;= 3.2.13 - Unauthenticated Content Restriction Bypass to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11090</link><description>The Membership Plugin – Restrict Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.13 via the WordPress core search feature. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from posts that have been restricted to higher-level roles such as administrator.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 06:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46881 | Develocity (formerly Gradle Enterprise) before 2024.1.8 has Incorrect Access Control. Project-level access control configuration was introdu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46881</link><description>Develocity (formerly Gradle Enterprise) before 2024.1.8 has Incorrect Access Control. Project-level access control configuration was introduced in Enterprise Config schema version 8. Migration functionality from schema version 8 to versions 9 and 10 (in affected vulnerable versions) does not include the projects section of the configuration. This leads to all of the project settings being reset to their defaults when the old schema is loaded. In the case of projects.enabled, the default is false. Thus, using an enterprise config v8 results in Project level access control being disabled, even if it was previously enabled, and previously restricted project information disclosed. Most commonly, this occurs when a Develocity instance is upgraded from an earlier version. Specifically, this occurs if: Develocity 2023.3.X is upgraded to 2023.4.X; Develocity 2023.3.X is upgraded to 2024.1.X up to and including 2024.1.7; or Develocity 2023.4.X is upgraded to 2024.1.X up to and including 2024.1.7. The flaw does not occur when upgrading to a fixed version. An upgrade can only be triggered via administrator access, and cannot be forced by an external attacker.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 06:32:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24858 | Develocity (formerly Gradle Enterprise) before 2024.3.1 allows an attacker who has network access to a Develocity server to obtain the hashe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24858</link><description>Develocity (formerly Gradle Enterprise) before 2024.3.1 allows an attacker who has network access to a Develocity server to obtain the hashed password of the system user. The hash algorithm used by Develocity was chosen according to best practices for password storage and provides some protection against brute-force attempts. The applicable severity of this vulnerability depends on whether a Develocity server is accessible by external or unauthorized users, and the complexity of the System User password.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 06:10:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-49043 | xmlXIncludeAddNode in xinclude.c in libxml2 before 2.11.0 has a use-after-free.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-49043</link><description>xmlXIncludeAddNode in xinclude.c in libxml2 before 2.11.0 has a use-after-free.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 05:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10574 | Quiz Maker Business, Developer, and Agency &amp;lt;= (Multiple Versions) - Missing Authorization to Google Sheets Integration Credentials Modification and Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10574</link><description>The Quiz Maker Business, Developer, and Agency plugins for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ays_save_google_credentials' function in all versions up to, and including, 8.8.0 (Business), up to, and including, 21.8.0 (Developer), and up to, and including, 31.8.0 (Agency). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the Google Sheets integration credentials within the plugin's settings. Because the 'client_id' parameter is not sanitized or escaped when used in output, this vulnerability could also be leveraged to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 05:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10628 | Quiz Maker Business, Developer, and Agency &amp;lt;= (Multiple Versions) - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10628</link><description>The Quiz Maker Business, Developer, and Agency plugins for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 8.8.0 (Business), up to, and including, 21.8.0 (Developer), and up to, and including, 31.8.0 (Agency) due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 05:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10633 | Quiz Maker Business, Developer, and Agency &amp;lt;= (Multiple Versions) - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10633</link><description>The Quiz Maker Business, Developer, and Agency plugins for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 8.8.0 (Business), up to, and including, 21.8.0 (Developer), and up to, and including, 31.8.0 (Agency). This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 05:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10636 | Quiz Maker Business, Developer, and Agency &amp;lt;= (Multiple Versions)  - Reflected DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10636</link><description>The Quiz Maker Business, Developer, and Agency plugins for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘content’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 8.8.0 (Business), up to, and including, 21.8.0 (Developer), and up to, and including, 31.8.0 (Agency) due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 05:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>