<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:37:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-9418 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System addowner.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9418</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /owner/addowner.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6188 | On affected platforms running Arista EOS, maliciously formed UDP packets with source port 3503 may be accepted by EOS. UDP Port 3503 is associated with LspPing Echo Reply. This can result in unexpected behaviors, especially for UDP based services that do n</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6188</link><description>On affected platforms running Arista EOS, maliciously formed UDP packets with source port 3503 may be accepted by EOS. UDP Port 3503 is associated with LspPing Echo Reply. This can result in unexpected behaviors, especially for UDP based services that do not perform some form of authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3456 | On affected platforms running Arista EOS, the global common encryption key configuration may be logged in clear text, in local or remote accounting logs. Knowledge of both the encryption key and protocol specific encrypted secrets from the device running-c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3456</link><description>On affected platforms running Arista EOS, the global common encryption key configuration may be logged in clear text, in local or remote accounting logs. Knowledge of both the encryption key and protocol specific encrypted secrets from the device running-config could then be used to obtain protocol specific passwords in cases where symmetric passwords are required between devices with neighbor protocol relationships.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9417 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System addemployee.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9417</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /employee/addemployee.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52130 | File upload vulnerability in WebErpMesv2 1.17 in the app/Http/Controllers/FactoryController.php controller. This flaw allows an authenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52130</link><description>File upload vulnerability in WebErpMesv2 1.17 in the app/Http/Controllers/FactoryController.php controller. This flaw allows an authenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files, including PHP scripts, which can be accessed via direct GET requests, potentially resulting in remote code execution (RCE) on the web server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:48:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9416 | oitcode samarium Pages Image webpage cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9416</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in oitcode samarium up to 0.9.6. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /cms/webpage/ of the component Pages Image Handler. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from a remote location. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9415 | GreenCMS index.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9415</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in GreenCMS up to 2.3.0603. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php?m=admin&amp;amp;c=media&amp;amp;a=fileconnect. The manipulation of the argument upload[] leads to unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9414 | kalcaddle kodbox Download from Link serverDownload server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9414</link><description>A vulnerability was found in kalcaddle kodbox 1.61. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /?explorer/upload/serverDownload of the component Download from Link Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument url results in server-side request forgery. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9413 | lostvip-com ruoyi-go system_router.go SelectListByPage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9413</link><description>A flaw has been found in lostvip-com ruoyi-go up to 2.1. This impacts the function SelectListByPage of the file modules/system/system_router.go. This manipulation of the argument orderByColumn/isAsc causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57811 | Craft Potential Remote Code Execution via Twig SSTI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57811</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences. From versions 4.0.0-RC1 to 4.16.5 and 5.0.0-RC1 to 5.8.6, there is a potential remote code execution vulnerability via Twig SSTI (Server-Side Template Injection). This is a follow-up to CVE-2024-52293. This vulnerability has been patched in versions 4.16.6 and 5.8.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50383 | alextselegidis Easy!Appointments v1.5.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the order_by parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50383</link><description>alextselegidis Easy!Appointments v1.5.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the order_by parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57802 | Airlink&amp;#x27;s Daemon Symlink Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57802</link><description>Airlink's Daemon interfaces with Docker and the Panel to provide secure access for controlling instances via the Panel. In version 1.0.0, an attacker with access to the affected container can create symbolic links inside the mounted directory (/app/data). Because the container bind-mounts an arbitrary host path, these symlinks can point to sensitive locations on the host filesystem. When the application or other processes follow these symlinks, the attacker can gain unauthorized read access to host files outside the container. This issue has been patched in version 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9412 | lostvip-com ruoyi-go DictDataDao.go SelectListByPage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9412</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in lostvip-com ruoyi-go up to 2.1. This affects the function SelectListByPage of the file modules/system/dao/DictDataDao.go. The manipulation of the argument orderByColumn/isAsc results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:44:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9411 | lostvip-com ruoyi-go LoginInforService.go SelectPageList sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9411</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in lostvip-com ruoyi-go up to 2.1. The impacted element is the function SelectPageList of the file modules/system/service/LoginInforService.go. The manipulation of the argument isAsc leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57772 | Dataease H2 JDBC RCE Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57772</link><description>DataEase is an open source business intelligence and data visualization tool. Prior to version 2.10.12, there is a H2 JDBC RCE bypass in DataEase. If the JDBC URL meets criteria, the getJdbcUrl method is returned, which acts as the getter for the JdbcUrl parameter provided. This bypasses H2's filtering logic and returns the H2 JDBC URL, allowing the "driver":"org.h2.Driver" to specify the H2 driver for the JDBC connection. The vulnerability has been fixed in version 2.10.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50722 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in sparkshop v.1.1.7 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Common.php component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50722</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in sparkshop v.1.1.7 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Common.php component</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29420 | PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 has a directory traversal vulnerability in the getThemeFilesByName function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29420</link><description>PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 has a directory traversal vulnerability in the getThemeFilesByName function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29421 | PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 has an arbitrary file read vulnerability in the getThemeFileContent function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29421</link><description>PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 has an arbitrary file read vulnerability in the getThemeFileContent function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57773 | Dataease DB2 Aspectweaver Deserialization Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57773</link><description>DataEase is an open source business intelligence and data visualization tool. Prior to version 2.10.12, because DB2 parameters are not filtered, a JNDI injection attack can be directly launched. JNDI triggers an AspectJWeaver deserialization attack, writing to various files. This vulnerability requires commons-collections 4.x and aspectjweaver-1.9.22.jar. The vulnerability has been fixed in version 2.10.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9410 | lostvip-com ruoyi-go GenTableDao.go SelectListByPage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9410</link><description>A weakness has been identified in lostvip-com ruoyi-go up to 2.1. The affected element is the function SelectListByPage of the file modules/system/dao/GenTableDao.go. Executing manipulation of the argument isAsc/orderByColumn can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53120 | Securden Unified PAM Path Traversal In File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53120</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in unauthenticated upload functionality allows a malicious actor to upload binaries and scripts to the server’s configuration and web root directories, achieving remote code execution on the Unified PAM server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57760 | Langflow Vulnerable to Privilege Escalation via CLI Superuser Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57760</link><description>Langflow is a tool for building and deploying AI-powered agents and workflows. A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in Langflow containers where an authenticated user with RCE access can invoke the internal CLI command langflow superuser to create a new administrative user. This results in full superuser access, even if the user initially registered through the UI as a regular (non-admin) account. A patched version has not been made public at this time.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6737 | Securden Unified PAM Shared SSH Key and Cloud Infrastructure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6737</link><description>Securden’s Unified PAM Remote Vendor Gateway access portal shares infrastructure and access tokens across multiple tenants. A malicious actor can obtain authentication material and access the gateway server with low-privilege permissions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53118 | Securden Unified PAM Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53118</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability exists which allows an unauthenticated attacker to control administrator backup functions, leading to compromise of passwords, secrets, and application session tokens stored by the Unified PAM.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53119 | Securden Unified PAM Unauthenticated Unrestricted File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53119</link><description>An unauthenticated unrestricted file upload vulnerability allows an attacker to upload malicious binaries and scripts to the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9409 | lostvip-com ruoyi-go CommonController.go DownloadUpload path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9409</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in lostvip-com ruoyi-go up to 2.1. Impacted is the function DownloadTmp/DownloadUpload of the file modules/system/controller/CommonController.go. Performing manipulation of the argument fileName results in path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:19:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3478 | OpenText Enterprise Security Manager Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3478</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in OpenText Enterprise Security Manager. The vulnerability could be remotely exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:55:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55574 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in docmost v.0.21.0 and before allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55574</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in docmost v.0.21.0 and before allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:55:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55301 | The Scratch Channel Allows Username Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55301</link><description>The Scratch Channel is a news website. In version 1, it is possible to go to application in devtools and click local storage to edit the account's username locally. This issue has been patched in version 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55575 | SQL Injection vulnerability in SMM Panel 3.1 allowing remote attackers to gain sensitive information via a crafted HTTP request with action=...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55575</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in SMM Panel 3.1 allowing remote attackers to gain sensitive information via a crafted HTTP request with action=service_detail.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29523 | D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ping6 function...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29523</link><description>D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ping6 function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55409 | FoxCMS 1.2.6, there is a Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in /index.php/article. This allows attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55409</link><description>FoxCMS 1.2.6, there is a Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in /index.php/article. This allows attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50900 | An issue was discovered in getrebuild/rebuild 4.0.4. The affected source code class is com.rebuild.web.RebuildWebInterceptor, and the affect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50900</link><description>An issue was discovered in getrebuild/rebuild 4.0.4. The affected source code class is com.rebuild.web.RebuildWebInterceptor, and the affected function is preHandle In the filter code, use CodecUtils.urlDecode(request.getRequestURI()) to obtain the URL-decoded request path, and then determine whether the path endsWith /error. If so, execute return true to skip this Interceptor. Else, redirect to /user/login api. Allowing unauthenticated attackers to gain sensitive information or escalated privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56212 | phpgurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in add-doctor.php via the docname parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56212</link><description>phpgurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in add-doctor.php via the docname parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56214 | phpgurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in index.php via the username parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56214</link><description>phpgurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in index.php via the username parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5302 | Denial of Service (DOS) in JSONReader in run-llama/llama_index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5302</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the JSONReader component of the run-llama/llama_index repository, specifically in version v0.12.37. The vulnerability is caused by uncontrolled recursion when parsing deeply nested JSON files, which can lead to Python hitting its maximum recursion depth limit. This results in high resource consumption and potential crashes of the Python process. The issue is resolved in version 0.12.38.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56215 | phpgurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in contact.php via the pagetitle parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56215</link><description>phpgurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in contact.php via the pagetitle parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:10:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56216 | phpgurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in about-us.php via the pagetitle parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56216</link><description>phpgurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in about-us.php via the pagetitle parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46412 | Incorrect access control in the prehandle function of Rebuild v3.7.7 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted GET request sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46412</link><description>Incorrect access control in the prehandle function of Rebuild v3.7.7 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted GET request sent to /commons/ip-location.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44179 | Hitron CGNF-TWN 3.1.1.43-TWN-pre3 contains a command injection vulnerability in the telnet service. The issue arises due to improper input v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44179</link><description>Hitron CGNF-TWN 3.1.1.43-TWN-pre3 contains a command injection vulnerability in the telnet service. The issue arises due to improper input validation within the telnet command handling mechanism. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by injecting arbitrary commands through the telnet interface when prompted for inputs or commands. Successful exploitation could lead to remote code execution (RCE) under the privileges of the telnet user, potentially allowing unauthorized access to system settings and sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46413 | Rebuild v3.7.7 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the type parameter in the com.rebuild.web.admin.rbstore.RB...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46413</link><description>Rebuild v3.7.7 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the type parameter in the com.rebuild.web.admin.rbstore.RBStoreController#loadDataIndex method.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29520 | Incorrect access control in the Maintenance module of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows authenticated attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29520</link><description>Incorrect access control in the Maintenance module of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows authenticated attackers with low-level privileges to arbitrarily change the high-privileged account passwords and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29521 | Insecure default credentials for the Adminsitrator account of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29521</link><description>Insecure default credentials for the Adminsitrator account of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows attackers to escalate privileges via a bruteforce attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29522 | D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ping function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29522</link><description>D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ping function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29524 | Incorrect access control in the component /cgi-bin/system_diagnostic_main.asp of DASAN GPON ONU H660WM H660WMR210825 allows attackers to acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29524</link><description>Incorrect access control in the component /cgi-bin/system_diagnostic_main.asp of DASAN GPON ONU H660WM H660WMR210825 allows attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29525 | DASAN GPON ONU H660WM OS version H660WMR210825 Hardware version DS-E5-583-A1 was discovered to contain insecure default credentials in the m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29525</link><description>DASAN GPON ONU H660WM OS version H660WMR210825 Hardware version DS-E5-583-A1 was discovered to contain insecure default credentials in the modem's control panel.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44178 | DASAN GPON ONU H660WM H660WMR210825 is susceptible to improper access control under its default settings. Attackers can exploit this vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44178</link><description>DASAN GPON ONU H660WM H660WMR210825 is susceptible to improper access control under its default settings. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability to gain unauthorized access to sensitive information and modify its configuration via the UPnP protocol WAN sides without any authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51281 | D-Link DI-8100 16.07.26A1 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the en`, `val and id parameters in the qj_asp function. This vulnerability al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51281</link><description>D-Link DI-8100 16.07.26A1 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the en`, `val and id parameters in the qj_asp function. This vulnerability allows authenticated attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by sending crafted GET requests with overly long values for these parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29519 | A command injection vulnerability in the EXE parameter of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows attackers to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29519</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the EXE parameter of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via supplying a crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32468 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the BMPv3 Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When loading a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32468</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the BMPv3 Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When loading a specially crafted .bmp file, an integer overflow can be made to occur when calculating the stride for decoding. Afterwards, this will cause a heap-based buffer to overflow when decoding the image which can lead to remote code execution. An attacker will need to convince the library to read a file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35984 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PCX Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When decoding th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35984</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PCX Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When decoding the image data from a specially crafted .pcx file, a heap-based buffer overflow can occur which allows for remote code execution. An attacker will need to convince the library to read a file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46407 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the BMPv3 Palette Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When loading...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46407</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the BMPv3 Palette Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When loading a specially crafted .bmp file, an integer overflow can be made to occur which will cause a heap-based buffer to overflow when reading the palette from the image. These conditions can allow for remote code execution. An attacker will need to convince the library to read a file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50129 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PCX Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When decoding th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50129</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PCX Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When decoding the image data from a specially crafted .tga file, a heap-based buffer overflow can occur which allows for remote code execution. An attacker will need to convince the library to read a file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52456 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the WebP Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When loading a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52456</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the WebP Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When loading a specially crafted .webp animation an integer overflow can be made to occur when calculating the stride for decoding. Afterwards, this will cause a heap-based buffer to overflow when decoding the image which can lead to remote code execution. An attacker will need to convince the library to read a file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52930 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the BMPv3 RLE Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When decompressi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52930</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the BMPv3 RLE Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When decompressing the image data from a specially crafted .bmp file, a heap-based buffer overflow can occur which allows for remote code execution. An attacker will need to convince the library to read a file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53085 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PSD RLE Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When decompressing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53085</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PSD RLE Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When decompressing the image data from a specially crafted .psd file, a heap-based buffer overflow can occur which allows for remote code execution. An attacker will need to convince the library to read a file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53510 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PSD Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When loading a s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53510</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PSD Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When loading a specially crafted .psd file, an integer overflow can be made to occur when calculating the stride for decoding. Afterwards, this will cause a heap-based buffer to overflow when decoding the image which can lead to remote code execution. An attacker will need to convince the library to read a file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26467 | Apache Cassandra: User with MODIFY permission on ALL KEYSPACES can escalate privileges to superuser via unsafe actions (4.0.16 only)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26467</link><description>Privilege Defined With Unsafe Actions vulnerability in Apache Cassandra. An user with MODIFY permission ON ALL KEYSPACES can escalate privileges to superuser within a targeted Cassandra cluster via unsafe actions to a system resource. Operators granting data MODIFY permission on all keyspaces on affected versions should review data access rules for potential breaches.



This issue affects Apache Cassandra 3.0.30, 3.11.17, 4.0.16, 4.1.7, 5.0.2, but this advisory is only for 4.0.16 because the fix to CVE-2025-23015 was incorrectly applied to 4.0.16, so that version is still affected.

Users in the 4.0 series are recommended to upgrade to version 4.0.17 which fixes the issue. Users from 3.0, 3.11, 4.1 and 5.0 series should follow recommendation from CVE-2025-23015.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29514 | Incorrect access control in the config.xgi function of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows attackers to downloa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29514</link><description>Incorrect access control in the config.xgi function of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows attackers to download the configuration file via providing a crafted web request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29515 | Incorrect access control in the DELT_file.xgi endpoint of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows attackers to modi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29515</link><description>Incorrect access control in the DELT_file.xgi endpoint of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows attackers to modify arbitrary settings within the device's XML database, including the administrator’s password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29516 | D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the backup functio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29516</link><description>D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the backup function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29517 | D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the traceroute6 fu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29517</link><description>D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the traceroute6 function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54370 | PhpSpreadsheet vulnerable to SSRF when reading and displaying a processed HTML document in the browser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54370</link><description>PhpOffice/PhpSpreadsheet is a pure PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Prior to versions 1.30.0, 2.1.12, 2.4.0, 3.10.0, and 5.0.0, SSRF can occur when a processed HTML document is read and displayed in the browser. The vulnerability lies in the setPath method of the PhpOffice\PhpSpreadsheet\Worksheet\Drawing class, where a crafted string from the user is passed to the HTML reader. This issue has been patched in versions 1.30.0, 2.1.12, 2.4.0, 3.10.0, and 5.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46411 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46411</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48005 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the RHS2000 parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Bran...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48005</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the RHS2000 parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted RHS2000 file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52461 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in the Nex parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52461</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in the Nex parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted .nex file can lead to an information leak. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52581 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the GDF parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52581</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the GDF parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted GDF file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53511 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53511</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53518 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the ABF parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53518</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the ABF parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted ABF file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53557 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53557</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53853 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the ISHNE parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53853</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the ISHNE parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted ISHNE ECG annotations file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54462 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Nex parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54462</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Nex parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted .nex file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54480 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54480</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8719 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 0:

				if (tag==0) {
					if (len!=1) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag0 incorrect length %i!=1\n",len);
					curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);
				}</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54481 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54481</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8744 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 3:

				else if (tag==3) {
					// character code
					char v[17];		// [1]
					if (len&gt;16) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag2 incorrect length %i&gt;16\n",len);
					curPos += ifread(&amp;amp;v,1,len,hdr);
					v[len]  = 0;

In this case, the overflowed buffer is the newly-declared `v` \[1\] instead of `buf`. Since `v` is only 17 bytes large, much smaller values of `len` (even those encoded using a single octet) can trigger an overflow in this code path.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54482 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54482</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8751 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 4:

				else if (tag==4) {
					// SPR
					if (len&gt;4) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag4 incorrect length %i&gt;4\n",len);
					curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54483 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54483</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8759 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 5:

				else if (tag==5)     //0x05: number of channels
				{
					uint16_t oldNS=hdr-&gt;NS;
					if (len&gt;4) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag5 incorrect length %i&gt;4\n",len);
					curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54484 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54484</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8779 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 6:

				else if (tag==6) 	// 0x06 "number of sequences"
				{
					// NRec
					if (len&gt;4) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag6 incorrect length %i&gt;4\n",len);
					curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54485 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54485</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8785 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 8:

                else if (tag==8) {
                    if (len&gt;2) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag8 incorrect length %i&gt;2\n",len);
                    curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54486 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54486</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8824 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 11:

                else if (tag==11)    //0x0B
                {
                    // Fs
                    if (len&gt;6) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag11 incorrect length %i&gt;6\n",len);
                    double  fval;
                    curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54487 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54487</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8842 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 12:

                else if (tag==12)    //0x0C
                {
                    // sampling resolution
                    if (len&gt;6) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag12 incorrect length %i&gt;6\n",len);
                    val32   = 0;
                    int8_t  v8;
                    curPos += ifread(&amp;amp;UnitCode,1,1,hdr);
                    curPos += ifread(&amp;amp;v8,1,1,hdr);
                    curPos += ifread(buf,1,len-2,hdr);

In addition to values of `len` greater than 130 triggering a buffer overflow, a value of `len` smaller than 2 will also trigger a buffer overflow due to an integer underflow when computing `len-2` in this code path.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54488 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54488</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8850 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 13:

                else if (tag==13) {
                    if (len&gt;8) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag13 incorrect length %i&gt;8\n",len);
                    curPos += ifread(&amp;amp;buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54489 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54489</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8970 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 63:

                else if (tag==63) {
                    uint8_t tag2=255, len2=255;

                    count = 0;
                    while ((count&lt;len) &amp;&amp; !(FlagInfiniteLength &amp;&amp; len2==0 &amp;&amp; tag2==0)){
                        curPos += ifread(&amp;tag2,1,1,hdr);
                        curPos += ifread(&amp;len2,1,1,hdr);
                        if (VERBOSE_LEVEL==9)
                            fprintf(stdout,"MFER: tag=%3i chan=%2i len=%-4i tag2=%3i len2=%3i curPos=%i %li count=%4i\n",tag,chan,len,tag2,len2,curPos,iftell(hdr),(int)count);

                        if (FlagInfiniteLength &amp;&amp; len2==0 &amp;&amp; tag2==0) break;

                        count  += (2+len2);
                        curPos += ifread(&amp;buf,1,len2,hdr);

Here, the number of bytes read is not the Data Length decoded from the current frame in the file (`len`) but rather is a new length contained in a single octet read from the same input file (`len2`). Despite this, a stack-based buffer overflow condition can still occur, as the destination buffer is still `buf`, which has a size of only 128 bytes, while `len2` can be as large as 255.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54490 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54490</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 9090 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 64:

                else if (tag==64)     //0x40
                {
                    // preamble
                    char tmp[256];  // [1]
                    curPos += ifread(tmp,1,len,hdr);

In this case, the overflowed buffer is the newly-declared `tmp` \[1\] instead of `buf`. While `tmp` is larger than `buf`, having a size of 256 bytes, a stack overflow can still occur in cases where `len` is encoded using multiple octets and is greater than 256.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54491 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54491</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 9191 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 65:

                else if (tag==65)     //0x41: patient event
                {
                    // event table

                    curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54492 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54492</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 9141 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 67:

                else if (tag==67)     //0x43: Sample skew
                {
                    int skew=0;     // [1]
                    curPos += ifread(&amp;amp;skew, 1, len,hdr);

In this case, the address of the newly-defined integer `skew` \[1\] is overflowed instead of `buf`. This means a stack overflow can occur using much smaller values of `len` in this code path.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54493 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54493</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 9184 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 131:

                else if (tag==131)    //0x83
                {
                    // Patient Age
                    if (len!=7) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag131 incorrect length %i!=7\n",len);
                    curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54494 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54494</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 9205 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 133:

                else if (tag==133)    //0x85
                {
                    curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45968 | An issue in System PDV v1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the hash parameter in a URL. The application contai...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45968</link><description>An issue in System PDV v1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the hash parameter in a URL. The application contains an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability, which occurs due to a lack of proper authorization checks when accessing objects referenced by this parameter. This allows direct access to other users' data or internal resources without proper permission. Successful exploitation of this flaw may result in the exposure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47799 | Mahara before 22.10.4 and 23.x before 23.04.4 allows information disclosure if the experimental HTML bulk export is used via the administrat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47799</link><description>Mahara before 22.10.4 and 23.x before 23.04.4 allows information disclosure if the experimental HTML bulk export is used via the administration interface or via the CLI, and the resulting export files are given to the account holders. They may contain images of other account holders because the cache is not cleared after the files of one account are exported.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39923 | An issue was discovered in Mahara 24.04 before 24.04.2 and 23.04 before 23.04.7. The About, Contact, and Help footer links can be set up to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39923</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mahara 24.04 before 24.04.2 and 23.04 before 23.04.7. The About, Contact, and Help footer links can be set up to be vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) due to not sanitising the values. These links can only be set up by an admin but are clickable by any logged-in person.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43960 | Adminer 4.8.1, when using Monolog for logging, allows a Denial of Service (memory consumption) via a crafted serialized payload (e.g., using...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43960</link><description>Adminer 4.8.1, when using Monolog for logging, allows a Denial of Service (memory consumption) via a crafted serialized payload (e.g., using s:1000000000), leading to a PHP Object Injection issue. Remote, unauthenticated attackers can trigger this by sending a malicious serialized object, which forces excessive memory usage, rendering Adminer’s interface unresponsive and causing a server-level DoS. While the server may recover after several minutes, multiple simultaneous requests can cause a complete crash requiring manual intervention.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9407 | mtons mblog profile cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9407</link><description>A flaw has been found in mtons mblog up to 3.5.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /settings/profile. Executing manipulation of the argument signature can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48303 | WordPress Post Type Converter plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48303</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Kevin Langley Jr. Post Type Converter allows Cross-Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Post Type Converter: from n/a through 0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8562 | Custom Query Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.4.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Path Traversal via lens Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8562</link><description>The Custom Query Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.0 via the 'lens' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the contents of files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 09:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7426 | MINOVA TTA Information Disclosure and Credential Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7426</link><description>Information disclosure and exposure of authentication FTP credentials over the debug port 1604 in the MINOVA TTA service. This allows unauthenticated remote access to an active FTP account containing sensitive internal data and import structures. In environments where this FTP server is part of automated business processes (e.g. EDI or data integration), this could lead to data manipulation, extraction, or abuse.  Debug ports 1602, 1603 and 1636 also expose service architecture information and system activity logs</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 08:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5191 | Unquoted Search Path Vulnerability in the Utility for Industrial Computers (Windows)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5191</link><description>An Unquoted Search Path vulnerability has been identified in the utility for Moxa’s industrial computers (Windows). Due to the unquoted path configuration in the SerialInterfaceService.exe utility, a local attacker with limited privileges could place a malicious executable in a higher-priority directory within the search path. When the Serial Interface service starts, the malicious executable could be run with SYSTEM privileges. Successful exploitation could allow privilege escalation or enable an attacker to maintain persistence on the affected system. While successful exploitation can severely impact the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the affected device itself, there is no loss of confidentiality, integrity, or availability within any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 08:18:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9118 | Dataform Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9118</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in the NPM package installation process of Google Cloud Dataform allows a remote attacker to read and write files in other customers' repositories via a maliciously crafted package.json file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54300 | Extension - norrnext.com - Stored XSS vulnerability in Quantum Manager component 1.0.0-3.2.0 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54300</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability in Quantum Manager component 1.0.0-3.2.0 for Joomla was discovered. The SVG upload feature does not sanitize uploads.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54301 | Extension - norrnext.com - Stored XSS vulnerability in Quantum Manager component 1.0.0-3.2.0 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54301</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability in Quantum Manager component 1.0.0-3.2.0 for Joomla was discovered. File names are not properly escaped.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8997 | OpenText Enterprise Security Manager Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8997</link><description>An Information Exposure vulnerability has been identified in OpenText Enterprise Security Manager. The vulnerability could be remotely exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5514 | Denial-of-Service(DoS) Vulnerability in Web server function on MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5514</link><description>Improper Handling of Length Parameter Inconsistency vulnerability in web server function on Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU module allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to delay the processing of the web server function and prevent legitimate users from utilizing the web server function, by sending a specially crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9406 | xuhuisheng lemon CmsArticleController.java uploadImage unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9406</link><description>A weakness has been identified in xuhuisheng lemon up to 1.13.0. This affects the function uploadImage of the file CmsArticleController.java of the component com.mossle.cms.web.CmsArticleController.uploadImage. This manipulation of the argument Upload causes unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 03:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9405 | Open5GS gmm-sm.c gmm_state_exception assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9405</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. The impacted element is the function gmm_state_exception of the file src/amf/gmm-sm.c. The manipulation results in reachable assertion. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The patch is identified as 8e5fed16114f2f5e40bee1b161914b592b2b7b8f. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 03:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9404 | Scada-LTS Folder pointHierarchySLTS cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9404</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Scada-LTS up to 2.7.8.1. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /pointHierarchySLTS of the component Folder Handler. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 03:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9403 | jqlang jq JSON jq_test.c run_jq_tests assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9403</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in jqlang jq up to 1.6. Impacted is the function run_jq_tests of the file jq_test.c of the component JSON Parser. Executing manipulation can lead to reachable assertion. The attack requires local access. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Other versions might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9402 | HuangDou UTCMS Config update.php server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9402</link><description>A vulnerability was found in HuangDou UTCMS 9. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file app/modules/ut-frame/admin/update.php of the component Config Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument UPDATEURL results in server-side request forgery. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9401 | HuangDou UTCMS Login login.php comparison</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9401</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in HuangDou UTCMS 9. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file app/modules/ut-frame/admin/login.php of the component Login. Such manipulation of the argument code leads to incorrect comparison. The attack can be executed remotely. The attack requires a high level of complexity. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:48:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9400 | YiFang CMS P_file.php mergeMultipartUpload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9400</link><description>A flaw has been found in YiFang CMS up to 2.0.5. This affects the function mergeMultipartUpload of the file app/utils/base/plugin/P_file.php. This manipulation of the argument File causes unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:48:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9399 | YiFang CMS L_tool.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9399</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in YiFang CMS up to 2.0.5. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file app/logic/L_tool.php. The manipulation of the argument new_url results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9398 | YiFang CMS Migrate.php exportInstallTable information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9398</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in YiFang CMS up to 2.0.5. Affected by this vulnerability is the function exportInstallTable of the file app/utils/base/database/Migrate.php. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 23:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9397 | givanz Vvveb media.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9397</link><description>A weakness has been identified in givanz Vvveb up to 1.0.7.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file /system/traits/media.php. Executing manipulation of the argument files[] can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue. The code maintainer explains, that "[he] fixed the code to remove this vulnerability and will make a new release".</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 23:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9396 | ckolivas lrzip strtol_l.c __GI_____strtol_l_internal null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9396</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in ckolivas lrzip up to 0.651. This impacts the function __GI_____strtol_l_internal of the file strtol_l.c. Performing manipulation results in null pointer dereference. The attack is only possible with local access. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 22:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9395 | wangsongyan wblog backup.go RestorePost server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9395</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in wangsongyan wblog 0.0.1. This affects the function RestorePost of the file backup.go. Such manipulation of the argument fileName leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 22:15:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9394 | PoDoFo PDF Dictionary PdfTokenizer.cpp DetermineDataType use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9394</link><description>A flaw has been found in PoDoFo 1.1.0-dev. This issue affects the function PdfTokenizer::DetermineDataType of the file src/podofo/main/PdfTokenizer.cpp of the component PDF Dictionary Parser. Executing manipulation can lead to use after free. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been published and may be used. This patch is called 22d16cb142f293bf956f66a4d399cdd65576d36c. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:16:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9393 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 addStaProfile stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9393</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This vulnerability affects the function addStaProfile of the file /goform/addStaProfile. Performing manipulation of the argument profile_name/Ssid/wep_key_1/wep_key_2/wep_key_3/wep_key_4/wep_key_length/wep_default_key/cipher/passphrase results in stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 15:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9392 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 qosClassifier stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9392</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This affects the function qosClassifier of the file /goform/qosClassifier. Such manipulation of the argument dir/sFromPort/sToPort/dFromPort/dToPort/protocol/layer7/dscp/remark_dscp leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 15:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9391 | Bjskzy Zhiyou ERP com.artery.workflow.ServiceImpl getFieldValue sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9391</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Bjskzy Zhiyou ERP up to 11.0. Affected by this issue is the function getFieldValue of the component com.artery.workflow.ServiceImpl. This manipulation of the argument sql causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 14:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9390 | vim xxd xxd.c main buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9390</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in vim up to 9.1.1615. Affected by this vulnerability is the function main of the file src/xxd/xxd.c of the component xxd. The manipulation results in buffer overflow. The attack requires a local approach. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. Upgrading to version 9.1.1616 addresses this issue. The patch is identified as eeef7c77436a78cd27047b0f5fa6925d56de3cb0. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 14:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9389 | vim memmove-vec-unaligned-erms.S __memmove_avx_unaligned_erms memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9389</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in vim 9.1.0000. Affected is the function __memmove_avx_unaligned_erms of the file memmove-vec-unaligned-erms.S. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack needs to be performed locally. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. Some users are not able to reproduce this. One of the users mentions that this appears not to be working, "when coloring is turned on".</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 13:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9388 | Scada-LTS watch_list.shtm cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9388</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Scada-LTS up to 2.7.8.1. This impacts an unknown function of the file watch_list.shtm. Executing manipulation of the argument Name can lead to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9387 | DCN DCME-720 Web Management Backend ip_block.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9387</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DCN DCME-720 9.1.5.11. This affects an unknown function of the file /usr/local/www/function/audit/newstatistics/ip_block.php of the component Web Management Backend. Performing manipulation of the argument ip results in os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. Other products might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9386 | appneta tcpreplay tcprewrite get.c get_l2len_protocol use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9386</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in appneta tcpreplay up to 4.5.1. The impacted element is the function get_l2len_protocol of the file get.c of the component tcprewrite. Such manipulation leads to use after free. The attack must be carried out locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.5.2-beta3 is sufficient to resolve this issue. You should upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 11:09:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9385 | appneta tcpreplay tcprewrite edit_packet.c fix_ipv6_checksums use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9385</link><description>A flaw has been found in appneta tcpreplay up to 4.5.1. The affected element is the function fix_ipv6_checksums of the file edit_packet.c of the component tcprewrite. This manipulation causes use after free. The attack is restricted to local execution. The exploit has been published and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.5.2-beta3 is sufficient to fix this issue. It is advisable to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9384 | appneta tcpreplay parse_args.c tcpedit_post_args null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9384</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in appneta tcpreplay up to 4.5.1. Impacted is the function tcpedit_post_args of the file /src/tcpedit/parse_args.c. The manipulation results in null pointer dereference. The attack is only possible with local access. The exploit is now public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.5.2-beta2 is recommended to address this issue. Upgrading the affected component is advised. The vendor explains, that he was "[a]ble to reproduce in 6fcbf03 but not in 4.5.2-beta2".</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:11:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9383 | FNKvision Y215 CCTV Camera passwd crypt weak hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9383</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in FNKvision Y215 CCTV Camera 10.194.120.40. This issue affects the function crypt of the file /etc/passwd. The manipulation leads to use of weak hash. The attack can only be performed from a local environment. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 09:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9382 | FNKvision Y215 CCTV Camera Telnet Sevice s1_rf_test_config backdoor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9382</link><description>A weakness has been identified in FNKvision Y215 CCTV Camera 10.194.120.40. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file s1_rf_test_config of the component Telnet Sevice. Executing manipulation can lead to backdoor. The physical device can be targeted for the attack. This attack is characterized by high complexity. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 08:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9381 | FNKvision Y215 CCTV Camera wpa_supplicant.conf information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9381</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in FNKvision Y215 CCTV Camera 10.194.120.40. This affects an unknown part of the file /tmp/wpa_supplicant.conf. Performing manipulation results in information disclosure. The attack may be carried out on the physical device. The attack's complexity is rated as high. It is indicated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 07:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9380 | FNKvision Y215 CCTV Camera Firmware passwd hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9380</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in FNKvision Y215 CCTV Camera 10.194.120.40. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /etc/passwd of the component Firmware. Such manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 07:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9379 | Belkin AX1800 Firmware Update data authenticity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9379</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Belkin AX1800 1.1.00.016. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Firmware Update Handler. This manipulation causes insufficient verification of data authenticity. The attack can be initiated remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 06:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8208 | Spexo Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.0.23 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8208</link><description>The Spexo Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Countdown widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.23 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 05:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36157 | IBM Jazz Foundation incorrect authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36157</link><description>IBM Jazz Foundation 7.0.2 to 7.0.2 iFix035, 7.0.3 to 7.0.3 iFix018, and 7.1.0 to 7.1.0 iFix004 could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to update server property files that would allow them to perform unauthorized actions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 03:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36174 | IBM Integrated Analytics System file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36174</link><description>IBM Integrated Analytics System 1.0.0.0 through 1.0.30.0 could allow an authenticated user to upload a file with dangerous types that could be executed by another user if opened.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 03:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9363 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 portTriggerManageRule stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9363</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This affects the function portTriggerManageRule of the file /goform/portTriggerManageRule. The manipulation of the argument triggerRuleName/schedule leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 14:21:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9362 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 urlFilterManageRule stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9362</link><description>A flaw has been found in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. The impacted element is the function urlFilterManageRule of the file /goform/urlFilterManageRule. Executing manipulation of the argument urlFilterRuleName/scheduleUrl/addURLFilter can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 13:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9361 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 ipRangeBlockManageRule stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9361</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. The affected element is the function ipRangeBlockManageRule of the file /goform/ipRangeBlockManageRule. Performing manipulation of the argument ipRangeBlockRuleName/scheduleIp/ipRangeBlockRuleIpAddr results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 12:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9360 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 accessControlAdd stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9360</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. Impacted is the function accessControlAdd of the file /goform/accessControlAdd. Such manipulation of the argument ruleName/schedule leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 10:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9359 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 RP_checkCredentialsByBBS stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9359</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This issue affects the function RP_checkCredentialsByBBS of the file /goform/RP_checkCredentialsByBBS. This manipulation of the argument ssidhex/pwd causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9358 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 setSysAdm stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9358</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This vulnerability affects the function setSysAdm of the file /goform/setSysAdm. The manipulation of the argument admpasshint results in stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 07:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5352 | Environment Variable XSS in Analytics Component in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5352</link><description>A critical stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Analytics component of lunary-ai/lunary versions up to 1.9.23, where the NEXT_PUBLIC_CUSTOM_SCRIPT environment variable is directly injected into the DOM using dangerouslySetInnerHTML without any sanitization or validation. This allows arbitrary JavaScript execution in all users' browsers if an attacker can control the environment variable during deployment or through server compromise. The vulnerability can lead to complete account takeover, data exfiltration, malware distribution, and persistent attacks affecting all users until the environment variable is cleaned. The issue is fixed in version 1.9.25.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 07:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5060 | Bravis User &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authentication Bypass to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5060</link><description>The Bravis User plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to the plugin not properly logging a user in with the data that was previously verified through the facebook_ajax_login_callback(). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as administrative users, as long as they have an existing account on the site, and access to the administrative user's email.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 06:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5821 | Case Theme User &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Authentication Bypass via Social Login</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5821</link><description>The Case Theme User plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This is due to the plugin not properly logging a user in with the data that was previously verified through the facebook_ajax_login_callback(). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as administrative users, as long as they have an existing account on the site, and access to the administrative user's email.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 06:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9357 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 langSwitchByBBS stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9357</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This affects the function langSwitchByBBS of the file /goform/langSwitchByBBS. The manipulation of the argument langSelectionOnly leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 06:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7813 | Event Manager, Events Calendar, Booking, Registrations and Tickets – Eventin &amp;lt;= 4.0.37 - Unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7813</link><description>The Events Calendar, Event Booking, Registrations and Event Tickets – Eventin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.37 via the proxy_image function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 05:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43764 | Self-ReDoS (Regular expression Denial of Service) exists with Role Name search field of Kaleo Designer portlet JavaScript in Liferay Portal ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43764</link><description>Self-ReDoS (Regular expression Denial of Service) exists with Role Name search field of Kaleo Designer portlet JavaScript in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.1, 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.1 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.20 and 7.4 GA through update 92, which allows authenticated users with permissions to update Kaleo Workflows to enter a malicious Regex pattern causing their browser to hang for a very long time.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 05:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43765 | A Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q4.0, 2024.Q3.1 through 2024...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43765</link><description>A Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q4.0, 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.13 and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows an remote non-authenticated attacker to inject JavaScript into the text field from a web content.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 04:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43766 | The Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.3.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q4.0, 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43766</link><description>The Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.3.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q4.0, 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12 and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows the upload of unrestricted files in the style books component that are processed within the environment enabling arbitrary code execution by attackers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 04:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7642 | Simpler Checkout 0.7.0 - 1.1.9 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7642</link><description>The Simpler Checkout plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in versions 0.7.0 to 1.1.9. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a user's identity prior to logging them in as an admin through the simplerwc_woocommerce_order_created() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as other users based on their order ID, which can be an administrator if a site admin has placed a test order.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 04:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7821 | WC Plus &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Settings Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7821</link><description>The WC Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'pluswc_logo_favicon_logo_base' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the site's favicon logo base.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 04:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7827 | Ni WooCommerce Customer Product Report &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7827</link><description>The Ni WooCommerce Customer Product Report plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ni_woocpr_action() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 04:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7828 | WP Filter &amp;amp; Combine RSS Feeds &amp;lt;= 0.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Feed Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7828</link><description>The WP Filter &amp; Combine RSS Feeds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the post_listing_page() function in all versions up to, and including, 0.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete feeds.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 04:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7839 | Restore Permanently delete Post or Page Data &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7839</link><description>The Restore Permanently delete Post or Page Data plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the rp_dpo_dpa_ajax_dp_delete_data() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete data via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 04:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7841 | Sertifier Certificate &amp;amp; Badge Maker for WordPress – Tutor LMS &amp;lt;= 1.19 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7841</link><description>The Sertifier Certificate &amp; Badge Maker for WordPress – Tutor LMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.19. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'sertifier_settings' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's api key via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 04:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7842 | Silencesoft RSS Reader &amp;lt;= 0.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to RSS Feed Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7842</link><description>The Silencesoft RSS Reader plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'sil_rss_edit_page' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete RSS feeds via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 04:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7957 | ShortcodeHub &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via author_link_target Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7957</link><description>The ShortcodeHub plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘author_link_target’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 04:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8062 | WS Theme Addons &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via ws_weather Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8062</link><description>The WS Theme Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's ws_weather shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 04:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9048 | Wptobe-memberships &amp;lt;= 3.4.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9048</link><description>The Wptobe-memberships plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the del_img_ajax_call() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 04:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9131 | Ogulo – 360° Tour &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via slug Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9131</link><description>The Ogulo – 360° Tour plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘slug’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 04:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43767 | Open Redirect vulnerability in /c/portal/edit_info_item parameter redirect in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.86 through 7.4.3.131, and Liferay DXP 202...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43767</link><description>Open Redirect vulnerability in /c/portal/edit_info_item parameter redirect in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.86 through 7.4.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3.9, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12 and 7.4 update 86 through update 92 allows an attacker to exploit this security vulnerability to redirect users to a malicious site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 03:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43768 | Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.7, 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43768</link><description>Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.7, 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.15 and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows authenticated users without any permissions to access sensitive information of admin users using JSONWS APIs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 03:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43769 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3.8, 2024...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43769</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3.8, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12 and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary web script or HTML via components tab.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 03:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43770 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43770</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.3, 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12 and 7.4 GA through update 92  allows an remote non-authenticated attacker to inject JavaScript into the referer or FORWARD_URL using %00 in those parameters.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 02:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>