<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:40:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-59952 | minio-java Client XML Tag is Vulnerable to Value Substitution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59952</link><description>MinIO Java SDK is a Simple Storage Service (aka S3) client to perform bucket and object operations to any Amazon S3 compatible object storage service. In minio-java versions prior to 8.6.0, XML tag values containing references to system properties or environment variables were automatically substituted with their actual values during processing. This unintended behavior could lead to the exposure of sensitive information, including credentials, file paths, or system configuration details, if such references were present in XML content from untrusted sources. This is fixed in version 8.6.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59950 | FreshRSS: Double clickjacking can lead to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59950</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. In versions 1.26.3 and below, due to a bypass of double clickjacking protection (confirmation dialog), it is possible to trick the admin into clicking the Promote button in another user's management page after the admin double clicks on a button inside an attacker-controlled website. A successful attack can allow the attacker to promote themselves to "admin" and log into other users' accounts; the attacker has to know the specific instance URL they're targeting. This issue is fixed in version 1.27.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61586 | FreshRSS is vulnerable to directory enumeration by setting path in its theme field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61586</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. Versions 1.26.3 and below are vulnerable to directory enumeration by setting path in theme field, allowing attackers to gain additional information about the server by checking if certain directories exist. This issue is fixed in version 1.27.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59948 | FreshRSS is vulnerable to XSS due to lack of CSP on HTML query page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59948</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. Versions 1.26.3 and below do not sanitize certain event handler attributes in feed content, so by finding a page that renders feed entries without CSP, it is possible to execute an XSS payload. The Allow API access authentication setting needs to be enabled by the instance administrator beforehand for the attack to work as it relies on api/query.php. An account takeover is possible by sending a change password request via the XSS payload / setting UserJS for persistence / stealing the autofill password / displaying a phishing page with a spoofed URL using history.replaceState()
If the victim is an administrator, the attacker can also perform administrative actions. This issue is fixed in version 1.27.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:18:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59942 | go-f3 module vulnerable to integer overflow leading to panic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59942</link><description>go-f3 is a Golang implementation of Fast Finality for Filecoin (F3). In versions 0.8.6 and below, go-f3 panics when it validates a "poison" messages causing Filecoin nodes consuming F3 messages to become vulnerable. A "poison" message can can cause integer overflow in the signer index validation, which can cause the whole node to crash. These malicious messages aren't self-propagating since the bug is in the validator. An attacker needs to directly send the message to all targets. This issue is fixed in version 0.8.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59941 | go-f3 is Vulnerable to Cached Justification Verification Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59941</link><description>go-f3 is a Golang implementation of Fast Finality for Filecoin (F3). In versions 0.8.8 and below, go-f3's justification verification caching mechanism has a vulnerability where verification results are cached without properly considering the context of the message. An attacker can bypass justification verification by submitting a valid message with a correct justification and then reusing the same cached justification in contexts where it would normally be invalid. This occurs because the cached verification does not properly validate the relationship between the justification and the specific message context it's being used with. This issue is fixed in version 0.8.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36245 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36245</link><description>IBM InfoSphere 11.7.0.0 through 11.7.1.6 Information Server could allow an authenticated user to execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges on the system due to improper validation of user supplied input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43817 | Multiple reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.74 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 throug...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43817</link><description>Multiple reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.74 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.6, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, and 7.4 update 74 through update 92 allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the `redirect` parameter to (1) Announcements, or (2) Alerts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43813 | Possible path traversal vulnerability and denial-of-service in the ComboServlet in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.107, and older unsuppo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43813</link><description>Possible path traversal vulnerability and denial-of-service in the ComboServlet in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.107, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.4, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, 7.4 GA through update 92, 7.3 GA through update 35, and older unsupported versions allows remote attackers to access arbitrary CSS and JSS files and load the files multiple times via the query string in a URL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59937 | go-mail has insufficient address encoding when passing mail addresses to the SMTP client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59937</link><description>go-mail is a comprehensive library for sending mails with Go. In versions 0.7.0 and below, due to incorrect handling of the mail.Address values when a sender- or recipient address is passed to the corresponding MAIL FROM or RCPT TO commands of the SMTP client, there is a possibility of wrong address routing or even ESMTP parameter smuggling. For successful exploitation, it is required that the user's code allows for arbitrary mail address input (i. e. through a web form or similar). If only static mail addresses are used (i. e. in a config file) and the mail addresses in use do not consist of quoted local parts, this should not affect users. This issue is fixed in version 0.7.1</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59940 | mkdocs-include-markdown-plugin susceptible to unvalidated input colliding with substitution placeholders</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59940</link><description>mkdocs-include-markdown-plugin is an Mkdocs Markdown includer plugin. In versions 7.1.7 and below, there is a vulnerability where unvalidated input can collide with substitution placeholders. This issue is fixed in version 7.1.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43812 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in web content template in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.4 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 thro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43812</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in web content template in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.4 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.4, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into a web content structure's Name text field</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59933 | libvips is vulnerable to Buffer Over-Read in poppler-based pdfload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59933</link><description>libvips is a demand-driven, horizontally threaded image processing library. For versions 8.17.1 and below, when libvips is compiled with support for PDF input via poppler, the pdfload operation is affected by a buffer read overflow when parsing the header of a crafted PDF with a page that defines a width but not a height. Those using libvips compiled without support for PDF input are unaffected as well as thosewith support for PDF input via PDFium. This issue is fixed in version 8.17.2. A workaround for those affected is to block the VipsForeignLoadPdf operation via vips_operation_block_set, which is available in most language bindings, or to set VIPS_BLOCK_UNTRUSTED environment variable at runtime, which will block all untrusted loaders including PDF input via poppler.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43811 | Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the related asset selector in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.50 through 7.4.3.111, and Lif...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43811</link><description>Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the related asset selector in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.50 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.4, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.7, and 7.4 update 50 through update 92 allows remote authenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into an asset author’s (1) First Name, (2) Middle Name, or (3) Last Name text field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43820 | Multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the Calendar widget when inviting users to a event in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.35 through...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43820</link><description>Multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the Calendar widget when inviting users to a event in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.35 through 7.4.3.110, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.4, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.6, 7.4 update 35 through update 92, and 7.3 update 25 through update 35 allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into a user’s (1) First Name, (2) Middle text, or (3) Last Name text fields.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59163 | vet MCP Server SSE Transport DNS Rebinding Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59163</link><description>vet is an open source software supply chain security tool. Versions 1.12.4 and below are vulnerable to a DNS rebinding attack due to lack of HTTP Host and Origin header validation. Data from the vet scan sqlite3 database may be exposed to remote attackers when vet is used as an MCP server in SSE mode with default ports through the sqlite3 query MCP tool. This issue is fixed in version 1.12.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43818 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Calendar widget in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.35 through 7.4.3.110, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 thro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43818</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Calendar widget in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.35 through 7.4.3.110, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.4, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.6, 7.4 update 35 through update 92, and 7.3 update 25 through update 36 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into a Calendar's “Name” text field</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:51:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57769 | FressRSS: Clickjacking can lead to XSS and/or privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57769</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. Versions 1.26.3 and below contain a vulnerability where a specially crafted page can trick a user into executing arbitrary JS code or promoting a user in FreshRSS by obscuring UI elements in iframes. If embedding an authenticated iframe is possible, this may lead to privilege escalation via obscuring the promote user button in the admin UI or XSS by tricking the user to drag content into the UserJS text area. This is fixed in version 1.27.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:51:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54875 | FreshRSS: Unauthorized creation of admin user when registration is enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54875</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. In versions 1.16.0 and above through 1.26.3, an unprivileged attacker can create a new admin user when registration is enabled through the use of a hidden field used only in the user management admin page, new_user_is_admin. This is fixed in version 1.27.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54592 | FreshRSS has Incomplete Session Termination on Logout</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54592</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. Versions 1.26.3 and below do not properly terminate the session during logout. After a user logs out, the session cookie remains active and unchanged. The unchanged cookie could be reused by an attacker if a new session were to be started. This failure to invalidate the session can lead to session hijacking and fixation vulnerabilities. This issue is fixed in version 1.27.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43815 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the page configuration page in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.102 through 7.4.3.110, and Liferay...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43815</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the page configuration page in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.102 through 7.4.3.110, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.2, and 2023.Q3.5 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the com_liferay_layout_admin_web_portlet_GroupPagesPortlet_backURLTitle parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30247 | An OS command injection vulnerability in user interface in Western Digital My Cloud firmware prior to 5.31.108 on NAS platforms allows remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30247</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability in user interface in Western Digital My Cloud firmware prior to 5.31.108 on NAS platforms allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary system commands via a specially crafted HTTP POST.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54591 | FreshRSS: Unauthenticated users can view default user&amp;#x27;s  information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54591</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. Versions 1.26.3 and below expose information about feeds and tags of default admin users, due to lack of access checking in the FreshRSS_Auth::hasAccess() function used by some of the tag/feed related endpoints. FreshRSS controllers usually have a defined firstAction() method with an override to make sure that every action requires access. If one doesn't, then every action has to check for access manually, and certain endpoints use neither the firstAction() method, or do they perform a manual access check. This issue is fixed in version 1.27.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34235 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Weak SSL/TLS Certificate Validation RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34235</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (Windows client deployments) contain a registry key that can be enabled by administrators, causing the client to skip SSL/TLS certificate validation. An attacker who can intercept HTTPS traffic can then inject malicious driver DLLs, resulting in remote code execution with SYSTEM privileges; a local attacker can achieve local privilege escalation via a junction‑point DLL injection. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34207 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Insecure SSH Client Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34207</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to 22.0.1049 and Application prior to 20.0.2786 (VA and SaaS deployments) configure the SSH client within Docker instances with the following options: `UserKnownHostsFile=/dev/null`, `StrictHostKeyChecking=no`, and `ForwardAgent yes`.  These settings disable verification of the remote host’s SSH key and automatically forward the developer’s SSH‑agent to any host that matches the configured wildcard patterns.  As a result, an attacker who can reach a single compromised container can cause the container to connect to a malicious SSH server, capture the forwarded private keys, and use those keys for unrestricted lateral movement across the environment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34212 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Insecure Build Pipeline</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34212</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 22.0.843 and Application prior to version 20.0.1923 (VA/SaaS deployments) possess CI/CD weaknesses: the build pulls an unverified third-party image, downloads the VirtualBox Extension Pack over plain HTTP without signature validation, and grants the jenkins account NOPASSWD for mount/umount. Together these allow supply chain or man-in-the-middle compromise of the build pipeline, injection of malicious firmware, and remote code execution as root on the CI host. This vulnerability has been identified by the vendor as: V-2023-007 — Supply Chain Attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34215 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Unauthenticate Firmware Update Endpoint RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34215</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 22.0.1026 and Application prior to version 20.0.2702 (only VA deployments) expose an unauthenticated firmware-upload flow: a public page returns a signed token usable at va-api/v1/update, and every Docker image contains the appliance’s private GPG key and hard-coded passphrase. An attacker who extracts the key and obtains a token can decrypt, modify, re-sign, upload, and trigger malicious firmware, gaining remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34216 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) RCE and Password Leaks via API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34216</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 22.0.1026 and Application prior to version 20.0.2702 (VA deployments only) expose a set of unauthenticated REST API endpoints that return configuration files and clear‑text passwords. The same endpoints also disclose the Laravel APP_KEY used for cryptographic signing. Because the APP_KEY is required to generate valid signed requests, an attacker who obtains it can craft malicious payloads that are accepted by the application and achieve remote code execution on the appliance. This vulnerability has been identified by the vendor as: V-2024-018 — RCE &amp; Leaks via API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34220 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Unauthenticated API Leaks Group Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34220</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contains a /api-gateway/identity/search-groups endpoint that does not require authentication. Requests to https://.printercloud10.com/api-gateway/identity/search-groups and adjustments to the `Host` header allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to enumerate every group object stored for that tenant.  The response includes internal identifiers (group ID, source service ID, Azure AD object IDs, creation timestamps, and tenant IDs). This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34221 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34221</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.2.169 and Application prior to version 25.2.1518 (VA/SaaS deployments) expose every internal Docker container to the network because firewall rules allow unrestricted traffic to the Docker bridge network. Because no authentication, ACL or client‑side identifier is required, the attacker can interact with any internal API, bypassing the product’s authentication mechanisms entirely. The result is unauthenticated remote access to internal services, allowing credential theft, configuration manipulation and potential remote code execution. This vulnerability has been identified by the vendor as: V-2025-002 — Authentication Bypass - Docker Instances.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34222 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Unauthenticated Admin APIs Used to Modify SSL Certificates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34222</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 22.0.1049 and Application prior to version 20.0.2786 (VA/SaaS deployments) expose four admin routes – /admin/hp/cert_upload, /admin/hp/cert_delete, /admin/certs/ca, and /admin/certs/serviceclients/{scid} – without any authentication check. The routes are defined in the /var/www/app/routes/web.php file inside the printercloud/pi Docker container and are handled by the HPCertificateController class, which performs no user validation.  An unauthenticated attacker can therefore upload a new TLS/SSL certificate replacing the trusted root used by the appliance, delete an existing certificate causing immediate loss of trust for services that rely on it, or download any stored CA or client certificate via the service‑clients endpoint which also suffers an IDOR that allows enumeration of all client IDs. This vulnerability has been identified by the vendor as: V-2024-028 — Unauthenticated Admin APIs Used to Modify SSL Certificates.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34223 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Insecure Installation Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34223</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 22.0.1049 and Application prior to version 20.0.2786 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain a default admin account and an installation‑time endpoint at `/admin/query/update_database.php` that can be accessed without authentication. An attacker who can reach the installation web interface can POST arbitrary `root_user` and `root_password` values, causing the script to replace the default admin credentials with attacker‑controlled ones. The script also contains hard‑coded SHA‑512 and SHA‑1 hashes of the default password, allowing the attacker to bypass password‑policy validation. As a result, an unauthenticated remote attacker can obtain full administrative control of the system during the initial setup. This vulnerability has been identified by the vendor as: V-2024-022 — Insecure Installation Credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34224 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Unauthenticated Device Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34224</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 22.0.1049 and Application prior to version 20.0.2786 (VA/SaaS deployments) expose a set of PHP scripts under the `console_release` directory without requiring authentication.  An unauthenticated remote attacker can invoke these endpoints to re‑configure networked printers, add or delete RFID badge devices, or otherwise modify device settings. This vulnerability has been identified by the vendor as: V-2024-029 — No Authentication to Modify Devices.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34225 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) SSRF via console_release Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34225</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain a server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability. The `console_release` directory is reachable from the internet without any authentication.  Inside that directory are dozens of PHP scripts that build URLs from user‑controlled values and then invoke either 'curl_exec()` or `file_get_contents()` without proper validation. Although many files attempt to mitigate SSRF by calling `filter_var', the checks are incomplete. Because the endpoint is unauthenticated, any remote attacker can supply a hostname and cause the server to issue requests to internal resources. This enables internal network reconnaissance, potential pivoting, or data exfiltration. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34228 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) SSRF via Lexmark update.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34228</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain a server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability. The `/var/www/app/console_release/lexmark/update.php` script is reachable from the internet without any authentication.  The PHP script builds URLs from user‑controlled values and then invokes either 'curl_exec()` or `file_get_contents()` without proper validation. Because the endpoint is unauthenticated, any remote attacker can supply a hostname and cause the server to issue requests to internal resources. This enables internal network reconnaissance, potential pivoting, or data exfiltration. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34229 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Blind SSRF via HP installApp.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34229</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain a blind server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability reachable via the /var/www/app/console_release/hp/installApp.php script that can be exploited by an unauthenticated user. When a printer is registered, the software stores the printer’s host name in the variable $printer_vo-&gt;str_host_address. The code later builds a URL like 'http://:80/DevMgmt/DiscoveryTree.xml' and sends the request with curl. No validation, whitelist, or private‑network filtering is performed before the request is made. Because the request is blind, an attacker cannot see the data directly, but can still: probe internal services, trigger internal actions, or gather other intelligence. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34230 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Blind SSRF via HP log_off_single_sign_on.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34230</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain a blind server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability reachable via the /var/www/app/console_release/hp/log_off_single_sign_on.php script that can be exploited by an unauthenticated user. When a printer is registered, the software stores the printer’s host name in the variable $printer_vo-&gt;str_host_address. The code later builds a URL like 'http://:80/DevMgmt/DiscoveryTree.xml' and sends the request with curl. No validation, whitelist, or private‑network filtering is performed before the request is made. Because the request is blind, an attacker cannot see the data directly, but can still: probe internal services, trigger internal actions, or gather other intelligence. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34231 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) SSRF via HP badgeSetup.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34231</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain a blind and non-blind server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability. The '/var/www/app/console_release/hp/badgeSetup.php' script is reachable from the Internet without any authentication and builds URLs from user‑controlled parameters before invoking either the custom processCurl() function or PHP’s file_get_contents(); in both cases the hostname/URL is taken directly from the request with no whitelist, scheme restriction, IP‑range validation, or outbound‑network filtering. Consequently, any unauthenticated attacker can force the server to issue arbitrary HTTP requests to internal resources. This enables internal network reconnaissance, credential leakage, pivoting, and data exfiltration. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34233 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Insecure Use of file_get_contents()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34233</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain a protection mechanism failure vulnerability within the file_get_contents() function. When an administrator configures a printer’s hostname (or similar callback field), the value is passed unchecked to PHP’s file_get_contents()/cURL functions, which follow redirects and impose no allow‑list, scheme, or IP‑range restrictions. An admin‑level attacker can therefore point the hostname to a malicious web server that issues a 301 redirect to internal endpoints such as the AWS EC2 metadata service. The server follows the redirect, retrieves the metadata, and returns or stores the credentials, enabling the attacker to steal cloud IAM keys, enumerate internal services, and pivot further into the SaaS infrastructure. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34209 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Hardcoded GPG Private Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34209</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to 22.0.862 and Application prior to 20.0.2014 (VA and SaaS deployments) contain Docker images with the private GPG key and passphrase for the account *no‑reply+virtual‑appliance@printerlogic.com*. The key is stored in cleartext and the passphrase is hardcoded in files. An attacker with administrative access to the appliance can extract the private key, import it into their own system, and subsequently decrypt GPG-encrypted files and sign arbitrary firmware update packages. A maliciously signed update can be uploaded by an admin‑level attacker and will be executed by the appliance, giving the attacker full control of the virtual appliance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34211 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Hardcoded SSL Certificate and Private Keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34211</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 22.0.1049 and Application prior to version 20.0.2786 (VA and SaaS deployments) contain a private SSL key and matching public certificate stored in cleartext. The key belongs to the hostname `pl‑local.com` and is used by the appliance to terminate TLS connections on ports 80/443. Because the key is hardcoded, any attacker who can gain container-level access can simply read the files and obtain the private key. With the private key, the attacker can decrypt TLS traffic, perform man-in-the-middle attacks, or forge TLS certificates. This enables impersonation of the appliance’s web UI, interception of credentials, and unrestricted access to any services that trust the certificate. The same key is identical across all deployed appliances meaning a single theft compromises the confidentiality of every Vasion Print installation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34218 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Exposed Internal Docker Instance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34218</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 22.0.1049 and Application prior to version 20.0.2786 (VA/SaaS deployments) expose internal Docker containers through the gw Docker instance.  The gateway publishes a /meta endpoint which lists every micro‑service container together with version information. These containers are reachable directly over HTTP/HTTPS without any access‑control list (ACL), authentication or rate‑limiting. Consequently, any attacker on the LAN or the Internet can enumerate all internal services and their versions, interact with the exposed APIs of each microservice as an unauthenticated user, or issue malicious requests that may lead to information disclosure, privilege escalation within the container, or denial‑of‑service of the entire appliance. The root cause is the absence of authentication and network‑level restrictions on the API‑gateway’s proxy to internal Docker containers, effectively turning the internal service mesh into a public attack surface. This vulnerability has been identified by the vendor as: V-2024-030 — Exposed Internal Docker Instance (LAN).</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:43:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34232 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Blind SSRF via Lexmark dellCheck.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34232</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain a blind server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability reachable via the /var/www/app/console_release/lexmark/dellCheck.php script that can be exploited by an unauthenticated user. When a printer is registered, the software stores the printer’s host name in the variable $printer_vo-&gt;str_host_address. The code later builds a URL like 'http://:80/DevMgmt/DiscoveryTree.xml' and sends the request with curl. No validation, whitelist, or private‑network filtering is performed before the request is made. Because the request is blind, an attacker cannot see the data directly, but can still: probe internal services, trigger internal actions, or gather other intelligence. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:43:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34234 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Hardcoded Encryption Private Keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34234</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain two hardcoded private keys that are shipped in the application containers (printerlogic/pi, printerlogic/printer-admin-api, and printercloud/pi). The keys are stored in clear text under /var/www/app/config/ as keyfile.ppk.dev and keyfile.saasid.ppk.dev. The application uses these keys as the symmetric secret for AES‑256‑CBC encryption/decryption of the “SaaS Id” (external identifier) through the getEncryptedExternalId() / getDecryptedExternalId() methods. Because the secret is embedded in the deployed image, any attacker who can obtain a copy of the Docker image, read the configuration files, or otherwise enumerate the filesystem can recover the encryption key. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45376 | Dell Repository Manager (DRM), versions 3.4.7 and 3.4.8, contains an Improper Handling of Insufficient Permissions or Privileges vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45376</link><description>Dell Repository Manager (DRM), versions 3.4.7 and 3.4.8, contains an Improper Handling of Insufficient Permissions or Privileges vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57266 | An issue was discovered in file AssistantController.java in ThriveX Blogging Framework 2.5.9 thru 3.1.3 allowing unauthenticated attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57266</link><description>An issue was discovered in file AssistantController.java in ThriveX Blogging Framework 2.5.9 thru 3.1.3 allowing unauthenticated attackers to gain sensitive information such as API Keys via the /api/assistant/list endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35030 | Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health cross site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35030</link><description>Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health has a cross site request forgery vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker to trick administrative users into clicking a crafted URL and perform actions on behalf of that administrative user. This issue is fixed as of 2025-04-08.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:21:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35031 | Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health includes session token in debug output</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35031</link><description>Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health includes the user's current session token in debug output. An attacker could convince a user to send this output to the attacker, thus allowing the attacker to impersonate that user. This issue is fixed as of 2025-04-08.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:21:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35032 | Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health arbitrary file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35032</link><description>Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health allows authenticated users to upload arbitrary files. The impact of this behavior depends on how files are accessed. This issue is fixed as of 2025-04-08.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35033 | Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health CSV injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35033</link><description>Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health has a CSV injection vulnerability that allows a remote, authenticated attacker to inject macros in downloadable CSV files. This issue is fixed as of 2025-03-14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35034 | Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health reflected cross site scripting via portlet_user_id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35034</link><description>Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health has a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in the 'portlet_user_id' URL parameter. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can craft a URL that can execute arbitrary JavaScript in the victim's browser. This issue is fixed as of 2025-03-14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56764 | Trivision NC-227WF firmware 5.80 (build 20141010) login mechanism reveals whether a username exists or not by returning different error mess...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56764</link><description>Trivision NC-227WF firmware 5.80 (build 20141010) login mechanism reveals whether a username exists or not by returning different error messages ("Unknown user" vs. "Wrong password"), allowing an attacker to enumerate valid usernames.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 19:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34196 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Hardcoded PrinterLogic CA Private Key and Hardcoded Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34196</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host versions prior to 25.1.102 and Application prior to 25.1.1413 (Windows client deployments) contain a hardcoded private key for the PrinterLogic Certificate Authority (CA) and a hardcoded password in product configuration files. The Windows client ships the CA certificate and its associated private key (and other sensitive settings such as a configured password) directly in shipped configuration files (for example clientsettings.dat and defaults.ini). An attacker who obtains these files can impersonate the CA, sign arbitrary certificates trusted by the Windows client, intercept or decrypt TLS-protected communications, and otherwise perform man-in-the-middle or impersonation attacks against the product's network communications.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 19:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41252 | Username enumeration vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41252</link><description>Description: VMware NSX contains a username enumeration vulnerability. An unauthenticated malicious actor may exploit this to enumerate valid usernames, potentially leading to unauthorized access attempts.


Impact: Username enumeration → facilitates unauthorized access.


Attack Vector: Remote, unauthenticated.


Severity: Important.


CVSSv3: 7.5 (High).


Acknowledgments: Reported by the National Security Agency.


Affected Products:



  *  VMware NSX 9.x.x.x, 4.2.x, 4.1.x, 4.0.x

  *  NSX-T 3.x

  *  VMware Cloud Foundation (with NSX) 5.x, 4.5.x












Fixed Versions: 



  *  NSX 9.0.1.0;  4.2.2.2/4.2.3.1 http://4.2.2.2/4.2.3.1 ; 4.1.2.7; NSX-T 3.2.4.3; CCF async patch (KB88287).






Workarounds: None.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 19:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41251 | Weak password recovery vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41251</link><description>VMware NSX contains a weak password recovery mechanism vulnerability. An unauthenticated malicious actor may exploit this to enumerate valid usernames, potentially enabling brute-force attacks.

Impact: Username enumeration → credential brute force risk.
Attack Vector: Remote, unauthenticated.
Severity: Important.
CVSSv3: 8.1 (High).

Acknowledgments: Reported by the National Security Agency.

Affected Products:VMware NSX 9.x.x.x, 4.2.x, 4.1.x, 4.0.x

NSX-T 3.x
VMware Cloud Foundation (with NSX) 5.x, 4.5.x

Fixed Versions: NSX 9.0.1.0;  4.2.2.2/4.2.3.1 http://4.2.2.2/4.2.3.1 ; 4.1.2.7; NSX-T 3.2.4.3; CCF async patch (KB88287).
Workarounds: None.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57424 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the MyCourts v3 application within the LTA number profile field. An attacker can...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57424</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the MyCourts v3 application within the LTA number profile field. An attacker can insert arbitrary JavaScript into their profile, which executes in the browser of any user viewing it, including administrators. Due to the absence of the HttpOnly flag on the session cookie, this flaw could be exploited to capture session tokens and hijack user sessions, enabling elevated access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57871 | BUG-000174020 - Reflected XSS vulnerability identified in Portal for ArcGIS. (11.3, 11.1, 10.9.1)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57871</link><description>There is a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.4 and below that may allow a remote authenticated attacker with administrative access to supply a crafted string which would execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the  browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57872 | BUG-000174150 - Unvalidated redirect in Portal for ArcGIS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57872</link><description>There is an unvalidated redirect vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.4 and below that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL that could redirect a victim to an arbitrary website, simplifying phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57873 | BUG-000175222 - Reflected XSS vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57873</link><description>There is a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.4 and below that may allow a remote authenticated attacker with administrative access to supply a crafted string which would execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the  browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57874 | BUG-000161627 - Reflected XSS vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS.  (11.3, 11.1, 10.9.1)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57874</link><description>There is a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.4 and below that may allow a remote authenticated attacker with administrative access to supply a crafted string which would execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the  browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57875 | BUG-000164122 - Reflected XSS vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57875</link><description>There is a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.4 and below that may allow a remote authenticated attacker with administrative access to supply a crafted string which would execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the  browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57876 | Stored XSS vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57876</link><description>There is a stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in  Esri Portal for ArcGIS  11.4 and below that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to inject malicious a file with an embedded xss script which when loaded could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser. The privileges required to execute this attack are high. The attack could disclose a privileged token which may result in the attacker gaining full control of the Portal.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57877 | Reflected XSS vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57877</link><description>There is a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.4 and below that may allow a remote authenticated attacker with administrative access to supply a crafted string which would execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the  browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57878 | BUG-000174149 - The Portal for ArcGIS has an unvalidated redirect.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57878</link><description>There is an unvalidated redirect vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.4 and below that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL that could redirect a victim to an arbitrary website, simplifying phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57879 | BUG-000171009 - URL manipulation vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57879</link><description>There is an unvalidated redirect vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.4 and below that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL that could redirect a victim to an arbitrary website, simplifying phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36099 | IBM WebSphere Application Server denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36099</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 8.5 and 9.0 is vulnerable to a denial of service, caused by sending a specially-crafted request. A privileged user could exploit this vulnerability to cause the server to consume memory resources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43400 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.1, macOS Tahoe 26.0.1, ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43400</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.1, macOS Tahoe 26.0.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.1, visionOS 26.0.1, iOS 26.0.1 and iPadOS 26.0.1, iOS 18.7.1 and iPadOS 18.7.1. Processing a maliciously crafted font may lead to unexpected app termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56807 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in FairSketch RISE Ultimate Project Manager &amp; CRM 3.9.4 allows an administrator to store a JavaSc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56807</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in FairSketch RISE Ultimate Project Manager &amp; CRM 3.9.4 allows an administrator to store a JavaScript payload using the file explorer in the admin dashboard when creating new folders.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41250 | Header injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41250</link><description>VMware vCenter contains an SMTP header injection vulnerability. A malicious actor with non-administrative privileges on vCenter who has permission to create scheduled tasks may be able to manipulate the notification emails sent for scheduled tasks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57197 | In the Payeer Android application 2.5.0, an improper access control vulnerability exists in the authentication flow for the PIN change featu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57197</link><description>In the Payeer Android application 2.5.0, an improper access control vulnerability exists in the authentication flow for the PIN change feature. A local attacker with root access to the device can dynamically instrument the app to bypass the current PIN verification check and directly modify the authentication PIN. This allows unauthorized users to change PIN without knowing the original/current PIN.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:34:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57483 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in tawk.to chatbox widget v4 allows attackers to execute arbitrary Javascript in the co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57483</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in tawk.to chatbox widget v4 allows attackers to execute arbitrary Javascript in the context of the user's browser via injecting a crafted payload into the vulnerable parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57412 | An issue in SunOS Omnios v5.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via repeatedly sending crafted TCP packets.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57412</link><description>An issue in SunOS Omnios v5.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via repeatedly sending crafted TCP packets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:23:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56233 | Openindiana, kernel SunOS 5.11 has a denial of service vulnerability. For the processing of TCP packets with RST or SYN flag set, Openindian...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56233</link><description>Openindiana, kernel SunOS 5.11 has a denial of service vulnerability. For the processing of TCP packets with RST or SYN flag set, Openindiana has a wide acceptable range of sequence numbers. It does not require the sequence number to exactly match the next expected sequence value, just to be within the current receive window, which violates RFC5961. This flaw allows attackers to send multiple random TCP RST/SYN packets to hit the acceptable range of sequence numbers, thereby interrupting normal connections and causing a denial of service attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:23:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7104 | Mass Assignment in danny-avila/librechat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7104</link><description>A mass assignment vulnerability exists in danny-avila/librechat, affecting all versions. This vulnerability allows attackers to manipulate sensitive fields by automatically binding user-provided data to internal object properties or database fields without proper filtering. As a result, any extra fields in the request body are included in agentData and passed to the database layer, allowing overwriting of any field in the schema, such as author, access_level, isCollaborative, and projectIds. Additionally, the Object.Prototype can be polluted due to the use of Object.assign with spread operators.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51495 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the WebSocket component of Mongoose 7.5 thru 7.17. By sending a specially crafted WebSocket requ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51495</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the WebSocket component of Mongoose 7.5 thru 7.17. By sending a specially crafted WebSocket request, an attacker can cause the application to crash. If downstream vendors integrate this component improperly, the issue may lead to a buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:51:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56234 | AT_NA2000 from Nanda Automation Technology vendor has a denial-of-service vulnerability. For the processing of TCP RST packets, PLC AT_NA200...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56234</link><description>AT_NA2000 from Nanda Automation Technology vendor has a denial-of-service vulnerability. For the processing of TCP RST packets, PLC AT_NA2000 has a wide acceptable range of sequence numbers. It does not require the sequence number to exactly match the next expected sequence value, just to be within the current receive window, which violates RFC5961. This flaw allows attackers to send multiple random TCP RST packets to hit the acceptable range of sequence numbers, thereby interrupting normal connections and causing a denial-of-service attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61659 | bash-git-prompt 2.6.1 through 2.7.1 insecurely uses the /tmp/git-index-private$$ file, which has a predictable name.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61659</link><description>bash-git-prompt 2.6.1 through 2.7.1 insecurely uses the /tmp/git-index-private$$ file, which has a predictable name.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56795 | Mealie 3.0.1 and earlier is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the recipe creation functionality. Unsanitized user input in the "no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56795</link><description>Mealie 3.0.1 and earlier is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the recipe creation functionality. Unsanitized user input in the "note" and "text" fields of the "/api/recipes/{recipe_name}" endpoint is rendered in the frontend without proper escaping leading to persistent XSS.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41245 | VMSA-2025-0015: VMware Aria Operations and VMware Tools updates address multiple vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-41244,CVE-2025-41245, CVE-2025-41246)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41245</link><description>VMware Aria Operations contains an information disclosure vulnerability. A malicious actor with non-administrative privileges in Aria Operations may exploit this vulnerability to disclose credentials of other users of Aria Operations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41244 | VMSA-2025-0015: VMware Aria Operations and VMware Tools updates address multiple vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-41244,CVE-2025-41245, CVE-2025-41246)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41244</link><description>VMware Aria Operations and VMware Tools contain a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious local actor with non-administrative privileges having access to a VM with VMware Tools installed and managed by Aria Operations with SDMP enabled may exploit this vulnerability to escalate privileges to root on the same VM.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41246 | Improper authorisation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41246</link><description>VMware Tools for Windows contains an improper authorisation vulnerability due to the way it handles user access controls. A malicious actor with non-administrative privileges on a guest VM, who is already authenticated through vCenter or ESX may exploit this issue to access other guest VMs. Successful exploitation requires knowledge of credentials of the targeted VMs and vCenter or ESX.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11155 | WEAK ENCODING FOR PASSWORD IN DEVICE SERVER CONFIGURATION</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11155</link><description>The credentials required to access the device's web server are sent in base64 within the HTTP headers. Since base64 is not considered a strong cipher, an attacker could intercept the web request handling the login and obtain the credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 15:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55795 | The openml/openml.org web application version v2.0.20241110 uses incremental user IDs and insufficient email ownership verification during e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55795</link><description>The openml/openml.org web application version v2.0.20241110 uses incremental user IDs and insufficient email ownership verification during email update workflows. An authenticated attacker controlling a user account with a lower user ID can update their email address to that of another user with a higher user ID without proper verification. This results in the victim's email being reassigned to the attacker's account, causing the victim to be locked out immediately and unable to log in. The vulnerability leads to denial of service via account lockout but does not grant the attacker direct access to the victim's private data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36351 | IBM License Metric Tool bypass security</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36351</link><description>IBM License Metric Tool 9.2.0 through 9.2.40 

could allow an authenticated user to bypass access controls in the REST API interface and perform unauthorized actions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36352 | IBM License Metric Tool cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36352</link><description>IBM License Metric Tool 9.2.0 through 9.2.40 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57516 | OS Command injection vulnerability in PublicCMS PublicCMS-V5.202506.a, and PublicCMS-V5.202506.b allowing attackers to execute arbitrary com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57516</link><description>OS Command injection vulnerability in PublicCMS PublicCMS-V5.202506.a, and PublicCMS-V5.202506.b allowing attackers to execute arbitrary commands via crafted DATABASE, USERNAME, or PASSWORD variables to the backupDB.bat file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56449 | A security vulnerability was identified in Obsidian Scheduler's REST API 5.0.0 thru 6.3.0. If an account is locked out due to not enrolling ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56449</link><description>A security vulnerability was identified in Obsidian Scheduler's REST API 5.0.0 thru 6.3.0. If an account is locked out due to not enrolling in MFA (e.g. after the 7-day enforcement window), the REST API still allows the use of Basic Authentication to authenticate and perform administrative actions. In particular, the default admin account was found to be locked out via the web interface but still usable through the REST API. This allowed creation of a new privileged user, bypassing MFA protections. This undermines the intended security posture of MFA enforcement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57428 | Default credentials in Italy Wireless Mini Router WIRELESS-N 300M v28K.MiniRouter.20190211 allows attackers to gain access to the debug shel...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57428</link><description>Default credentials in Italy Wireless Mini Router WIRELESS-N 300M v28K.MiniRouter.20190211 allows attackers to gain access to the debug shell exposed via Telnet on Port 23 and execute hardware-level flash and register manipulation commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13150 | SQLi in Fayton Software&amp;#x27;s fayton.pro ERP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13150</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Fayton Software and Consulting Services fayton.Pro ERP allows SQL Injection.This issue affects fayton.Pro ERP: through 20250929.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 13:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9648 | Denial of Service in CivetWeb</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9648</link><description>A vulnerability in the CivetWeb library's function mg_handle_form_request allows remote attackers to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition. By sending a specially crafted HTTP POST request containing a null byte in the payload, the server enters an infinite loop during form data parsing. Multiple malicious requests will result in complete CPU exhaustion and render the service unresponsive to further requests.

This issue was fixed in commit 782e189. This issue affects only the library, standalone executable pre-built by vendor is not affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 11:50:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8868 | Chef Automate compliance service SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8868</link><description>In Progress Chef Automate, versions earlier than 4.13.295, on Linux x86 platform, an authenticated attacker can gain access to Chef Automate restricted functionality in the compliance service via 

improperly neutralized inputs used in an SQL command using a well-known token.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 11:41:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6724 | Chef Automate SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6724</link><description>In Progress Chef Automate, versions earlier than 4.13.295, on Linux x86 platform, an authenticated attacker can gain access to Chef Automate restricted functionality in multiple services via improperly neutralized inputs used in an SQL command.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 11:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11150 | asdasdasdasdasdasdasd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11150</link><description>asdasdasdasdasdasdasd</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 11:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11146 | Reflected Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Apt-Cacher-NG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11146</link><description>Reflected Cross-site scripting (XSS) in Apt-Cacher-NG v3.2.1. The vulnerability allows an attacker to execute malicious scripts (XSS) in the web management application. The vulnerability is caused by improper handling of GET inputs included in the URL in “/acng-report.html”.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 09:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11147 | Reflected Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Apt-Cacher-NG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11147</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) in Apt-Cacher-NG v3.2.1. The vulnerability allows malicious scripts (XSS) to be executed in “/html/.html”.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 09:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10346 | HTML injection in Perfex CRM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10346</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability in Perfex CRM v3.2.1 consisting of a 
stored HTML injection due to lack of proper validation of user input by 
sending a POST request in the parameters 'subject' at the endpoint 'knoewledge_base/article'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 08:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10341 | HTML injection in Perfex CRM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10341</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability in Perfex CRM v3.2.1 consisting of a 
stored HTML injection due to lack of proper validation of user input by 
sending a POST request in the parameter 'company' at the endpoint '/clients/client/x.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 08:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10342 | HTML injection in Perfex CRM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10342</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability in Perfex CRM v3.2.1 consisting of a 
stored HTML injection due to lack of proper validation of user input by 
sending a POST request in the parameter 'name' at the endpoint '/subscriptions/create'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 08:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10343 | HTML injection in Perfex CRM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10343</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability in Perfex CRM v3.2.1 consisting of a 
stored HTML injection due to lack of proper validation of user input by 
sending a POST request in the parameter 'expense_name' at the endpoint '/expenses/expense'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 08:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10344 | HTML injection in Perfex CRM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10344</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability in Perfex CRM v3.2.1 consisting of a 
stored HTML injection due to lack of proper validation of user input by 
sending a POST request in the parameters 'name' and 'clientid' at the endpoint '/projects/project/x'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 08:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10345 | HTML injection in Perfex CRM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10345</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability in Perfex CRM v3.2.1 consisting of a 
stored HTML injection due to lack of proper validation of user input by 
sending a POST request in the parameters 'name' and 'address' at the endpoint 'admin/leads/lead'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 08:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48006 | Improper restriction of XML external entity reference issue exists in DataSpider Servista 4.4 and earlier. If a specially crafted request is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48006</link><description>Improper restriction of XML external entity reference issue exists in DataSpider Servista 4.4 and earlier. If a specially crafted request is processed, arbitrary files on the file system where the server application for the product is installed may be read, or a denial-of-service (DoS) condition may occur.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 07:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5200 | Postie &amp;lt; 1.9.71 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5200</link><description>The Postie WordPress plugin before 1.9.71 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 06:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11141 | Ruijie NBR2100G-E branch_passw.php listAction os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11141</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Ruijie NBR2100G-E up to 20250919. Affected by this issue is the function listAction of the file /itbox_pi/branch_passw.php?a=list. Performing manipulation of the argument city results in os command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 04:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10504 | Heap Memory Corruption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10504</link><description>Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in ABB Terra AC wallbox.This issue affects Terra AC wallbox: through 1.8.33.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 04:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11140 | Bjskzy Zhiyou ERP com.artery.richclient.RichClientService openForm xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11140</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Bjskzy Zhiyou ERP up to 11.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function openForm of the component com.artery.richclient.RichClientService. Such manipulation of the argument contentString leads to xml external entity reference. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 04:13:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11139 | Bjskzy Zhiyou ERP com.artery.form.services.FormStudioUpdater uploadStudioFile path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11139</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Bjskzy Zhiyou ERP up to 11.0. Affected is the function uploadStudioFile of the component com.artery.form.services.FormStudioUpdater. This manipulation of the argument filepath causes path traversal. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 03:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11138 | mirweiye wenkucms common.php createPathOne os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11138</link><description>A vulnerability was found in mirweiye wenkucms up to 3.4. This impacts the function createPathOne of the file app/common/common.php. The manipulation results in os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 03:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11137 | Gstarsoft GstarCAD File Renaming cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11137</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Gstarsoft GstarCAD up to 9.4.0. This affects an unknown function of the component File Renaming Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 02:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11136 | YiFang CMS Backend File.php webUploader unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11136</link><description>A flaw has been found in YiFang CMS up to 2.0.2. The impacted element is the function webUploader of the file app/app/controller/File.php of the component Backend. Executing manipulation of the argument uploadpath can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 02:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11135 | pmTicket Project-Management-Software Cookie class.database.php loadLanguage deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11135</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in pmTicket Project-Management-Software up to 2ef379da2075f4761a2c9029cf91d073474e7486. The affected element is the function loadLanguage of the file classes/class.database.php of the component Cookie Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument user_id results in deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 02:53:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11134 | Cudy TR1200 Wireless Settings config cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11134</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Cudy TR1200 1.16.3-20230804-164635. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/luci/admin/network/wireless/config/ of the component Wireless Settings Page. Such manipulation of the argument SSID leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7698 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic Pl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7698</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPS4 Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPSLX Printer Driver / Generic Plus PS Printer Driver</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9903 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic P...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9903</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPS4 Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPSLX Printer Driver / Generic Plus PS Printer Driver</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9904 | Unallocated memory access vulnerability in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Gener...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9904</link><description>Unallocated memory access vulnerability in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPS4 Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPSLX Printer Driver / Generic Plus PS Printer Driver</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11130 | iHongRen pptp-vpn XPC Service HelperTool.m shouldAcceptNewConnection missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11130</link><description>A weakness has been identified in iHongRen pptp-vpn 1.0/1.0.1 on macOS. This issue affects the function shouldAcceptNewConnection of the file HelpTool/HelperTool.m of the component XPC Service. This manipulation causes missing authentication. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11126 | Apeman ID71 system.ini hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11126</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Apeman ID71 218.53.203.117. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /system/www/system.ini. The manipulation results in hard-coded credentials. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11125 | langleyfcu Online Banking System Error Message connection_error.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11125</link><description>A vulnerability was found in langleyfcu Online Banking System up to 57437e6400ce0ae240e692c24e6346b8d0c17d7a. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /connection_error.php of the component Error Message Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument Error results in cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 23:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11124 | code-projects Project Monitoring System postjob.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11124</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Project Monitoring System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /onlineJobSearchEngine/postjob.php. Such manipulation of the argument txtapplyto leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 23:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11123 | Tenda AC18 saveAutoQos stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11123</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.19. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/saveAutoQos. This manipulation of the argument enable causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 22:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11122 | Tenda AC18 WizardHandle stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11122</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.19. This affects an unknown function of the file /goform/WizardHandle. The manipulation of the argument WANT/mtuvalue results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 22:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11121 | Tenda AC18 AdvSetLanip command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11121</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.19. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /goform/AdvSetLanip. The manipulation of the argument lanIp leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 21:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11120 | Tenda AC8 SetServerConfig formSetServerConfig buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11120</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.06. The affected element is the function formSetServerConfig of the file /goform/SetServerConfig. Executing manipulation can lead to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 21:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11119 | itsourcecode Hostel Management System POST Request index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11119</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Hostel Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /justines/index.php of the component POST Request Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument from results in cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 20:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11118 | CodeAstro Student Grading System adminLogin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11118</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in CodeAstro Student Grading System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /adminLogin.php. Such manipulation of the argument staffId leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 20:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11117 | Tenda CH22 GstDhcpSetSer formWrlExtraGet buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11117</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda CH22 1.0.0.1. This vulnerability affects the function formWrlExtraGet of the file /goform/GstDhcpSetSer. This manipulation of the argument dips causes buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 19:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11116 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System add.home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11116</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /add.home.php. The manipulation of the argument faculty results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 19:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11115 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System addtime.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11115</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /addtime.php. The manipulation of the argument starttime/endtime leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11114 | CodeAstro Online Leave Application leaveAplicationForm.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11114</link><description>A flaw has been found in CodeAstro Online Leave Application 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /leaveAplicationForm.php. Executing manipulation of the argument absence[] can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11113 | CodeAstro Online Leave Application signup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11113</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in CodeAstro Online Leave Application 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /signup.php. Performing manipulation of the argument city results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 17:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11112 | PHPGurukul Employee Record Management System myprofile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11112</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in PHPGurukul Employee Record Management System 1.3. This impacts an unknown function of the file /myprofile.php. Such manipulation of the argument First name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 17:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11111 | Campcodes Advanced Online Voting Management System candidates_edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11111</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Advanced Online Voting Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/candidates_edit.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 16:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11110 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System school_year.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11110</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/school_year.php. The manipulation of the argument school_year results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 16:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11109 | Campcodes Computer Sales and Inventory System us_edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11109</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Campcodes Computer Sales and Inventory System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /pages/us_edit.php?action=edit. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 15:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11108 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System addroom.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11108</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /schedulingsystem/addroom.php. Executing manipulation of the argument room can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 15:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11107 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System addcourse.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11107</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /schedulingsystem/addcourse.php. Performing manipulation of the argument corcode results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 14:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11106 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System addfaculty.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11106</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /schedulingsystem/addfaculty.php. Such manipulation of the argument falname leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 14:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11105 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System addsubject.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11105</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /schedulingsystem/addsubject.php. This manipulation of the argument subcode causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 13:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11104 | CodeAstro Electricity Billing System bill.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11104</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in CodeAstro Electricity Billing System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/bill.php. The manipulation of the argument uid results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 12:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11103 | Projectworlds Online Tours and Travels change-image.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11103</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Projectworlds Online Tours and Travels 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/change-image.php. The manipulation of the argument packageimage leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 11:17:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11102 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System edit_content.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11102</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_content.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Title can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 07:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11101 | itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11101</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /jobportal/admin/company/index.php?view=edit. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 07:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11100 | D-Link DIR-823X set_wifi_blacklists uci_set command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11100</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This affects the function uci_set of the file /goform/set_wifi_blacklists. Such manipulation leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 06:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11099 | D-Link DIR-823X delete_prohibiting uci_del command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11099</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. The impacted element is the function uci_del of the file /goform/delete_prohibiting. This manipulation of the argument delvalue causes command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 06:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11098 | D-Link DIR-823X set_wifi_blacklists command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11098</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /goform/set_wifi_blacklists. The manipulation of the argument macList results in command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 05:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11097 | D-Link DIR-823X set_device_name command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11097</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /goform/set_device_name. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 05:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11096 | D-Link DIR-823X diag_traceroute command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11096</link><description>A flaw has been found in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/diag_traceroute. Executing manipulation of the argument target_addr can lead to command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 04:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11095 | D-Link DIR-823X delete_offline_device command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11095</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/delete_offline_device. Performing manipulation of the argument delvalue results in command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 04:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11094 | code-projects E-Commerce Website admin_product_details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11094</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects E-Commerce Website 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /pages/admin_product_details.php. Such manipulation of the argument prod_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 03:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11092 | D-Link DIR-823X set_switch_settings sub_412E7C command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11092</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. Affected by this issue is the function sub_412E7C of the file /goform/set_switch_settings. This manipulation of the argument port causes command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 03:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11091 | Tenda AC21 SetStaticRouteCfg sscanf buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11091</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda AC21 up to 16.03.08.16. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sscanf of the file /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg. The manipulation of the argument list results in buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 02:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11090 | itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11090</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/employee/index.php?view=edit. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 02:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11089 | kidaze CourseSelectionSystem COUNT3s4.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11089</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in kidaze CourseSelectionSystem up to 42cd892b40a18d50bd4ed1905fa89f939173a464. This impacts an unknown function of the file /Profilers/PriProfile/COUNT3s4.php. Executing manipulation of the argument cbranch can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11088 | itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11088</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/vacancy/index.php?view=edit. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 23:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11083 | GNU Binutils Linker elfcode.h elf_swap_shdr heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11083</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in GNU Binutils 2.45. The affected element is the function elf_swap_shdr in the library bfd/elfcode.h of the component Linker. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack must be carried out locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is 9ca499644a21ceb3f946d1c179c38a83be084490. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch. The code maintainer replied with "[f]ixed for 2.46".</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 23:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11082 | GNU Binutils Linker elf-eh-frame.c _bfd_elf_parse_eh_frame heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11082</link><description>A flaw has been found in GNU Binutils 2.45. Impacted is the function _bfd_elf_parse_eh_frame of the file bfd/elf-eh-frame.c of the component Linker. Executing manipulation can lead to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack is restricted to local execution. The exploit has been published and may be used. This patch is called ea1a0737c7692737a644af0486b71e4a392cbca8. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue. The code maintainer replied with "[f]ixed for 2.46".</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 22:44:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11081 | GNU Binutils objdump.c dump_dwarf_section out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11081</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in GNU Binutils 2.45. This issue affects the function dump_dwarf_section of the file binutils/objdump.c. Performing manipulation results in out-of-bounds read. The attack is only possible with local access. The exploit is now public and may be used. The patch is named f87a66db645caf8cc0e6fc87b0c28c78a38af59b. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 22:23:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11080 | zhuimengshaonian wisdom-education ExamInfoController.java selectStudentExamInfoList improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11080</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in zhuimengshaonian wisdom-education up to 1.0.4. This vulnerability affects the function selectStudentExamInfoList of the file src/main/java/com/education/api/controller/student/ExamInfoController.java. Such manipulation of the argument subjectId leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 21:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11079 | Campcodes Farm Management System file information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11079</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes Farm Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation results in file and directory information exposure. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 21:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11078 | itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal controller.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11078</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/user/controller.php?action=photos. The manipulation of the argument photo leads to unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 20:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11077 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System add_content.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11077</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/add_content.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Title can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 20:26:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11076 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System edit_teacher.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11076</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_teacher.php. Performing manipulation of the argument department results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 19:34:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11075 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System de_activate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11075</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/de_activate.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 19:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11074 | code-projects Project Monitoring System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11074</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Project Monitoring System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /login.php. This manipulation of the argument username/password causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 18:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11073 | Keyfactor RG-EW5100BE HTTP POST Request cmd command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11073</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Keyfactor RG-EW5100BE EW_3.0B11P280_EW5100BE-PRO_12183019. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/luci/api/cmd of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument url results in command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 18:16:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11071 | SeaCMS Cron Task Management admin_cron.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11071</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SeaCMS 13.3.20250820. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin_cron.php of the component Cron Task Management Module. The manipulation of the argument resourcefrom/collectID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11070 | Projectworlds Online Shopping System cart_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11070</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Projectworlds Online Shopping System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /store/cart_add.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11069 | westboy CicadasCMS Add Department save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11069</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in westboy CicadasCMS 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /system/org/save of the component Add Department Handler. This manipulation of the argument Name causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 16:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7647 | Insecure Temporary File Handling in run-llama/llama_index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7647</link><description>The llama-index-core package, up to version 0.12.44, contains a vulnerability in the `get_cache_dir()` function where a predictable, hardcoded directory path `/tmp/llama_index` is used on Linux systems without proper security controls. This vulnerability allows attackers on multi-user systems to steal proprietary models, poison cached embeddings, or conduct symlink attacks. The issue affects all Linux deployments where multiple users share the same system. The vulnerability is classified under CWE-379, CWE-377, and CWE-367, indicating insecure temporary file creation and potential race conditions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 16:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8014 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8014</link><description>Denial of Service issue in GraphQL endpoints in Gitlab EE/CE affecting all versions from 11.10 prior to 18.2.7, 18.3 prior to 18.3.3, and 18.4 prior to 18.4.1 allows unauthenticated users to potentially bypass query complexity limits leading to resource exhaustion and service disruption.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 16:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11068 | westboy CicadasCMS save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11068</link><description>A vulnerability was found in westboy CicadasCMS 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /system/cms/category/save. The manipulation of the argument categoryName results in cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 16:22:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11067 | Projectworlds Visitor Management System Add Visitor myform.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11067</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Projectworlds Visitor Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /myform.php of the component Add Visitor Page. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 15:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11066 | code-projects Online Bidding System bidlist.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11066</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Online Bidding System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /administrator/bidlist.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 14:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11064 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System teachers.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11064</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/teachers.php. The manipulation of the argument department results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 14:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11063 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System edit_department.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11063</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/edit_department.php. The manipulation of the argument d leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 13:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11062 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System save_student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11062</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/save_student.php. Executing manipulation of the argument class_id can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 13:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11061 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System edit_student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11061</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit_student.php. Performing manipulation of the argument cys results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 12:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11057 | SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software print_inv.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11057</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/print_inv.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 12:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11056 | ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System select-students.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11056</link><description>A flaw has been found in ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file owner_panel/fetch-data/select-students.php. This manipulation of the argument select causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 10:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11055 | SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System updateaddress.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11055</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/updateaddress.php. The manipulation of the argument address results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 10:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11054 | itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11054</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /jobportal/admin/category/index.php?view=edit. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 09:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11053 | PHPGurukul Small CRM forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11053</link><description>A weakness has been identified in PHPGurukul Small CRM 4.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /forgot-password.php. Executing manipulation of the argument email can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 08:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11052 | kidaze CourseSelectionSystem COUNT3s5.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11052</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in kidaze CourseSelectionSystem 1.0/5.php. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /Profilers/PriProfile/COUNT3s5.php. Performing manipulation of the argument csslc results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 07:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9893 | VM Menu Reorder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9893</link><description>The VM Menu Reorder plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the vm_set_to_default function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset all menu reordering settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 06:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9894 | Sync Feedly &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Sync Trigger</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9894</link><description>The Sync Feedly plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the crsf_cron_job_func function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to trigger content synchronization from Feedly, potentially creating multiple posts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 06:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9896 | HidePost &amp;lt;= 2.3.8 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9896</link><description>The HidePost plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.8. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the options.php settings page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 06:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9898 | cForms – Light speed fast Form Builder &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9898</link><description>The cForms – Light speed fast Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the cforms_api function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify forms and their settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 06:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9899 | Trust Reviews plugin for Google, Tripadvisor, Yelp, Airbnb and other platforms &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9899</link><description>The Trust Reviews plugin for Google, Tripadvisor, Yelp, Airbnb and other platforms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the feed_save function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create or modify feed entries via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 06:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9944 | Professional Contact Form &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Test Email Sending</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9944</link><description>The Professional Contact Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the watch_for_contact_form_submit function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to trigger test email sending via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 06:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11051 | SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11051</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 06:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10954 | Versions of the package github.com/nyaruka/phonenumbers before 1.2.2 are vulnerable to Improper Validation of Syntactic Correctness of Input...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10954</link><description>Versions of the package github.com/nyaruka/phonenumbers before 1.2.2 are vulnerable to Improper Validation of Syntactic Correctness of Input in the phonenumbers.Parse() function. An attacker can cause a panic by providing crafted input causing a "runtime error: slice bounds out of range".</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 05:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3193 | Versions of the package algoliasearch-helper from 2.0.0-rc1 and before 3.11.2 are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution in the _merge() function...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3193</link><description>Versions of the package algoliasearch-helper from 2.0.0-rc1 and before 3.11.2 are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution in the _merge() function in merge.js, which allows constructor.prototype to be written even though doing so throws an error. In the "extreme edge-case" that the resulting error is caught, code injected into the user-supplied search parameter may be exeucted.&#13;&#13;This is related to but distinct from the issue reported in [CVE-2021-23433](https://security.snyk.io/vuln/SNYK-JS-ALGOLIASEARCHHELPER-1570421).&#13;&#13;**NOTE:** This vulnerability is not exploitable in the default configuration of InstantSearch since searchParameters are not modifiable by users.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 05:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11050 | Portabilis i-Educar periodo-lancamento improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11050</link><description>A flaw has been found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This affects an unknown part of the file /periodo-lancamento. Executing manipulation can lead to improper authorization. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 04:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9816 | WP Statistics &amp;lt;= 14.5.4 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via User-Agent Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9816</link><description>The WP Statistics – The Most Popular Privacy-Friendly Analytics Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the User-Agent Header in all versions up to, and including, 14.5.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 04:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11049 | Portabilis i-Educar unificacao-aluno improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11049</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /unificacao-aluno. Performing manipulation results in improper authorization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 04:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10498 | Ninja Forms – The Contact Form Builder That Grows With You &amp;lt;= 3.12.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Limited File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10498</link><description>The Ninja Forms – The Contact Form Builder That Grows With You plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 3.12.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation when exporting CSV files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete those files granted they can trick an administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 03:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10499 | Ninja Forms – The Contact Form Builder That Grows With You &amp;lt;= 3.12.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10499</link><description>The Ninja Forms – The Contact Form Builder That Grows With You plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.12.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the maybe_opt_in() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to opt an affected site into usage statistics collection via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 03:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43192 | IBM Storage TS4500 Library cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43192</link><description>IBM Storage TS4500 Library 1.11.0.0 and 2.11.0.0 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 02:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36239 | IBM Storage TS4500 Library cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36239</link><description>IBM Storage TS4500 Library 1.11.0.0 and 2.11.0.0 

is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 02:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8440 | Team Members &amp;lt;= 5.3.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8440</link><description>The Team Members plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the first and last name fields in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 02:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59932 | FlagForgeCTF Unauthenticated Resource Modification/Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59932</link><description>Flag Forge is a Capture The Flag (CTF) platform. From versions 2.0.0 to before 2.3.1, the /api/resources endpoint previously allowed POST and DELETE requests without proper authentication or authorization. This could have enabled unauthorized users to create, modify, or delete resources on the platform. The issue has been fixed in FlagForge version 2.3.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59945 | SysReptor Susceptible to Privilege Escalation by Authenticated Users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59945</link><description>SysReptor is a fully customizable pentest reporting platform. In versions from 2024.74 to before 2025.83, authenticated and unprivileged (non-admin) users can assign the is_project_admin permission to their own user. This allows users to read, modify and delete pentesting projects they are not members of and are therefore not supposed to access. This issue has been patched in version 2025.83.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59936 | get-jwks poisoned JWKS cache allows post-fetch issuer validation bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59936</link><description>get-jwks contains fetch utils for JWKS keys. In versions prior to 11.0.2, a vulnerability in get-jwks can lead to cache poisoning in the JWKS key-fetching mechanism. When the iss (issuer) claim is validated only after keys are retrieved from the cache, it is possible for cached keys from an unexpected issuer to be reused, resulting in a bypass of issuer validation. This design flaw enables a potential attack where a malicious actor crafts a pair of JWTs, the first one ensuring that a chosen public key is fetched and stored in the shared JWKS cache, and the second one leveraging that cached key to pass signature validation for a targeted iss value. The vulnerability will work only if the iss validation is done after the use of get-jwks for keys retrieval. This issue has been patched in version 11.0.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59938 | Heap buffer overflow in wazuh-analysisd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59938</link><description>Wazuh is a free and open source platform used for threat prevention, detection, and response. In versions starting from 3.8.0 to before 4.11.0, wazuh-analysisd is vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow when parsing XML elements from Windows EventChannel messages. This issue has been patched in version 4.11.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59939 | WeGIA vulnerable to SQL Injection into method `excluir` of  the `ProdutoControle` class in the parameter `id_produto`.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59939</link><description>WeGIA is a Web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to version 3.5.0, WeGIA is vulnerable to SQL Injection attacks in the control.php endpoint with the following parameters: nomeClasse=ProdutoControle&amp;amp;metodo=excluir&amp;amp;id_produto=[malicious command]. It is necessary to apply prepared statements methods, sanitization, and validations on theid_produto parameter. This issue has been patched in version 3.5.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36144 | IBM watsonx.data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36144</link><description>IBM Lakehouse (watsonx.data 2.2) stores potentially sensitive information in log files that could be read by a local user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>