<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 11:17:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-7196 | SourceCodester Complaints Report Management System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7196</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Complaints Report Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272617 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 11:17:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7195 | itsourcecode Society Management System check_admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7195</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/check_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272616.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 10:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7194 | itsourcecode Society Management System check_student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7194</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file check_student.php. The manipulation of the argument student_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272615.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 10:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7193 | Mp3tag DLL tak_deco_lib.dll uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7193</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Mp3tag up to 3.26d and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code in the library tak_deco_lib.dll of the component DLL Handler. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.26e is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-272614 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early, responded in a very professional manner and immediately released a fixed version of the affected product.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 09:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7192 | itsourcecode Society Management System student.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7192</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/student.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272613 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 09:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41139 | Incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability exists in SKYSEA Client View Ver.6.010.06 to Ver.19.210.04e. If a user who can log in to the PC...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41139</link><description>Incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability exists in SKYSEA Client View Ver.6.010.06 to Ver.19.210.04e. If a user who can log in to the PC where the product's Windows client is installed places a specially crafted DLL file in a specific folder, arbitrary code may be executed with SYSTEM privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 08:56:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41143 | Origin validation error vulnerability exists in SKYSEA Client View Ver.3.013.00 to Ver.19.210.04e. If this vulnerability is exploited, an ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41143</link><description>Origin validation error vulnerability exists in SKYSEA Client View Ver.3.013.00 to Ver.19.210.04e. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary process may be executed with SYSTEM privilege by a user who can log in to the PC where the product's Windows client is installed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 08:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41726 | Path traversal vulnerability exists in SKYSEA Client View Ver.3.013.00 to Ver.19.210.04e. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41726</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability exists in SKYSEA Client View Ver.3.013.00 to Ver.19.210.04e. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary executable file may be executed by a user who can log in to the PC where the product's Windows client is installed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 08:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41881 | SDoP versions prior to 1.11 fails to handle appropriately some parameters inside the input data, resulting in a stack-based buffer overflow ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41881</link><description>SDoP versions prior to 1.11 fails to handle appropriately some parameters inside the input data, resulting in a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability. When a user of the affected product is tricked to process a specially crafted XML file, arbitrary code may be executed on the user's environment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 08:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7191 | itsourcecode Society Management System get_balance.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7191</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/get_balance.php. The manipulation of the argument student_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272612.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 08:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7190 | itsourcecode Society Management System get_price.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7190</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/get_price.php. The manipulation of the argument expenses_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272611.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 08:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7189 | itsourcecode Online Food Ordering System editproduct.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7189</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Online Food Ordering System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file editproduct.php. The manipulation of the argument photo leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272610 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 07:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7188 | Bylancer Quicklancer GET Parameter listing sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7188</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Bylancer Quicklancer 2.4. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /listing of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument range2 leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272609 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 07:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41013 | xfs: don&amp;#x27;t walk off the end of a directory data block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41013</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

xfs: don't walk off the end of a directory data block

This adds sanity checks for xfs_dir2_data_unused and xfs_dir2_data_entry
to make sure don't stray beyond valid memory region. Before patching, the
loop simply checks that the start offset of the dup and dep is within the
range. So in a crafted image, if last entry is xfs_dir2_data_unused, we
can change dup-&gt;length to dup-&gt;length-1 and leave 1 byte of space. In the
next traversal, this space will be considered as dup or dep. We may
encounter an out of bound read when accessing the fixed members.

In the patch, we make sure that the remaining bytes large enough to hold
an unused entry before accessing xfs_dir2_data_unused and
xfs_dir2_data_unused is XFS_DIR2_DATA_ALIGN byte aligned. We also make
sure that the remaining bytes large enough to hold a dirent with a
single-byte name before accessing xfs_dir2_data_entry.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41014 | xfs: add bounds checking to xlog_recover_process_data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41014</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

xfs: add bounds checking to xlog_recover_process_data

There is a lack of verification of the space occupied by fixed members
of xlog_op_header in the xlog_recover_process_data.

We can create a crafted image to trigger an out of bounds read by
following these steps:
    1) Mount an image of xfs, and do some file operations to leave records
    2) Before umounting, copy the image for subsequent steps to simulate
       abnormal exit. Because umount will ensure that tail_blk and
       head_blk are the same, which will result in the inability to enter
       xlog_recover_process_data
    3) Write a tool to parse and modify the copied image in step 2
    4) Make the end of the xlog_op_header entries only 1 byte away from
       xlog_rec_header-&gt;h_size
    5) xlog_rec_header-&gt;h_num_logops++
    6) Modify xlog_rec_header-&gt;h_crc

Fix:
Add a check to make sure there is sufficient space to access fixed members
of xlog_op_header.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41015 | ocfs2: add bounds checking to ocfs2_check_dir_entry()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41015</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ocfs2: add bounds checking to ocfs2_check_dir_entry()

This adds sanity checks for ocfs2_dir_entry to make sure all members of
ocfs2_dir_entry don't stray beyond valid memory region.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41016 | ocfs2: strict bound check before memcmp in ocfs2_xattr_find_entry()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41016</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ocfs2: strict bound check before memcmp in ocfs2_xattr_find_entry()

xattr in ocfs2 maybe 'non-indexed', which saved with additional space
requested.  It's better to check if the memory is out of bound before
memcmp, although this possibility mainly comes from crafted poisonous
images.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41017 | jfs: don&amp;#x27;t walk off the end of ealist</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41017</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

jfs: don't walk off the end of ealist

Add a check before visiting the members of ea to
make sure each ea stays within the ealist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41018 | fs/ntfs3: Add a check for attr_names and oatbl</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41018</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fs/ntfs3: Add a check for attr_names and oatbl

Added out-of-bound checking for *ane (ATTR_NAME_ENTRY).</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41019 | fs/ntfs3: Validate ff offset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41019</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fs/ntfs3: Validate ff offset

This adds sanity checks for ff offset. There is a check
on rt-&gt;first_free at first, but walking through by ff
without any check. If the second ff is a large offset.
We may encounter an out-of-bound read.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7187 | TOTOLINK A3600R cstecgi.cgi UploadCustomModule buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7187</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument File leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272608. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41090 | tap: add missing verification for short frame</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41090</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tap: add missing verification for short frame

The cited commit missed to check against the validity of the frame length
in the tap_get_user_xdp() path, which could cause a corrupted skb to be
sent downstack. Even before the skb is transmitted, the
tap_get_user_xdp()--&gt;skb_set_network_header() may assume the size is more
than ETH_HLEN. Once transmitted, this could either cause out-of-bound
access beyond the actual length, or confuse the underlayer with incorrect
or inconsistent header length in the skb metadata.

In the alternative path, tap_get_user() already prohibits short frame which
has the length less than Ethernet header size from being transmitted.

This is to drop any frame shorter than the Ethernet header size just like
how tap_get_user() does.

CVE: CVE-2024-41090</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41091 | tun: add missing verification for short frame</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41091</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tun: add missing verification for short frame

The cited commit missed to check against the validity of the frame length
in the tun_xdp_one() path, which could cause a corrupted skb to be sent
downstack. Even before the skb is transmitted, the
tun_xdp_one--&gt;eth_type_trans() may access the Ethernet header although it
can be less than ETH_HLEN. Once transmitted, this could either cause
out-of-bound access beyond the actual length, or confuse the underlayer
with incorrect or inconsistent header length in the skb metadata.

In the alternative path, tun_get_user() already prohibits short frame which
has the length less than Ethernet header size from being transmitted for
IFF_TAP.

This is to drop any frame shorter than the Ethernet header size just like
how tun_get_user() does.

CVE: CVE-2024-41091</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4483 | Email Encoder &amp;lt; 2.2.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4483</link><description>The Email Encoder  WordPress plugin before 2.2.2 does not escape the WP_Email_Encoder_Bundle_options[protection_text] parameter before outputting it back in an attribute in an admin page, leading to a Stored Cross-Site Scripting</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5285 | WP Affiliate Platform &amp;lt; 6.5.2 - Affiliate Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5285</link><description>The wp-affiliate-platform WordPress plugin before 6.5.2 does not have CSRF check in place when deleting affiliates, which could allow attackers to make a logged in user change delete them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5882 | Ultimate Classified Listings &amp;lt; 1.3 - Unauthenticated LFI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5882</link><description>The Ultimate Classified Listings WordPress plugin before 1.3 does not validate the `ucl_page` and `layout` parameters allowing unauthenticated users to access PHP files on the server from the listings page</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5883 | Ultimate Classified Listings &amp;lt; 1.3 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5883</link><description>The Ultimate Classified Listings WordPress plugin before 1.3 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6362 | Ultimate Blocks &amp;lt; 3.2.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6362</link><description>The Ultimate Blocks  WordPress plugin before 3.2.0 does not validate and escape some of its post-grid block attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6366 | User Profile Builder &amp;lt; 3.11.8 - Unauthenticated Media Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6366</link><description>The User Profile Builder  WordPress plugin before 3.11.8 does not have proper authorisation, allowing unauthenticated users to upload media files via the async upload functionality of WP.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6487 | Inline Related Posts &amp;lt; 3.8.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6487</link><description>The Inline Related Posts WordPress plugin before 3.8.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7186 | TOTOLINK A3600R cstecgi.cgi setWiFiAclAddConfig buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7186</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function setWiFiAclAddConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument comment leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272607. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:15:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37381 | An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2024 flat allows an authenticated attacker within the same network t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37381</link><description>An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2024 flat allows an authenticated attacker within the same network to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 05:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41637 | RaspAP before 3.1.5 allows an attacker to escalate privileges: the www-data user has write access to the restapi.service file and also posse...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41637</link><description>RaspAP before 3.1.5 allows an attacker to escalate privileges: the www-data user has write access to the restapi.service file and also possesses Sudo privileges to execute several critical commands without a password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 05:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7185 | TOTOLINK A3600R cstecgi.cgi setWebWlanIdx buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7185</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setWebWlanIdx of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument webWlanIdx leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272606 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 05:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7184 | TOTOLINK A3600R cstecgi.cgi setUrlFilterRules buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7184</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setUrlFilterRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272605 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 05:20:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7183 | TOTOLINK A3600R cstecgi.cgi setUploadSetting buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7183</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected is the function setUploadSetting of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272604. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 04:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7182 | TOTOLINK A3600R cstecgi.cgi setUpgradeFW buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7182</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This issue affects the function setUpgradeFW of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272603. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 04:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7181 | TOTOLINK A3600R cstecgi.cgi setTelnetCfg command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7181</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This vulnerability affects the function setTelnetCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument telnet_enabled leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272602 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 03:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7202 | Simopro Technology WinMatrix3 Web package - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7202</link><description>The query functionality of WinMatrix3 Web package from Simopro Technology lacks proper validation of user input, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 03:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7180 | TOTOLINK A3600R cstecgi.cgi setPortForwardRules buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7180</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This affects the function setPortForwardRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument comment leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272601 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 03:28:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7201 | Simopro Technology WinMatrix3 Web package - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7201</link><description>The login functionality of WinMatrix3 Web package from Simopro Technology lacks proper validation of user input, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 03:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32671 | Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Samsung Open Source Escargot JavaScript engine allows Overflow Buffers.This issue affects Escarg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32671</link><description>Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Samsung Open Source Escargot JavaScript engine allows Overflow Buffers.This issue affects Escargot: 4.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5670 | Softnext Mail SQR Expert and Mail Archiving Expert - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5670</link><description>The web services of Softnext's products, Mail SQR Expert and Mail Archiving Expert do not properly validate user input, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary OS commands and execute them on the remote server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7179 | TOTOLINK A3600R cstecgi.cgi setParentalRules buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7179</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument startTime/endTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272600. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7178 | TOTOLINK A3600R cstecgi.cgi setMacQos buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7178</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setMacQos of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument priority/macAddress leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272599. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7177 | TOTOLINK A3600R cstecgi.cgi setLanguageCfg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7177</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function setLanguageCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument langType leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272598 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7176 | TOTOLINK A3600R cstecgi.cgi setIpQosRules buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7176</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function setIpQosRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument comment leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272597 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 01:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7175 | TOTOLINK A3600R cstecgi.cgi setDiagnosisCfg os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7175</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ipDoamin leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272596. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 01:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7174 | TOTOLINK A3600R cstecgi.cgi setdeviceName buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7174</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This affects the function setdeviceName of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument deviceMac/deviceName leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272595. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 01:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7173 | TOTOLINK A3600R cstecgi.cgi loginauth buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7173</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected by this issue is the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument password/http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. VDB-272594 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 23:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7172 | TOTOLINK A3600R getSaveConfig buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7172</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getSaveConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272593 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 23:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7171 | TOTOLINK A3600R cstecgi.cgi NTPSyncWithHost os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7171</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected is the function NTPSyncWithHost of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostTime leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272592. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 22:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7170 | TOTOLINK A3000RU product.ini hard-coded password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7170</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3000RU 5.9c.5185. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272591. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 22:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7169 | SourceCodester School Fees Payment System ajax.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7169</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester School Fees Payment System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /ajax.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272583.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 19:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7168 | SourceCodester School Fees Payment System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7168</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester School Fees Payment System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272582 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 19:16:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7167 | SourceCodester School Fees Payment System manage_course.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7167</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester School Fees Payment System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /manage_course.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272581 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 18:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7166 | SourceCodester School Fees Payment System receipt.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7166</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester School Fees Payment System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /receipt.php. The manipulation of the argument ef_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272580.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 18:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7165 | SourceCodester School Fees Payment System view_payment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7165</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester School Fees Payment System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /view_payment.php. The manipulation of the argument ef_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272579.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 17:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7164 | SourceCodester School Fees Payment System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7164</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester School Fees Payment System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /ajax.php?action=login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272578 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 17:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7163 | SeaCMS index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7163</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SeaCMS 12.9. This affects an unknown part of the file /js/player/dmplayer/player/index.php. The manipulation of the argument color/vid/url leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272577 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 16:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7162 | SeaCMS cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7162</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SeaCMS 12.9/13.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file js/player/dmplayer/admin/post.php?act=setting. The manipulation of the argument yzm leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272576.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 16:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7161 | SeaCMS Password Change cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7161</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SeaCMS 13.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /member.php?action=chgpwdsubmit of the component Password Change Handler. The manipulation of the argument newpwd/newpwd2 leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272575.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 15:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7160 | TOTOLINK A3700R cstecgi.cgi setWanCfg command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7160</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513. Affected is the function setWanCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostName leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272574 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 15:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7159 | TOTOLINK A3600R Telnet Service product.ini hard-coded password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7159</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini of the component Telnet Service. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272573 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 14:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7158 | TOTOLINK A3100R HTTP POST Request cstecgi.cgi setTelnetCfg command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7158</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setTelnetCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument telnet_enabled leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272572. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 13:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7157 | TOTOLINK A3100R getSaveConfig buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7157</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function getSaveConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272571. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 11:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7156 | TOTOLINK A3700R apmib Configuration ExportSettings.sh information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7156</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh of the component apmib Configuration Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272570 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 10:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7155 | TOTOLINK A3300R shadow.sample hard-coded password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7155</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /etc/shadow.sample. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272569 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 10:18:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7154 | TOTOLINK A3700R Password Reset wizard.html access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7154</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513. Affected is an unknown function of the file /wizard.html of the component Password Reset Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272568. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 09:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42054 | Cervantes through 0.5-alpha accepts insecure file uploads.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42054</link><description>Cervantes through 0.5-alpha accepts insecure file uploads.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 03:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42055 | Cervantes through 0.5-alpha allows stored XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42055</link><description>Cervantes through 0.5-alpha allows stored XSS.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 03:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42050 | The MSI installer for Splashtop Streamer for Windows before 3.7.0.0 uses a temporary folder with weak permissions during installation. A loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42050</link><description>The MSI installer for Splashtop Streamer for Windows before 3.7.0.0 uses a temporary folder with weak permissions during installation. A local user can exploit this to escalate privileges to SYSTEM via an oplock on CredProvider_Inst.reg.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 02:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42051 | The MSI installer for Splashtop Streamer for Windows before 3.6.2.0 uses a temporary folder with weak permissions during installation. A loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42051</link><description>The MSI installer for Splashtop Streamer for Windows before 3.6.2.0 uses a temporary folder with weak permissions during installation. A local user can exploit this to escalate privileges to SYSTEM by replacing InstRegExp.reg.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 02:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42052 | The MSI installer for Splashtop Streamer for Windows before 3.5.8.0 uses a temporary folder with weak permissions during installation. A loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42052</link><description>The MSI installer for Splashtop Streamer for Windows before 3.5.8.0 uses a temporary folder with weak permissions during installation. A local user can exploit this to escalate privileges to SYSTEM by placing a wevtutil.exe file in the folder.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 02:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42053 | The MSI installer for Splashtop Streamer for Windows before 3.6.0.0 uses a temporary folder with weak permissions during installation. A loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42053</link><description>The MSI installer for Splashtop Streamer for Windows before 3.6.0.0 uses a temporary folder with weak permissions during installation. A local user can exploit this to escalate privileges to SYSTEM by placing a version.dll file in the folder.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 02:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42049 | TightVNC (Server for Windows) before 2.8.84 allows attackers to connect to the control pipe via a network connection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42049</link><description>TightVNC (Server for Windows) before 2.8.84 allows attackers to connect to the control pipe via a network connection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 02:06:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7153 | Netgear WN604 siteSurvey.php direct request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7153</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Netgear WN604 up to 20240719. Affected is an unknown function of the file siteSurvey.php. The manipulation leads to direct request. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272556. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 22:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7152 | Tenda O3 setMacFilterList fromSafeSetMacFilter stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7152</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda O3 1.0.0.10(2478). It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function fromSafeSetMacFilter of the file /goform/setMacFilterList. The manipulation of the argument time leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272555. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 21:20:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7151 | Tenda O3 setMacFilter fromMacFilterSet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7151</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda O3 1.0.0.10(2478). It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function fromMacFilterSet of the file /goform/setMacFilter. The manipulation of the argument remark leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272554 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 20:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6703 | Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp;amp; Drop WP Form Builder &amp;lt;= 5.1.19 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Welcome Screen Fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6703</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the description and 'btn_txt' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for attackers with the Form Manager permissions and Subscriber+ user role, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 12:58:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6518 | fluentform &amp;lt;= 5.1.19 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6518</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6520 | fluentform &amp;lt;= 5.1.19 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6520</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5614 | Piotnet Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.4.29 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5614</link><description>The Piotnet Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.29 via the 'pafe_posts_list' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including titles and excerpts of future, draft, and pending blog posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 11:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6521 | fluentform &amp;lt;= 5.1.19 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6521</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 11:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6627 | Happy Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.11.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via PDF View Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6627</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's PDF View widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.11.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 11:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6897 | aThemes Starter Sites &amp;lt;= 1.0.53 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6897</link><description>The aThemes Starter Sites plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.53 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 11:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6458 | WooCommerce Product Table Lite &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - Missing Authorization to (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6458</link><description>The WooCommerce Product Table Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized post title modification due to a missing capability check on the wcpt_presets__duplicate_preset_to_table function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber access and above to change titles of arbitrary posts. Missing sanitization can lead to Stored Cross-Site Scripting when viewed by an admin via the WooCommerce Product Table.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 08:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6569 | Campaign Monitor for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.8.15 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6569</link><description>The Campaign Monitor for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.15. This is due the plugin not properly restricting direct access to /forms/views/admin/create.php and display_errors being enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 08:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5969 | AIomatic - Automatic AI Content Writer &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Email Sending</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5969</link><description>The AIomatic - Automatic AI Content Writer for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary email sending vulnerability in versions up to, and including, 2.0.5. This is due to insufficient limitations on the email recipient and the content in the 'aiomatic_send_email' function which are reachable via AJAX. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send emails with any content to any recipient.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 07:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42029 | xdg-desktop-portal-hyprland (aka an XDG Desktop Portal backend for Hyprland) before 1.3.3 allows OS command execution, e.g., because single ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42029</link><description>xdg-desktop-portal-hyprland (aka an XDG Desktop Portal backend for Hyprland) before 1.3.3 allows OS command execution, e.g., because single quotes are not used when sending a list of app IDs and titles via the environment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 04:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1798 | Tutor LMS  Migration Tool &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Missing Authorization in tutor_lp_export_xml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1798</link><description>The Tutor LMS  Migration Tool plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the tutor_lp_export_xml function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export courses, including private and password protected courses.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1804 | Tutor LMS  Migration Tool &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Missing Authorization in tutor_import_from_xml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1804</link><description>The Tutor LMS  Migration Tool plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the tutor_import_from_xml function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to import courses.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4410 | IgnitionDeck Crowdfunding Platform &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4410</link><description>The IgnitionDeck Crowdfunding Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in versions up to, and including, 1.9.8. This is due to missing capability checks on various functions called via AJAX actions in the ~/classes/class-idf-wizard.php file. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or higher, to execute various AJAX actions. This includes actions to change the permalink structure, plugin settings and others.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6152 | Flipbox Builder &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6152</link><description>The Flipbox Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.5 via deserialization of untrusted input in the flipbox_builder_Flipbox_ShortCode function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6431 | Media.net Ads Manager &amp;lt;= 2.10.13 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6431</link><description>The Media.net Ads Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation and missing capability check in the 'sendMail' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level and above permissions, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. The vulnerability is only exploitable if anyone has ever logged in through the API.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6545 | Admin Trim Interface &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6545</link><description>The Admin Trim Interface plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.1. This is due to the plugin utilizing bootstrap and leaving test files with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6546 | One Click Close Comments &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6546</link><description>The One Click Close Comments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.1. This is due to the plugin utilizing bootstrap and leaving test files with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6547 | Add Admin CSS &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Unauthenticated Full Path Dislcosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6547</link><description>The Add Admin CSS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1.  This is due to the plugin utilizing bootstrap and leaving test files with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6548 | Add Admin JavaScript &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Unauthenticated Full Path Dislcosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6548</link><description>The Add Admin JavaScript plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 2.0. This is due to the plugin utilizing bootstrap and leaving test files with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6549 | Admin Post Navigation &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6549</link><description>The Admin Post Navigation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 2.1. This is due to the plugin utilizing bootstrap and leaving test files with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6566 | Aramex Shipping WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.21 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6566</link><description>The Aramex Shipping WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.21. This is due the plugin not preventing direct access to the composer-setup.php file which also has display_errors enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6573 | Intelligence &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6573</link><description>The Intelligence plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0. This is due the plugin not preventing direct access to the /vendor/levelten/intel/realtime/index.php file and display_errors being enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6591 | Ultimate WordPress Auction Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Email Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6591</link><description>The Ultimate WordPress Auction Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized email creation and sending due to a missing capability check on the 'send_auction_email_callback' and 'resend_auction_email_callback' functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to craft emails that include links and send to any email address.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6634 | Master Currency WP &amp;lt;= 1.1.61 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Currency Converter Form Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6634</link><description>The Master Currency WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's currencyconverterform shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.61 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6661 | ParityPress &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6661</link><description>The ParityPress  Parity Pricing with Discount Rules plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via  'Discount Text' in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>